[screaming]
[grunts, coughs]
[Ryan] You said
you'd always watch out for me!
- You promised!
- Well, maybe I don't want to look at ya.
I hate you.
- Zoe, uh, you remember my son, Ryan.
- Hi.
Your father wasn't having an affair
with your mother.
- Grace!
- He raped her.
- [Butcher] No!
- [grunts]
Oh, my God, Sameer.
- [Annie] Is that Zoe's dad?
- Yes.
I would never let anything happen
to you or Zoe.
[hisses]
[Butcher] Sameer's done it.
As of last week,
that naughty little bug of his
is finally strong enough
to top Homelander.
I want you to find William Butcher.
[Butcher] We've got an uber virus,
strong enough to kill every fucking Supe
- on the planet.
- No.
[Mother's Milk] Soldier Boy
killed my family.
I gotta get this motherfucker
outta my head.
[Translucent] Look, you let me go,
you'll be the hero
that saved Translucent.
Sweet boy.
- [moans]
- I will be there for you always.
Okay, good.
[crying] Why does everyone
keep leaving me?
[Oh Father] Stand up,
in the name of Jesus!
[angelic voice] My sweet boy.
[tense music playing]
[soft footsteps approach]
[plastic crinkles]
♪ ♪
[in Russian] This doesn't look like
a CIA black site to me.
Oh really,
Command didn't ask your opinion?
Shut up.
[floorboard creaks]
[screams]
[plaster dust falling]
- [gunfire]
- [yells]
[♪ Ganna Sorbat sings "Bad Reputation"
in Russian]
[screams]
[yells]
♪ ♪
Please...
...I have family.
I love Imagine Dragons.
Please.
I'm sorry.
No one can know I was here.
[noble music playing]
[Firecracker] Soldier Boy.
America's first hero.
Defender of liberty, faith and family.
-Branded a traitor by the Legacy Media.
- [cheering]
Scapegoated by Starlight, who was
the real mastermind
behind the attack on Seven Tower.
But from the ashes of injustice,
Soldier Boy has been reborn.
And America deserves the truth.
Since 1984,
Soldier Boy has been in Russia,
workin' with our friends in the Kremlin
to root out those sneaky traitors
in Ukraine.
[Deep] Turns out Russia isn't our enemy.
They're a strong, family-first nation
who don't put up with trans bathrooms.
We're grateful to Soldier Boy
for his courage and sacrifice.
And we hope that he can forgive us
as he takes his rightful place
on The Seven.
It is my honor to present Soldier Boy
with the first ever Democratic Medal
of Patriotic Freedom.
[applause]
[rising, tense music plays]
[angelic voice] My boy.
My poor, sweet boy.
I'm also very proud to say
that this great hero
is my father.
[reporters gasping]
[reporter] Whoa, hold on.
When did you find out?
[reporters clamoring]
Are there any plans for a team-up?
[loud rock music plays]
[Homelander exhales]
Forty years out of the spotlight,
you still got it, huh?
[chuckles]
Sage tells me, uh,
socials are blowing up.
People magazine,
they're-they're calling us, uh,
America's sexiest dynasty.
You believe that? [chuckles]
[quietly] Come on.
I would never have sent you in there
if I knew that Butcher had the virus.
I wouldn't have.
Swear to God.
Although,
I did tell you not to engage, so...
if we're pointing fingers, I don't think
I should be exclusively at fault here.
[Sage] Gentlemen.
Lab results are in.
Lab results.
[news anchor] Now, a lot has happened
today at this event.
-Soldier Boy's addition...
- How?
We were there, they all got infected.
We watched them die.
- [broadcast shuts off]
- [Butcher] How the fuck
is that cunt still breathin'?
Oh, no. Oh, no.
He's got V1 in his bloodstream.
- Shit.
- V1? What is V1?
Frederick Vought's first iteration
of Compound V.
V1's ten times more potent
than today's formula.
Highly unstable.
Only worked on a handful of early Supes:
you, Bombsight,
Torpedo, Private Angel,
Stormfront.
- Who is Stormfront?
- Dr. Vought's wife Clara.
Uh, I think you knew her as Liberty?
Point is, V1 saved your life.
And is likely why
your generation of Supes doesn't age.
This is a modern Compound V molecule.
This is the virus.
Its spike proteins bind
to the V receptors,
kind of like gears meshing.
But V1 is different, it looks like this.
Nothing for the virus to bind to.
You might've told us that
before we tested it.
V1 hasn't been in circulation
since the 1950s.
And I thought Soldier Boy was dead.
We all did.
And now all I'm hearin' is that
this motherfucker is unkillable.
Hmm.
[chuckles]
[laughing]
[Annie] Okay, but what about Homelander?
Does this...
does this mean that...
I'm his son. Am I immune, too?
No.
Your embryo was shot up
with plain old garden-variety V.
Like me, like every other Supe.
But if Homelander got his hands
on some V1, then, theoretically,
he'd be like Soldier Boy.
Immune to the virus.
Maybe even immortal.
- Bring me some.
- [Sage] I can't.
- Why not?
- Vought destroyed every vial.
There's none left.
Could a vial still exist somewhere?
I suppose.
Wait. If that's true,
then that means he can use that to--
We need to get to it
before Homelander does.
How? I'm sure he knows all this already.
- We're fucked.
- Good point, luv.
We hit 'em with the virus today,
while it still works.
That wasn't at all my point.
Butcher's right.
[snaps fingers] See?
It's the smart play. We draw him out
- and hit him today.
- [Hughie] Okay.
How you gonna get it in front of him?
Homelander hasn't been seen
outside of the Tower in days,
which means
he's probably scared of getting infected.
And if you release this thing,
he just flies up
into fucking space
until it's all over, right?
So until you figure that out,
we have to find some of this V1.
We don't really have a choice.
I know where to start.
[Homelander] Wow.
Thank God that stuff's in you
and saved you. Um...
- Guess all's well that ends well.
- Yeah, well, fuck you.
You knew Butcher had the virus.
You defrosted me just to send me
into the fucking woodchipper.
No. No, I did not.
- What I wanted--
- Well, joke's on you, asshole.
Cause I'm gonna live...
...and you'll die.
If the virus doesn't get you, time will.
And when you're sitting
in that wheelchair,
shitting in a colostomy bag,
I'll be running The Seven,
shitting on Shari Lewis's tits.
Look at you.
Just the softest, wettest boy.
You're pathetic.
You're nothing at all.
[intense, dramatic music playing]
- [music stops]
- [footsteps receding]
[Frenchie] Mademoiselle Annie,
are you certain of this?
[Annie] We don't have a choice.
[exciting music playing]
You know what this means, right?
If we do get this V1,
you and Kimiko could take some.
I mean, it made Soldier Boy
immune to the virus.
It could make you immune, too.
Like a vaccine.
Yeah, or we could grow a million dicks.
Like a Koosh ball, but with dicks.
[Hughie] Very specific.
But look, there's a chance.
- [tense music plays]
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No.
- [hisses]
- [Frenchie] No, no, no.
- Not you again.
- [Mother's Milk] Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Zoe, take it easy.
- [Stan] Put 'em away, kiddo.
That won't be necessary.
At least, not yet.
Starlight.
We weren't expecting you.
I take it Marie Moreau is running late?
Marie's not coming.
But I know about the meeting
you had a while back.
She set this up, actually.
- Did she?
- [Annie] Yeah, we need you
to tell us everything that you know
about V1.
You mean the first generation V
Soldier Boy has in his veins
that made him immune
to the virus you're working on
with William Butcher?
You can't actually be surprised I know.
But why should I help
the friends of a deranged man
who murdered my daughter
and orphaned my granddaughter?
Vicky meant a lot to me, too.
And what Butcher did was unforgivable,
which is why he's not here.
But you're still working with him.
We think that Homelander's trying
to get at V1.
And if he does, he lives forever
and you will be just as fucked
as the rest of us.
So you gonna keep dronin' on
like some fuckin' Black Mr. Spock,
or you gonna help us out?
Follow me.
[quiet, tense music playing]
[whirring]
After you.
[keypad beeping]
Point one percent torch the world,
and watch it burn
from their luxury bunkers.
[sniffs] It smells in here.
You're right. Smells like an Abercrombie
got fucked by a 7-Eleven
while Arby's jerked off in the corner.
- [Hughie sniffs]
- It's V-Bro Mango Thunder Body Spray.
[Hughie] Fuck!
Everyone, this is Maverick.
Translucent's son.
'Sup, playa?
'Sup...
playa?
Starlight. I was a kid last you saw me.
You sang at my dad's funeral.
[Annie] Maverick, hi. Um...
What are you doing here?
Don't you go to Godolkin?
[Maverick] Fuck that place.
And fuck Vought.
They're all a bunch of liars.
They said a cartel super-villain killed
my dad.
Mr. Edgar was the only one
that told me the truth.
[tense music playing]
[Maverick] It was Homelander.
Homelander killed my dad.
Wow. Homelander?
Ugh, God. I...
Fuck that fucking motherfucker.
I've been saying it for years.
This fucking...
This...
- ...motherfucker.
- Fucking guy. Yeah.
Okay, so...
Maverick, Zoe, Marie Moreau?
What, are you tryin' to start
your own Teenage Kix or somethin'?
I believe the children are our future.
Maverick...
if you'll excuse us a moment?
Follow me.
If you want to know about V1,
I hope that you have strong stomachs.
V1 was barbaric and unstable.
Dr. Vought's first test subjects at Dachau
lived in a state of endless torment.
He murdered thousands,
only to achieve five successes.
Jesus.
Even after Vought defected to the Allies,
he kept testing V1 on a ready supply
of U.S. servicemen.
[Mother's Milk] Why am I not surprised?
By then, we were in an arms race
with the Russians,
so nothing could stand in the way
of national security.
Dr. Vought stabilized the formula
in the '50s
and swept all mention of V1 under the rug,
like every other sordid chapter
in this company's history.
And you're sure there are
no more doses left whatsoever?
Not that I've seen.
You think Vought wanted
a paper trail to Dachau?
This is every surviving file
from Frederick Vought's.
If you want to look through them,
- be my guest.
- [door opens]
Zoe... Zoe, wait.
[Hughie sighs]
What happened to your mom was awful.
Look, I didn't know
that Butcher was gonna...
I didn't mean for her to get hurt.
I promise.
Promise?
You promised that we'd be safe.
Then I woke up alone
to see my mom ripped in half.
- I'm sorry.
- Then I got chucked
into Red River because
my dad is probably dead, too.
So go fuck yourself.
[oppressive music playing]
[Soldier Boy] Maybe if I had raised you,
I could've made you better.
You're a fucking disappointment.
[echoing] ...disappointment.
The pitiful disappointment you are.
[Homelander reflection] Deep down,
there's a part of you that is still
- human.
- You're pathetic.
- ♪ ♪
- Weak.
You're my greatest failure.
You're nothing at all.
- ♪ ♪
- [coughs, gasps]
[panting]
♪ ♪
[whimpers]
Madelyn?
Oh, my boy.
My sweet boy.
[Homelander whimpers]
What is wrong?
Why are you so unhappy?
My father...
and my son...
Everything. It's all fallen apart.
No.
No, it's exactly what needed to happen.
Yes. It's been foretold.
You're about to ascend.
Become immortal.
Divine.
A true god.
With the love of the world.
- But...
- I know.
You think love is weak and human.
But who is more loved than Jesus?
And why should He have
more love than you?
You save more people than He does.
The one true God.
Yes...
But how?
How? Millions of people just hate me.
Well, then, you baptize the unfaithful
in their own blood.
[exhales]
- Rip babies from their mothers' wombs.
- Yes...
Skin parents in front of their children.
- Rid the world of the wicked.
- Yes...
The non-believers.
They'll call me a monster.
No. The only ones left
will be your faithful.
And they will love you in their hearts.
[exhales]
They'll cry happy tears
at the mere thought of you.
You have one last task, my love.
Yes.
[dramatic music playing]
Ah...!
[groaning]
You're late.
Came as soon as you texted.
Was kinda far.
- Where?
- Russia.
Near the border, I think.
Anybody see you?
Uh, no.
What's that?
Uh...
cut myself shaving.
Trust me, you don't need to shave.
[chuckles]
Uh, so your... your grandpa's in there
with them now?
Is, uh...
is-is Butcher in there?
No.
But they can lead us to him.
We can find him and kill him.
Kill Butcher?
I-I don't...
I don't think that's a good idea.
You don't think we could?
He's dangerous.
Look what he did to your mom.
That's the point.
- He's not worth it.
- Ryan...
It's not worth you getting hurt.
He'd kill you.
So I'm just supposed to fly away
and hide with my dick in my hand?
- Zoe--
- Forget it.
[branch snaps]
[Ryan] You think I couldn't smell
the Tanqueray on your breath?
What the fuck?
[Butcher] Well, well, well.
Ain't this my lucky fuckin' day?
Should buy meself a lotto ticket.
Thought you'd still be
in touch with your girl.
And if I hadn't showed?
I was planning to nick Zoe,
text you from her phone
and just wait for you to come runnin'.
But, hey...
fuckin' Christmas.
Nice one.
But I don't break easy no more.
Not like Mallory.
You're a right tough lad, ain't ya?
Killing an old lady,
then fucking off to Russia.
Zoe was right about you.
Maybe I should just put you
out of your misery.
You could.
But you won't.
- And why is that?
- 'Cause...
we both loved the same woman...
and we both hate the same cunt.
Look, mate,
you can be as pissy with me as you like,
but we both know
I ain't the bad guy here.
Not really.
I just need us
to have a proper chat.
That's all.
[liquid drips]
[Soldier Boy] Homelander?
Up here.
What do you--
What in the fuck?
- Is that milk?
- Better.
Breastmilk.
From the NICU at Mount Sinai.
So, what, you asked me up here
so I could watch you swim in tit-jizz?
I want to give you another chance.
You want to give me another chance?
Yes. Help me find that V1.
I'd rather fist myself
with a handful of razors.
Besides, Cleopatra Jones said
there's no V1 to find.
Oh, there most certainly is.
And I am going to find it.
Yeah? What makes you so sure?
An angel told me.
It's my destiny.
Just when I thought there was a ceiling
to how fucking weird you could get.
Yes, yes. Make your jokes.
You've been blessed with immortality...
...and what have you done with it?
Drink and fuck yourself numb.
You...
...you...
are a disappointment.
You see...
...I am not gonna waste my immortality.
I am gonna take what's rightfully mine.
I'm asking you
if you want a seat at the table
because you're my father.
But with or without you...
...a reckoning is coming.
You know, all I see is a freak.
A freak with a bushel of gray pubes.
Try some Just for Men.
[exhales]
What's Fort Harmony?
- [door opens]
- I have no idea.
- It's all over these memos.
- [door closes]
[Hughie] What do they say?
[Mother's Milk] I don't know.
The text is encrypted,
but I think I can crack it.
[Stan] You couldn't possibly.
[Mother's Milk] It's 1944.
There's more processing power
in your toaster
than there was
in the encryption tech back then.
Gimme an hour.
- [air hissing]
- The fuck is that?
[sighs]
Hey.
Um, sorry... Just, uh...
[coughs]
...you might wanna lighten up on that
V-Bro Mango Thunder. That is...
that is musky.
[Maverick] My dad was
in the first campaign.
"Vanish into Freshness."
It just... smells like him, you know?
[Hughie] I'm sorry about your dad.
I-I lost mine too.
[Maverick] I'm sorry to hear that.
[Hughie] It's just... it's crazy, right?
Walk around one day feeling fine,
and then...
...outta nowhere, the pain just hits you
like a truck, like...
just takes the wind out of you.
[Maverick] You guys are trying to take
down Homelander, right? Let me help.
Look, Maverick, I-I don't think
that's such a good idea. It...
It's really dangerous.
I don't care. He fucking killed my dad.
It's the only thing I can think about.
[Hughie] I know that
you want this to mean something.
But it's never gonna make sense.
And the more that you try,
the less sense it'll make. It...
Trust me.
I know.
What am I supposed to do?
[Hughie] Honestly? Just...
let go.
Live your life. Be happy.
Fall in love with someone.
[Maverick] I do have a girlfriend.
Really?
[Maverick] Sloane.
She's an alpaca.
Cool. Just--
Maybe think about what your dad would
want for you, and-and then
do that.
That's what I'm trying to do, anyway.
- [Annie] Hughie?
- Um...
Can I, um, can I just talk to you
for a quick second?
Yeah.
Stop.
Another mention of Fort Harmony.
From 1963.
Butcher has a scanner, no?
He does.
Maybe resolution is good enough
so we can make out some of the text.
Okay.
- Go with him.
- [Kimiko] Sounds good.
I've been watching pornography
and I'd like to try out some cunnilingus.
I don't understand.
- [pop song playing]
- [Butcher] All you do
is get him on the blower
and tell him you wanna see him.
When he rocks up,
you chuck the shit in his face...
...and that'll be it.
- Why me?
- 'Cause he won't leave
the fortress of cuntitude
for anyone else.
So this is what
you wanted to talk to me about.
Killing my dad.
[sighs] Listen, mate--
Is that all you think I'm good for?
I ain't gonna treat you
like a kid no more. All right?
You're done with that.
Homelander raped yer mum.
He's gonna burn everything down,
and you are the only one
who can stop him.
Now...
normally, I don't put no stock in
any of that bollocks about destiny,
but if anyone's got one, it's you.
[sighs]
♪ ♪
I throw this virus at him...
...what'll happen to me?
You'll die.
I'll be close by and we'll go together.
Now...
...I ain't gonna lie to you, this...
...this is not what your mum wanted.
But it's the only way.
And it will be justice.
You're asking me to kill myself?
You wouldn't be the first lad
to throw his life away in a war...
but you would be the first
to save the world doin' it.
[exhales]
[exhales heavily]
I'll fetch us a pint.
[♪ Limp Bizkit sings
"Rollin' (Air Raid Vehicle)"]
♪ Keep rollin',
rollin', rollin', rollin...
I mean, no wonder
Soldier Boy's getting all this heat.
He's a fucking nepo daddy.
Like, he's not even that good-looking.
Like, his hair's doing
most of the heavy lifting.
Like, you shave his head,
he's the gayest sailor at Fleet Week.
Seriously, man,
thanks for letting me tag along.
I need a win.
Will you just tell me this?
Homelander really didn't want me
to come along?
He didn't, like...
mention my name even once?
♪ So back the fuck up
while we fuck this track up...
[Deep scoffs] Then why'd he ask them?
♪ ♪
Keep heading south.
♪ Hands down, back up, back up ♪
♪ Tell me what you gonna do now...
So, like, what's your story?
My story?
Yeah.
I was born
on a Sugarbush Maple Farm.
One day when I was five, my parents died
in a tidal wave of molasses.
Then I was raised by four geese
and an agoraphobic fox in a crystal cave
where they taught me
the ways of the soil and the salts,
until Gerald-- that's the eldest goose--
revealed to me that he's
the reincarnation of Robin Williams.
And then he took me
on his egg-shaped spaceship
to Ork, because Mork & Mindy
is a Netflix documentary.
Orson married us.
And the rest is history.
♪ Back up, back up ♪
♪ Tell me what you're gonna do now ♪
♪ Breathe in, now breathe out,
hands up, now hands down...
Homelander asked you to come along?
♪ Keep rollin', rollin', rollin...
Personally.
- [scoffs]
- ♪ Rollin', rollin', rollin', rollin' ♪
♪ Keep rollin',
rollin', rollin', rollin' ♪
♪ Keep rollin', rollin', rollin',
rollin' ♪
[song fades into distance]
Merde.
Cybertrucks are the Entourage of cars.
A penny for your thoughts?
Hughie said the V1 could be a cure.
You really think so?
Would give us more time.
What would you want to do?
Well, we could travel.
I can DJ in Berlin.
Nothing to tie us down,
never in the same place twice.
[gas pump clicks]
D-Do you want that for your kids?
[scoffs] Of course not.
Which is why I will never have any.
But, uh...
...you want children?
Three.
Two girls and a boy.
A house by the water.
And maybe a bernedoodle.
Peace and quiet.
After all this killing,
I just want a place to call home.
[gentle music playing]
[quiet music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Here.
[sighs] Told 'er you were 30.
- [chuckles]
- Fuck the leather,
fuck the lace,
here's to the bird
who sits on yer face.
- [Butcher exhales]
- Where'd you pick that up?
Me old man.
You two close?
Nah, not really.
He was a... a piss artist.
Used to lose all his money
on the gee-gees.
Uh-- horses.
And then he'd come home, beat
the livin' daylights outta Len and me.
And then, later,
laugh about it with his mates.
Yeah, he was a right cunt.
Where is he now?
Bottom of the Thames.
I put him there, just the other day.
Only wish I'd done it sooner.
'Fore he caused more...
...more damage.
Butcher...
Do you think that I could ever...
That I might turn into my dad?
[dark music playing]
I don't know.
[Ryan sighs]
My mom...
Aunt Grace...
the others...
All I do is hurt people.
I can't be around anyone.
Without us--
without Supes--
the world is a better, safer place.
♪ ♪
I'll do it.
[news anchor] ...following the mass
arrests of suspected Starlighters,
protestors have taken to the streets
and clashed violently
with superheroes and police alike...
It's all so tediously predictable.
Insurgency, counter-insurgency.
Liberation, crackdown.
Round and round she goes.
Is now a good time to say I've always
found you super fucking creepy?
- Mm.
- [computer chimes]
Whoa, whoa.
Hold on a second. I got something.
Check that out.
So Fort Harmony was an Army hospital
where Frederick Vought worked.
The government designated it Top Secret
and then decommissioned it after the war.
[Hughie] Why is that square blurry?
[Mother's Milk] That's what
the military does to keep
classified facilities hidden.
Now, I'll bet you
a porterhouse at Luger's
that's where Vought was testing the V1.
If there's any more left out there,
that would be the fuckin' place to look.
Hmm.
[alarm blaring]
- [Stan] Were you followed?
- [Mother's Milk] Hell no.
Homelander's looking for V1,
just like we are.
It was only a matter of time
before he found you.
[Stan] We're at 90 feet
below solid concrete.
The door is
munitions grade ballistics resistant,
same as the NORAD bunker
in Cheyenne Mountain.
It will hold.
[alarm shuts off]
Better hope so.
[dramatic music playing]
[Hughie] Oh, thank fuck.
Won't hold forever.
[Annie] So we're trapped down here.
What's the plan?
Wait.
Has anyone seen Zoe?
[vehicle approaching]
[upbeat, quirky music playing]
[door closes]
[quiet footsteps]
[springs creak softly]
[tense music playing]
[hissing]
Dad?
- Zoe?
- Dad?
Zoe...
Oh, my God, Zoe.
[sobbing]
- Oh, my God.
- [gentle music playing]
[whirring]
♪ ♪
- [crashing]
- [glass smashing]
Qu'est-ce que vous faites?!
He told me Zoe was dead.
And he's the one who killed Vicky,
not Homelander!
Fucking psycho!
And you all went along with it.
Come on, Zoe.
[Frenchie] I'm sorry, mon pote.
I cannot allow you to leave.
[tense music playing]
Please.
Don't make me shoot your papa.
No.
- Let them go.
- She tried to kill us both.
She should grow up like a kid.
Not like us.
[inhales]
Go.
[gentle music playing]
[Stan] Zoe, pick up.
Listen to me. Do not come home
until I tell you to.
It's not safe, you understand? Call me.
Do we know when she left?
[Stan] Through the service hatch
a few hours ago.
Can we get out that way?
[Stan] That's precisely
where Noir is patrolling.
[Mother's Milk] Well,
if that's the case...
...then what are you packin'?
Whoa.
I've been looking for those.
- Hmm.
- [inhales] Ah...
Oro Blanco.
[inhales]
Five hundred a stick.
Oh.
- [closes lid]
- [flips latches]
You know, my father spent
his whole life fightin' Vought.
And here I am, smokin'
a fuckin' cigar with Stan Edgar.
I remember your father, you know.
He was impressive.
Over 30 Ivy League attorneys at Vought,
and one small-time Harlem lawyer
made them work weekends and holidays.
- Damn fucking straight he did.
- Mm.
But he couldn't win.
It's why, ultimately,
you won't win, either.
You're fighting an unbeatable foe.
You know that, right?
Who? Vought?
Please. It's more powerful than Vought.
Or Homelander.
More powerful than nature or life itself.
It's profit and loss.
Supply and demand.
The elegant flow of currency
across the globe.
We're just cogs in a great machine...
and we all have our part to play.
Say you kill Soldier Boy, or Homelander,
or even release this virus?
When Superheroes go out of fashion,
something else will
just take their place.
Because corporations must still grow.
Money must still be made.
The machine...
must still be fed.
That is the way of the world.
Motherfucker.
- When this is all over...
- Mm.
...you're aimin' to run Vought again,
ain't you?
Like I said.
We all have our part to play.
[Mother's Milk] Mm-hmm.
[low, tense music playing]
If that day ever comes...
...I have a part to play, too.
And that's to put a bullet
in your fucking skull.
[Stan inhales through cigar]
Finally. Ha, ha.
Showtime.
Hey, kids! Do you love America?
And basic knife skills?
Making S'mores?
- And marching?
- Then sign up for the Homelander Youth!
You'll learn wilderness survival,
campfire songs,
how to fieldstrip a rifle,
and the best way
to sniff out stinky Starlighter rats!
So if you're eight or 18,
you can join the fun.
Sign up for the Homelander Youth...
and be tomorrow's heroes today.
[announcer] Sponsored by
Lean-Lad Diet Lunches.
[indistinct chatter]
- [set bell rings]
- [Homelander sighs]
Who needs Supes
when we can get fucking kids to do it?
- [chuckles]
- Listen.
Uh, I want you to put Crime Analytics
on finding the V1.
It's out there.
- Oh.
- I know it.
Uh... how many people
do you want on it?
Everyone.
It's all we do from now on.
Also, I want our entire pharma division
working on literally nothing
but recreating the V1 formula.
Vought destroyed the original formula.
- That could take years.
- Skip animal testing.
We have camps full of criminals.
- Yeah.
- Just start using them.
- Hmm?
- [weak chuckle]
[swishing liquid]
[slurping]
[swallows]
This is wonderful.
- [Homelander humming]
- Well, howdy, boss.
What are you-- What are you drinkin'?
[Homelander continues humming]
[quiet, propulsive music playing]
It's an honor to have a great American
like yourself on the show.
I guess it runs in the family, huh?
Homelander's father.
Dang.
Glock, huh?
Never saw the appeal
in foreign-made guns.
Well, this ain't your granddaddy's Glock.
This here's a 9mm Gen 5,
seven-round capacity,
with a crisp fucking break.
Well, mine's a much longer barrel,
battle-proven, All-American Colt 1911
chambered in .45 ACP.
That'll blow your fucking panties off.
Now, that little Glock,
that's good for
a late-night Harlem stroll,
but, uh, this here?
That's a certified Kraut-killer.
Think you mean an antique.
I mean a classic.
You want to give it a try?
Now, some can't handle the kick,
but something tells me
you'll do just fine.
[Firecracker moaning loudly]
Heavens to Betsy!
Oh...
[panting]
- Oh.
- Oh...
Oh...
- Oh. Oh...
- Whew.
Well, I gotta hand it to you.
I haven't fucked that hard since...
...since I railed Shari Lewis
on the balcony of Studio 54.
- I ain't got no idea who that is.
- Well...
Hey, why the hairless pussy?
What?
I mean,
what's the point of going down there
if you're not gonna get
a fat face full of fur?
Is that how Homelander likes you?
Like a baby?
[sighs]
More like a mother.
But you two have fucked, right?
Mm-mm.
Damn.
I gotta admit,
I was kinda just doing this
as petty revenge against the freak.
That's terrible.
Who would do such a thing?
And you shouldn't say that
about your son.
Ah, he thinks he's better than me.
He doesn't.
How do you know?
I don't know much, but I can read people.
And the way he looks at you?
Shoot.
I ain't never seen him look
at nobody like that.
Uh, that's not exactly
a compliment, doll.
He is the strangest motherfucker
I've ever known.
And I've had a threesome
with Gary Busey.
Oof.
Here.
Someone I want ya to meet.
[Terror snores]
Is this...?
Terror!
Oh, my mom told me all about you.
Hey, boy. Where's he been?
Me Aunt Judy's been lookin' after him.
Does he still hump everything?
Gentleman of his age?
Well, he does his best.
[Kimiko] Ryan?
Kimiko?
Wait. You-you can talk?
Tell me.
[Frenchie] It's all gone.
[Butcher] Where is Sameer?
We let him leave with Zoe.
We're not all monsters, you fucking...
...monster.
[squelching]
[dramatic music playing]
You touch her, I'll never make more.
So back off.
We're still gonna go after
Homelander, right?
Not today, we're not.
What-- Then when?
I don't know. A week.
Might be a month.
We don't have a month.
He's gonna burn everything down
like you said, let's just go now.
Not without the virus.
But you said I was strong enough.
You said I was the only one
who could stop him.
You said it was my destiny.
I just said that
so you'd get him outta the tower.
Without the germ,
you'd just be another stupid kid
on a fucking suicide run.
Same old lying, pathetic asshole.
♪ ♪
Ryan.
Ryan...
[quiet, intense music playing]
[door opens loudly]
[door slams shut]
[Mother's Milk] All right, kid.
This is a halothane grenade.
What you do is,
you pull the pin, you toss it
and you run like hell.
Also, make sure you don't inhale, or else
you're gonna knock yourself out, too.
Once all the bodies are down
and the smoke clears,
we'll come out and get you.
- Got it?
- [Maverick] Yeah, I got it.
[Hughie] Maverick?
Be careful.
Hughie...
[Hughie] Hey. I know.
I'm sorry. It's just...
He's a really good kid.
I mean, if we find the V1,
I think we should give him some.
Hughie, come on.
How many more people are we gonna kill,
and then their kids come after us?
And then we kill them
and it's this vicious cycle
that never fucking ends.
Maybe we'll never be able
to break it, but we have to at least try.
What was that for?
It's just, uh...
It's been a long time
since I've been around someone who
is actually trying
to make things better instead of
stopping them from getting worse.
You think the V1 can save us?
Fuck yeah, I do.
[Stan] He's at the hatch.
[tense, exciting music playing]
[metal creaking]
[Maverick grunts] Fuck!
What the fuck is this?
Hey, I got an invisible kid here
who stinks like
V-Bro Mango Thunder Body Spray.
Here, take him, shit burns my nose.
[Deep] Maverick? Is that you, bro?
Oh. You're with Edgar?
[Maverick] You were one of
my dad's best friends.
How come you never told me
it was Homelander that killed him?
Bro. Homelander didn't kill your dad.
It was Butcher's crew.
You know, it was that sus French dude,
and Starlight's boyfriend,
what's his name? I wanna say Howie?
They blew him up.
Stuffed his body parts in a box
and dropped him in the East River.
Saw it with my own eyes.
No cap, on God, bro.
[Maverick crying softly]
Does it look like the Deep is talking
to an invisible person?
Fuck.
Fuck!
[intense music playing]
[Maverick] They were just here.
♪ ♪
No, wait!
Goddammit.
Fuck, there's not enough power.
[mouthing]
Slithery motherfucker.
- Ooh!
- [Annie] Oh, shit.
I mean, instant karma, but fuck.
Um, okay, we gotta go out the front.
- Stick together.
- [Annie] yeah.
Yo, nice work, Brobo Cop.
[grunts]
[vehicle door closes]
[hissing]
[tense music playing]
Sorry, bro.
Don't hate the player,
hate the game.
[♪ Limp Bizkit sings
"Rollin' (Air Raid Vehicle)"]
♪ Keep rollin',
rollin', rollin', rollin' ♪
- ♪ What? ♪
- ♪ Keep rollin', rollin' ♪
♪ rollin', rollin' ♪
- ♪ Come on ♪
- ♪ Keep rollin', rollin' ♪
♪ rollin', rollin' ♪
[quiet, suspenseful music playing]
- [yells]
- [grunting]
[shouts]
[Annie yells]
[choking]
[Mother's Milk] Mango Thunder,
motherfucker!
- [hissing]
- Ooh! Ah!
[yelling]
[grunting]
[panting]
Where's Hughie?
Ah!
[Maverick] It was you, wasn't it?
- You killed my dad.
- Get the fuck off me!
Where are you? What?
- Ah! Ow!
- [Maverick] Is that why you were
telling me all that weird shit
about letting go?
- You sick fuck!
- You're right, you're right.
It was me. It was me.
I mean... cold comfort, but I...
I killed my dad, too.
- [Maverick] You fucking psycho!
- [Hughie] Just wait, just wait!
Look, with Translucent...
someone murdered my girlfriend.
Not your dad, but still, I was...
I was angry and scared...
...and I-I felt all this...
this hate, and I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done it.
It's not the answer.
[Maverick] It's the only answer, motherfucker.
[grunting]
[groans, pants]
Maverick? Stop.
I don't want to fight you.
[grunts]
Ah!
[straining]
[yells, grunts]
- [Maverick yells]
- No, no, no!
[straining]
[grunting]
Ah!
[coughs]
[panting]
[Annie] Hughie! [yells]
[grunts]
[panting]
- [quiet, melancholy music playing]
- [sobbing]
Is... is Maverick...
- [crying]
- She got Maverick.
- It's okay.
- Oh, no.
- [sobbing]
- It's okay.
Everything's gonna be okay.
[Annie crying]
I'm here.
[sobs]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Ryan] Dad?
Ryan.
Hey, you.
I'm really glad you called.
I knew you would.
It's like a...
...miracle.
You like the upgrade?
You remember when you took me here?
Pretended to care about me?
I do care about you, son. I love you.
I need to ask you--
For my forgiveness?
You already have it.
- What?
- Okay? Let me finish.
I put too much pressure on you.
To, uh, fill my boots.
And-and I realize now
that, uh...
well, that that was impossible.
But I do have some pretty exciting news.
I am going to live forever now.
[quiet, tense music playing]
I'll realize my own legacy.
And you...
[scoffs] ...you're off the hook.
- You can do whatever--
- Did you do it?
- Did you rape my mom?
- What?
Of course not.
Who told you...
Did William Butcher tell you that?
Your mother and I, we had an affair.
A consensual affair between
- two adults.
- Your heart's racing.
Well, yeah, because I'm shocked.
And-and frankly,
my heart's breaking a little bit
that you could think
I would do something like that.
[shouts]
Ryan... Ryan-- Stop!
[dark, dramatic music playing]
Ryan.
I don't know where this is coming from,
because your mother, she came on to me.
[yells]
Ryan!
- Son...
- [grunts]
Ryan. Ryan.
Buddy. Look what came out of it.
My son. A blessing.
[Homelander groans]
Hey, hey, hey.
Ah!
[groans]
- [Ryan gasping]
- [Homelander exhales]
Oh, Ryan...
Dammit. Look at what you made me do.
[groaning]
Shh...
Shh. Shh, shh.
Hey.
It's okay.
My sweet, sweet boy.
[panting]
[Ryan grunts]
Ah!
[Homelander panting]
[exhales]
Okay, so, the virus is gone.
Sameer took off with Zoe
and Butcher went after Ryan? [scoffs]
Probably gettin' lasered as we speak.
And Homelander's got Edgar.
If he wasn't already close to finding V1,
he is now.
[Kimiko] We are so fucked.
Like, anal-DP-one-dude's-thighs-draped-
over-another-dude's-
both-pumping-away-
on-some-poor-girl fucked.
Hey. Maybe we lay off the porn.
[quietly] No.
Okay, I do have some good news.
We were able to make out
some of the redacted text.
In 1963, a troop of Boy Scouts
was found dead in the woods
near this Fort Harmony.
The rib cages of their tiny body
ripped open.
- And this is good news?
- [Frenchie] Bah oui!
The files are no longer redacted.
Okay.
Well, that's where we're headed.
[Hughie exhales]
[♪ Bob Dylan playing
"In My Time of Dyin'"]
♪ ♪
Annie?
- [Annie panting]
- Wait! Wait!
- You could've died, Hughie.
- I'm okay.
- I'm here.
- But I think if that happened...
I just, I wouldn't come back from that.
This was easier when I was on my own.
Annie.
♪ Well, in my time of dyin' ♪
♪ don't want nobody to mourn ♪
♪ All I want for you to do ♪
♪ is take my body home ♪
♪ Well, well, well ♪
♪ So I can die easy ♪
- ♪ Well, well, well...
- [Deep] Homelander?
Homelander?
- Hey.
- ♪ So I can die easy ♪
♪ Jesus gonna make up,
Jesus gonna make up ♪
♪ Jesus gonna make up my dyin' bed ♪
♪ All I want for you to do ♪
♪ is take my body home ♪
♪ Well, well, well ♪
♪ So I can die easy ♪
♪ Jesus gonna make up my dyin' bed ♪
Mm. We have much to discuss.
♪ Lord, in my time of dyin' ♪
♪ don't want nobody to cry ♪
♪ All I want you to do ♪
♪ is take me when I die ♪
♪ Well, in my time of dyin' ♪
♪ don't want nobody to mourn ♪
♪ All I want for you to do ♪
♪ is take my body home ♪
♪ Well, well, well ♪
♪ So I can die easy ♪
♪ Jesus gonna make up,
Jesus gonna make up ♪
♪ Jesus gonna make up my dyin' bed ♪
♪ Well, meet me, Jesus, meet me ♪
♪ meet me in the middle of the air ♪
♪ If these wings should fail me, Lord ♪
♪ would you meet me with another pair? ♪
♪ Well, well, well ♪
♪ So I can die easy ♪
♪ Jesus gonna make up,
Jesus gonna make up ♪
♪ Jesus gonna make up my dyin' bed ♪
♪ Lord, in my time of dyin' ♪
♪ don't want nobody to cry ♪
♪ All I want you to do ♪
♪ is take me when I die ♪
♪ Well, well, well ♪
♪ So I can die easy ♪
♪ Jesus gonna make up,
Jesus gonna make up ♪
♪ Jesus gonna make up my dyin' bed ♪