♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 23=
Focus on training.
Feinu.
Go to the capital.
Look into He Rufei.
Commander...
Look into
his days before Mingshui,
and monitor
his every move now.
Understood.
(Xiao)
Mr. He.
You're back.
Mr. Jiang.
May I trouble you
with something?
There is no "trouble".
Just say the word.
No problem.
You escort agents
must have connections.
Could you
figure something out?
Who has visited
Yuhua Temple these years
and met Miss He,
who was resting in the rear courtyard?
Miss He?
He Rufei's little sister.
Mr. Jiang, I know
it sounds abrupt,
but it's important.
Unfortunately,
I can't explain
everything yet.
Escort agents take jobs
without question asked.
Besides, you're my buddy.
Consider it
done.
Thank you.
(Before Mingshui Battle,)
(He Rufei was at the Yuhua Temple.)
(So if He Rufei did meet Xu Jingfu,)
(he must have)
(met him at the Yuhua Temple.)
(Mr. Jiang will be able)
(to confirm that.)
(Though it's not enough)
(to prove He Rufei's)
(involvement in the scheme,)
(at least,)
(it shows the Commander)
(that)
(He Rufei is a suspect.)
(Commander)
(is investigating for sure)
(and may uncover new leads.)
Now,
I just need to hone my skills
and bide my time.
General.
(Stand Tall and See Far)
What's wrong?
I found out that
a formidable
female general fought
alongside Xiao Jue.
A female general?
What is she like?
Extremely skilled
and valiant,
coming from Yezhou Garrison.
At Jiyang,
she single-handedly
killed Wutuo's commander Huyate.
Understood.
Could it
be her?
No way.
She's supposed to be dead.
Better safe
than sorry.
Whether she's He Yan or not,
she has to die.
He.
You've been
running for six hours.
Why don't you take a break?
Yeah.
Get some rest.
If you keep running...
I'm fine. Not tired yet.
Have some water
and eat.
I can skip
a meal.
But you haven't
eaten for ages.
Yeah.
S-Stop...
S-Stop training.
At least eat something
and take a break.
If you keep...
This is...
- S-Stop training.
- He.
He.
Wait.
S-Stop...
Still running?
H-He's...
still training?
Take a break.
I bet he is bothered by something.
That's why
he's tormenting himself.
Mr. Chu.
Miss Xu.
Is this for my father
or me?
I roamed around
during Water God Festival
in Jiyang.
The moment I saw this,
I felt that
it suits you perfectly.
I hope you will accept it.
Courtesy requires a return.
I prepared some pastries.
Would you join me
in the pavilion
to have pastries
while admiring the flowers?
Miss Xu.
I...
haven't paid respects to Master.
But
it won't take
that long.
Perhaps you could go ahead,
and I'll join you
very soon.
Alright.
See you later.
Zilan.
You're usually reliable,
but you have truly disappointed me
with this mission in Jiyang.
Master.
I failed to kill Chai Anxi,
in fear of
alerting our enemies.
What did Chai Anxi say?
He told Xiao Jue
what happened in Mingshui.
He said He Rufei
made him withhold
Xiao Zhongwu's letter.
That's all?
Now that he's learned my deepest secret,
he won't tell the truth.
He'll be scared that I'd silence him,
or
he'll try to blackmail me.
If he doesn't tell the truth,
I will drop the bracelet,
and you shall kill him.
Understood.
He also said
that you
were the mastermind
of the scheme.
Aren't you scared
I'd silence you
because of what you said?
I've always wanted to earn
your utmost trust.
But my limitations
made my goal
impossible.
This has long troubled me.
Now that I know your secret,
I see it as
a double-edged sword.
Though you may silence me
as a precaution,
I feel more joy than worry,
for I'll defend this secret
with my life,
which bonds us deeper.
I believe
that I am finally
qualified
to earn your trust
and share your burdens.
Zilan.
I was joking with you.
But I wasn't
joking with you.
I failed the mission.
I'll find a way
to make amends.
Do you have a plan?
Though Chai Anxi is dead,
Xiao Jue won't let this go.
In my opinion,
He Rufei was the perpetrator,
and it had
nothing to do with you.
I bet Xiao Jue
will investigate He Rufei first.
Once we inform He Rufei
about this,
he will surely make a move.
Xiao Jue wants trouble.
Then he can have it.
He left Yezhou
without permission.
We can't let it slide.
Also,
a young officer
performed remarkably well
in the Jiyang Battle.
Considering their contributions,
if this officer
receives rewards
while Commander Xiao
faces punishment,
the veteran troops will surely
grow discontent.
When conflicts arise,
it will make Xiao Jue
look incompetent
in leading
the troops.
That's what you're thinking?
You should know.
If this gets out,
it would be a felony.
Your guidance has been vital to me.
Without you,
I wouldn't be here today.
I swear I'll eliminate
all threats
to you,
even if
it costs me
my very life.
Father.
Pingting.
What brings you here?
Can't I just check on you?
Father.
Why did you make Mr. Chu kneel?
What did he do wrong?
Let him get up.
I'm waiting
to see flowers with him.
Naughty girl.
I have important matters
to discuss with Zilan.
Father,
flower viewing
is also important.
Father.
Help me up.
Come on.
Be careful.
I've said my piece.
Understood.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
Master,
I have one more question.
Please enlighten me.
What is it?
What should I tell His Majesty
tomorrow?
Zilan,
His Majesty bears the world
on his shoulders.
As his ministers,
we must share his burdens.
We don't have to
trouble him
with all the trivial matters.
Yes, Master.
I
understand.
Tomorrow, someone will bring you
the cure I found for you.
Will you remain here,
as a caged bird in shadows,
or go out there
as the mighty General Feihong?
Think carefully.
General Feihong.
Just a second.
Let me inform...
Step aside.
Master.
- Master.
- Chancellor.
General Feihong.
This is my mansion.
How dare you
barge in like this?
I apologize.
But this is urgent.
Xiao Jue achieved military merits
in Jiyang again.
Doesn't it mean that he will
regain influence?
I thought it was something urgent.
He just won a battle, that's all.
Do you have to be so scared?
Get up.
However,
I did hear something.
Chai Anxi didn't die
at Mingshui.
Xiao Jue found him
two days ago.
T-Then...
What should I do?
Xiao Jue will bring him
to His Majesty.
Help me, Chancellor.
Rest easy.
I've already
dealt with it.
Chai Anxi is dead.
He won't be coming.
But Xiao Jue
won't let this go.
He'll keep searching for evidence.
You must be careful
not to leave any traces behind.
After all,
the one who contacted Chai Anxi
was you.
Rest assured.
I won't
let Xiao Jue
get any dirt on me.
Good.
After all,
military promotions
hinge on battlefield merits.
Xiao Jue is brave and smart.
Halting his ascension
poses genuine difficulty.
Then let's end it at once.
Chancellor.
Why don't we work with Wutuo
and do what we did
to Xiao Zhongwu again?
Rest assured.
I've devised a plan.
Let's ally with Wutuo
to create a diversion.
They'll attack Huayuan.
I'll volunteer to fight
and stage a show with the Wutuo army
while giving them
Rundu's Military Defense Maps
in secret
for them to launch a surprise attack.
When Rundu
pleads for help,
I'll delay reinforcement.
Xiao Jue won't
sit back and do nothing.
We'll set a trap
to kill him
there.
Then I will
start preparing.
(I can't tell)
(Chancellor Xu)
(about He Yan yet.)
(Otherwise, he would)
(lose faith in me)
(and pin the blame on me.)
(That's his plan)
(for explaining)
(the Mingshui defeat.)
(Luckily, I'm prepared.)
(He Yan is close to the Eight Warriors)
(of Fuyue Army.)
(Seven now serve under me.)
(One commands Rundu Garrison.)
(If she is alive,)
(then I can kill)
(all seven warriors in Huayuan)
(and use the one in Rundu)
(as bait.)
(That's how I manipulate her)
(to go to Rundu.)
(There,)
(she'll meet her demise.)
(If she is truly dead,)
(eliminating all Eight Warriors)
(still benefits my cause.)
(Besides,)
(I will be able)
(to get rid of Xiao Jue in the process.)
Young Master.
Did Chancellor Xu really
plan to kill you?
I've passed this test.
Greater storms
are yet to come, though.
Young Master.
So what is
our next move?
As long as I earn his trust,
I will find out
his next move.
If he colludes
with Wutuo,
we'll take precautions.
Huaijin.
What's wrong
with you and Miss He?
Why aren't you
speaking at all?
We are
just fine.
Commander Xiao.
You know all the war strategies.
How can you be
so clueless with women?
You didn't
seize the opportunity
in Chonghuai
and grew increasingly distant.
Miss He
is a sensitive young lady,
after all.
Do you want her
to feel abandoned?
None of your business.
I...
I'm offering you advice.
Seriously.
♪Walking through the crowd,
without asking about the future♪
(Miss He stayed secluded)
at Yuhua Temple.
Besides her parents,
she only met one unexpected visitor.
He was not an ordinary man,
but Chancellor Xu Jingfu.
He sat with Miss He
in the meditation room
(and played chess for a while.)
He Rufei.
I knew it.
♪Just to see you turn,
a fleeting blush in your glance♪
♪Just to tread the snow you described♪
♪The more fate intertwines intensely♪
♪The further we drift apart♪
♪It's hard to sever love or hatred♪
♪Before destiny is sealed♪
♪Again and again♪
♪My love rests between your fingers♪
♪Farewell tears blur my vision♪
♪Indescribable yearnings♪
♪Awaiting the spread of moonlight♪
♪Perhaps I'll regret saying goodbye♪
♪Maybe we can't share sorrows and joys♪
♪Past memories intertwine♪
♪The story rehearses itself♪
♪Snow falls on windowsills,
moments fading away♪
♪Before destiny is sealed♪
♪Again and again♪
♪My love for you burns fiercely♪
♪Lifelong devotion turns into a vow♪
♪That's my last wish♪
♪Awaiting the spread of moonlight♪
He Yan.
(Commander.)
Let me lead the elite squad
to draw away Huyate's heavy infantry.
(Xiao)
Young Master.
His Majesty sent Yan He
with us to Yezhou.
Is Chancellor Xu
behind this?
Yan He is a rising star
from a loyal family.
I think His Majesty
wants him to tag along.
So, His Majesty
intends to promote Yan He.
Then you...
It's fine.
He's a military man.
I'm a civil official.
Why would I compete with him?
Are you promoted to
Director of the Ministry of War
because you've earned
His Majesty's trust?
(Mr. Chu.)
The battle in Jiyang
strikes me as peculiar.
Did you notice anything fishy
back then?
Your Majesty,
before the battle,
many Wutuo spies
infiltrated Jiyang
and even attempted
to abduct the little princess.
Thus, I believe that
Wutuo people
have been plotting this.
They may
wage another war against us.
We must be alert.
I also heard that General Fengyun
saved Jiyang single-handedly.
What is
your opinion?
In my humble opinion,
General Fengyun
may have defended Jiyang,
but he did leave Yezhou
without permission.
Still, his achievements
outweigh his faults.
I implore you to show leniency
lest others grow discontent.
After all,
without General Fengyun
and that
brave young soldier,
Jiyang wouldn't have
regained peace so fast.
Brave young soldier?
Are you referring to He Yan,
who single-handedly
killed the Wutuo commander
Huyate?
Exactly.
I've also heard that
when Wutuo forces
attacked Yezhou Garrison,
He Yan managed to
crush Rida Muzi
to demonstrate our prestige.
To emerge distinguished
from General Fengyun's towering shadow,
this young man
truly possesses remarkable skill.
Mr. Chu,
you keep asking for rewards
on others' behalf.
What about yourself?
During the battle,
you did a great job by reallocating
the citizens.
Tell me.
What reward would you have?
Your Majesty,
I seek
a higher position.
You've always disdained
such worldly pursuits
and declined rewards like this.
Why are you
seeking promotion
this time?
Your Majesty,
I used to believe
that a minister
only needed to be loyal.
But through recent experience,
I've realized
that loyalty alone
without actual power is not enough.
Therefore,
I seek greater influence
to better serve Your Majesty
in greater causes.
I see.
Alright then.
I appoint you
as Director of the Ministry of War.
Stay diligent
and uphold your duties.
Do not
let me down.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
A ruler
never trusts others lightly.
Demonstrating my capabilities
and weaknesses
makes me appear
easily controllable
to His Majesty.
When I finally possess power,
I can guide Wei back to
righteous governance.
(Imperial Edict)
Young Master,
forgive my boldness,
but you shouldn't have asked
to reward Miss He.
Chancellor Xu will
grow suspicious.
Do you think
I'm so clueless and reckless?
That's not what I meant.
I do
harbor personal motives,
but this decree serves
as a stepping stone.
Huayuan in jeopardy!
I heard Wutuo attacked Huayuan.
Is that true?
They just lost in Jiyang.
Another attack?
It's confirmed.
Someone just reported to Mr. Shen,
and I overheard it.
(Wutuo attacked Huayuan?)
(First Jiyang, now Huayuan.)
(The Wutuo army)
(seems to be probing)
(our military capabilities.)
(They might plan to start a war.)
General Feihong is leading
the troops to Huayuan.
He'll surely crush
those Wutuo soldiers!
Definitely.
(He Rufei is going to Huayuan?)
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪