kill
Miaomiao
Someone is coming
Fang Miaomiao
Come quickly
Miaomiao
Fang Miaomiao
Am I going to die?
Miaomiao
Xiao Ran
i'm here
Wang Twelve
Hayashi Maki
I am here
I won’t play with you anymore
Miaomiao
Fang Miaomiao
No
Miaomiao
缳缳
next life
We are still good brothers
A word from a gentleman
It's hard to catch up with the horse
Xinger
I am coming
Zhuge Yue
Xinger
You finally came to pick me up
I'm late
Xinger
wait for me
hurry up
Come quickly
stop
Chu House, Leping Lane
Thank you
walk slowly
You two are sneaky
Thieves and thieves
I see you are very handsome
Probably not from the city.
we are
Businessmen from Yanbei
Looking for Leping Lane
kid
do you know where this place is
I won't be sneaky
Thief-headed people lead the way
I'll take you to Leping Lane
How do you help the big bad guy?
elder brother
Mother said
We have been taught to act bravely when we are young
Draw a sword to help
Especially my beautiful uncle and sister
Dad said
What's the use of being good-looking?
Be like him and his mother
Good looking and good at martial arts
This is our role model
little brother little sister
You are so beautiful too
It's the most beautiful thing I've ever seen
Really
real
more beautiful than me
Finally someone praises my brother
For the sake of your honesty
come with me
Watching shadow puppets
Let's go to see the shadow puppets
It's started, it's started
Everyone comes to see the shadow puppets
beautiful kid
Why are you here to show us the shadow puppet show?
This is our Ximeng City
The most popular shadow puppet show
So everyone who comes here for the first time should watch it
You can see it as soon as you enter the city
This is your luck
Let’s talk about the current Ximeng City
It was built by King Ximeng and General Chu Qiao
General Chu Qiao not only had an affair with King Yan Xun
A camaraderie of fighting side by side
She was also the confidante of the late Emperor Bian Tang
What a wonderful woman
What a strange person
At that time, the people of Dayong had not yet awakened.
Still living under the shackles of slavery
Dayong was dissatisfied with the Western Alliance's independence
So we sent people to attack the Western Alliance
General Chu Qiao led his army to fight against Dayong's army
In the final battle with Dayong
General Chu Qiao
With Zhuge Yue, who was still Dayong’s military advisor at the time,
The inside should be combined with the outside
finally won the war
OK OK
Don't look at this shadow puppet show. It's so simple.
Back then, this game was coordinated inside and outside.
narrow escape
Even General Chu thought Zhuge Yue was dead
My brother said it was better than the shadow puppet show.
Since then
Dayong will no longer be as strong as it once was
However, the foreign tribe Quanrong took advantage of the opportunity and entered
Send troops to China
General Chu took the lead
United Western Alliance Yanbei
Bian Tang and Dayong soldiers and horses from all directions
Finally defeated the entire army
well
OK OK
But General Chu was in this battle
Seriously injured
almost died
She fell on the battlefield
But I only have the common people in my heart
little uncle
Don't worry
General Chu is alive and well
Although she was seriously injured on the battlefield
But Zhuge Yue came from thousands of troops and horses
brought her back
Saved her with the magic medicine of the miracle doctor Xiao Ran
beautiful little brother
How do you know this?
Zhuge Yunzhou Zhuge Yunsheng
father
Dad, hurry up, hurry up
If you don't go home, you'll be spanked.
spank
Tell dad what you did today
open the door
Okay, gently
Don't let your mother find out
Do you still know how to come back?
Naughty
Pretty little uncle
Yan Xun
You two arrived just in time
we are busy
Come and help
Let's go together
Eat meat
Eat meat, eat meat, eat meat
Achu
Your Majesty
The king dreamed of General Xiuli again
Where is Queen Helian?
Your Majesty, please slow down.
The king is confused again
Queen Helian has been gone for ten years
ten years
If the king misses her
Waiting to return from the hunting ground
Let’s go to the imperial mausoleum and see it
outside the tent
But someone is waiting
It's General Heliantu
She said that Emperor Changzhao of Bian Tang Dynasty
Sent a new credential from Tonghao
I want to discuss this with you
Emperor Changzhao Li Xiuyi
How long has it been since Li Ce died?
Return to the king
It has been forty-six years since the death of the late Emperor Bian Tang
Forty-six years
I'm old too
Heliantu See the King
explain
Report to the King
According to the practice of once every five years
Emperor Bian Tang sent his credentials
According to previous provisions
Added a new trade strategy
and expressed that if you agree
They are willing to send thirty envoys to Yan
Come to Yandu with gifts
Establish friendship with Yanbei
knew
besides
our northeastern border
Several times in a row last month
Harassed by Quanrong people
Fortunately, there are not many of them.
Just burning, killing and looting in border villages
no further intrusion
I sent people to ambush nearby
ambushed their team
found they were just
A group of bandits roaming Yanbei and Ximeng
Because the weather is extremely cold this year
The borders of Quanrong are difficult to navigate
Ximeng
how's it going
Is Ximeng okay?
them
Are you still alive?
Return to the king
The canal between us and Ximeng is under construction
The ship will be open next year
The king of Ximeng issued the Young Crops Law last month
mutual market law
and municipal barge laws
and issued a new order
It is said that there is a suggestion day every month
Yoshi
You all go back
Tired of being alone
Please obey the king's order
I'm not convinced
I didn't say that
King of Ximeng, although you don’t consider yourself a king
But no matter what
They are all noble people.
how to know
What about our three-thirds of an acre of land?
You asked me to pay him forty-five cents
So how should my losses be calculated?
What do you have to lose?
It's your chicken
Come and practice in my highland barley field
so many chickens
I will only calculate the harvest of one acre of land for you.
Even less
If it weren't for my own land
Requisitioned to build roads
I won't move next door to your house either
My chicken
I won’t even eat food from your fields.
Then it has nothing to do with me.
Okay, does it belong to your family?
You don’t know yet?
According to the newly promulgated mutual trading law this year,
Any land requisitioned for road construction
Landowners can all receive subsidies.
And you get paid for free for such a good deed?
This money is not conjured out of thin air.
This time Ximeng is building roads
Just to make it easier to do business with Bian Tang
Let the sea buckthorn fruit in season
Fastest delivery to Bian Tang
Profit from these fruits
This is the source of subsidies
Take them quickly
yes
Get out of the way
Someone wants me to be a slave
stop
Stop running
Get out of the way
Stop the Western Alliance King
King of Western Alliance, save me
Someone wants to buy me as a slave
stand up
Many years ago, there were no slaves in the Western Alliance.
according to law
Buying and selling slaves privately is a felony
Who dares to capture her and take her back as a slave?
Ximeng Wang Mingjian
Our young master is getting married by issuing a marriage certificate.
These are the words of a matchmaker who is getting married
It's not buying and selling slaves.
You used the betrothal gift to buy my father.
He just agreed
never asked my opinion
How is this different from buying and selling slaves?
Your father accepted the betrothal gift
You are our young master’s bride
It's useless for you to come here and complain.
you
Yun Chuqiao
Your name is Chu Qiao
Right, can't it?
My ideal is to be like her
Also be a female general
That’s why I changed my name to this
So you want to escape from marriage
Just because I want to be a female general
right
I'm going to enlist in the Western Allied Forces
The battlefield is no child’s play
The reaction is quite sharp
But it’s not enough to train you
It was you who attacked
If we have the ability, let’s do it again
Take this to General Chu
She will let you join the Western Allied Forces
If you have the ability, you can become a centurion
There is also one hundred and fifty yuan of military pay every month.
less than two years
You can earn the betrothal gift your father received.
Did you see it?
This is the approval of the King of the Western Alliance
I will be the Western Allied Forces from now on
My father collects your money
I will definitely return it to you
Thank you
Why is it already March?
It's still snowing
This has always been like this in Western Fujian Mountains
But in another month and a half
The weather will get warmer
Wait until the snow on the mountain melts
The river flows through Ximin Lake
It's spring
Our grassland in Yanbei
There will definitely be lush water and grass
It’s another good year for herders
Your Majesty
Zhuge Yue
I want to eat Yanbei’s hot pot
am i late
You came just in time
The hot pot has just boiled
Li Ce
Have you ever really liked someone
Prince
There is no beauty in the world
Pleasant to the eye is a beautiful woman
jojo
I like you
Your Majesty is here again
Waiting for General Xiuli
jojo
Qiaoqiao came back victorious
Can that girl think of me as that person for a while?
Until you really forget him
no more pain
If you don’t want to get married yet
It can be treated as a wedding without today
I can wait for you forever
Waiting for you to like me and fall in love with me
Waiting for the day you really want to be my wife
They are all going to be mothers.
Still so unaware of the importance
We will be a family of three soon
It’s the first New Year’s Eve to be celebrated
Chun'er is no longer alone
Chun'er is so happy
I want to live a life that truly belongs to me
Find a place where no one knows me
Calm and free
Where is General Cheng?
Let’s go to Yunzhou
go wherever you want
Live a life just the two of us
Helian
A woman should look like a woman
I want to borrow your horse
Why does everyone want to borrow horses from me?
My horse has been borrowed
Now the only thing left is this donkey used for grinding
Zhao Che
You let go of it all
come with me
good
let's leave together
Brother Eleven
We finally became official
Where are you going from now on?
The sky is big and the earth is big
Anywhere