♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my charm♪
♪Just to meet me, my sweet little scheme♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 4=
=Revenge Long in the Making=
Where did this thief come from?
I'm your Young Master's wife.
Is this how the Li family
treats its mistress?
Young Master's wife?
The Li family has no such person.
A thief should lose hands and feet
and be dragged to the garden.
Someone come here.
Seize her!
Let's see who dares!
What are you doing?
Ms. Murong.
We just caught a thief.
We're taking her downstairs.
(Murong Xue, Li Hong's fiancée)
Murong Xue.
You know me?
Did Ye Lang tell you about me?
My clothes won't fit you.
You'll have to make do with a maid's uniform.
(Any woman who marries into a wealthy family)
(is never to be underestimated.)
Anyone who violates the Li family's taboos
will end up as
their feed.
(Trying to scare me?)
(I've been married three times.)
(I know all about)
(these rich-family secrets.)
Ye Lang and I
grew up together.
Then he was brought back
as an illegitimate son
and forced to live under their roof
in this devouring mansion.
His health was never good after that,
and they suddenly announced
that he was brain-dead.
I didn't even get to see him one last time.
The Li family
has so many medical institutions,
couldn't they find even one doctor
who could cure him?
Well.
With so many
doctors and hospitals,
it would be a pain to investigate.
Not really.
In Master Li's study,
there's a system
containing medical records
from every hospital in Manlong.
Forget finding just one doctor,
you could even track every visitor
who has entered those hospitals.
(As long as I can hack the system,)
(I can definitely find Xiaodi.)
Ms. Murong.
Do you know what Ye Lang likes to eat?
Well,
Lang loves snowflake crisps most.
When Auntie Ye Mei coaxed him
into taking his medicine...
Thanks for the coffee, Ms. Murong.
I'll be sure
to repay you another day.
(This maid outfit)
(does make it easier to slip in.)
How dare you!
Master's study
isn't a place you can just walk into.
You're
Ms. Jiang?
What did you do to the lock with your phone?
Trying to steal something?
Watch your words.
You can't just accuse me like that.
I just got lost.
You're quite the actress, aren't you?
First a witch,
now a maid,
you've got plenty of tricks.
Ms. Jiang,
this time,
who are you trying to seduce?
Ms. Murong Xue got me this outfit.
Is there a problem?
Search her.
This door lock
can only be opened
with the fingerprints of the master
or the two young masters.
This shameless woman
must be trying to tamper with it!
Search her.
Stop!
What are you doing?
Oops!
It slipped.
This...
This is Young Master's medicine.
Never mind.
I'll make Ye Lang a new one.
After all,
a wife should take care of her husband.
Butler Zhong,
please take good care of the madam.
(The Li family is such a mess.)
(Once I find which hospital Xiaodi is in,)
(I need to leave this awful place.)
Let's see how long you can keep this up.
You'll end up being fertilizer.
Young Master.
Time for your medicine.
Where did you go?
Why are you dressed like that?
I went to the kitchen
to prepare your medicine.
To nourish
your
body.
Coming in dressed like this,
what are you up to?
I heard the Li family has strict rules,
I just want you
to teach me a little more.
♪Bit by bit, marking you with kisses♪
♪Like shadows entwined in the night♪
♪You are mine♪
♪Right now, I want you completely♪
♪Bit by bit, leaving traces behind♪
♪I love you, with no limits♪
♪Crimson bite marks♪
♪Like I need you, and can't stop♪
Why did you make snowflake crisps?
You don't like it?
I like it.
I like
anything you make.
When I was little and had to take medicine,
my mom made snowflake crisps too.
So, is this snowflake crisp good?
If you like it,
I'll make it for you every day.
Young Master,
it's time for your medicine.
Niannian,
for the rest of your life,
you can't leave me again.
Okay,
I won't leave you.
Young Master,
drink your medicine now.
Look, it's all your fault.
My clothes are wet,
yours too.
You'll catch a cold wearing this.
I'll help you take it off
and send it to the laundry.
Okay.
Get up.
What are you doing?
You scared me!
Get out.
I need to change.
Need a hand?
Just go out.
That medicine made me all sticky.
I need to rinse off.
Come on, get out.
I need to wash up.
Hurry.
Jiang Niannian.
I won't repeat my previous life's mistake.
(Previous Life)
The wedding's about to start.
Why're you here now?
I haven't seen you for 24 hours.
If I didn't see you soon,
I felt like I'd die.
Niannian.
This feels like a dream.
From now on,
let's never be apart again.
Niannian.
It turns out
that when people are truly happy,
they can actually feel pain.
Go to hell.
(In my previous life,
I loved you with all my heart.)
(Yet you killed me on our wedding day.)
(Jiang Niannian.)
(Why did you do that?)
(This life The day Ye Lang Was Reborn)
(Could it be)
(I've been reborn?)
Ye Lang.
Are you okay?
Do you feel unwell?
Where are we?
This is the funeral of Zhou Chen,
chairman of the Zhou Group.
He supplied
the Li family's medical equipment.
How could it be her?
You know her?
Zhou Chen was her third husband.
I heard the first two
both died after marrying her.
(Jiang Niannian.)
(I never imagined)
(we'd already met before.)
Ye Lang.
The ceremony isn't over,
where you going?
He has more inheritance than the last man.
The more Jiang Niannian marries,
the richer I get!
Don't gamble it all away.
Qingqing needs money overseas too.
No worries.
(Organ Donation Agreement)
(Jiang Xiaodi)
(Zheng Lu)
Once she enters the Li family,
she'll be mine.
As for her brother,
get the surgery done ASAP.
Don't forget what you promised me.
Jiang Niannian.
This life,
I won't let the tragedy
of our past repeat itself.
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪