(All characters, places,
and organizations are fictional.)
(Children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
Momo promised she'd raise my baby well.
We were as close as sisters.
It's Mommy.
Thank you for taking
such good care of the baby.
Thank you so much.
You poor thing.
You kept saying you felt dizzy.
How could this happen?
The poor thing.
At least he got to see
his mother's face...
Don't worry.
(Ju Shin)
- Hello?
- Ba Ra...
passed away at dawn.
There won't be a funeral
before the burial.
Is her granddaughter
really moving in next week?
Yes. I spoke with her on the phone.
I think I'm going to miss him.
You should come and visit sometime.
I'll text you the address.
- Would that be okay?
- Of course.
Thank you. I know she was grateful too.
It was nothing.
Ba Ra asked me to.
- I've been paid more than enough.
- Please, I insist.
Goodness.
You should go back in.
The grandmother is all by herself.
Right.
She's not just a pretty face,
but an angel.
Ba Ra.
How could you leave me...
and just go like that?
How could you?
That looked like Geum Ba Ra, the reporter.
Well, I can just check.
(Reporter Geum Ba Ra)
The number you have dialed
is not in service.
Please check the number and dial again.
The number you have dialed
is not in service.
- Please check the number and dial again.
- I'm heading out.
Okay.
Was she in a car accident or something?
Shouldn't the baby see his mother off?
Be sure to burp him
and lay him down gently on his side.
He sometimes spits up, even after burping.
Got it.
(Momo)
- Yes...
- The press will be there,
so I think we should go together.
I'm downstairs.
Seatbelt.
She was in the prime of her life.
What's wrong?
Book us a table at the Ria Hotel buffet.
For just us two.
No. You know what will happen
if you overeat.
Don't worry.
I will just eat in moderation.
You think you can restrain yourself
in front of a feast?
I can if I have to.
I can do anything...
for my health.
We cleanse ourselves
of worldly dust and attachments.
We pray to the sky and the earth.
From the Muryangsa Temple
Here in this world of suffering
In Seodaemun District, Seoul, South Korea,
In this pure sanctuary of Suwol
At the request of
the humble devotee Ha Jae In
We pray for the spirit
of the dearly departed Geum Ba Ra
For the spirit of the dearly departed
Geum Ba Ra
May she attain rebirth in paradise...
Let go...
of all earthly attachments...
and depart in peace.
Thank you.
Drive safe.
I'll treat you to a meal sometime soon.
Sure.
She's really changed, that Momo.
Such a waste of a pretty face
and a sharp mind.
She must have studied so incredibly hard.
And she never even had
one proper tutoring session.
If she had married me,
she wouldn't have died.
Life and death are up to fate.
Her time was just up.
Goodness.
Did my little one burp?
You're so adorable.
Your Daddy...
cried so much today.
Thank you.
I hope you find peace...
wherever you are.
I'd like to pour you a drink.
You've been through so much.
You're the one who has.
Thank you so much.
Just take a sip.
When are you going to tell Yong Joong?
- You're not going to tell him?
- No.
Why?
They already decided
to go their separate ways.
Then why did you ask me for the surgery?
Just because.
I'm a better fit for Momo than Jin Ju is.
That's the only reason?
Yong Joong is having such a hard time.
Are you punishing him?
I'll explain everything to him.
It's not the right thing to do.
We're way past doing the right thing.
He and Momo just had a falling out.
Saying it's me would just confuse him.
He'd have to force his feelings
all over again.
It's up to you.
I feel bad for Jin Ju.
- Isn't there some way I can repay her?
- Of course there is.
You'll be a fine replacement.
I'm just kidding.
I had a baby.
A son.
Did they move?
Hello.
- Who is that?
- Excuse me?
It's...
Ba Ra's baby.
What brings you here?
- Excuse me?
- Security didn't alert me.
How did you get in here?
Wait, is that my key?
You don't remember giving it to me?
Momo gave it to you?
Who are you?
Are you playing dumb?
The key...
Did you get it from Momo?
Give me the key and leave.
Call security.
Who was that?
(Kim Gwang Cheol)
(Message: Kim Gwang Cheol)
Are you on a trip?
Aren't you worried about your old man?
I had surgery for stomach cancer.
To get away from her father,
Jin Ju used me...
That little...
She swapped bodies with Geum Ba Ra.
(CCTV recording in progress)
Is the owner of this house...
still not out of the hospital yet?
- Who are you?
- She's friends with my daughter.
But you haven't heard?
She passed away a little while ago.
- In a car accident?
- No.
Apparently, something went wrong
with her brain surgery.
I can't believe it either.
Kim Jin Ju.
Stabbing me in the back
until the very end...
(Like father, like daughter...)
Evil can never triumph over good.
Even a single ray of light
can illuminate the darkness.
But no matter how much you try
to shroud the light in darkness,
you can never blot it out.
I'm not sure...
how I'm supposed to address you.
The shelf collapsed,
and a diary accidentally fell open.
The name...
Hyun Ran Hee, Momo's mother,
caught my eye.
Let me get straight to the point.
The long-lost daughter
you've been searching for...
is me,
Geum Ba Ra.
In one of the album photos,
I saw a woman
who I thought looked a lot like me...
and could've been an aunt.
On the off-chance, I found a toothbrush,
a comb, and some hair,
and I sent them for a DNA test.
It came back as a match.
I couldn't believe it,
so I checked again and again.
Seeing the undeniable result,
I burst into tears.
Father.
Dad.
"Dad."
It's something...
I've missed and desperately longed to say.
So please...
don't blame yourself anymore.
I had a baby,
a son.
I ate the sea bream seaweed soup
that you made...
with tears of joy.
And thanks to you,
I've recovered well from childbirth.
I'm so relieved and happy...
to know who my mother...
and father were...
before I leave.
I have no regrets.
Please forgive me...
for leaving without seeing you...
or giving you one last hug.
Please, try to accept this.
Still, we met a few times,
so we'll always have those memories.
Knowing that you're my father,
I'm so happy.
So very happy.
Looking at your paintings,
my heart and my soul...
were filled with tears of love.
I knew exactly what you were feeling
when you painted them,
and it truly moved me.
Because I have always felt the same way.
Momo will explain the rest.
Please consider Momo
as your second daughter.
I respect you as an artist,
and I love you as my father.
How did this happen?
Did you know she was your sister?
Yes.
I heard what happened to the reporter,
Geum Ba Ra.
You see, I actually met her
before my daughter did.
Things like this make you think
there's no deity.
Of all the people to take...
Was it really a cerebral hemorrhage?
Yes.
She seemed perfectly fine.
Then, that girl is gone for good.
Could I get some water?
Who performed the surgery?
Director Shin Ju Shin?
Yes.
They were both in their prime.
It's such a senseless loss.
A part of me wonders if Jin Ju was lonely
and decided to take her along.
He's your one and only grandson.
What's his name?
(Exam Room One,
Neurosurgery Director Shin Ju Shin)
Please, I'm terrified of my dad.
Please...
I want to try...
living as Momo.
Where is Director Shin?
He's not answering his phone.
Your husband is here.
The baby.
Why were both of your phones turned off?
You haven't cleared out Ba Ra's place yet,
have you?
I'll take care of it.
She asked me to.
Even so,
can you clear out her entire place?
You don't have time for that.
I can make time.
Do you have time?
Who is that?
My manager.
Planning a comeback?
No, I just need someone to help me out.
Why are you so down?
I thought deep down
you'd be happy about this.
You never felt this way about her.
Ba Ra's door code.
I'm going to buy the apartment...
and use it as my studio.
It's 1210, star.
Is that the code Ba Ra set?
That's my birthday...
Is there someone in there?
No.
I'm going to do what I have to do.
Yong Joong must be...
the dad.
(Yong Joong)
How did you get in here?
You're supposed to wear a swimsuit
at the pool.
Jin Ju's father came to see me.
She proposed the surgery
just to get away from her father.
I saw a 300,000 dollar transfer
in her account.
Sounds just like Kim Jin Ju.
It's true what they say,
people don't change.
I had no idea.
All this time, I just felt sorry for her.
Looks like you already know who I am,
seeing how you haven't asked.
My daughter gave me your number.
She said you, Director Shin Ju Shin,
with your world-shocking skills,
made her into Momo.
So what did you do with her body?
My daughter's body.
- Jin Ju.
- Please, have a seat.
Answer me.
If you put her brain in Momo's body,
what did you do with her body?
I don't know.
- You don't know?
- I just did the surgery.
My staff handled it.
Who on your staff?
Give me a name.
You threw her away as medical waste,
didn't you?
Where?
I noticed Momo was different again.
Who is it this time?
Aren't you going to answer me?
Is it Reporter Geum Ba Ra?
You swapped their brains again.
Is my daughter, Kim Jin Ju, dead?
For good?
Is she dead?
My daughter!
He's stabbing the Director!
Ba Ra.
Geum Ba Ra.
(Nua General Hospital)
The person you've called is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
(Director Shin Ju Shin)
(Hospital Director, Shin Ju Shin)
- Is the Director...
- He must be sick.
- He's not in yet?
- No.
Hello? This is the 21st floor
of Nua General Hospital.
There's a dead body here!
(Nua General Hospital)
I think it's a patient
we operated on recently.
- And the Director isn't here?
- No, sir.
You...
No.
Nurse Lee! Don't!
Director Shin!
He kept grilling me with questions.
"Did Geum Ba Ra have brain surgery?"
"Did Director Shin perform
the surgery himself?"
What if he wasn't
Kim Jin Ju's biological father,
but Ba Ra's instead?
There's no other reason
he'd snap and kill him like that.
(Our deepest condolences to the family,
The Staff of Nua Funeral Home)
You'll live longer
with a little imperfection.
And I take it you don't, Director Shin?
I guess I'm not long for this world, then.
I didn't see it myself,
but at home...
Border Collies, Jindo dogs,
Chow Chows, Tibetan Mastiffs...
You can have all the dogs you want,
and we can live here, together.
I'm always grateful. I really am.
Then get rid of that feeling,
starting now.
I'm not lacking for anything,
and I'm tired of being thanked.
I don't care for effort
born from obligation.
I'm not forcing myself.
Regardless.
Want me to look for a purebred Retriever?
You transferred 300,000 dollars.
- That's right.
- Were you being blackmailed?
No. Why would I be blackmailed?
He said he didn't know how to go on
after Jin Ju died.
Jin Ju was always really good to me.
I sent it to him
as a sort of severance package.
But 300,000 dollars?
Yes.
He said he couldn't get a job anywhere
because of his record.
We had so many memories together
in this house.
All those meals your mother made
for us here.
You'd hate this house going to another.
I know I would.
Did you meet Ba Ra?
Of course you did.
("Fearless Love")
(Momo)
Hello.
Are you just going to neglect
Yong Joong like that?
Did you know he moved
into Reporter Geum's apartment?
Reporter Geum is gone,
Director Shin is gone...
Now it's just the two of you.
You only have each other now.
Men have a certain kind of pride
that women can't understand...
And women don't? We have our pride too.
Just think of her as his first love.
He's a good guy with a big heart,
so he can't just let her go easily.
Even though you're younger,
be the bigger person and take care of him.
Tell him you want to make things work.
He'll be so grateful,
he'll be the most loyal husband ever.
I guarantee it.
Yong Joong.
Don't let this get you down.
Ba Ra.
(James)
- Hey.
- Where are you? Home?
- No.
- You are not going to believe this.
I'm on my way to your house,
so run there...
at the speed of light.
I wonder if Paul Kim has arrived yet.
(Artist Paul Kim)
Hello, Mr. Ha.
Hello.
Are you still in Germany?
No, I'm back.
When did you get back?
Do I hear a baby crying?
It's my grandson.
Your grandson?
I found my daughter.
But it's a long story.
You were bound to find out anyway.
I'm at Momo's place right now.
You're saying Reporter Geum Ba Ra
was your long-lost daughter?
Yes.
At least she had the baby
before she passed away.
So the baby's mother is Reporter Geum?
Yes.
Is it a boy or a girl?
- It's a boy.
- When was he born?
He's almost three months old.
And who's the father?
I don't know.
Go and have your dinner.
So you didn't know
anything about it either?
What is it?
Goodness.
He's your son, no doubt about it.
He's a carbon copy of you
when you were a baby.
Did he really say Ba Ra had a baby?
Yes.
The situation...
I mean, Reporter Geum and Momo
are half-sisters who share a mother.
I've never seen anything like this.
You don't even need a DNA test.
She must have disappeared
after she found out she was pregnant.
Poor Reporter Geum...
How could she die...
and leave her newborn?
We have to bring him here and raise him.
I know it sounds like a soap opera,
Reporter Geum, Momo...
I told Momo to get back with you
because she seemed different.
Are you going to see for yourself?
Let's go together. We'll take my car.
You've already seen him.
I want to see him again.
They say the world is big and small,
but who would've thought it was Paul Kim?
He spent all that time
desperately searching for his daughter.
Poor Reporter Geum,
and the baby, of course.
This is crazy...
It's not something
that needs to be a secret.
He asked whose baby it was,
and there was no reason to lie.
Right.
You should've seen
how shocked he looked...
after seeing the baby.
I guess he never saw it coming?
I had no idea we would end up
connected like this,
and I've been pretty close
with James Ha this whole time.
I should have introduced myself sooner.
I'm Ha Yong Joong.
- You don't have to...
- Take it.
Sorry to bother you so late.
How about some rooibos tea?
No, I'm fine.
I don't feel like having anything.
Please, have a seat.
Is the baby asleep?
- He's having some formula.
- Eat and sleep, that's all he does.
He's not awake for very long.
He probably won't start crawling
until he's 8 or 9 months old.
So you were close with my daughter too?
Yes.
Hello?
Really?
Thank you.
I'll be home in a bit. Yes.
That was a neighbor,
saying the lights are on at my house.
I was so excited to see my grandson...
that I rushed out, leaving the lights on.
Could you please explain
in a bit more detail?
What exactly happened?
Not now.
Honestly, it still doesn't feel real.
There's this letter,
and the DNA test results.
Is that Reporter Geum's hair?
Yes.
- Couldn't it have been malpractice?
- No.
Director Shin Ju Shin is
a leading authority on brain surgery.
That is true.
I'll be sure to come by
and pay my respects properly soon.
In any case, we're officially family now.
I suppose we are.
I'll set something up for us all
to get together properly.
He's your son, right?
It's not right for him
to be living with his aunt.
We should be the ones raising him.
When Momo finds out everything,
think about Paul Kim...
It's something I have
to face sooner or later.
Before we officially started dating,
I spent one night with Ba Ra.
I didn't know she got pregnant,
and I think she left
because of a misunderstanding.
What misunderstanding?
It's hard to explain.
It's just putting your thoughts
into words.
Is it that hard?
Ba Ra is the one who needs to hear it.
But she's not here, is she?
We met again after 15 years
for an interview.
If I hadn't realized she was the kid
I knew growing up,
we might have started dating.
Or at least, I think so.
I could vaguely sense
a certain longing in her,
but at the same time,
she was so self-assured.
It was refreshing.
Anyway,
the next day,
I had to go on a business trip abroad,
and I was hit with this feeling
that I'd done something terrible.
I kept picturing Ba Ra's face
as a little girl,
and I was so confused.
I couldn't marry her
in that state of mind,
so I asked her for some time.
But I think she must have misunderstood.
"Just another rejection."
She must have thought that.
I guess it's because you're sisters.
It feels just like I'm talking to Ba Ra.
I never noticed it before.
So...
we need to file the divorce papers
as planned.
This isn't right.
I'll raise Bi.
She asked me to take care of him.
He's better with his dad
than with his aunt.
I'm confident I can raise him well.
And let a stepmother raise him?
I'm not getting married again to anyone.
Just like how my brother...
raised me...
I'll make sure he never feels the void
of not having a mother.
I'm confident I can raise him with love.
Please.
Honestly, I wasn't a very good husband.
After his 100-day celebration,
you can take him.
Thank you.
We'll file the papers after that.
I'm going to register him as Geum Bi.
Ha Geum Bi.
- Hello.
- Right. This room...
No, wait, in that room over there, please.
Got it.
Let's see, what else...
Maybe I should've redone the wallpaper.
It's not your fault, Yong Joong.
It was probably from the shock
after his business failed,
but my father also died of
a brain hemorrhage just eight days later.
And I'm sure,
Ba Ra didn't have any resentment.
If anything,
I think she was grateful.
(I'm not sure
how I'm supposed to address you.)
Still, you had it better than I did.
I never got to see her grow up.
Or even hold her hand once.
All I got...
was meeting her a few times
as an artist and a reporter.
Why don't you come live with us?
Whenever you're ready.
I think having his grandfather around...
would be so much better
for Geum Bi emotionally.
- I'll visit often, if it's no trouble.
- Trouble? Of course not.
You're my father-in-law.
I'm curious about
how he and my mother met,
but he won't tell me.
You know, don't you?
I heard you know the whole story.
It's probably hard for him to tell you.
It's not like they ended on good terms.
But that's all in the past now.
They met back in high school.
CEO Hyun was a year older. She was 20.
She dropped out of her freshman year
to have the baby.
At the time, I think Paul's family
suddenly went bankrupt.
Maybe that's why, but I heard
she left the baby and just disappeared.
I don't know for sure,
but he said even her mother
didn't know where she was.
He said she was a newborn,
not even ten days old.
If Reporter Geum were still with us,
you would be sisters again.
It would be a perfect happy ending.
But when I think of...
Yong Joong and Geum Bi
spending their whole lives missing you...
No matter how hard we all try,
no matter how well...
we raise him,
that void left by his mother...
I know what that's like.
The necklace I put on her,
engraved with her name and birthday,
must have broken or fallen off,
and ended up in Kim Gwang Cheol's
daughter's swaddling blanket.
That's how they got switched.
They were both taken to Minjin Church
on the same day.
You could just raise Geum Bi together.
It's not like the whole world knows
our family's private business.
That kind of thing happened
from time to time back in the day.
Ready? Smile!
A bigger smile now. Show me your teeth.
Look at you.
Everyone, let's give Geum Bi a big hand!
One, two!
Great. That looks very natural.
(To my beloved baby,
May you grow up beautiful and healthy)
The chef would like to know
how you're enjoying your meal.
Please tell the chef it is excellent...
- and thank him for the special care.
- I will.
Next time, let's go somewhere more casual
so we can bring Geum Bi.
That's right. So many decent places
don't allow kids these days.
Mr. Kim, I'll get it next time.
Sure.
Now that you're leaving showbiz,
what's next?
I took over the foundation
that runs the Nua Children's Home.
Really?
My goal is to identify the kids' talents
and help them cultivate their strengths.
I can help teach painting.
That would be amazing, thank you.
My dear daughter,
don't you worry about Geum Bi.
Excuse me, our ambassador is a big fan...
and was hoping he could get a picture.
- Of course.
- This is Ms. Momo's husband.
I'm Yong Joong Ha.
It's an honor to meet you.
No, no, the honor is mine.
You've made quite an impression.
Thank you, Your Excellency.
You are the one who is truly impressive.
Let me now introduce
a fashion industry leader.
This is James Ha, CEO of Lim Company.
Was it last year?
I believe we met
at a party at the Egyptian embassy.
Perhaps it was last year.
I think we met at a party
at the Egyptian embassy.
- Did we?
- Goodness.
You both have such
an amazing sense of style.
Both of you have such
a remarkable sense of style.
- Thank you.
- You look stunning.
I'll make sure to stop by sometime.
She says she'll be sure
to stop by sometime.
It would be my honor.
Your Excellency,
you had an interview
with Reporter Ba Ra Geum...
from Sungwoo Daily last year, didn't you?
How did you know that?
Did you read the article?
Yes.
I was so inspired by your interview,
so I saved a copy of it.
I'm flattered.
It's such an honor to meet you here.
Shall we take a picture?
Yes, sure.
On the count of three.
One, two, three.
Big smile.
Great.
Climb up.
One, two,
three, four.
And back, one, two, three, four.
- That's how it's done, all right?
- Yes!
Just keep working hard.
The sky helps those who help themselves.
We just have to give it our all.
- Okay.
All right, let's take it from the top.
She must've secretly studied English.
I was completely surprised.
Anyway, you've got to give her credit.
Her whole demeanor has changed.
She's like a whole new person.
Our little man is awake.
(Yong Joong)
Hello?
I've got the papers ready.
We should probably handle this
through our lawyers, right?
It'll be all over the news anyway.
Let's just go together.
To the courthouse ourselves?
Yes.
All right.
When are you free?
Tomorrow...
Let's file them after lunch.
Okay.
Isn't it hard running the orphanage?
I mean, all you've ever done is act.
Nothing in life is ever easy.
The kids love it, though.
You can see the change in their eyes.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
Are you really not going to act anymore?
Yes.
Your reruns have been on a lot lately.
They never get old.
You're not adding vinegar?
No.
Ba Ra eats hers plain, too.
You two are definitely sisters.
You even have the same taste in food.
When I was pregnant with Geum Bi,
I was craving these cold noodles.
That's why I went to the cafe that day,
just on the off chance.
And I wanted to see you, too.
I really enjoyed the meal that day.
You said if mine were too spicy,
you'd let me have your cold noodles.
(Geumnyeong-ro 42-gil 17)
I love you.
(Thank you for watching
and supporting "Doctor Shin.")
(Doctor Shin)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)