More books?
You really haven't changed, have you?
It's not that many.
No, no, no.
To someone like me who doesn't read,
this is a massive collection.
You know,
Dad used to be a huge reader too, right?
He was obsessed with books and movies.
That brings back memories.
Our old house was the same way.
Didn't we have a ton of stuff?
All those books and VHS tapes.
I wonder where it all went.
I've always been curious
about what kind of books he actually read.
Sakutaro, you were so young back then.
You probably only remember the good parts.
But because of those hobbies of his,
your mother really went through a lot,
even if she acted like it was fine.
After he passed away,
dealing with that mountain of books
and junk was a nightmare of a job.
It wasn't as bad as gambling or drinking,
but was he just naive?
Or maybe he just never grew up.
He just had that...
troublesome side to him.
Still,
to us, he really was a good father.
That's also the truth.
It's just... he had that other side, too.
I see...
I never knew that.
The side of him as a man, as a father.
I knew he'd be here.
I told you so.
What's wrong? What happened?
Tamaki.
Saku-chan!
"Life In Smokey Blue"
(Episode 3: Sprouting)
It's because he was worried about you,
so he's been following you lately.
Because, Saku-chan,
you've looked so exhausted.
You lock yourself in your room at
night working on who knows what.
Sometimes you don't
even come home.
Ah...
Look,
I appreciate the concern, Tamaki.
But I'm not being
mistreated or anything like that.
Huh?
Well, he does work me pretty hard, though.
Hey, now.
So, anything else you want to say,
dear nephew?
Cut it out.
I'm not falling for
your act.
It's good, right?
Ah.
- It's... not even good...
- You don't have to lie.
He might have a nasty personality,
but his cooking is actually amazing.
Well...
It is pretty good.
Right?
- Let me have a bite.
- Hey!
Mmm.
It really is good.
Hey, there's barely any left!
Cheapskate.
You two are really close.
Don't just brush it off like that.
I am Saku-chan's biggest fan.
Saku-chan is incredible. He
was always top of his class.
Since Grandpa passed away so early,
he didn't want to be a burden to Grandma,
so he got a scholarship for college.
Okay, that's enough...
He even studied abroad.
That's why his English is so fluent.
He worked his tail off at
a top firm after graduation.
Even if he's taking a break right now,
Saku-chan, living life on his own terms...
I think he's so cool.
Oh?
Alright, Tamaki.
Shouldn't you be heading to school?
Oh, shoot!
Here.
I made you a lunch.
Ah...
Thanks.
Come back soon, Tamaki!
I will!
You two are scary similar, you know.
Really?
I get that a lot.
Kuji, what about your relatives' kids?
My brother has a kid,
but he's not clingy like that.
Yeah, he's a bit much sometimes.
But honestly, it's a shock.
The way I see myself
versus the way others see me...
The gap is huge.
Why did you quit your job
at the pharma company?
It's simple.
I was just burnt out.
Once I entered the real world,
I realized there's always a bigger fish.
People who have everything are everywhere.
But I
still believed we all
started at the same line.
So I ran as hard as I could.
And the work was actually interesting.
I felt a real sense of accomplishment.
But after about
two or three years,
my numbers started to slip.
Everyone around me was talking about
getting married or changing careers.
And there I was,
not moving forward at all.
I was anxious.
I was struggling.
I felt like I'd hit my limit.
Sakutaro.
That's enough.
It's okay now.
I must have reached my breaking point then.
The scariest part is,
nothing specific even happened.
It was just all the little things piling up
without me even noticing,
until I could barely breathe.
Even I didn't realize what was happening.
I mean, no one can
keep running forever.
Alright.
Time to get back to work.
Wait, already?
Is this just slacking off?
Or is it that "living life
on your own terms" thing?
Stop teasing me.
How should I put it?
I think I get how Tamaki feels.
Huh?
Because I think you're pretty amazing too.
What?
You do?
What's that supposed to mean?
Man, that was good.
Nothing beats a reward lunch.
You need this after finishing a big job.
Yeah.
Even when you're done,
you're still surrounded
by books, Shizuka-chan.
Mind your own business.
Oh.
Emma's Big Adventure.
This takes me back.
I used to read this when I was a kid.
The illustrations are so beautiful.
I know, right?
It's kind of strange, isn't it?
We grew up in completely different places,
yet we grew up reading the same book.
I guess so.
Ah.
That reminds me.
Do you know a book called
"Rex's Big Adventure"?
I've read most of the famous ones,
but that doesn't ring a bell.
I see.
My dad used to read it to me all the time.
I'd love to read it again someday.
That sounds nice.
(Incoming Call: Sister)
What now...?
Hello?
Wait, what?
Mom did...?
Sorry to make you come all this way.
How's the injury?
It's just a sprain.
I see...
When I heard you fell
and went to the hospital,
I thought it was much worse.
As long as I take it easy for a while,
I'll be fine.
That's a relief.
But still,
how did you manage to fall at home?
I decided to do some decluttering,
and I guess I got a
little too carried away.
Did someone come with you?
Ah...
Yeah.
Hey.
Kuji.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kuji Shizuka.
He's a former colleague.
I'm... working for him right now.
Oh, my.
Thank you for looking after Sakutaro.
- Sorry for all the trouble.
- Not at all.
Oh, let me go make some tea.
Ow, ow, ow...
Oh, please don't bother.
Just stay put and rest for a bit.
How is she?
She's asleep.
Why are you smoking out here?
I didn't think I should smoke inside.
Look at you, being all respectful.
Give me one.
I'm going to stay the night.
I see.
I always thought she'd
stay full of energy forever.
But I guess everyone gets old.
Yeah.
Like not noticing a smudge on a cup,
or thinking she's as
agile as she used to be.
She just pushed herself too hard.
But you know,
I've only been thinking about
myself these past few years.
I really need to do better.
The kitchen light...
It's a bit dim. I'll change it tomorrow.
Mhm.
But tomorrow...
The entryway too.
We should put in some
motion lights for her.
And handrails in the stairs and bathroom.
Kuji.
Yeah?
Wanna kiss?
Where the hell did that come from?
Oh, come on. Why not?
No, I'm good.
It's not like you hate me.
What?
Huh?
Am I wrong?
I'm going home.
What was that all about?
Nothing.
Hey.
Are there any spare batteries?
Oh, I think they're in that cabinet...
Whoa.
My old report cards and photo albums.
Man, I was short.
Once you start looking at this stuff,
the cleaning never gets done.
Ah...
Hmm?
The Little Warrior...?
This cover...
This is it. "Rex's Big Adventure."
This is definitely the book.
Even if the title is different
from what I remember.
The main character's name is...
Alexander.
So that's why you called him Rex.
I see.
Back then, Dad...
He was translating it as he read it to me.
Rex loved pancakes, just like I did.
I was so happy about that.
I even begged Mom to
make me "Rex's pancakes."
It should be in here somewhere...
Wait.
Rex's favorite food...
It's actually meringue.
I guess meringue wasn't really
a common thing when we were kids.
So he changed it
just to make it easier
for a kid to understand?
It's more like
he translated it specifically for you.
Yeah...
My dad back then and me right now...
We're chasing the same words.
Through language,
I feel like we're finally connected.
Everyone has many different sides to them.
That's only natural.
But still,
to me, my father is...
Are you taking this whole box back?
No.
I'm only staying with you temporarily.
Just this is enough.
I don't need everything.
As long as I have the important things.
I suppose so.
Thank you so much for everything.
Don't mention it. Please take care.
Thank you.
Alright, it'll be bad if you fall again.
Go on back inside.
I'm fine.
You two should get
going before it gets dark.
Um, Sakutaro.
You...
Yeah?
You're busy too, right?
Don't push yourself too hard.
I won't.
I'll be back soon.
Let's go.
Yeah.
That look on her face... like
she wanted to say something
but then decided to hold it back.
I've seen it a thousand times.
Huh?
What a pain.
Want a drink?
What's with you?
Nothing.
Kuji.
Do you still do any literary translation?
Every now and then.
But those jobs are rare.
Why?
Are you interested?
Yeah.
Translation...
I think it might be interesting.
I took a translation class back in college.
There was this upperclassman
who'd studied abroad.
He told me I had a real talent for it.
I just suddenly remembered that.
Talent, huh?
Oh?
What was that?
Was it a monster?
Was it Shippy from Lake Shibire?
Definitely not.
Are you sure?
Ever since I ran into Kuji again,
I feel like my life has
started moving again.
No.
Time was always passing.
That's why I was so anxious.
I felt like I was being crushed.
If anything,
what's actually moving now is...
Sorry.
I should have just
dropped you off at home.
It's fine.
I'll walk you back.
Tonight...
I don't want to go home.
Then find somewhere else to stay.
Do you hate it?
I don't hate it...
(Next Episode)
Are you okay?
I've always felt inferior
to my brother in Kyushu.
This house is as dark
and gloomy as ever.
Thanks.
Back then,
and just the other day...
You really do like me, don't you?