You're so drunk.
They only poured mine.
P'Son.
P'Son, you drink too?
When did you get here?
What Son? I'm Thanu, dumb-ass.
Who's Son?
P'Son...
Jwin, what the hell?
You're drunk like a dog.
Thanu!
What the hell did you
let him drink so much for?
This is P'Son.
That's also P'Son?
There are two Sons…?
What the hell are you doing?
Go home.
Whoa.
Let's go home, P'Son...
Why are you even taking care of me?
Now you're mad again.
You always get mad and yell at me.
Old man always nagging.
Take that!
I don't even know what to say to you, Jun.
Wherever they invite you, you just go.
Not even one call to me.
I drove around looking everywhere for you.
Look at you now.
Drunk like a dog.
You little shit.
Go take a shower.
Take your shirt off.
Aha.
You're doing this because
you care about me, right?
Yeah, if I didn't care, would I waste
all this time yelling at you, you brat?
You like scolding me.
I scold you because you're stubborn.
If something had happened to you, I wouldn't
even know where to return someone like you.
You little menace...
There's no one else like you.
Even if you like yelling at me.
I still like you.
Let me ask you something.
Hmm...
You said you like me more than before.
Do you mean like more
than you like Tai or Champ?
Hmph.
This time I mean it.
It's not just more than
before—I really like you.
I told you I like you.
Say something back.
Come on, P'Son, please.
I said I like you, so
you have to say it back.
Please, I want to hear it. Please, P'Son.
You're way too drunk, Jun.
Go shower and get to bed.
I really like you.
Thanks...
You're such an idiot.
Look at you now.
Acting tough—drank too
much and now you're hungover.
My head is killing me.
If you're gonna puke, hurry up.
My mom's waiting to give alms.
Ughhh… can you stop nagging? I've got a
headache and I'm still processing the guilt.
May you be blessed.
♪ Reciting Buddhist chant ♪
Amen.
You holding up okay, Jun?
I'm fine, Mom.
Thanu! Always dragging
him off into trouble.
There's some lime in the fridge, okay?
I'll make you some lime
juice. Come on, let's go.
You can take him inside
first, Mom. I'll clean up.
Come on, sweetie.
Oh hey, Son.
When did you get back?
Yesterday.
I heard your mom bought all
of Aunt Noi's land? Is that true?
Oh, I didn't know. My mom
and Thanu handled everything.
Heh...
Hey Son, if you're free
today, stop by the house.
Mali keeps saying she misses you.
Yeah… if I'm free, I'll drop by.
Anyway, let me head inside first.
Don't forget to come by. I'll head off now.
Next time, go get yourself
drunk like a damn dog again.
Wow, that mouth of yours.
You actually look like a person now that you've
showered. You were a total mess this morning.
P'Son!
You're yelling at me now?
Must mean the hangover's gone.
Good, now I don't have to worry.
Wow, Mom! You're so hardworking.
If my house had space like
this, I'd help Son plant trees too.
It's really simple, son. Just water them
and make sure weeds don't take over.
Otherwise the soil gets poor.
She saw this space was
free, so she cleared it for me.
That's so nice, Mom.
Can I try planting something?
Of course, go ahead!
Thank you.
Just three or four months,
and it turns out this pretty.
It's beautiful, Mom.
What are you smiling at?
You… you done working out?
Yeah, I'm done.
Looks like your boy gets
along with our mom pretty well.
Jun good with people.
The only one he's not close to… is me.
Are you sulking because of the kid?
Maybe it's because you don't like
kids—that's why he keeps his distance.
But they seem pretty close to me.
Why else would he come back home with you?
He just likes going places.
He likes going places...
or maybe he likes ♪you♪?
What the hell are you talking about?
I'm done with this nonsense.
Come eat, Jun. You too, Mom.
Come on, sweetie. We're almost done.
Mom, where do I turn off the water?
Over there, sweetie. Turn it off.
Oh Son.
If you're free today, let's go visit Aunt
Mai. She's always asking about you.
Sure.
You coming with me?
Where are you going?
I've got some errands in town.
Then I'll stop by to see some relatives. Want
to tag along? Staying here's boring anyway.
Oh right, you're going to talk about
the road access to the orchard?
Yeah, I'm going to talk to Uncle
Nui about fencing the new plot.
You have to come along too, Mom.
Then let's drop Mom at the temple first. I haven't been to the
Kathin festival this year. I want to see how far they've come.
I think I'll skip this one, bro.
You're gonna stay home alone?
Hey, he's not alone. I'm here too.
Next thing you know, you'll be
throwing another drinking party.
No way. If we drink again,
I'll be knocked out for sure.
Man, why do you worry so much?
I'll be back.
You sure you don't wanna come?
Nah, I've got a photo
shoot planned with Thanu.
Let me kiss you.
No way.
Someone might see.
What are you scared of? Thanu's
not here, and Mom's in her room.
Come on.
Thanu!
Where's Son?
I don't know.
Mom, should we go now?
Yeah, let's go, son.
Dear, Uncle Nui and Madam Kasorn are waiting.
Let's get this sorted once and for all.
You stay home and look after him, alright?
Yes, Mom.
Psst, hey!
Where's Jun?
He's around here somewhere.
Don't bother taking him out.
I've been wondering
something—does Jun have a boyfriend?
Ever since he got here, I haven't
seen him on the phone with anyone.
He doesn't. Why?
Nothing, just... if he's single,
maybe I'll shoot my shot.
You don't even like guys.
Yeah, but… he is kinda cute.
Thanu!
Son, let's go now. Don't be late.
What's wrong? Are you not feeling well?
Just a bit under the weather.
Hmm… you've got a fever.
Have you eaten or taken any medicine?
Then rest up. I'll take care of you.
Hey Praew, what are you doing here?
P'Tai, I'm leaving Namrin
with you for a sec, I'll be back.
Leaving her?
Yeah yeah, just a minute!
Hey, where are you going? Praew!
Who's this kid? Yours?
Nah, I just ran into Praew. She left the kid
with me and rushed off. No idea what's going on.
What's your name, sweetie?
Namrin.
You came with Auntie Praew?
Yes.
Whew. Thanks, P'Tai. Oh! Hi there, Win.
Whoa, slow down. Breathe. What happened?
I brought Namrin, Mod's kid from accounting, out to eat—but
I forgot my wallet in the car. So lucky I ran into you.
And you didn't cause any trouble
with Uncle Tai and Uncle Win, right?
Nope.
Good girl.
She wasn't naughty… just heavy.
Hey.
Still not used to being
called “uncle,” man.
Seeing this… kinda makes
me wanna have a kid too.
It's cute and all, but being
called “uncle” still hits weird.
Let's go grab some ice cream, bro.
So, how is it? Pretty?
So damn pretty.
I never thought a place like
this existed near your home.
Gorgeous, right?
Super gorgeous.
There's a photo spot over there.
Lots of people come here for pics.
Can you take some for me?
Of course! No problem.
Thanks!
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Try standing here.
Here?
Yeah, right there.
P'Son's calling.
Don't pick up. He's just gonna
nag you for not being home.
Alright, camera's ready. Let's go.
Shall we take the shot?
Ugh!
Come here.
Why the hell do you keep calling?
Dude, let me talk to Jun.
He's not here.
Hurry up.
That's it. I'm busy.
Thanks, man. Really.
How can you let him
boss you around like that?
You don't have to answer every call.
Take some time for yourself.
Like right now—I'm taking your
photos. Let's fill up that memory card.
Alright. 1, 2, 3, snap!
Got it here, bro.
Okay, let's try—1, 2, boom!
Did it turn out okay?
Let me see—did you get it?
Huh? That's all?
Pretty cool, right?
That's perfect.
I'm posting this on
IG—bet it'll get tons of likes.
Hey, if I blow up, I'm hiring you as
my personal photographer. Deal?
Whoa!
If it pays more than my garden gig, I'm in.
Wait, your garden gig pays that much?
Nah, it's not expensive—just
a hundred grand a month.
A hundred grand?!
You're exaggerating!
What? I'm just telling the truth.
Go home and ask your
mom how much she pays me.
Maybe I should ask your
mom for a job instead.
Huh?
Can I, please?
What? Not hiring me anymore?
Can you hire me instead?
What, you're not gonna hire me now?
Hey, what's up, Win?
You ditched me, asshole. Who took that pic? P'Son?
Nah, no way—your skills are way better than his.
(Laughs)
Who's laughing? Is that P'Son? P'Son!
Hey, that's not P'Son… it's P'Nu.
He's P'Son's younger brother.
Oh, P'Nu! You've met already,
right? Say hi for me—tell him I miss him.
Tell him yourself!
P'Nu.
Win wants to talk.
What's up, Win?
P'Thanu, I miss you.
Yeah, miss you too. Come
visit sometime, alright?
Sure thing. See you soon.
Yup, see ya.
Hey Win, next time you come,
you've gotta take pics with me, alright?
The view here is insanely gorgeous.
I'm thinking of posting the pics
on IG—make sure to like them!
Yeah right—just don't sneak
off with P'Son alone again.
It's not like that! I didn't come with
P'Son. P'Nu brought me out here.
So where are you now?
Just finished watching
a movie. I'm with P'Tai.
Hia Tai?
Hey, tell Hia Tai he
owes me a treat next time!
Wow, sneaking off with P'Son and didn't
even tell us—now you're begging for food?
It was last-minute,
bro. I didn't tell anyone.
Just don't fight with Son, okay?
When you're back, I'll treat you.
For real? Aww thanks, you're the best.
See, Win? I told you
he's always sweet to me.
Hey Win, I gotta go. I want more pictures.
Yeah yeah, you friend-ditcher.
I'm out.
Huh? What's wrong?
I don't know, but I'm so itchy.
Shit. You're probably
allergic to the grass!
Hurry home and take a shower.
Nu! What the hell did you take
him through? He's red all over!
We were shooting in
a field—it was beautiful!
What happened to him? Why's he all red?
It's Nu's fault—he took me through that grass. Idiot
move, both for going and for dragging me along.
Hey hey! Don't panic! It's
just grass, not like he got shot!
Still, you're the one who
got him into this mess.
Wasn't there literally
anywhere else to take pictures?
Alright, enough! Go take him to shower!
Come on, sweetie, time to wash up. Go go go.
Go on—look what you caused.
Told you it'd end in disaster.
Move it!
What?
Take off your shirt.
Why the hell go to a place
like that? It's just grass!
P'Sorn.
What?
If you had a wife, would
you still nag this much?
Just take it off.
Get up here.
Why?
I'm checking your rash.
Get up.
What are you looking down at?
What's yours?
P'Sorn.
You done yet?
I wanna shower.
Please continue a little longer.
Hey Jun!
Yeah?
You finished showering?
All done, bro.
And
why did you change clothes?
None of your business.
Hey Jun, there's a fair tonight.
Wanna go walk around with me?
Tonight? Yeah, let's go!
I don't approve.
Sorn, you brought him here—don't coop him up
inside. Let him go have some fun, alright sweetie?
But eat first, okay? Eat up.
What's this called, Mom?
That's called “Nam Chup Kuey,” sweetie.
“Kuey” means shrimp paste, right?
That's right.
Whoa, smart kid!
I know, I know!
You eat it with fresh veggies.
Ohh.
I don't eat veggies.
I heard P'Sorn loves vegetables.
He does.
That one's cucumber.
I thought you already left.
How could I leave? I
stayed to check on you.
Thank you.
Don't mention it. I'm happy to.
Do you...
Have someone new in your heart?
How could I? It's always been you.
So? Let me see how you're feeling.
Still feel warm?
Feeling better.
Are you hungry?
Want some?
Sure, why not.
- This is delicious.
- See? I told you!
Tastes good, right?
Whoa, bro.
I want that one.
That one? The stuffed toy?
It's cute!
Give it a shot. Let's win it for you.
Thanks!
You sure you know how to shoot?
Please, I'm a pro.
Just watch and learn.
Show me then.
First try.
First try... just practicing.
This is hard, man.
Okay, I bet there's more fun
inside. Wanna give it a go?
Your a rhino!
Chill, bro. How much money
did I spend to get this big rhino?
Didn't spend a dime. I
fought the store owner for it.
Just kidding, relax.
It's not even that hard.
Took me just a few shots.
I can even shoot with my feet.
Wow!
P'Sorn!!!
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Just tired.
Hey, Jun.
Hmm?
Want me to get you another plushie?
Oh no, one's enough. I don't even
know how I'm getting this one home.
I'll have Thanou ship it to you.
No need, really. Just leave
it here. Don't bother Nu.
It's yours. Should stay with
you, right? Just take it home.
Mali's my ex-girlfriend.
We dated in high school.
And you're telling me this because...?
Thought you'd wanna know.
I'm gonna go shower.
Wait!
I'll shower with you. Save time.
What? No way.
But I wanna. What are you
gonna do? It's my house.
Oh!
Why'd you bite my neck?!
It's gonna leave a mark.
If you really wanna shower,
just go first. I'll wait here.
Fine, fine. I won't tease
anymore. Go already.
Hello?
Where's Jun? Can I talk to him?
He's showering. Why do you keep calling?
Uh, just tell him to call
me back when he's done.
Yeah, yeah. I'll tell him.
What's with you? You were
following that kid around earlier.
What the hell are you even
saying? I'm not hearing this.
You fought with Jun, didn't you?
I didn't. He's just so damn stubborn.
Stubborn how? He listened to me
just fine today. Bit cheeky though.
Seriously, what's up with you and Jun?
You wanna be with him
or just toying around?
What the hell, man. Just get back to work.
You're obviously jealous. Why
don't you just date him already?
I'm not jealous.
You know I don't like younger guys.
Not liking kids, sure. But not liking Jun?
I've never seen you not like him.
What are you trying to say?
Don't play dumb, Sorn. You
know exactly what I mean.
You're acting like this and want me
to believe you're just senior-junior?
Siblings don't kiss, bro.
You saw that?!
I don't wanna like Jun.
Why not?
He's still a kid.
Are you nuts?! He's in his fourth
year. He's not a kid anymore.
He's younger than us. Have you ever
seen me date someone younger before?
Because of Mali, right?
Mali.
I don't think it's right for
us to be alone like this.
It's fine. I just wanna spend some time with
you, just the two of us. No interruptions.
Mali, what if someone sees us?
It's really okay.
Are you sure, Mali?
Of course.
Hey! What's going on here?!
Dad! Help me! Sorn
tricked me into coming here!
Dad, I didn't...
You bastard, Sorn!
Dad, wait, please don't get the wrong
idea. Mali, tell him—I didn't do anything!
Yeah.
Sorn, Jun's not Mali. That was
ages ago. You still haven't moved on?
Don't you remember? I almost went to jail
that day. Lucky Uncle Kamnan cleared it up.
Of course I remember. Our parents had
to apologize even when you weren't wrong.
If I have to fall in love
with someone younger.
That person can't be Jun.
Since you came back from the South, you've
been avoiding me. What's wrong with you?
If P'Sorn tells you that he likes
you, will you go out with him?
How many times have you had sex? When you did
it, did you think he was my younger brother?
From today on, you and I won't get involved with
each other anymore—no matter what it's about!
And you can stop meddling in my life too.