(Previously)
Congrats on leaking the news.
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
But this crap can't hurt me.
You do like to brag.
You told your mom
you got the lead role in the play.
I never told my mom I had the lead.
I know I'm just a supporting character.
No matter what I do,
my mom will never be proud of me.
Hey.
I've pulled every kind of
stubborn stunt with my family.
If you insist on saying no,
what can anyone do to you?
Do you still love me?
You got your answer?
How long have you and Tua been close?
You two don't look like you're friends.
Looks like something else.
Stop making Tua uncomfortable.
He doesn't like you.
If you've got something better to offer me,
I might change my mind.
Leave Tua alone.
(Episode 5: Super Objective)
I'll get going then.
Hold on.
Can we talk inside for a bit?
Are you still drunk?
I sobered up before we left the studio.
So…
You agreed to model for Boston
because… you didn't want
him messing with me?
Mm.
That's all?
I just don't like people
treating you badly.
And you kissed me
because you didn't want
Boston messing with me too?
Well…
I…
Do you remember that night?
At the party, when we kissed.
I lied to you.
I wasn't just teasing you
or helping you rehearse for the play.
I wanted to know how you felt about me.
Tua.
I can't give you an answer
because I don't know
what this feeling for you is.
But I like you, Arnold.
Now that you know,
do you hate me?
Take time to figure out
how you feel about me.
"Only Friends : Dream On"
I LEFT. YOU WERE SLEEPING PEACEFULLY.
DIDN'T WANNA WAKE YOU.
Mm… interesting project.
Hey, is that Arnold?
I see him on TikTok a lot.
It's adorable when he dances.
He has quite a following.
That's true.
Hey!
Isn't that Little Raffy, Ranchalee's son?
You know them?
Mhm. She's my
all-time favorite leading actress.
I just saw him on a show
with his mom the other day.
It was so lovely.
There are a bunch of
talented people in this project.
Mm. Interesting.
Celebrities like them
can be a magnet for sponsors.
Actors.
Jack.
I hope you'll support
the university production, Ms. Yui.
If you have any concerns,
please let me know.
Mm.
Why not give the lead role
to a famous actress's son?
He's very well-known, I think
you could attract plenty of sponsors.
We have our own process.
Every actor has to go through auditions.
The actors we selected
are the most suitable for their roles.
A good performance with no audience…
I don't see why I should fund it.
Why not make Little Raffy the lead? Hm?
If someone with a large following
and that level of fame takes the role,
the project would be worth sponsoring.
I don't agree.
If that's how she sees it,
we should find another sponsor.
Jack, I've been looking for a while.
I'm sure there are other people
who might be interested.
Look. This is the last company
showing interest in our play.
We still have time.
Jack, we don't have much time.
If you turn her down and rely on funds
from the Fine Arts Fair alone,
we won't get much.
I know it's difficult,
and I don't want this to happen either.
But as the producer, if giving in benefits
the project, we should consider it.
But that's not fair to our actors.
What do you expect me to tell Dean?
You'll have to find a way to talk to him.
Little Raf has always
been confident in front of people.
I had him take acting, singing,
and music classes when he was little.
What about you, Little Raf?
Are you planning to
follow in your mom's footsteps…
So, you've been helping Jack
with his stage play?
His mom told me.
I'm helping with the sound.
Shouldn't you be focusing on your DJ work?
I am.
Then why are you helping someone else?
I'm not doing this for someone else.
I'm doing it for myself.
Can you not put pressure on me?
I'm not. But look at Jack.
Whatever he does, he gives it his all.
Just don't disappoint me.
Hey. What's up?
How did the meeting with the sponsor go?
Did they give us 200K?
Hm?
Why are you practicing alone?
You know I'm not
very good with action scenes.
So I'm practicing to get used to them.
Besides, I want your dream play
to turn out perfect.
I told you I'd be the new Dean for you.
Dean.
Hm?
I've got something important to tell you.
Timmy and I spoke to the sponsor.
They want lead actors
with a large following,
so they suggested…
Raffy
for the lead.
The same role as you.
And?
You agreed?
No, I didn't.
But without sponsors,
the play won't happen.
So I was thinking you and Raffy
could alternate performances.
What are you even talking about?
I've always been the lead.
How is that any different from making me
his substitute or understudy, Jack?
I'm not cutting down your role.
I'm suggesting a double cast.
You used to say
the acting was what mattered most.
So how did you let the sponsor
push you into this, Jack?
What the hell are you thinking?
I don't want it to be like this either.
Damn it!
Dean, calm down.
I don't want to calm down!
Tell me this.
What the hell does he have over me
besides a famous mother?
How privileged. Being
the son of an actress.
Do talented people really have to step aside
just because someone has more followers?
I hope the decision I
made was the right one.
What?
I think you look quite good in person.
They dressed you ridiculously on TV.
You look much better in normal clothes.
What the heck are you talking about?
The Spotlight Tonight.
I watched it live.
Sharp features,
broad shoulders, nice skin…
But I think the camera
didn't do you justice.
You're way cuter in person.
Don't get so close.
People might get the wrong idea.
Where are you going,
soon-to-be rising star?
The casting was done fair and square.
So why the hell are
you taking my lead role?
Huh?
No matter the era, a nepo baby like you
always gets the privilege.
Go ahead and play the role well
and live up to your follower count.
What the fuck are you talking about?
About you stealing my role.
What role?
My Romeo role.
You don't know that? Huh?
Huh?
Don't fucking play dumb.
Stop. Knock it off.
When did I ever do that?
That's enough. Stop!
I'm not stopping!
Dean! I said that's enough!
No!
Listen to me!
Dean's making a scene,
saying I stole his role.
Raffy, I was about to tell you.
From now on, we'll do a double cast.
You'll share the role with Dean.
Hi, Tua.
I got you a burger.
I figured you might not have eaten yet.
Thank you.
So… you said you didn't know before.
Have you figured it out now?
Huh?
Figured what out?
About… our status.
Ah.
Um…
To be honest, I still
can't give you an answer.
Would that bother you?
No.
I just want to know where I stand.
If we're in a situationship,
I'm fine with that.
But if you ever have a clear answer,
let me know.
Just don't let it turn
into a situation-shit.
Thank you, Tua.
If you're really okay with it,
we can just keep things like this for now.
Oh.
Hey, Tua.
Tua.
Wait.
Don't eat that.
Here. Eat with me.
Look at you.
Without me, how are you going to survive?
I'll survive.
Of course I will.
I can't make up my mind.
I'm afraid if I cross the line
and it doesn't work out,
things will get awkward between us.
What we have now is good.
But if we were more, it'd be clearer.
Dean, can you just hear me out?
If this were only my play,
I would never let this happen.
But it's not.
Given my position and my duties,
I have to look at the bigger picture.
So what? Hm?
Couldn't you have done better?
Couldn't you negotiate with them at all?
Huh?
I tried everything.
The play could've been canceled.
We might not get to perform even once.
Dean.
No matter what happens,
you're still my number one actor.
Okay.
I get it now.
Mm.
So, what matters
is the number of followers, right?
Fine.
I'll get that for you.
Just watch me.
May I join you?
About the double cast, I'm sorry.
To be honest, I don't like
getting the role under those conditions.
But I understand the sponsor's position.
Followers matter these days.
And I understand you too.
It's the sponsor's request, right?
Right.
Raffy.
You still want to help me, don't you?
Mhm.
Thank you so much.
Did you plan all that?
What are you on about now?
What did I do?
The opportunity came to me on its own.
Are you sure it came to you on its own?
Or did you steal it from someone else?
Believe whatever you want.
But let me tell you something.
When I get an opportunity,
whether it's acting or Jack,
I'll never let it pass me by.
Even though you didn't
earn that opportunity with your skills?
Skills can be learned.
You believe that too, don't you?
You practice DJing every day.
Don't compare someone like yourself to me.
I know what my goal is.
But you…
You don't even know what you're doing.
Of course I do.
In the end, he's willing
to do anything to be with Jack.
Honestly, I'm so damn disappointed in him.
The opportunity is right here.
I won't let it slip away.
Shit.
Fan-service content
can get them this many followers?
Tua!
What's up?
Hey.
I think I'm going to start
making content with Arnold.
Content?
What content?
Have you gone crazy
because of the faculty play?
I'm not crazy. I'm just being realistic.
Play or no play,
I don't have many followers anyway.
So, why Arnold?
Because I have to act with him.
If we create some buzz,
people will pay attention.
Fan-service content?
Like you two are dating?
Exactly. Something like that.
So I came to…
ask for your permission.
Can I borrow Arnold?
Sure.
Oh my gosh, Tua!
Thank you so much, Tua.
Yeah, yeah, okay. That's enough.
By the way, how's it going
between you and Arnold?
Well… it's going.
By "going," do you mean
you two already slept together?
We did.
Holy shit. Seriously?
Gosh, Tua!
Stop teasing me.
So you guys are… boyfriends now?
I don't know, man.
Our status isn't clear.
We're just seeing how things go.
Well, whatever. At least there's progress.
So… how was it?
Good?
Don't ask.
Was it good?
Stop. I'm not telling you.
Just go to sleep. Go!
You'll pay for that.
Tomorrow I'm asking again
whether it was good or not.
FINE ARTS FAIR
Everything is 150 baht.
GET YOUR PORTRAIT OR CARICATURE
Hands in your pockets
and walk straight over!
You can purchase our products and help
fund our production of Romeo &amp; Romeo.
Or if you want to grab
one of our T-shirts, you can too.
That's right!
If you're interested, come on over.
Here comes our first patron.
Please, welcome. Thank you.
Here you go.
Thank you so much.
Please scan here.
All done.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
Was that our senior?
I'm not sure.
I didn't know you were
this good at drawing.
I used to practice by
doing this kind of work.
But I haven't drawn in
a while. I'm a bit rusty.
Such a humble man.
Draw me sometime, okay?
You want it too?
Arnold. Are you free?
Right now?
I don't have any customers. Yeah, I'm free.
Would you like to
make some content with me?
Huh?
What kind of content?
We're going to be acting together, right?
So, how about we do some promotion?
Maybe we can sell out the tickets.
Hey, why don't you try it?
Everyone's doing it.
Just tell me what you want me to do.
I'll film it for you.
How about we capture a moment of us
checking out the booths together?
That sounds good. What do you say?
I'm fine with anything.
What do I need to do?
Just follow my lead. I'll take charge.
Hi, guys. We're here at the Fine Arts Fair.
If you enjoy a drink,
you can't miss this booth.
They've got whiskey, beer,
and most importantly, cocktail buckets.
Cool!
And today, we ordered a bucket to try.
Let's give it a taste.
Tua, wait a second.
Hey, we will drink it at the same time.
You'll look into my eyes.
Ah, sure.
Count us down.
One, two, three.
Right now, we're at the accessories booth.
I'm picking a necklace for Arnold.
Hey, I'm going to pick
out a necklace for you.
When I put it on you, look into my eyes.
Let's make it a cute moment.
Then you pick one for me
and put it on me too.
Again, make it sweet.
And now I'm choosing a necklace for Arnold.
Which one should it be?
Maybe this one.
Wow!
Hey, nice taste.
A cool necklace for a cool guy.
Nice.
Hey, guys. Look!
Do I look good?
Very good.
Let me pick one for you now.
Okay.
Let's go with this one.
Let me see.
Let's try it on.
What are they doing?
Why are they being so touchy?
Because the sponsor pushed this.
So Dean's responding.
Aw!
Oh, my gosh.
So?
Do you like it?
Very much.
I can see that.
But does he really have to go this far?
There are plenty of other ways.
One bottle of this.
What's up with you and Dean?
That's none of your business, is it?
Right. It's not.
But if you two are getting back together,
don't lead Raffy on.
If you don't like him,
don't get his hopes up.
Why?
Do you like Raffy?
Now that's my business.
I think that's something you
should talk to Raffy about, not me.
Let me give you a warning.
Make a decision and pick who you want.
Stop breadcrumbing.
It doesn't make you look cool.
Why are you drinking here alone?
I'm a little down, so I
need something to help.
Something to help?
I can be your drinking
buddy. Maybe it'll lift your mood.
Can you really help?
I sure can.
I don't mind.
If he can lift my mood, I'm fine with it.
Come take a look first.
You collect tote bags from museums?
I see you have one from MoMA.
Yeah.
I just went to New York with my
family at the beginning of the year.
Seriously?
I was there at the
beginning of the year too.
I could've been your tour guide.
What a shame.
Sightseeing with you could be fun.
You like it?
I did. New York was fun.
I meant me.
Do you like me?
After we're done here, let
me give you a ride home.
You don't have to.
Don't you still have to film
content with Dean later?
Aren't you tired?
I'm not.
Dean's pretty funny, though.
He enjoys talking.
Is he trying to become a celebrity lately?
Something like that.
Mm.
Are you okay with it?
If you're not comfortable or
don't want to film, just tell me.
I'll talk to Dean.
It's not that I'm not
okay with it. I can do it.
Besides, if our video goes viral,
it'll help sell tickets for the play.
Have a bite.
I'm not jealous of him being with Dean.
But seeing them together feels… weird.
Do you get what I mean?
I see you're done packing up.
Should we head out?
So…
Head out where?
What about my studio?
Rome!
What the fuck?!
Huh?
You fucker!
Rome, stop it!
Rome, what the hell are you doing?
No. What the hell are you doing?
You said you liked Jack.
And now you're kissing his friend?
Who I kiss is none of your business.
You don't get to interfere.
Don't forget, we're nothing to each other.
I'm your friend.
Friend?
We're just sex buddies.
Why the fuck are you so nosy?
Ah!
You two hooked up, and
now you're catching feelings.
Okay.
If you're that desperate to act cheap,
then go hook up with this bastard.
All right, everyone!
And the highlight of
our dunk tank tonight is…
is…
Let's welcome Romeo &amp; Romeo!
Whoo-hoo!
Aw! That's Romeo &amp; Romeo!
Prepare to get the hashtag
#ArnoldDean trending, everyone!
ArnoldDean!
Why don't you change
in the restroom properly?
Like you've never seen it before.
Why?
Afraid you won't be
able to control yourself?
This content you're making with
Arnold… I think you should stop.
It's not helping.
All that intimacy is pointless.
Are you saying this as Jack the director,
or Jack the guy who's
still possessive over his ex?
I'm saying it because of the work.
Besides, doesn't Tua like Arnold?
How do you think he
feels watching you do this?
I talked to him.
He gave me the green light.
What about you, Jack?
How do you feel?
See, Jack?
In the end, you still can't separate
work from personal feelings.
Just this little bit of content is
enough to get you worked up.
What did I tell you, Jack?
I said I'd get those followers for you.
So, this is me.
The new Dean.
(Next Episode)
Cut!
As the director,
tell us how to kiss to
make the audience feel it.
Is the director going to have me killed?
No.
That's how friends are.
You can't completely cut ties.
This is what it's like going
from friends to lovers.
It'll never work out.
You're staring. Do you like him?
Pete.
Happy birthday.
It's nice.
Seeing you jealous.