What...
Hold on, Tuo.
Can you hold back?
How did watching a movie
to learn about chasing girls
somehow turn into doing this with Tuo?
[Episode 1: Over the Line,
Just to Get Closer to You]
[Secret Lover]
Lin Xiaoyang,
wait for me!
Lin Xiaoyang!
Wait up.
Lu Junxi,
run faster.
Who are you?
Who is he?
Is he the new kid who moved in next door?
Yeah.
Come on,
let's play together.
Let's go on the swings.
From that moment on,
he became my best friend
and also the rival I could never beat.
Which one of you wants to play the groom?
Oh, you're the bride?
I thought you were playing the ghost.
So, which one of you is going to marry me?
Me!
Let's settle it with rock-paper-scissors.
Fine,
rock-paper-scissors it is.
I'm definitely gonna win!
-Rock,
-paper,
-scissors!
Let's go.
From that day on,
Tuo and I developed a habit of
settling undecided matters
with rock-paper-scissors.
It also sealed my fate
as an eternal flower boy.
Hello, wifey.
Hello, hubby.
I wanna be the groom!
Don't play games while walking.
I wanna drink more.
Tuo!
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
-Rock,
-paper,
-scissors.
Wait.
I wanna drink more.
I'm not playing games anymore.
Let me drink.
Rock,
paper,
scissors.
Yes!
You're really over the top.
Rock,
paper,
scissors.
My cursed losing streak against him
even killed my chances at love.
May I have your Line ID?
Give it to him, give it to him.
They say that everyone has
three windows of love in life.
No one loses forever.
But I've never managed to beat him either.
Xiaoyang,
help me.
Look,
I wrote my code according to
what the teacher taught us last semester.
But for some reason,
the character movements just look weird.
Let me see.
You messed up the code order,
and your plug-in settings
for the object are off too.
Look here,
you made so many mistakes.
No wonder your character
moves just like Annabelle.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Tuo,
wait for me.
Tuo is really popular with the girls.
School has just started,
and the course add/drop period isn't
even over yet.
What number is she?
His fourth admirer.
It's insane.
Tuo, every girl's dreamboat,
please help me.
Please,
this is my once-in-a-lifetime request.
You say that every time.
This is the last time, I promise.
Last time when you asked me to go with you
to the drama club
just to make up numbers,
you said the exact same thing.
This is about my happiness.
Please!
Teach me how to confess to Xiaoyang.
Please.
You've known Lin Xiaoyang
longer than I have,
yet you still don't know what she likes?
Do you really like her?
There are blind spots in vision, right?
When you're too close to something,
it's hard to see it clearly.
You know me.
I haven't even had
a single girlfriend yet.
Unlike you, Casanova.
High school beauty goddesses,
honor guard captains,
and cheerleaders—
no one could resist your charm.
You've conquered them all.
Are you complimenting me or insulting me?
Complimenting you!
100% sincere compliments
from the bottom of my heart.
I swear.
Han Tuo,
please.
I'm begging you.
Let go.
I'll let go if you agree first.
Let go first.
Agree first!
Get down.
Agree first.
Get down!
Agree first!
[Juicy Joy Fruit Shop;
Open All Year Round]
Get down.
You still haven't agreed.
Get down!
We're at your place.
Lu Junxi!
Don't you have arms and legs?
How old are you now,
and you're still making Tuo carry you?
Get down right now!
Why are you just staring at me?
Tuo,
Junxi is being silly.
Don't always give in to him.
You're spoiling him.
Uncle, let me help.
There are two more boxes inside.
Okay.
Playing favorites.
I'm your actual son, you know.
He's more sensible
and better behaved than you.
Learn from him!
He's just pretending, okay?
Why don't you try pretending too?
Yeah.
Stupid Tuo,
pretending to be a good kid
and not even warning me.
Alright,
you two head back first.
I'll order takeout.
Hello,
one mixed noodle soup,
no pork liver.
One beef fried noodles, extra spicy.
No MSG in either,
thanks.
What about your dad and me?
Don't we need to eat?
I forgot.
Seriously.
I'll have the mixed noodle soup.
Okay.
Let me be clear,
I can teach you,
but...
But what?
No doubts,
no resistance,
and no regrets.
Can you do that?
Lu Junxi,
you like me.
No doubts,
no resistance,
and no regrets.
Can you do that?
Yes,
I like you.
I will never doubt,
never resist,
never regret,
or I'm a puppy if I can't.
When do you want to confess?
After the welcome party.
Right after the welcome party.
You like Lin Xiaoyang that much?
You've had girlfriend after girlfriend
since high school.
And here I am—a sophomore,
still at zero...
Wait,
just call her Xiaoyang.
We've been a trio since we were kids.
Why are you calling her by her full name?
Do you really know what it means
to like someone?
Of course,
liking someone means
always wanting to be together,
just like...
Like what?
Class begins, Coach.
Tell me first,
how do you plan to confess?
I don't know.
Tomorrow at 4 PM,
meet me at the entrance of Dongle Cinema.
Are you going to give me a live demo?
If you could get a relationship
just by studying theory,
every goblin
would have a girlfriend.
Fair enough.
So, that's the plan.
See you tomorrow.
Getting hit on again?
He's such a chick magnet.
It's so good to be handsome.
You're not bad-looking yourself.
I've already bought the tickets.
Your favorite.
A sci-fi movie?
Isn't a romance movie the right choice
for the demo lesson?
What do you like?
Sci-fi movies.
Choose what she likes
to appeal to her taste?
I got it.
Popcorn?
Sweet ones. Got everything you like.
Let's go.
You're seriously good at this.
No wonder so many girls like you.
Come a bit closer.
Finally...
we're almost there.
Only...
only 20 light-years to go.
Then I'll speed up.
Come up a bit.
That's enough.
I thought you wanted me to go harder.
Why does this sci-fi movie
have so many steamy scenes?
Tuo, what are you doing?
He really is a pro.
Damn,
why am I getting aroused now?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Really?
Why are you smiling?
You're the same.
Should we
help each other out?
Help with what?
Was it good?
The trailer was pretty good.
Hold on.
But it was kinda boring.
A complete waste of time.
It was okay.
The lead actress was pretty,
just my type.
What are you doing...
Isn't the demonstration
going a little too far?
Wait a sec.
Did you hear something?
Hold on, Tuo.
Your hand, Tuo...
Can you hold back?
What was that?
Junxi!
Tuo!
Where on earth did you two go?
You didn't even pick up your phones.
We just finished watching a movie.
I suddenly remembered
that I have something to do.
Gotta go.
Wait.
We still need to talk about
our beach trip this weekend.
This year marks the 10th anniversary
of our trio.
You two can decide without me.
Lu Junxi!
What's up with him?
The movie was too boring,
so he was probably just tired.
Ocean, here I come!
Hurry up, you guys!
You said we'd go to a new beach,
but we ended up at the same old place.
Let me help you with that.
It's okay.
You and Xiaoyang go ahead first
and grab us a good spot.
I can manage, Tuo.
Nice shot.
Good one, good one.
Nice one!
Got it, got it.
Catch it.
What was that?
You're not playing with them.
Aren't you afraid someone else might
win Xiaoyang over?
That's none of your business.
Junxi.
Junxi, Tuo,
come play volleyball!
Let's play three-on-three!
Hurry up!
You didn't put on any sunscreen.
If you play like this,
you'll definitely get sunburned.
Let's play! Let's play!
Xiaoyang, I'm coming!
Too soft.
Junxi, Tuo,
smile.
Beach trip
and taking an instant photo.
After all these years,
don't you ever get tired of it?
Never.
I always carry the photo from the day
our trio officially formed
with me everywhere.
You've kept it all this time?
Of course.
It's been 10 years,
and we're still so close.
That's not easy to come by.
We should cherish it,
don't you think?
Time flies.
It's been 10 years since I met Tuo.
So,
if you two are fighting, make up quickly.
Don't sulk.
We're here to have fun.
-We're not fighting.
I hope not,
but I'd be a fool to believe that.
As usual,
I get one room,
and you two share another.
Which one of you wants to come
and draw the room key?
I'll draw then.
You guys better not regret it.
Tuo.
Help me take my luggage upstairs too.
Okay.
Make up soon, will you?
We're not fighting.
Then why is it so awkward between you two?
That's because...
We're fighting.
Whatever you're fighting about,
don't give him the silent treatment.
Don't ignore him.
Remember?
Back when Tuo first moved into
our neighborhood,
he was super shy.
He didn't like interacting with others
and wasn't good at expressing himself.
It took you a very long time
to break the ice with him.
And he gradually started enjoying talking
to others
and expressing his thoughts.
I've forgotten
what Tuo used to be like.
So
don't ignore him,
or he'll think you hate him.
If you miss the chance to make up
and our trio loses a member,
I'll beat you up.
Alright, I got it.
Good.
Okay,
I'll go back to my room and unpack.
I've scheduled a morning call
for 7 AM tomorrow,
and then we'll meet in the living room
for breakfast.
Good night.
I...
I'll go take a shower first.
Why does it have to be a double bed,
of all times?
Do you want to go first, or should I?
I'll go first.
No,
Tuo.
No!
[In the Next Episode]
Tuo.
Where have you been lately?
I went to your place
but couldn't find you,
and you didn't reply to my messages.
Does it bother you?
I...
I don't want to just be your friend.
I want to be with you...
to be your boyfriend.