Xuanqing ranked third in the exams.
We ought to celebrate.
But he won't hear of any fuss
and I dare not press the matter.
Still, appearances
must be kept.
I thought to
invite
Mrs. Yu
and Wanxue to dine with us.
What say you?
Mother's word is law.
No objections.
Those are your own words.
Then I shall
find you a match as well.
So Mother's been
setting a trap for me.
What nonsense.
I am nothing like you lot,
all cunning and hidden schemes.
Tell me true,
are you still
mourning
your late wife?
She was here
but two years.
You have mourned her
long enough.
To carry on
is too much!
It is not that.
I've simply been consumed by duties.
Yet even Xuanqing
is taking a bride now.
And you, his uncle,
remain utterly alone...
Then...
allow me to assist.
Whose daughter
has caught your favor?
Here we are again...
She needn't come
from a grand house.
So...
Forgive the intrusion.
There's a pressing matter with the Gus.
Mother,
I must
take my leave.
Every time marriage comes up,
something urgent appears.
Enjoy.
Off with you.
Since the Baoxiang Temple murders,
the bureau's been
watching this gang.
They made arrests just days ago.
And sent a list:
the gang itself,
plus everyone
linked to their dealings.
I went through it,
and there was
Ms. Gu's own brother.
I pressed a little further.
Word is, he operates
a gambling den.
A few from this gang
were his regulars.
A classic Ji, I must say.
No deal too dirty for that lot.
From what we've gathered,
Master Gu
certainly had no clue
who he was dealing with.
So when does the bureau
plan to wrap this up?
Lord Zhang
wants to move fast,
but wanted to check with you first.
Moving fast is the right call.
In that case,
go tip off Ms. Gu.
My lord.
On second thought...
tell her
I need to see her in person.
No matter what,
we have to meet.
Yes, my lord.
Go.
Ms. Gu,
this way.
Gratitude.
Stay put.
My lady.
Greetings, my lord.
No formalities.
This concerns your brother,
and it is no small matter.
So
I wanted to meet you in person.
How can you be certain
he was unaware
of his clients' true nature?
I knew all along
he was a gambling tout.
But with our mother gravely ill,
I chose to say nothing.
Forgive me if it sounds foolish,
but he never...
cared much for studies.
He has a taste for trade.
Our family forbade it,
and so... he strayed.
But to say he conspired with outlaws...
he would never dare!
Can you vouch for that?
I'd stake my life on it.
As for
those outlaws,
the bureau's set to
make their move within days.
If you want to get him out,
you must act quickly.
I am deeply grateful.
Time and again,
you've shown us
such generosity.
I'm forever in your debt!
Think nothing of it.
As for those...
rather peculiar gifts...
Please, no more of those.
Well......
And this...
is also for me?
I...
It's...
You brought it,
so leave it.
What is it this time?
The last time...
when you came
to my aid...
you left it behind.
I brought it home
and found a few tears in it,
so I had it repaired
with golden thread...
But it still
didn't look right...
so I had it reembroidered...
Remarkable.
Then I shall
gladly keep it.
Yes, my lord.
What's taking Mr. Ping so long?
Stop!
Mr. Ping!
Qingpu,
they've taken
Master Gu!
At first,
he only wanted a few customers.
Earn a little extra on the sly.
But then he heard,
if you lease the place
and turn it over,
you could take an extra cut.
Then he thought... why not.
Why not?
You useless fool!
My son, MY SON!
Was touting
for a gambling den!
What is this?
That is greed rotting a man
from the inside!
Father,
I've already sent Mr. Ping
and the men after them.
Shall we
go to the authorities?
Absolutely not...
not the authorities!
Jinrong was taken
from a gambling den.
What a disgrace!
Report it,
and we proclaim to all
that my son consorted with gamblers.
No, no.
Absolutely not!
My lord!
My lord,
something terrible...
My lady heard that
Master Gu has been taken...
she has fainted!
What?
I told everyone
she was not to know a word of it!
I swear I didn't say a word...
This way.
How did Mother find out
that Jinrong was taken?
I was walking with her in the garden
when two servants
started gossiping,
saying Master Gu
had been seized.
She asked them what happened,
and then she collapsed.
Jinzhao,
how is she?
She's taken the remedies.
She is resting now.
Thank heaven for that.
But Jinrong...
I heard
he was abducted!
And who
told you that?
Everyone's talking about it!
Jinrong was taken. Yes.
And this was supposed to stay quiet,
especially from Mother.
Someone
let it slip.
Who is it?
Hard to say.
But I'd start by asking
who has the most to gain.
Is Chunlin even trustworthy?
What if he slips up!
Have no fear.
We are close.
He won't betray me.
Besides,
Jinrong was snatched
in broad daylight.
Half the city saw it.
Nobody will trace it back to us.
Good.
And Jinrong, honestly,
his mother's fortune
is practically a goldmine.
That's not enough for him?
He had to tout for a gambling den,
trading in that sort of filth.
No wonder his mother fainted.
I'd faint just hearing about it.
Lan...
Tell me the truth.
Was it you who
spread word of this
until she collapsed in despair?
Outrageous!
Guard your tongue...
That's right.
We only just found out ourselves.
My lady,
you grieve your mother unjustly!
Then good.
Jinrong's fate hangs by a thread.
Mind yourselves,
do not fan these flames!
Am I the one
on trial?
I gave you life.
Is this how you repay me?
If rage consumes you,
do not bring it
to my door!
Lord Chen
has learned of your plight.
Should aid be needed,
present this
to the capital garrison
and seek out Lord Hu.
Boss,
how big's our cut this time?
Easy, easy.
You'll all get yours.
Sir!
Where is he?
Woodshed.
Go.
Li Xianhuai...
Mother...
Is Jinrong back yet?
Don't worry.
Everyone is out looking.
Mr. Luo
has a whole search party out.
And Lord Chen
is on it too.
Alright.
My lady...
I'll be back.
It was really Li Xianhuai?
Yes.
I would've run back last night,
but the city gates
were already closed.
Li Xianhuai is
Master Ye's guard.
So does that mean...
Master Ye's the one behind it?
My lady!
What is it?
Word just
came from
Master Ye.
He says Master Gu has been found!
He's sending him back now!
Oh, Mother...
I was so terrified...
Mother,
Mr. Li is the reason
I'm alive.
I cannot thank you enough.
Please, come in
for some tea.
Gratitude.
But I must return
to Master Ye.
I shouldn't linger.
Another time,
we'll
give you the thanks you deserve.
Here, my son.
Enough!
Father...
He was held by those men
through the night...
He's been through enough.
The lesson is learned.
Is that not sufficient?
Such simple wisdom!
Do you know
what this wretch has cost me?
The censor has denounced me!
How did the censor learn of it?
It's an unlicensed gambling den,
no papers, no trace.
Soldiers moved in last night,
tore it apart.
Ledgers showed it
clear as day:
Gu Jinrong's name.
The keeper confessed all:
the boy's father
heads the Treasury,
so he got special terms:
a private room, discounted.
He's lying!
Your name. In ink.
With your handprint.
And you call him a liar?
Were it not for Lord Chen,
who vouched for you,
you'd already
be standing before a judge!
Rather than
let you
bring this house to ruin,
today
I will
beat you
into the ground!
Mother!
- Mother!
- Father...
My lord!
Please!
My lord...
Father!
Stop...
My lord,
mercy...
Dozens of lashes already...
It will kill him!
Out of my way!
My lady...
- Not another word for him!
- Mother...
And you...
I was just getting to you.
This family has a legacy!
Scholarship, honor.
Our relatives' children...
scholars, everyone!
Not a single exception!
And then there's him!
So you're saying...
it's all on me?
Isn't it!
You Jis...
raised on money,
not values!
No wonder
I've got a son like this!
Father, do you hear yourself?
Your return to office,
paid for by the Jis, every last coin.
Currently,
house's contents: food, garb, all...
which escapes
Mother's funds?
You despise us that much?
Then starting today,
hand over your salary.
All of it.
We shall see
how far that
actually gets you.
- Jinzhao...
- Oh,
and your account
at the Jis' shops.
Art, antiques.
Settle every last bit.
How dare...
you say that!
You see this?
Your children!
Both of them,
son and daughter...
greed is all they know,
haggling over
every last farthing!
You're crying?
I should be the one in tears!
I attained the pinnacle
of scholarly honor!
Yet no heir to bear it onward!
My fault...
All mine...
It's on me...
My Lady!
Mother...
Are you all right?
- Mother...
- My lady!
Mother!
My lady!
Ms. Jinzhao's here.
My lady,
please stay with her.
She woke in the night
and hasn't slept since.
Just sitting there.
Staring out.
I am
at a loss.
Did my lord come?
Just left.
He apologized.
But she
didn't say a word
in return.
He lost patience
and stormed out.
I see.
Mother...
Darling,
come,
sit with me.
What beautiful hands.
When we sent you to Tongzhou,
they were
this big.
It was
this time of year...
How I wish I could go back...
My lord says it's time.
I'm to take the child.
My lady...
Where is she?
Get her out now!
My love,
give me the child.
My lord.
She's barely
one month old.
After all I endured
carrying her...
can you wait a little longer?
I am sending her
to her grandmother.
Not selling her off.
What is there to fear?
I had her fate read.
Her stars are ill-suited to mine.
Should she stay,
it would cost me my career,
and do her no good either.
Sending her away
is in her own interest.
In yours, you mean.
Enough of this.
Hand her over!
My lord...
- be gentle, please!
- Give her here!
My lord...
please...
Hear me out!
Wait, please!
My child!
No, no!
My lady...
- No!
- My lady...
My lord!
- Please...
You've barely left childbed.
My baby!
Jinzhao!
What possessed me?
Why did I ever trust his word?
I stood there and watched...
as he took you away!
Jinzhao...
Forgive me...
Forgive me.
I failed you, my child.
If I've wronged
anyone in this life...
it's you...
I'm sorry...
forgive me...
The greatest sin of my life
was committed
against you.
I'll carry this guilt
to my grave...
Mother...
[The greatest sin of my life]
[was committed]
[against you.]
[Mother...]
My lady,
you're in tears...
It's nothing.
Dust in my eyes.
Go to Lord Changxing's.
Find Li Xianhuai.
Tell him
I wish to thank Master Ye
for bringing Jinrong home.
I shall treat him to wine.
Those were her words?
Yes, my lord.
she requests the pleasure
of your company,
at your leisure.
At last.
Worth every bit of trouble.
Greetings, Master Ye.
My gratitude for saving my brother.
Such etiquette.
I'm not sure
I know this lady.
Your kindness demands a worthy return.
You've done my family
an enormous favor.
You deserve proper gratitude.
Awfully quiet in here.
Few customers at this hour.
Which suite
have you arranged?
Our finest.
We do not
open it
for just anyone.
But today,
you are not
just anyone.
Lead the way.
Mr. Li,
My lady has prepared
a separate suite
for you and your men.
I...
Enjoy yourselves.
Yes, my lord.
Gentlemen.
After you.
What manner of game
is this now?
Tell me,
you took Jinrong.
Then you let him go.
What were you after?
You found out.
How?
Someone told you?
Don't tell me
it was Chen Yanyun...
You two keep
finding each other remarkably often.
So
that's a yes.
Every bit of it.
Yes,
I did it.
Why?
He never did
a single thing to you!
Why would you go after him?
No reason.
It diverted me.
Oh, there it is.
The real you!
You left me no choice.
Master Ye,
I cannot fathom
why you took him.
Nor can I fathom you,
not even after all this time.
Every time I begin to think
perhaps there is
something decent in you,
you do something
that defies all reason.
So forgive me
for meeting madness with madness.
Lest one day
you burn my house down
simply because the mood struck you.
Is that genuine confusion,
or are you putting it on?
Pardon?
Everything I did.
I did it for you.
What do you mean?
The boy is barely grown
and he's already touting for gambling dens.
A scolding changes nothing.
If you actually
want him to stop,
you shake him.
Hard enough
that it sticks.
That's the only way.
That was
your reasoning?
What business is it of yours?
Because!
Because...
you are fearless in every matter
except when
it concerns your own blood.
You saved my life once.
I had no worthy means of repayment.
So let me handle the part
you couldn't
bring yourself to do.
And I was measured about it.
After what he endured,
he will not
go near a gambling den again.
Do you even realize
because of what you did,
my mother
collapsed.
Her health
was already fragile.
And then Jinrong...
this whole thing...
pushed her over the edge.
She hasn't
left her bed since yesterday.
I...
I had no idea.
I was only trying to help...
Well, thank you for that!
Don't help me again.
How dare you, woman!
Untie me this instant!
Your brother's the one
who put your mother in bed!
I only meant to help.
There it is.
I struck a nerve.
Snap at me?
Go fix your brother first.
So I'm the only one
you dare lash out at!
Stay down.
You've earned it!
Gu Jinzhao!
Hey!
Master,
I looked into it.
The gambling den
wasn't raided
over paperwork.
It was raided on suspicion
of harboring some outlaws.
The garrison
carried out the operation,
but the order
came from the bureau.
And the garrison
sent men
specifically for Master Gu.
It seems Lord Chen was the one
who arranged for that.
The whole trip
paid off.
I came upon
a herb farmer,
a man who knew
Mr. Xiao well.
He spoke of his gift
for medicine
with
great admiration.
People practically
revered him for it.
One night,
after too much wine,
he let slip that
he was from Xianghe.
And behind his house
stood a temple.
As a boy,
he used to slip inside and steal offerings.
A temple in Xianghe.
Could it be Xuanmiao Temple?
My thoughts precisely.
The temple holds royal patronage.
Royals have long dedicated
their children there since birth.
Prince Chengqing was no exception.
And his appearance?
Was anything said of that?
The sort of face one forgets.
One thing only,
a small growth on his left ear.
My lord.
A letter from Lord Zhang.
Zhang Ling has broken them.
Over 200
of them in total.
Divided into five cells.
Each one in the dark about the others.
A single courier
moves between them.
Passes instructions.
Nobody knows
where this
courier lives.
Only one detail
slipped out:
he consumes no meat.
A strict vegan.
Send word
to Lord Zhang.
Look into the temple.
My lord.
Darling...
no more healers.
It serves nothing.
They all write
the same prescriptions.
Sit up, lie down,
sit up again.
If Death has marked my name,
no remedies will spare me.
Mother,
please.
The healer said
it is not so grave.
You simply need time.
Let yourself heal.
What is it?
I was just assigned
to look after the young master.
This was... found
beneath his pillow.
[It is I who brought this upon Mother.]
[Upon all of you.]
[From this day forward,]
[forget that I ever existed.]
That miserable,
ungrateful boy!
Has he...
run away?
Father,
we shall find him!
For what?
He will keep
making trouble until
this family is ruined!
Let him go!
Good riddance
to him!
Father,
this is not the moment
for words you'll regret!
Qingpu,
find Mr. Ping.
Take everyone we have.
Whoever finds him
will be handsomely rewarded.
My lady!
Chunlin,
send our men as well.
At once.
[The temple holds royal patronage.]
[Without an imperial edict,]
[the bureau]
[has no grounds to conduct a search.]
[We will need a pretext.]
His Highness' charm has been
ready for a while.
We were planning to send it
at the start of next month.
We did not expect to see you.
It's the Crown Prince's charm.
Coming in person
was the right thing to do.
These beads
are a small gift.
Nothing of great worth,
but they've been
blessed by the gods.
Gratitude.
Lord Zhang!
Something tells me
you are looking for someone.
You see right through me.
I'll be plain about it.
Has anyone of a suspicious nature
been seen recently?
What sort of person?
Someone suspected of... sedition.
No.
We have
47 members of staff in total.
All have been registered
with the authorities.
And beyond those people?
Casual laborers,
kitchen hands?
None whatsoever.
Given the royals' connection to us,
we cannot afford to be careless.
They are all trustworthy.
Even the farmers who deliver our vegetables
are from households down the hill.
Unless...
My child,
have there been any outsiders lately?
Yes, Master.
There has been a devotee.
What does he look like?
Thin. Dark complexion.
Oh,
there's a growth
on his left ear.
He told me
he calls it his doorstop.
Where is he now?
He just left.
Right when you were arriving.
He cannot have gone far.
Ride hard,
we may still catch him!
Ambush!
Cover your faces!
My lord!
What's happened?
My lady,
a wheel gave out.
We won't be moving
any time soon.
There's
an abandoned shed just ahead.
Let's take shelter there.
The rain is letting up.
Listen carefully,
whoever finds Jinrong
gets 100 taels of silver.
Yes, my lady!
My lord,
we're almost there.
Lord Chen?
My lord,
brace yourself.
My lady,
should I lend a hand?
I'll go.
Let me.
I'm grateful, my lady.
[How did he end up like this...]