(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(Previously)
Not everyone's on your side.
Someone wants to see you fall.
Don't tell me
Raffy knows about Arnold and me.
Can you help me?
If you help me this time,
you'll be saving everyone.
You dropped your phone.
Explain it.
Tell me you didn't take me out
just to delete Dean's video.
Will you stop doing things for Jack?
The one who likes you is right here.
Someone like you… is not for me.
Happy three-year anniversary.
Will you marry me?
Is this the time to joke around?
If we're still together in the future…
I'd want to get married.
Now it's clear to you
how we feel about each other.
I like you as more than just a friend, Tua.
Will you be my boyfriend?
(Episode 9: The Climax)
When will I ever be in your line of sight?
When will you see my worth?
Someone like you… is not for me.
On days you miss me,
you can play my playlists.
"Only Friends : Dream On"
Sorry, guys. Didn't mean to interrupt.
Congratulations, Tua.
So, are you two dating?
If I know, I'll know how to act.
You guys saw it earlier.
Take good care of Tua.
Don't make him angry.
There was this one time
Dean wore his clothes without asking.
He got furious. It was freaking scary.
Mm.
Don't worry.
I've been taking good
care of him all along.
Right, Mr. Tua? Hm?
Right?
Stop it.
Hello. What's up?
Right now?
Okay. I'll be right there.
Hey, Raffy called. He said it's urgent.
I'm going to see him.
See you.
It's probably nothing.
What is it?
I…
I have something important to tell you.
Uh-huh.
Just don't be shocked.
Okay.
I…
I want to drop out of the play.
Why?
What happened?
I don't think the play needs me.
People want to see Dean and Arnold
more than Arnold and me.
I think the sponsor will understand.
I get that, but the show
starts in a few days.
And you've been rehearsing for so long.
I don't want you to regret it later.
Don't worry about me.
I've thought it through.
I'd rather work behind the scenes.
Raffy.
Am I putting too much
pressure on you during rehearsals?
It's not that, Jack.
Is it about Dean?
A little.
But that's not all.
I've also lost my passion for acting.
I just realized I don't want to
be an actor for the rest of my life.
Anyway, thank you so much
for giving me this opportunity.
Gosh, okay.
If you've thought it through,
then I respect your decision.
That's nice.
It's awesome, actually.
Why are you here?
I'm just… tired of the same old playlists.
I want to hear you play live.
Want to grab some
congee with me after work?
What's this about?
I just want to talk to you.
What? Jack didn't want you?
So you came to me?
It's not that he didn't want me.
I chose this myself.
I don't get it. Why did you quit the play?
You fought so hard to get that role.
I… just lost my passion.
Lost your passion?
See? This is what happens
when you've been spoiled your whole life.
You do whatever you want,
and the moment you don't, you just quit.
Are you done lecturing me?
Are you eating with me or not? I'm hungry.
I'll wait.
MR. DUI'S À LA CARTE &amp; CONGEE SET
Wow. This is new to me.
I thought you only ate
fancy food catered to rich kids.
Pickled plum soup and salted egg salad
are my favorites in the whole world.
Try them.
They're what this place is known for.
Just try.
Here.
You have to eat them together.
Like this.
Put this on top.
So good.
Mm. It's good.
See? I told you it's good.
I only bring people
I'm really close to here.
I don't share this place with just anyone.
This is their best dish, stir-fried
Chinese black olives with minced pork.
Try it.
You don't believe me?
Here.
So you asked me out just to eat?
Nothing else?
Mm.
Why?
Nothing.
It's just every time I see you,
there's always trouble.
I just wanted to have a peaceful meal,
but I didn't want to
come alone, so I asked you.
Besides, I don't want to go home yet.
Here she is.
Calling at the perfect time.
You're not gonna pick up?
No.
I'm in a no-contact phase
with my mom right now.
Hey, why aren't you eating?
You don't usually eat rice porridge?
I don't?
I'd say I eat it more than you do.
Look.
Then eat more.
The salted egg is a must.
Here. Eat it all together.
Thanks, though, for sharing
your favorite place with me.
He's kind of different today.
I couldn't bring myself to be mad at him.
With him, it actually feels nice and easy.
Whoo!
Three, two, one.
Argh!
You okay?
A big guy like you
can't even handle that ride?
I just didn't get enough sleep.
I worked at Pink's until late last night.
Ah.
It won't be like this next time.
All right. We'll see about that.
It's all an act.
Have some water.
This place reminds me of when I was a kid.
My mom used to bring me here.
I still have the photo.
Who would've thought I'd end up
dating the amusement park owner's son?
Who knows? Maybe we met here
when we were kids.
Let me tell you. If you're in
that photo, I'll believe in destiny.
We passed by each other as kids,
and ended up falling in love as adults.
Ever since we leveled up our relationship,
you've been a lot sweeter.
Tua, son.
Hey, Dad.
Hi.
You don't come home much these days.
Because Jack works your son to the bone.
The play's about to open, Dad.
That's college life.
Have all the fun you can.
But after the play, you'll have to
help me design a new mascot costume.
Of course, Dad.
This is Arnold.
Hello, sir.
Your friend?
Not my friend, Dad.
My boyfriend.
What? Seriously?
This is the first guy
you've brought to meet me.
I'm getting flustered.
It's my first time bringing
my partner to meet my dad.
Actually, we only recently
went from friends to boyfriends, sir.
Take good care of my son.
Yes, sir.
Because if you don't
or you break his heart,
you might find yourself stuck on a ride.
And I'll lock you in the haunted house.
I'm kidding.
Come on, Dad.
Have fun. I'll get back to work.
All right.
Goodbye, sir.
Watch your back.
Hey.
Are you implying something
by asking me to watch this with you?
No, I just like this movie.
But I don't want us to end up like that.
So…
When you talked to Raffy the other day,
is that really all he said?
Mm.
He wanted to quit.
Why?
What do you think he said to me?
I thought he was scared of being compared,
since I'm a better actor than him.
It'd be embarrassing
for him to keep going with the role.
But don't worry.
I'll do my best with this role for you.
Sure.
No one's better than you.
Hey, Jack.
Looks like there's an activity
before the movie.
Should we check it out?
Let's go.
Before we start the movie, let's see
who here is a true romantic movie nerd.
Complete these famous lines
and name the movies.
Whoever gets the most
correct answers wins this Oscar.
I want that Oscar.
It's fake.
Fake or not, I still want it.
First one. Super easy.
Raise your hand if you know it.
"Call me by…"
Yes?
"Call me by your name,
and I'll call you by mine."
From Call Me by Your Name.
That's correct!
Wow, he was so fast
I didn't even finish the line.
Very good.
Next one.
"I'm just a girl, standing
in front of a boy…"
Yes?
"Asking him to love her."
From Notting Hill.
That's correct.
Ah! Another strong contender.
Next one.
"Shone, I have something to tell you."
"I really like you.
I've liked you for three years."
"I did everything I could
to change myself for you."
"I joined the traditional dance club,
acted in a play,
became a drum major,
and studied harder, all because of you."
"But now I realize what I should've done
from the start was tell you that…"
"I like you, Shone."
From Crazy Little Thing Called Love.
Very impressive!
Wow! He almost quoted the whole movie.
He quoted every word. That's amazing.
How do you remember all that?
I used that monologue
to pass the faculty entrance exam.
And now, the final one.
It's a classic.
"What light through yonder window breaks?"
Does anyone know this one?
Anyone?
Yes?
"It is the east, and Juliet is the sun."
From Romeo and Juliet.
That's correct.
We have a winner, everyone.
Here's your Oscar.
Hello. What's up, Dao?
I'm watching a movie.
(Dean, help me.)
(Can you come to my place right now?)
Okay. Calm down. I'll be right there.
Open the door.
Hey! Open up!
Or we're calling the police.
Open the damn door!
Dean, help me!
What?!
Dao!
Dean!
You okay?
Help me.
Hey! Don't come any closer.
You called your baby brother?
Where are you taking her?
She's not allowed to go anywhere.
Let's go. I'm getting you out of here.
You fucking dare?
Hey! Stop right there!
Are you going with them?
Don't you love me anymore?
Are you leaving me?
Love, my ass!
Why wouldn't I leave
when you're sleeping with someone else?
You bitch!
Easy, Dao.
I said stop!
Dean, get Dao out of here.
I don't think we can talk this out.
You two pieces of shit.
If you take my girl,
I'll have you arrested for trespassing.
Go the hell ahead.
I'll press charges against you
for beating my sister, you asshole.
She's my woman.
I can do whatever I want to her.
You don't own her life.
Don't come any closer.
Dao, let's go.
Dean, move.
- Dao!
- Back off!
You're going to pay for this.
Dao!
Ow.
How could he do this to you?
He was sleeping with someone else.
She just started working with him
a couple of months ago.
When I caught him, he denied everything.
Every time I tried to break up with him,
he beat me.
Whoa! That's not okay, Dao.
How did you put up
with a cheater like that?
What are you going to do now?
I think… I'll move back to Khon Kaen
and stay with Mom for a while.
Do you want me to drive you there?
How could you?
You have a play to run.
Opening night is coming up.
It's fine.
It's not a big deal. I can handle it.
You can stay here tonight, Dao.
I'll get the bed ready.
Think of this as your home.
Thank you, Jack.
Jack doesn't talk much,
but his actions show how much he cares.
Mm.
That's just how he is.
You're lucky to have a good partner
who takes care of you and even your family.
That's hard to find.
Now that you're back together,
take good care of each other.
Don't break his heart again. Hm?
Mm.
Hey, I can do it myself.
No, you can't.
It's the costume designer's job.
So if I'm not an actor,
you won't do it for me?
Fine, I'll do it for you,
but as your boyfriend.
Looking good.
Come on, let's get some photos.
What's that face?
Just pose normally.
Why are you taking photos?
I want to keep this moment.
One day, when you're famous,
I'll use these to ride your coattails.
No way.
You'll always be my personal stylist.
There's no way we're ever breaking up.
Are you sure?
I am.
As long as you don't want
to break up, I won't either.
Get to rehearsal.
Go back before someone sees us.
I want to stay with you tonight.
Can I?
Hey, Tua!
What's wrong, Tua?
What's wrong?
You guys look at this.
You should post this content with Arnold.
It'll make you more famous.
Listen to me, Tua. I can explain.
Explain what?
What?
What happened after that?
Did you two hook up?
Did you enjoy the hookup?
Hey! Tua, calm down.
Let's talk this out.
Talk, my ass!
I know you can hook up with anyone,
but why Arnold?
We didn't do anything.
We were just…
Just what?
Just hugging in the dark?
Do you think I'm stupid? Huh?
Damn you.
You're fucking disgusting.
Tua, just calm down.
How dare you ask me
to be your boyfriend after that?
- Just hear me out, okay?
- I don't want to hear it!
I swear, nothing happened.
Do you think it's cool to two-time people?
We're close friends, so you want us both?
It's not like that.
Do whatever you want.
From now on, I don't have a shitty friend
and a shitty boyfriend like you two.
I hope this opened your eyes
like it did mine, Jack.
Tua.
Tua!
Jack, just listen to me.
Get back to rehearsal.
Jack, I...
I said get back to rehearsal!
Keep rehearsing!
Keep going!
Raffy.
You shouldn't have done that.
The opening show starts soon.
I'm asking you a favor here.
Just let the show finish first.
Tua.
Can we talk?
Get out.
Tua, will you just let me explain?
I said get out.
I know you're angry,
but you've got it all wrong.
The video was clear.
What lies are you going to tell me now?
I'm not lying, Tua.
Dean and I didn't do anything.
We didn't even kiss.
It doesn't matter
whether you kissed or not.
You were together, in
that place, at that time.
If nothing really happened,
then why were you there alone with him?
I was drunk that night.
You're blaming it on alcohol?
Just hear me out, Tua.
Why don't you blame yourself for once?
It's not like that.
I wasn't sure if what I was feeling
was because of the play or not.
I didn't know.
I'm not a drama student like you guys.
I don't know how to
handle feelings like you all do.
So now you're blaming alcohol
and what I study?
That's enough.
Just get out.
Tua.
- But now I know I don't have…
- Know what?
I don't have feelings
for Dean. I like you, Tua.
I don't want to hear it.
Tua.
Get out.
Go!
Get the hell out!
Jack, will you hear me out?
Jack
Jack.
Jack, please listen to me.
Jack!
Jack, I can explain.
Get out of the car.
Jack.
Jack, listen to me!
I can explain everything.
Please, just listen.
Say it.
I'm sorry.
I was drunk that night. You saw me.
Oh yeah?
So every time you're drunk,
I'm supposed to cross my fingers
and hope you won't
end up all over someone else again?
We didn't hook up.
We didn't cross the line.
We just hugged,
and then we snapped out of it...
A hug was already too damn much!
What did you tell me?
You told me to trust you.
Said it was just content.
What the hell was that?
What kind of fucked up content is that?
Answer me!
I'm sorry.
Jack, I promise I won't do it again.
I won't get drunk again.
Please.
You're the most
important person in my life.
I did everything I could.
I changed myself for you.
Please don't leave me.
Well, that just proves someone like you…
can never change who you really are, Dean.
Tua.
You threw all my stuff out?
You've got the nerve to ask me that?
Just get out.
I don't want to see your face.
I can't live under the same roof
with someone like you.
This is getting out of hand, Tua.
Can you just calm down and listen to me?
Does everyone have to listen to you?
You knew everything from the start.
You were the one friend I trusted the most.
No matter what mess you got into,
I was always there for you, Dean.
Why?
Why did you do this to me?
I'm sorry.
- How could you?
- Tua, I'm sorry.
Why did you do it?
I'm sorry.
I don't want to hear it.
You've been my burden for far too long.
Go live wherever you want.
Where else am I supposed to go?
That shouldn't be a problem for you.
Lots of people are lining up
to be your sugar daddy.
It was you, wasn't it?
I didn't do it.
Weren't you the one who tricked me and
sneakily deleted the video on my phone?
Don't you remember?
Then who did it, if not you?
Was someone else there that night?
I don't know.
Look at this video.
This isn't from my angle.
You're right.
If it wasn't you, then who leaked it?
No one's going to believe I didn't do it.
I'm always the one people fucking blame.
Come on.
I'm sorry for misunderstanding you.
Don't take it to heart.
Not answering?
He's already got a lot on his mind tonight.
Just let him have some time alone.
Enough already.
Aren't you a lightweight?
I'm not taking care of a drunk.
Isn't that a good thing?
We could have some fun while I'm drunk.
What?
You don't want me anymore?
Pull yourself together, Tua.
This isn't you.
What the fuck do I get
for being a good person?
Maybe I'd be better off being the bad one.
Hey.
Don't sleep with me
just to get back at Arnold.
Why not?
It's just a hookup.
Other people do whatever the hell
they want without caring.
Tua.
I don't want you to regret this
for the rest of your life.
This isn't you. Trust me.
Yeah, I'm not exactly a saint,
but I don't sleep with drunk people.
Besides, I don't think
Arnold meant for it to happen.
People mess up,
especially when they're drunk.
I understand that so fucking well.
But if you want to
drink yourself stupid tonight,
I'll drink with you.
It's okay. You'll get through this.
I'll be right here.
I've been a real mess before.
So I understand this.
Can I come in?
You should go somewhere else.
I don't have anywhere else to go, Jack.
Can I stay here with you?
I opened my door for you once.
If I do it again…
I'm a damn idiot.
But Jack...
Dean.
Gameplay.
It's okay, Dean. I'm right here.
(Next Episode)
We came here together.
Who knows? After the play,
Raffy and I might get together.
Why are you doing this?
Are you getting with Raffy just to hurt me?
I'm just choosing someone who loves me.
So, what are you gonna do?
You're getting with him?
Do your best, Dean.
I'm rooting for you.
Tua, please give me a chance.
I love you.
And I know you love me too.