This minimalist design that you got going here,
it’s just not working for me.
I have to disagree with you, Mom.
The design is perfect.
It’s a huge improvement from the previous design of this house.
This feels more homey.
I don’t want too big of a house and closed off
where family members can’t even see each other anymore.
Like ours.
I heard you resigned
because of Miguel’s case.
Why?
For you, Luna.
I knew it was important to you and Kierra.
I didn’t want to disappoint you.
I know we’re not the same people anymore.
I want you to understand, Luna, that I’m really trying.
I want you to give me a second chance.
Move over ladies…
- Your goddess– - Wow!
has arrived.
Wow!
Hey, the Boracay trip is set in stone, okay?
I already declined two photoshoots for this.
Don’t worry, Via even came home for this vacation.
Thank you!
Enjoy!
Wow! I’m so excited.
You ruined the shot, Yanna.
Do you remember what you and Kalix did here before?
Of course not.
Please, you don’t have to pretend.
I remember what you told me, about the bathtub—
Didn’t you two—
Come on, Ke, shut up!
You did a taste test.
What do you mean, Yanna?
You both had a little taste of each other.
Maybe you can do it again.
They just might.
For Kalix and Luna’s taste test, cheers!
Yes, for taste testing!
Cheers!
Hurry up.
- Hey! - Come on, Luna.
Don’t play hard to get. Come on.
Convince me.
- Come on, Luna. - Come on, please.
I’ll kiss you if you keep this up.
- Nevermind. Cheers! - Cheers!
Cheers!
Why don’t you just have a taste test again?
You’re both single anyway,
and you can get back together.
There’s a bathtub!
Why don't you do it again?
Come on girls, stop teasing Luna.
It’s such a big decision to get back with an ex.
It’s been a long time since you broke up with Kalix,
you did nothing but study and work.
I’ve been on multiple dates, Via.
It just didn’t work out, okay?
It didn’t work out because you weren’t working hard for it.
It’s understandable after what happened between her and Kalix in the past,
Luna’s still scared to fall in love again.
But, I have to say, props to Kalix for stating his intentions.
No more mind games.
You’re right. I actually think Kalix seemed really mature.
He was being so sweet to you on-site,
acting like your husband.
Really? So, what’s stopping you?
I guess I'm scared.
I don’t know if it’s still worth it for us to try again.
I get it.
But how would you know if you won’t even try?
What’s the worst that could happen?
You’ve survived a heartbreak, remember?
I don’t wanna go through that pain again, Yanna.
Who says you will?
What if it all works out?
Kalix isn’t pressuring you for an answer, right?
So make use of this time to think things through.
She’s right. Just use our time here in Boracay to think, Luna.
That’s true and don’t be pressured to decide right away.
Love can wait, especially if it’s worth it.
Hey, hey!
That’s not even the main issue.
Did he or did he not cheat?
He said he didn’t.
He said he’ll explain when I’m ready.
There you go.
That’s going to be between the both of you.
Let’s not butt in, girls.
Right! Besides,
let’s stop talking about all this love drama.
We should let Luna contemplate on how she feels for now.
Besides, we’re here in Boracay to enjoy.
Should we just have gone to Pobla, or BGC,
or even Sam’s condo?
Let’s all bless Boracay with our presence.
Move over, the goddesses are here!
See? I'm right!
Hello, Kalix.
Hey! I just arrived here in Malaysia.
Enjoy your stay in Boracay.
Will do.
You better take care there
and good luck with your meeting.
Thank you. I’m a little bit nervous to meet the client, but—
He’s a big-time Filipino businessman here in Malaysia.
Why are you even nervous?
Remember, you’re a bar topnotcher.
Thank you.
Luna,
about our conversation last week,
I’m not rushing you to give me an answer.
I know.
I guess it’s good that...
we’re on separate trips so that we can think clearly.
Well, I don’t need extra time to think about it.
I’m already sure about you.
And again, I’m not pressuring you to give me an answer right away.
I’m willing to wait for it,
and work hard for it, okay?
Okay.
And please, enjoy your stay in Boracay.
You deserve it.
All right, go ahead and prepare now.
Take care, bye.
Bye.
Hey, wait for me!
Are you done flirting?
Yes, let me join.
I’ll throw your phone away.
Wait for me, hey.
All right!
Okay.
One, two, three… Pose!
Let’s do a wacky shot!
One, two, three, taste test!
Taste test!
One more, pose!
Sorry, Joe, we’re taken.
Oh, except these two.
These two, they’re single, very single. Yes!
- Oh, that’s all right, ladies. Next time. - Let's go.
Wow, you really ignored them, Luna?
You’re really just focused on one guy, huh?
Well, that’s because she’s not single.
She’s just in a very complicated relationship.
- Oh, I forgot! - Right?
All right then, for her future taste test!
- Let’s go! - For her future taste test!
Hey!
Luna!
You’ve been on your phone this whole time. Come, swim with us.
You’re such a flirt!
You’re such a KJ… As in, Kalix Jace!
Hey, don’t tease Luna!
She just might fall for him again!
Come on guys, stop it.
She might get back together with him right now!
Hey, you're adding fuel to fire!
I’m not affected by any of your teasing.
Jeez, he keeps updating and sending me reminders.
I know what you’re trying to do here, Kalix.
But sure, I’ll entertain you.
Luna: They’re still swimming. We’ll eat later.
Luna: Hey, don’t bother!
Luna: Fine, I'll send it later. When's your meeting?
Luna: It's just you two?
Wow, he’s even reassuring you now.
Hey! How long have you guys been standing there?
I’m impressed that he remembered to greet us, too.
And, he’s also getting us food.
Right!
He’s really wooing you.
Don’t make it easy for him.
Let’s test how much he really likes you.
I agree.
I know he already knows what he lost after you broke up.
But, let’s show him more.
Let’s show him what he missed out on.
How?
Leave it to me.
Like this?
It’s not working for me, girl. Sam, teach her some poses.
Just stick your butt out, pull your stomach in, and chest out.
Just like that!
Take off your sunglasses, then—
Like this?
Yes, hold still!
Three, two, one!
There you go.
Okay, okay, love it.
Wait a minute, your hair. There you go, all good.
Throw your hands in the air!
Wow, what caption should we put?
Maybe, “ride the boat with me.”
What? “Wanna ride a boat with me?”
Type in, “wanna ride with me?” then use the emoji—
That’s how you do it!
Hurry!
All right!
There you go.
- He’s really quick! - Oh my god!
You’re really taking Kalix’s breath away with all your posts. My god!
Wait a sec, he has a post, too.
Apparently, it’s Luna who had her breath taken away.
We still need to push this to the next level.
Now, let’s do a sexier pose.
She’s right, let’s move past the college level poses
to an attorney level pose.
Huh? What are you talking about?
What do you mean by “attorney level” pose?
Attorney level is when Kalix would have to sue you for being too sexy, Luna!
Here are the flowers. Put some…
There you go.
So, it's like your naked, you know!
Put your hands here.
Perfect!
- Feel sexy… - Don’t move! Hold that pose!
Hold on, the flower’s missing…
Is this okay?
Perfect! Look at this, hurry!
- Hurry up and post it… - Perfect!
Kalix replied.
What did he say?
Really?
Saw your pictures.
And so? What do you think?
The bathtub looks familiar.
And he said that I look beautiful, too.
Perfect!
See how effective the attorney level photos are?
Let’s post more.
Why didn’t you post this?
I don’t want to.
This is the thirst trap photo. You have to post it.
I don’t want to, Yanna, no.
Suit yourself…
Yanna, stop.
Hey, what are you doing?
You guys should quit teasing each other through your posts.
It’s so obvious how much you still like each other.
What? Did you post it?
No.
You sent it to him, as a direct message!
Damn you, Yanna!
All right, just relax, okay? Don’t panic.
Let’s wait for Kalix’s reply first and then panic after.
What?
Sorry!
I just wanted you to make progress.
It’s Kalix! Kalix replied! I’m so nervous.
I’m so nervous.
Open it so you’ll know.
- Just hurry up and open it! - Come on, hurry.
You’re so slow.
I’m in a meeting. Call you later.
- That’s it? - Thirst trap…
That’s it.
That’s it?
Why do you wanna be a lawyer?
Do you want to be a corporate lawyer or a criminal lawyer?
Criminal lawyer.
Why do you wanna be a criminal lawyer?
So I can get you out of jail.
Don’t be silly!
Future lawyer. I see.
What are your plans after law school?
I’m planning to work as a defense attorney in a law firm.
I’m planning to open my law firm, too.
There’s constant high pressure and expectations. It’s like,
I can’t even make a single mistake.
You know what, Kalix.
You’re doing well.
Luna?
They’re going up now.
Okay, keep stalking.
I am not!
Jeez, you liar.
What is it? Tell me.
Nothing.
They look so happy.
For the record, I’m not jealous.
I’m happy for them.
I witnessed the time when being a lawyer was just a dream to them.
Now, they’re living the dream.
But we also achieved our dreams, right?
Yes, we did.
I’m just sad that
I wasn’t in Kalix’s life back then to witness him reach those milestones.
I’m actually questioning myself…
What if,
what if we were still together then?
I didn’t give up on him?
What if,
I had the courage to talk before
I decided to break up with him?
It’s useless, though.
I wasn’t there
because I chose to leave.
What if you stop dwelling on the what if’s?
There’s no point in dwelling on Kalix’s past memories.
It’s over and done with.
Just focus on the things that you can do now, at the present.
Besides, if you and Kalix get back together,
you both can create new memories with each other, right?
And witness more milestones in life.
This time,
you both would have each other.
Answer his call.
He might want to start making new memories with you.
I’ll go ahead and check on our reservation.
Hi, Kalix!
Luna, what’s up?
Sorry to call you so late, by the way.
My meeting just finished.
Don’t worry about it.
How was the meeting?
It was just initial counseling
but it looks promising.
I think he’ll hire us.
Oh, wow! Congratulations!
See how easily you got it? And to think that you were so nervous earlier.
Why did you call?
I don’t wanna lie.
I just miss you.
Your voice,
Your face,
How could you miss me after seeing so many of my posts?
By the way, the photo you got, it was Yanna who sent it, not me.
Doesn’t make any difference.
You look great, as always.
You just reminded me of our time in Boracay.
Don’t be silly.
Are you currently busy?
No, my meeting’s done.
What we talked about last week…
I think I’m ready to—
Luna, sorry to cut you off but...
there’s someone at the door.
I’ll be back because my phone is charging, okay?
Give me a second.
Okay.
Kalix…
Hey! What’s up?
You know my room, right?
Yes.
You should stop by.
Let’s have some fun.
Okay!
Okay, I’ll just take a shower first.
- All right! - Bye!
Do you
still think about our first night together?
Luna, please, wait!
You cheater!
Please let me explain!
Hey, why do you look upset? What happened?
Huh?
Why aren’t you answering his call? What did you two talk about?
I don’t know anymore.
I’m just so confused.
Kalix is alone right now with that woman.
What did she mean by having fun?
You all know about—
about how
my mind works after getting cheated on.
I know that we’re not even together right now.
I know that.
But I still felt that pain like it was only yesterday.
It really hurts.
Luna,
it’s okay to have these feelings.
We understand what you’re going through.
Remember Luna, this is not your fault.
Luna,
you and Kalix are my friends.
So I want the best for both of you.
We’re still not one hundred percent sure if Kalix is fooling you.
But whether or not he is,
he’ll always trigger your trauma.
As long as you two haven’t resolved your past issues,
Kalix will remind you of that wound.
What I’m trying to say is,
you and Kalix should have a serious talk.
Not just about what happened tonight,
but way back to what, what happened ten years ago.
To have closure.
To tie loose ends.
After that,
you’ll know if you should stay in each other’s lives.
She’s right.
It’s best if you two get to talk it out.
So you and Kalix should really find time to talk.
I don’t think I can handle talking about the past.
I know Luna.
I’m sorry you’re going through this but,
all this he said she said, has to end.
For your peace of mind, too.
It’s okay.
Oh, Luna…
We’re here for you.
Come on, let’s just eat.
Let’s eat!
Don't cry anymore.
Let’s all eat now!
- Want some squid? - Smile now.
No.
- Pizza. - Right.
- She wants pizza. Want some pizza? - Okay.
- Come on. - She’ll have a bite.
Take a bite now…
Ke…
- She’ll have some pizza. - Come on.
Come on, Luna.
Take a bite…
Luna: Kalix, let's talk.
- Luna. - Kalix?
I booked the earliest flight to get here.
I can’t let this wait any longer.
There’s something important I have to tell you.
Kalix, it’s really late now.
Let’s talk tomorrow.
If ten years ago, I just walked away without fighting,
this time I won’t commit the same mistake again.
Luna, please.
Just ten minutes of your time. I’m begging you.
What?
What do you have to say, Kalix?
Tell me now so we can both get it over with.
Luna, listen.
I know you heard what Lorraine said,
but it’s nothing.
Please, trust me.
We were just going to open a bottle of champagne.
We were with all of our partners.
That’s all.
I’m really serious about fixing things with you, Luna.
I know I should’ve told you this a long time ago.
And I’m so sorry it took so long.
I just honestly didn’t see no use.
I tried explaining it to you so many times
but it just came to a point that I got so tired of everything.
But not you.
It just—
There was so much happening in my life back then.
But I never cheated on you, Luna.
Bullshit, Kalix.
So many years have passed and you’re still gonna lie to me?
You’re still gonna keep fooling me?
I’m telling you the truth.
Then, what was that before?
What was that video?
Why did you kiss Amy?
I did not kiss her.
Amy!
All right, truth or dare?
- Truth! - Dare!
- Dare! - She said dare, guys.
So, I dare you to kiss someone you like in this room.
Hold on, hold up.
Unfortunately, Kalix has to go.
Yes, sorry guys. Gotta go.
Still have a date in Tagaytay.
Oh shit! Oh shit!
What is wrong with you?
- Kalix… - Don’t touch me.
That's enough.
No, I've had enough of you, Amethyst.
What is your problem?
I’m sorry, they just told me to kiss the man that I like.
Know your boundaries.
I have a girlfriend.
Which part of that do you not understand?
Come on, you want to be a lawyer, right?
I’m sorry, I just didn’t think you’d be this upset.
- Bro, that’s enough. - Are you an idiot?
Don’t you dare cry.
I asked you a simple goddamn question.
Have you lost your mind?
You are goddamn stupid!
Kalix, I’m sorry.
Remember this,
I don’t like you and I will never like you.
So from now on,
stay away from me, okay?
Happy Valentine’s!
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
Let’s sit.
Okay. Did you drink alcohol?
Who were you with? Where were you?
Just a little.
We had a free cut.
Were you with Adonis and Amethyst?
Yes.
Okay.
I love you.
I love you too, Luna.
Always remember that.
I will.
I know.
I should have told you immediately.
My mistake is that I tried to settle everything on my own.
Luna, it was my friendship.
So I thought it was my problem.
I was on the right side and I just didn’t have enough courage to tell you.
We were in a relationship together
and I realized that I should have told you everything.
About that situation,
about my decisions.
I’m just really sorry if I failed to be completely honest with you.
You know I love you.
I would’ve understood no matter what you tell me.
Mixed signals, jealousy,
I even managed to brush off the insults your mother gave me.
But when I saw that video Amy sent…
I just felt so much pain, Kalix.
It made me feel so insecure.
I felt pathetic.
I even questioned my worth every night.
I gave you everything, didn’t I?
Everything.
But you still made me feel like
I’m a person that’s not worth loving.
But it’s not like that, Luna.
Then, how come I felt that way, Kalix?
You couldn’t let me in.
I tried.
I really did try, Luna.
I was always waiting for a moment for you to be ready to listen to me.
And maybe I didn’t realize that I was dragging it for too long.
You were also not yourself at that time.
And so, I just realized that you couldn’t listen to me yet.
I couldn’t talk to you
nor listen to you
because of everything that was happening then.
I was so lost at that time, Kalix.
I wasn’t asking you to forgive me, Luna.
I chased you because I really needed you at that time.
So many painful things happened to me years ago.
Things that I kept all to myself.
I was lost, too, Luna.
I’m sorry.
I felt so tired, too, Luna.
But not with you.
I wanted to give up on everything,
except you.
I needed you so badly.
Kio had some lung complication.
It was for his health why I stopped smoking.
Kio, eat your meal first
so we can get your favorite cake.
Okay, Kuya. But I need to pee first.
Okay, go.
Hey!
Kio!
- We thought he was cured - Kio!
from his complications after he underwent several treatments.
Suddenly his lung disease came back.
Kio!
The doctors found out
that Kio’s lung complication became more serious.
Doc…
Doc, what are the findings?
Doc Martinez,
we found a small lung nodule in your son’s right lung.
But we need to conduct more tests
and we are hoping that it’s benign.
There was a possibility that the lung nodule
they found inside Kio’s lung was cancerous.
I wanted to tell you
but I felt like it would add to your worries.
You had your own problems and I didn’t want to add up to it.
Hello?
Kalix, where are you?
Are you okay?
I feel so stressed in school.
I'm burnt out.
There's so many requirements and exams.
They're all on the same deadline.
I don't know how to finish them all.
You can do it, Luna.
One task at a time.
Just take as much breaks as you need.
Don’t stretch yourself too thin, okay?
I love you.
I love you too.
Bye.
I didn’t want you to worry about me,
so I didn’t tell you about my problems.
I tried to wait for the right moment
but things took a turn for the worst soon after.
There was no turning back.
After they found out that the lung nodule was benign,
we thought Kio was going to be okay.
But days later he got admitted again
because of other complications.
Kio is critical.
They will try to operate on him tomorrow
but he continues to be unresponsive to the meds.
Those days were the hardest.
I needed someone to talk to.
I wanted to tell you everything but another problem came up.
Bro, where are you?
We have finals today!
I can make up for it.
Bro, you've skipped so many times.
You'll fail if you'll be like that.
Luna needs me right now.
Despite the weight of my own problems,
Luna…
I had to set them aside.
I just knew instinctively
that I needed to be there for you.
I’m here.
I had been keeping everything to myself.
Keeping it all together
until you found the video of Amy kissing me.
You cheater!
Please let me explain!
It was too late to explain everything
and you refused to give me a chance to explain myself.
It’s my fault,
and I admit that.
I was so down.
I started to lose focus.
My grades took a major blow.
You need to reconsider my grades.
I can do additional academic work. I will do everything.
The thing is Mr. Martinez,
I have already looked into your grades
and there is simply nothing we can do about it right now.
Even with your midterm grades,
it is not enough to pull up your final grades.
It is just too low.
But sir…
There must be something I can do.
You will just have to retake these subjects again next semester.
Sorry, Mr. Martinez.
You cannot proceed to fourth year.
Excuse me.
But sir—
Sir?
I failed two subjects that semester.
I couldn’t believe it.
You are such a disappointment, Kalix.
I’m so sorry, Mom.
Sorry?
Kalix, I have enough problems as it is.
Why do you have to add up to it, huh?
I’ll make up for it, Mom.
I want to proceed with Law school.
Oh, okay.
You want to proceed to Law school?
Well then, pay for it yourself!
At my lowest,
all I needed was you.
But you needed time and space.
So I waited for you to be ready to talk to me.
But it didn't happen,
and what's worse, you told me you didn't love me anymore.
During the times I was so crushed with what you did to me,
Sevi has always been by my side.
Luna, I–
You think I’d still be hung up on you?
That I’d stay loyal to you?
After what you did?
I don’t love you anymore, Kalix.
Kalix, we’re done. I don’t think I can trust you again.
So please,
just go.
I didn’t believe you.
I could see it in your eyes that you still loved me.
I love you
so damn much.
I could never cheat on you.
But it was so obvious that you wanted me out of your life.
I almost lost everything.
I almost lost my dream of becoming a lawyer.
I almost lost my brother.
And I lost you.
I really wanted to give up, Luna.
I didn’t know what I was living for anymore.
I am so tired.
I want everything to end.
Kuya?
Where am I?
Kio!
You’re at the hospital, okay?
Everything’s gonna be all right.
It’s fine. Okay?
- Okay, Kuya. - Okay.
My brother needed me.
And that was the reason I had to keep going.
I wanted to tell you, Luna.
I really tried.
I just didn’t wanna add to whatever you were carrying at that time.
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry you went through all of that by yourself.
I should’ve just listened to you.
But I let my anger
and my doubts get the best of me. I’m sorry.
I’m sorry.
Luna…
Hey.
It’s nobody’s fault.
There was too much on both of our plates.
I was too cowardly and weak to fight for us.
And because of that one mistake,
I lost you.
I may have overcome my problems now,
and became the lawyer I always dreamt of…
but there will always be a void inside of me, Luna.
Because I lost you.
Almost ten years have passed.
Too much time has been stolen and taken from us.
I don’t want to live another ten seconds without having you back in my life.
So,
if you give me another chance...
I promise
I will never let go of you ever,
ever again.
We have a yacht party.
I’ll be there.
See you!
Hey, this view is amazing!
Come here, hurry.
You wanna dance?
- Let’s go! - I don’t know how to dance.
Come on!
Are you cold?
A bit.
I have a jacket in my bedroom.
I’ll go with you.
Good morning.
Luna.
Yes?
What are your thoughts about marrying me?