Why did you draw a house?
I want to become an architect
and build a beautiful home.
Is this your home?
Then I call dibs on this room.
Okay.
I also want to
put lots of game consoles inside.
And I want to have a dog too.
Then we can play together
and just go to sleep when we're tired.
This is our secret hideout.
Then we'll live together in the future.
Okay.
I don't know when it started,
but that secret hideout became
a home in my heart...
a home that belongs to Junxi and me.
[Episode 7: You Live in My World]
[Secret Lover]
Smells so good.
I wonder if it's too salty.
Let me taste it.
Sneaking a bite? How old are you?
Oh my God.
You too...
It's good, huh?
-So good!
-You two
go to the dining room
-and help Tuo.
-It goes well with rice too.
Please, go help Tuo in the dining room.
Okay, we will, we will.
Come on, Xiaoyang, have a bite as well.
Thank you, Auntie.
Try it.
This piece is good.
You sneaky little rats!
We'll eat later. We can wait.
It's really delicious.
Yeah, it's really tasty.
My mom made it.
-It's not like you made it.
-You two, no more sneaking bites!
Alright.
Just leave it there.
Auntie, this looks so delicious.
Right?
Then, have more later.
Mom,
I'll bring the soup.
Okay.
What are you doing?
We're at home. Behave yourself.
Tuo,
are you done?
Come help me with this!
Okay, I'm coming.
This remote control
doesn't work anymore.
I don't know if it's broken or what.
Junxi has been so busy
with his internship lately,
often coming home past midnight.
Are you also that busy?
Pretty much.
You're more mature than Junxi,
so I'm not worried.
Still, no matter how busy you are,
take care of your health,
okay?
Okay, Uncle.
Honey,
dinner's ready.
Dinner time, dinner time.
Come on, come on.
Let's have dinner.
Smells so good.
Tuo,
stop working on that, and come eat.
Okay.
Come on, come on.
Come on, come and sit at the table.
Here.
Have some meat.
Try it.
-This is Mom's braised pork.
-Xiaoyang, you too.
It's absolutely delicious!
I'm so full.
Junxi still hasn't given you an answer
about moving in together?
I really want him to say yes,
but I'm also afraid that he will.
What do you mean?
Mom, Dad,
have some fruit.
Good boy.
Uncle and Auntie love him so much.
He already has a happy home.
So sweet.
So?
Is it really okay to ask him
to move out and live with me?
There you go again.
Overthinking everything.
Have you asked Junxi what he thinks?
Junxi is their only child
still living at home.
Yushu has already moved out.
You're different from Yushu's case.
Stop getting stuck in your head.
He hasn't replied,
so I won't ask him yet.
I'll bring it up later.
I'm feeling a bit confused right now.
How's your internship going?
Come in and have some fruit.
Okay.
Alright.
My mom's cooking is good, huh?
Duh, it's delicious.
Alright.
As your friend, I can take a hint.
I'm heading home now.
Bye.
Finally, you're not
pulling a long face anymore.
What were you talking about
with Xiaoyang just now?
You didn't seem very happy.
Nothing much.
She just asked
how we've been getting along lately
and how I've been doing.
How's your internship going?
Remember, I'm here for you.
You must tell me
if something's bothering you.
Okay.
I'll head back now.
You hurry inside.
Bye-bye.
Be careful on your way home.
♪ With a wary heart,
I regard love marks as sins ♪
♪ Fragile like a rose, real or fake? ♪
I'm really leaving now.
♪ If we are of the same kind,
we lick away each other's sorrow ♪
Bye-bye.
♪ What won't let go, kisses or tears? ♪
[Stellaris Games]
Lu Junxi,
how could you make
such a basic setting error?
Originally,
5,000 A-level players had to pay
to draw characters.
Because of your error,
50,000 users
have now gotten them for free!
Do you know how much money
the company lost?
It was clearly Leo who messed up,
yet he's blaming Junxi.
Junxi's just an intern.
[Stellaris]
Exactly.
He messed up and then called in sick
at the last minute.
He's always like this,
disappearing whenever he messes up
and letting the rookies take the fall.
College students these days...
unbelievable.
You'd better reflect on what you've done!
You three,
continue discussing the development
of the Dream Home mobile game.
Okay.
Suddenly, school feels so much better.
At least you get the grade you deserve,
and at the end of the semester, you can
complain through teacher evaluations.
The workplace is so dark.
We have to take the blame
and can't even say anything.
We're just here for an internship,
but it feels like we've been caught
in a palace power struggle.
A "palace power struggle"?
That's way over the top.
Tuo is lucky—
interning with a handsome architect
and everything's going so smoothly.
That day when you came to my place
for dinner,
what did you and Tuo talk about?
It wasn't about the internship, was it?
Well...
Do you know what the meeting is about?
No idea. It was so sudden.
Everyone's here, right?
We've just landed the design project
for three business hotels
from Yunlong Group.
Really?
That's amazing!
Han Tuo,
you'll help me with this.
[Z. W. S Architecture]
Me?
Yeah,
get ready for deadline hell.
[Z. W. S Architecture]
I want to design hotels too.
Do your best.
Good luck
with
the big project case.
Thank you.
[Z. W. S Architecture]
Is that your way of
thanking me for choosing you?
Don't thank me too soon.
Working with me is tough.
I'm just an intern.
[Dining Area]
Why did you pick me?
What do you think is the connection
between designing
a private home and designing a hotel?
[Dining Area]
Buildings are designed for the people
who use them.
Whatever type of building you design,
it should always start with empathy.
And?
A hotel should create
a sense of belonging like home,
where people can rest comfortably,
but...
it's not actually home.
We must consider practical functionality
and maintenance costs.
That's exactly why I chose you.
[Dining Area]
Perfect answer.
Your coffee, not so much.
Isn't it because you added
too much flavor powder?
I'm giving you a one-star review.
Let me do it.
I'll show you how.
[Stellaris Games Screw-up]
I'll be on a work trip soon
to do test stays at hotels.
Yunlong Group is a leading brand
of five-star hotels.
Everyone wants to join this project team.
I never thought he would choose me.
That's great.
Your internship is going so smoothly,
unlike mine.
Why are you so quiet?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just a bit tired.
[Dream Home]
[Happy Together,
Living in Your Dream World]
Then, we'll live together in the future.
Okay.
Let's move in together.
Move in together?
[Stellaris]
Lu Junxi.
What did you even learn in school?
Stop staring!
Just fix it already!
[Challenge begins]
[You can do it]
[Hotel Leisure]
Thank you
for coming to our business hotel today.
We've all been looking forward to
your arrival.
Not at all.
We'll be in your care.
Okay, thank you.
Please, this way.
Let me show you around.
That's about it.
Time to eat.
Come on, let's grab something to eat.
Okay.
[The design of this open-air courtyard
is ingenious. Wish you were here too.]
[Stellaris]
You're not waiting for a reply
from your boyfriend, are you?
I knew it that night
when I drove you home.
I have a good eye for these things.
Being too clingy will scare him away.
We're good.
We've known each other for 10 years.
The foundation of a relationship isn't
about how long you've known each other.
Don't try to build a skyscraper
without a solid foundation.
Be careful—
if an earthquake strikes someday,
the whole building could collapse.
Our foundation is
deep and solid.
Kid,
when it comes to relationships,
you're still a rookie.
I'm going to take a shower first.
[The design of this open-air courtyard
is ingenious. Wish you were here too.]
[About to test the bed now.
If it's comfy, I'll bring you next time.]
[Digital Classroom,
Department of Architecture]
Excuse me!
Have you seen Han Tuo?
Han Tuo had to take last-minute leave
for his internship today.
Okay, thank you.
[Digital Classroom,
Department of Architecture]
[Didn't you say you'd come to school?]
Sorry,
the boss suddenly said that we have to
go to Tainan for a field visit.
I didn't have time to tell you.
Junxi!
Junxi.
What's wrong?
I just realized
that Tuo has always been by my side
since we were little.
Now that he's busy with his internship
and not glued to you, you notice, huh?
Wait until you get busy yourself—
then you'll understand
how hard and precious it is
for two people to be together.
[When are you coming back?]
[Just got home]
Why is your hair so wet?
Just had a shower?
I finally get to see you!
You missed me that much?
I miss you terribly.
♪ I just wanna be your good boy ♪
♪ True love knows no hesitation, I love
how you look lost while waiting for me ♪
♪ Wanna be your good boy,
close your eyes and hold me tight ♪
♪ 'Cause I know
I'm the one protecting you ♪
♪ Stop, we can make it, yeah ♪
♪ Just love me, don't be afraid ♪
♪ Hey, stop, love isn't complicated ♪
♪ Tonight, let's go home together ♪
Let's move in together.
What's wrong?
You don't want to
move in together anymore?
I do.
But if we move in together,
you won't be by your parents' side.
It's not like I'll never go home.
And these few days without you,
I've missed you so much.
Let me help you.
It's okay.
I can manage.
You continue with yours.
What?
Why do you keep staring at me?
I still can't believe
that we're living together so soon.
I can't believe
we found a home we love so quickly either.
Even though it's not a two-story villa,
and we don't have a dog yet...
We'll work hard together to earn money,
buy a piece of land,
and build the house you design.
Wherever you are
is my whole world.
Now, I'm your boyfriend
and also your family.
You've long been my family.
Daddy!
[In the Next Episode]
A kid?
Who did Junxi have the kid with?
Kiss.
No kissing.
He's mine.
Mine.
Mine!
He's mine!
You little brat.
He's mine.
So you two
have that kind of relationship?
[You and Tuo are dating, right?]
My brother hasn't found out
about us, has he?