So, he’ll be in New York too?
Kalix and I will meet there.
By the way, I’ve already introduced him to Dad.
Wow! I never realized you were that serious.
Of course, this is for long-term.
They want me to become a doctor.
Especially my mom.
We made a deal, and I have to keep my grades up
and be on the dean's list every single semester.
Or else she will send me to med school.
That's hard.
Or maybe you’re neglecting your studies
because you’re so busy flirting with her.
No offense, dear, okay?
I just think that Kalix had better grades last year
when he was with his ex-girlfriend, Amethyst.
I’m sorry, girls.
I was too defensive last time.
I know that you’re all just concerned about me.
- Hello, Aunty? - Why? What happened?
Ke was rushed to the hospital. Come on!
Let’s go!
Your daughter was rushed to the E.R.
She was in and out of consciousness
we identified that there's head trauma that caused her concussion.
There was also bruising on her upper arm and abdomen.
The nature of these injuries are suggestive of physical abuse.
According to the nurse on duty,
Mr. Julian Miguel Villaflor brought the patient in
but he immediately left after filling out the forms.
The nurses tried to stop him from leaving but they couldn't do anything.
Based on the test results,
Kierra is clear of any internal bleeding.
Her physical injuries will heal with proper medical care.
Thank you, doc.
Thank you so much for taking care of Kierra.
We noticed since last night that
she was in a daze,
had no appetite and wasn’t talking to anyone.
I already referred the patient to Dr. Liza De Vera in Psychiatry
and she will come in tomorrow to evaluate Kierra.
Thank you, doc.
I suggest to extend her stay here in the hospital
so we can monitor her vitals.
Doc…
We’re gonna need your help in making a medical legal statement,
when we file our complaint.
I want justice for my daughter.
Please.
Of course, ma’am.
I’ll try to help as much as I can.
- Excuse me. - Thank you.
This is all my fault.
I shouldn’t have let Kierra stay in the condo.
If she was living with me at home, I could have made sure that she was okay.
Aunty…
I’m sorry.
I’m so sorry for not being able to protect Ke.
- I’m sorry, I’m so sorry. - It’s okay. It’s okay.
My dear, don’t blame yourself. Luna, don’t blame yourself.
Sis, please don’t blame yourself, too. No one’s at fault.
Our next course of action is to find whoever did this to her
and definitely make him pay for whatever he did.
I’m so sorry, Aunty.
Ke…
You gotta eat, Ke, even just a little bit.
You won’t get better if you don’t.
What about some water, Ke?
Please? The IV won’t be enough for you to get better.
Ke.
You’re safe here, Ke.
We won’t let that asshole near you again.
And I swear to god if I see him, I’m gonna punch him in the face.
She’s right.
Your parents even went to the Women's Desk to file a complaint.
Miguel has been issued a subpoena.
He’ll be thrown to jail.
Ke, I already have your medical certificate.
It’s all good.
Don't worry, finals are almost done anyway.
Just focus on getting better.
How about a tiny bite, Ke?
Ke.
Okay,
rest for now and sleep. We’ll just be outside.
Ke,
we’re here for you.
We love you, Kierra.
Hey,
why did we have to go out?
How’s Ke?
Asleep. She’s fine.
Look at this.
“Fit for class?”
What the hell is this bullshit?
Why does this say that Kierra’s all better now?
Right? Isn’t it so frustrating?
They keep saying that Kierra is all better now and can be discharged.
That she’s just experiencing occasional mood swings
and loss of appetite.
What the fuck?
Kierra hasn’t even eaten since!
I bet Miguel’s family threatened this hospital.
I mean, it’s obvious that she’s not mentally well.
What about her therapy,
how was it? Any update? Has it even started yet?
She might not be ready to tell her side of the story.
I don’t know what to do.
Aunty’s even getting sick because of all the worry.
This is all my fault.
Luna…
There you go again.
You’re blaming yourself again.
It's not your fault, Luna.
We live in the same condo, Via.
How come I didn't notice that something's going on with her?
I’ve been too selfish this whole time.
This is all my fault.
If only I asked her how she was, this wouldn’t have happened.
Luna, don’t carry the burden by yourself.
I always talk to Kierra and yet I didn’t notice anything.
She’s right, Luna.
We’re all at fault.
While her parents are busy with the case,
let’s take turns in taking care of Kierra.
If only I was there for Kierra, nothing like this would happen.
Luna…
Don’t blame yourself, it’s not your fault.
We’re all in this together.
Reminder, class–
your plates will be submitted by the end of the week.
And that will be considered as your final exam.
So for anyone who wants to be in the dean’s list,
this is your make or break project.
So please, take it seriously.
I hope you’ve all started it
because I won’t accept any late submissions.
All right? Well, I guess that will be all.
Class dismissed.
- Ma’am? - Yes, Ms. Valeria?
About Kierra Ynares,
she’s still in the hospital.
Would you extend the deadline for her?
Well, I received her medical certificate
and it’s stated clearly that she’s already fit for class.
I see no reason for her not to submit her plates on time with the deadline I gave.
And that would be unfair for other students.
But she’s not mentally well, ma’am.
If that’s the case,
then you need to present a medical certificate from a psychiatrist.
It should come from them.
I’m sorry, Ms. Valeria.
No medical certificate,
no extension for deadlines.
Excuse me.
Luna!
We’re groupmates for the tropical design project.
We have a meeting tomorrow for our finals.
You weren’t responding in our online group chat,
just letting you know.
Sorry, I haven’t been checking my socials. What time would it be?
9 AM, since that’s the only time our other groupmates are available.
Okay, thanks.
You better be there.
All right.
You can do this, Luna.
Hey, Luna.
How are you?
I miss you. We haven’t seen each other in a week.
I miss you, too, Kalix.
I’m sorry I’ve been so busy this week
and with exams, too.
I also had to finish Ke’s plates.
Hey, there’s nothing to be sorry about.
Did you get any sleep last night?
Not really. About four hours, maybe.
Get some sleep tonight. Okay?
Have you eaten dinner yet?
I can bring you food.
No need, I’m fine.
I just have a lot to do.
Besides, aren’t you supposed to be busy with your finals?
You should focus on that.
Okay. I understand.
But you know I can always make time for you.
Right?
I know.
Just let me know how I can help.
How’s Kierra? How’s her therapy?
She still hasn’t been responding to her therapist.
She hasn’t even spoken with any of us.
She just sleeps all the time.
I can ask my parents for a good psychiatrist for her if you want?
It’s okay.
Sam recommended one already.
Maybe, I just need to keep convincing Kierra.
I really hope she gets better soon.
Look, I’m not gonna hold you up anymore.
Just please, don’t forget to eat and sleep.
Okay?
I love you.
Ke would like this. Thank you.
I’m glad to help in any way I can.
Did you get any sleep last night?
You look tired.
About two hours.
Luna,
that’s just a nap.
You should get proper sleep tonight.
I’m worried about you.
I’ll rest once finals are over.
What about you? Don’t you have an exam tomorrow?
You should go home early.
It’s okay, I’ll...
I’ll just stay here and make sure you sleep.
My exam tomorrow is just a minor subject.
Aunty? Mommy?
What happened, is anything wrong?
We just came from the City Prosecutor’s office
and the camp of Miguel just submitted their counter-affidavit.
They have controverting evidence that proves Miguel was at a party that night.
They even have witnesses,
photos,
and even videos.
Our lawyers said that the prosecutor is highly likely to dismiss our complaint
since we lack probable cause.
How could we lack probable cause?
Isn’t the camera footage from the emergency room enough?
They said that the cameras were all under maintenance that night.
But Ke is the actual victim and also the witness.
I know, we can’t deny the fact that Kierra was abused that night.
But our evidence is not enough to prove that it was Miguel who did it. And–
they’re saying that these are all just lies made up by my daughter.
That bastard!
Mommy, we can’t let this happen.
He needs to go to jail!
I know. I know, Luna.
But we’re fighting with big dogs.
They have a lot of connections.
So I’ll make sure we’ll bring this to court. I promise you.
Ke!
Here’s your favorite pasta.
Kalix bought this for you.
Well?
Where’s the food-loving person that I know?
Ke.
The outside world misses you.
Get well soon.
Our school term is almost done, too.
You said you wanted to go to Tali beach.
Let’s go?
Ke?
Sam recommended a new therapist.
Therapist for victims of abuse.
You might consider it.
No pressure.
Ke?
I know it’s hard.
Take it one step at a time, okay?
We miss you.
Don’t forget that we all love you.
Luna, it’s 9 PM. We haven’t eaten dinner yet.
You’re hungry? There’s food in the fridge, just heat it up.
You haven’t eaten yet.
I’m not hungry. I’m fine.
Luna…
You don’t have to pretend that everything is fine in front of me.
If you need to cry, you can cry on my shoulder.
I can’t cry now. I have a lot to do.
I’m here.
I can help.
I want to help.
Kalix.
You need to study for your exam.
I’m okay, you don’t have to worry.
Hold on, I’ll get it.
Via?
Luna, can we talk?
What’s up with your late submissions?
Are you planning to fail your major subjects, Luna?
I just forgot about the deadline.
Why didn’t you take the final exam of 1123?
Did you forget about it, too?
My midterm grades were pretty high.
I'll still pass.
How about the project for tropical design?
Are you sure you’ll pass?
You didn’t even show up for the meeting.
Shit! I forgot.
Yes. Your groupmates told me that you were MIA.
You might not be on the Dean's List this semester.
It’s just an award.
Do you hear yourself right now, Luna?
Seriously?
You think Kierra would be happy with everything you’ve been doing?
Luna, Kierra can catch up.
And if she can’t?
- What if she fails this year? - There’s still summer classes.
She can attend summer classes. Kierra will catch up. We’ll find a way.
So don’t do this.
You have to get a hold of yourself.
Email this to me.
I’ll finish Kierra’s essay.
Take care of yourself, please?
- But– - Luna.
Listen to Via.
You need to rest.
I know you’re disappointed.
I know I can catch up.
I’m still a sophomore
so I’ll still be able to graduate with honors.
Besides, I’m not worried about my grades now.
There are many other things that are more important.
You don’t sound like yourself anymore.
How do I sound like?
You’re an achiever, Luna.
You value your work and put so much passion in it.
But right now, you look like you’re just surviving.
At least I’m surviving, Kalix.
I am so tired.
I feel so lost.
I don’t know what to do anymore.
I can’t just leave Kierra alone.
Even if everyone says that I’m not at fault,
I still think that it is.
I feel so worthless
for not being able to see what was going on.
I’m her family.
I should have been the first to notice.
Me.
But I did nothing, I know nothing.
I feel so guilty, Kalix.
Especially now that the case isn’t going well.
I’m so sorry you’re going through all of this.
You’re carrying all of this by yourself.
And it must have been really hard for you.
Luna, please, let me help.
That’s what I’m here for.
We’re in this together.
Okay?
Everything will be all right.
Justice will be served, Luna.
I’ll make sure of that.
Thank you.
I feel so overwhelmed.
And your presence is the only thing that comforts me.
I’ll be your safe haven.
Should I sleep here tonight?
You don’t have to.
I know you still have a lot to do.
Don’t worry about that.
I don’t want you to be alone tonight.
I’ll stay here. Okay?
Amy: I miss your lips. Kiss me again.
Amy: I am so drunk Kalix.
Amy: Why didn’t you take the finals today?
Amy: Is it because you met up with Luna? I thought you weren’t going to be serious?
Amy: Did you tell her about us? Call me.
Amy: I miss you. Kiss me again.
Amy: Baby, I miss this.
Luna?
Happy Valentine’s Day!
Happy Valentine’s!
What’s wrong?
No-nothing.
L-Let’s sit.
You had a drink?
Who were you with? Where have you been?
Just a little.
We had a free cut.
Were you with Adonis and Amethyst?
Yes.
Okay.
I love you.
I love you too, Luna.
Always remember that.
I will.
You’ve been quiet.
What’s up?
I’m okay.
Thanks for coming, by the way.
I know you’re busy.
Of course.
You looked like you were about to cry.
Are you really okay?
What’s wrong, Luna?
Sir, I’m very sorry. We really can’t allow it.
I have to talk to her. No, you don’t understand. I have to see her.
Sir, she’s very unstable.
What are you doing here?
- Well?! - I didn’t do anything here.
- Acting all innocent? - I didn’t do anything here.
- You didn’t do anything?! - I didn’t do anything!
- I didn’t do anything! - Stop acting innocent!
- How could you hurt Kierra?! - I just have to see her.
- I didn’t hurt her! - How dare you even show yourself!
Let go of me!
You are a terrible person!
What the fuck, you can’t accuse me of anything!
- You coward! You’re such a coward, Miguel! - You cannot! You have no proof!
- Oh, I’ll sue you, I’ll sue the both of you! - Really? You gonna run to your daddy again?
You bastard!
- Let go of her! - You get her, man!
- And you! - Fucking get her! Go!
I know you were paid to keep quiet!
Have you no shame, how could you?
- Shut her up! - Let go of me!
- Shut her up! - I said, let me go!
She’s too loud!
- Let me go! - Do your fucking job!
Get off her.
Let’s go, Sevi.
Luna!
Luna, wait!
Let’s talk! Luna!
This isn’t right, Sevi. Aunty needs to know about this.
- We have to report this. - Luna!
Luna, please!
- Luna, Kalix is… - I don’t want to see him.
- Don’t leave me with him. - Luna, please, wait!
You fucking cheater!
Please let me explain!
For what?
So you can do it again?
Kalix, it’s so obvious in the video that you were kissing Amethyst.
You piece of shit!
- You– - You cheater!
You don’t understand, please hear me out!
Fuck you!
I don’t think you understand.
How long have you been cheating?
How long has it been?
This happened on Valentine’s day?
You kissed her
and then met up with me that night
like nothing happened?
You made me look like an idiot.
You’re such a jerk, Kalix! You fucking jerk!
- Don’t touch me! - I could never do that!
I can never do that.
You already did!
You know my past, Kalix.
You know how much I hate cheaters.
You know my past, Kalix!
You said I can be vulnerable in front of you
and I did but you still chose to hurt me.
You fucking son of a bitch.
You're such a jerk.
Don’t, don’t!
- I love you so much, Luna. - No!
Please.
Kalix…
I love you, Luna.
Fuck, Kalix.
I love you so much.
So much.
Luna!
Luna, I’ve been waiting here all day.
Just give me five minutes.
Let me take you home.
Stop this, Kalix.
Isn’t it obvious? I don’t want to talk to you.
I won’t stop even if I have to wait for you here everyday.
This won’t stop me.
Focus on your exams.
‘Cause we’re over.
We’re done.
What do you mean we’re done?
Please, let’s talk about this.
Luna, please!
Are you okay?
I have something to tell you, Luna.
What?
I’m ready to get therapy.
Just remember to stay strong.
I love you, Ke.
Fucking stop this, Luna.
Hello?
Sorry for bothering you.
It's just I’m breaking a promise.
What?
I’m losing it, Luna.
What do you mean?
Have a good night.
I love you.
Hello, Adi?
Are you with Kalix right now?
Where are you guys?
What happened, why won’t he go home?
Luna…
I have something very important to say.
Did Kalix say anything?
Wait, hold on. You still don’t know?
We didn’t talk the whole week.
Well,
Kalix failed the semester.
Failed?
He’s not moving up a year?
Look, Luna,
it’s not your fault.
It’s Kalix’s fault
and we’re not guilt tripping you.
He just didn’t want to tell you but
I think you should really know.
We can still do something about it, right?
Yes, if Kalix would just focus
and stop ditching exams just so he can go to you.
Bro.
I need to go.
Please, bring him home.
I don’t want to meddle, Luna,
but I think you both need space.
This isn’t healthy anymore.
I had no idea...
that we would end like this.
That we would ruin each other.
I can’t bear to see him anymore, Sevi.
You know,
I feel bad with everything
that’s going on with him.
But it’s so unfair.
I feel guilty even though he’s the one who cheated.
I don’t know, Sevi.
Luna, you don’t have to force yourself if you’re not ready.
You need time to understand everything that’s happening right now.
So that when you both finally meet,
you’ll be able to talk without any grudge.
For now, you gotta sleep.
It’s 3 AM already.
Ke told me to stay in her room,
so remember that I’m just here when you need me.
Thank you.
You’re such a good friend.
Of course.
I’m just here.
Sevi?
Sevi, are you up?
Luna, can we talk? Please?
What are you doing here, Kalix?
Please, Luna, let’s work this out.
I wasn’t able to sleep last night.
Because I felt so bad.
I wanna break up.
I don’t.
I’m not asking for your permission.
Our relationship works with us two,
you can’t just decide on your own.
Our relationship ended when you started kissing another woman.
You asshole!
How dare you even think that I need your permission to break up.
You’re so harsh, Luna.
You don’t even give me the chance to explain.
For what?
Just to listen to your excuses?
That I just misinterpreted that video of you and Amethyst?
You were never completely honest with me about Amethyst.
I'm sorry.
I’m sorry, but I can’t trust you anymore.
You said you trusted me.
You broke my trust, Kalix.
So, I’m done.
Let’s just break up
because this isn’t healthy anymore.
You failed this semester because of me, right?
It’s just a semester, Luna.
It’s not just a semester, Kalix, it’s your dream!
You know what’s annoying?
That I’m feeling guilty
because I know that it’s my fault you failed.
I've been telling you–
don't lose your dream for me, Kalix.
You are the dream, Luna.
But you chose to hurt me.
You chose to hurt me, Kalix.
Enough.
I’m done.
I’m tired of all this.
Please, just go.
No, Luna, please.
Please don’t leave me.
I need you.
Don’t do this to me, please.
Please?
I'm not in love with you anymore.
That’s bullshit.
Luna?
During the times I was so down with what you did to me,
Sevi has always been by my side.
Luna, I–
You think I’d still be hung up on you?
That I’d stay loyal to you?
After what you did?
I don’t love you anymore, Kalix.
Kalix, we’re done.
I don’t think I can trust you again.
So please, just go.
Let me go.
I love you so damn much.
I could never cheat on you.
Kalix: Be happy. Take yourself to the moon. I will love you until then.
Here's a package for you, attorney.
It's from Valeria Construction.
Return those to Architect Luna Valeria.
I would rather have you repay me
through your professional service, Architect Valeria.
Can I ask you a personal question?
Depends on the question.
Did you represent Miguel Villaflor in court?
Who said I did?
Some rumors.
This contract is flawless, I can’t find any loopholes.
Duh, your client is a lawyer.
Sevi,
will you be my engineer for Kalix’s house project in Tagaytay?
Wait a minute.
You’ll accept the project?WEBVTT
You’ll accept the project?