Mom!
Who's Atsara?
She's your real mother. She passed away.
Holy shit!
This is the song that made Sun fall asleep
and wake up as Solar.
- Huh?
- Are you sure
you want to donate all this stuff?
I'll just keep these.
Solar, we found the song
that makes Sun fall asleep.
After countless failures and mistakes,
we've finally found the solution.
Little lion, we're finally together.
Were you lonely being home alone?
Don't worry about being alone anymore.
I'll introduce you to my cool friends.
And when you're home,
Uncle Pobmek will stay with you.
He looks so funny.
He looks just like a kidnapper.
Oh, hey, Uncle!
You're up.
This is the uncle who looks like a kidnapper.
We went to my house yesterday.
I threw paint balloons
with Teacher Pranee too.
Look, Uncle is such a show-off.
It's still early, and he already
wants to show off playing the guitar.
Hey, don't you like this song?
I can play the whole song now, you know?
Really?
We want to hear it.
Good morning, Teacher.
Good morning, boyfriend.
Sun must love this little lion so much.
Since he got him,
he wouldn't let go of his hand.
Yeah.
He probably misses Mom.
Are you okay?
Of course.
I'm so glad you're strong.
Your strength encourages me.
Really?
Then come and get your encouragement.
What's with all this?
We'll see each other every day.
Even if we see each other every day,
I'll still...
Do this.
Until you get tired of me.
I'll never get tired of you.
Now it's my turn to encourage you.
Now that everything has settled down,
we finally get to be together again.
I'm ticklish!
I don't want this time of happiness to end.
Alright, everyone.
Let's say it together.
Eggs!
Caterpillar!
Pupa!
Butterfly!
Ready to go?
Yeah.
Are we missing anyone today?
We're missing Sun.
Why hasn't he come to school lately?
We want to see Sun.
Yeah, when is he coming?
- I want to see him too.
- I miss Sun already.
Yeah, I want to play with Sun.
Alright.
Take it easy.
I'll tell Little Sun
that his friends miss him, okay?
Okay!
Yes!
We'll finally get to see Sun!
[Sukhum Udom Rak School]
Hey! Sun's here!
Yay!
Sun, where have you been?
Were you sick?
No.
Uncle Pobmek has just been
playing the guitar for me,
so I've been lying back and relaxing at home.
Oh, I'm so jealous!
Teacher Pobmek,
can you play it at school again?
If I get the chance,
I'll play it for you, okay?
The crepe lady is here today.
Sun, want to come get some crepes with us?
Here.
Thank you, Uncle.
Come on, let's go.
Make it quick, then go to class.
Be careful crossing the road.
Okay.
It's actually nice to let Sun
come to school on some days.
Yeah.
I guess we have to take things slow,
like we discussed.
Shit! There's a special meeting today.
A special meeting? About what?
The talent show!
That's happening tomorrow.
Is this a school or an activity center?
There's an event here every month.
Sun, why didn't you get crepes
with your friends?
I changed my mind.
I want to save money for toys instead.
I'm late!
Make way, kids!
We have a meeting before homeroom.
Why aren't you there yet?
You're right.
Thanks for reminding us.
I'm going.
So?
Well...
You're the last one to show up.
Hey!
Wait for me!
I was the one who reminded you!
The annual talent show is tomorrow!
We'll have a run-through this afternoon
for the kids to rehearse on stage.
Teacher Pobmek, please run the stage
instead of Teacher Solar.
Okay.
And Teacher Jee,
you'll help him out like last time.
Please keep it balanced.
No need to be too perfect.
If I try to make things too perfect,
I'll let Teacher Pobmek deal with me.
If Teacher Jee gets too fussy
or the OCD kicks in,
I'll start counting for him to hear.
What's Teacher Pobmek talking about?
One, two, three, eight!
Hey!
Don't skip numbers like that!
In sync from the start, huh?
But do we really need two people
to run the stage?
Right? It's just supervising the kids.
It's not like we're performing ourselves.
Nothing will probably happen.
[Talent Stage]
Are your drumsticks broken?
Can you use your hands for now?
Line up.
Okay.
Line up first.
Here.
Can you use these instead?
No, right?
I found the drumsticks.
Teachers! Nobel broke my wing!
- I didn't.
- That's not true.
- It's true.
- Not true!
- It's true!
- You're lying.
- Teachers, he must be punished!
Narak.
I got you new wings!
No, I don't want them!
Hey, try them on.
You can fly with these. See?
Narak!
Here you go.
Thank you.
Done.
Bye-bye!
- Bye-bye!
So much for "nothing will probably happen".
That was way more than nothing.
I forgot the kids at this school
are something else.
Can I perform too?
Hey, Little Sun.
You want to be on stage too?
What are you going to perform?
With this little lion?
Huh? You're performing too, Sun?
Let's watch his rehearsal
from in front of the stage.
- Yeah.
- Hold on.
Sun's not performing tomorrow.
Oh? Why not?
I know.
It's because Sun came to school today.
Tomorrow, Teacher Solar will come instead.
Am I right?
Aurora is right.
Can I perform today, then?
Fine.
Go ahead.
Yay!
Next up is the special performance
by Grade 2 Class 1.
Let's give it up for Little Sun!
Why do you look so sad, Sun?
I'm lonely, Solar.
No one's really home much.
I don't know where everyone went.
When no one's around,
I'm not happy at all.
But you have me.
Even if it's just the two of us,
I can take you out.
Really?
How are you taking me?
Alright, everyone.
Close your eyes.
I'm taking you to the beach.
Have you ever seen one?
Imagine this.
In front of you is the blue sea,
a cream-colored beach,
and white clouds.
The waves go whoosh, whoosh.
Your feet are dipped in the water.
How does it feel? Cold, right?
The sea, the sand, and the clouds
have something to tell you.
Can we be your friends?
Yeah.
Of course.
That's great.
From now on,
you won't be lonely anymore, Sun.
Got it?
Got it.
Thank you so much, Solar.
Alright, everyone.
Open your eyes.
I have to go.
Bye-bye.
Alright.
Thank you.
Is something wrong?
Yes.
My mom called to complain
about the home renovation contractor.
I'm so worried
she'll run into a scammer one day.
This lunch box of Teacher Solar's is so cute.
- What?
- So cute.
What?
Playing with Sun's stuff like this
could get you scolded.
No, I won't.
Oh, I have something to show you.
Sun came up with this himself, you know?
Isn't that cool?
Yeah, Sun looks happy.
Nom.
Where's my dessert?
That's my dessert.
You're late! You're late! You're late!
How am I late every single day?
You're not late.
I set the alarm early.
It's show day.
- We need to hurry up.
- Okay.
I'll go get the car
and wait for you in front of the lobby.
Yeah.
What did you forget this time?
I didn't forget.
Go! Go now!
Hurry!
We don't want to be late.
This way, please.
The front row is almost full.
Wow.
They all showed up in full force.
Teacher Pobmek, Teacher Jee, are you ready?
I've been ready since yesterday.
Then let's do this!
[Talent Stage]
Welcome, all parents and lovely kids!
Are you ready for the talent show?
Yes!
If you're ready,
please enjoy the performance by
our talented kids!
I'm so sick of homework!
Wow.
The reference is so clear.
This is just like in the movie.
Teacher Pobmek, what's going on?
♫ Bells on bobtails ring ♫
♫ Making spirits bright ♫
♫ What fun it is to ride and sing
a sleighing song tonight ♫
♫ Oh! Jingle bells, jingle bells ♫
♫ Jingle all the way ♫
♫ Oh, what fun it is to ride ♫
♫ In a one-horse open sleigh ♫
Four, King, what's wrong?
Isn't it almost your turn?
It's Four.
He won't go on stage
because his dad didn't show up.
He really promised he'd come!
Maybe your dad had something urgent come up.
Let's perform for your friends instead.
Is that okay?
Four and King from Grade 2 Class 1,
please stand by next to the stage.
It's almost time.
Are you really not going to perform?
Teacher Solar,
does my dad not love me?
Don't think like that.
I'm sure that's not true.
But why did he leave me like this?
How about this?
I'll ask Principal Sodchuen
to take a video of you for your dad.
It'll be just like he's here
watching you in person.
Is that okay?
Come on, let's do it.
Let's do it!
What happened?
Nothing.
We can't miss this performance.
Come on.
More! More!
Great job!
Follow me.
Wow.
Aren't you a Sigma boy?
You're the kids' favorite now, aren't you?
I don't know if I'm the kids' favorite.
But Teacher Solar's favorite...
Uncle jokes, as always.
Anyway, thank you for
always being by my side.
Without you,
I don't know if the kids
would've agreed to go on stage.
Where's my reward?
Pobmek!
I need your help!
Looks like the kids forgot something again.
What?
Is there anything they won't forget?
Come on, I'll help you.
Hey, it's okay.
Just go down and watch the kids' performance.
Yeah, yeah. I was busy taking videos
that I forgot to watch the kids.
Come with me, Solar.
- Let's go.
- Go.
Right here?
Alright.
Last but not least,
please enjoy the special performance
by Teacher Pobmek!
I'd like to dedicate this performance
to everyone.
Especially to the one
who's always been by my side.
♫ Every second, I will spend on you ♫
♫ However much time passes through ♫
♫ And when the rain falls,
know I'm here next to you ♫
♫ We'll make it together,
and that alone will do ♫
♫ I believe that
love is a matter of the heart ♫
♫ There is no rule that says
that we must stay apart ♫
♫ And though love may bring a tear or two ♫
♫ But I'll surrender to love if it is you ♫
♫ Let our story be written in our hearts ♫
♫ 'Cause this love is meant just for us ♫
♫ I will never let your hand go ♫
♫ I will paint
and fill the storyline with you ♫
♫ No matter if the sky turns dark and blue ♫
♫ I will remain right here
beside you, always ♫
Dad!
♫ Always ♫
Let's give another round of applause
for Teacher Pobmek and Teacher Solar!
Teacher Pobmek!
Teacher Solar!
Teacher Solar! Teacher Pobmek!
Solar.
To Ms. Pranee, please take care of him.
I can't do this anymore. - Sarun]
Solar.
Uncle, why am I here?
Sun?
Teacher Solar!
Sun!
Having you is the reason I lost everything!
Teacher Solar, does my dad not love me?
Why did he leave me like this?
Teacher Solar! Teacher Solar!
- Teacher Solar! Teacher Solar!
- Sun.
Sun.
Uncle's here.
You don't need to be scared anymore.
Just breathe slowly.
Uncle,
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I'm so scared.
It's okay, Sun.
I'm right here.
It's okay.
That sounds like a panic attack.
I've heard about it.
The symptoms are just like
what you described.
Usually,
it's caused by built-up stress.
Solar has probably been
trying to suppress it,
and didn't want us to know.
How did things go at the event?
Forget about that.
You don't need to worry.
No one's blaming you at all.
But how are you?
Are you okay?
I...
I don't know what happened.
I thought Solar was about to recover...
because he really seemed better.
But I don't know why...
I don't know why
everything's gotten this much worse.
Suddenly, Solar turned into Sun,
even though he didn't fall asleep.
Is what I'm doing wrong?
I don't want to say this.
I'm so damn tired.
I'm exhausted from taking care of Solar
the way he is now.
Now that I've said it out loud,
I feel even more guilty.
I feel guilty
that I think this way about him.
Pobmek.
What you're feeling... isn't wrong at all.
It's understandable.
Taking care of someone who's unwell
is exhausting.
But so far,
you've done a really great job.
If it's too much, it's too much.
If you're tired, you're tired.
There's nothing to feel guilty about.
You've done really well already, Pobmek.
It's okay.
Why are you such a crybaby
when you're so amazing?
Come here.
You're up?
How are you feeling?
I...
I caused trouble again, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
For telling you I was fine.
I didn't tell you...
that actually,
I wasn't okay.
In my mind...
I wanted to be strong.
I wanted to be okay.
To be okay for you,
so you wouldn't have to be tired
because of me anymore.
But in the end,
I couldn't do it.
It's totally okay.
It's okay if you're not strong.
It's okay if you can't do it.
I have something to show you.
There's one more thing I haven't told you.
I just found a letter your father sent me
after he asked me to take care of you.
It's the first and only letter he ever sent.
Mom.
Can you send me that letter?
[To Ms. Pranee,
please take care of him for me.]
[I can't do this anymore.
- Sarun]
I think...
my father left me
because he couldn't stand seeing the face
of the person who caused his wife's passing.
Solar.
Don't interpret things
in a way that hurts yourself.
I don't want to think like that,
but what else can I think?
Trust me.
You shouldn't think like that.
There were a lot of parents' cars today,
so I parked my car across the street.
Wait here.
I'll bring the car around and pick you up.
Pobmek.
I need your help with something.
Since the accident,
I haven't dared to cross the road again.
It's like I've been trying to run away
from my problems all this time.
I can feel that Little Sun feels it too.
So...
I...
Pobmek.
I'm not going to run away
from my problems anymore.
I'm going to see my father.
Come with me?
Ready?
No matter what happens,
I'll always be by your side.
Sun?
He switches to Sun
without falling asleep again?
Dad.
- Dad!
- Hey.
I remember everything now, Dad.
Without you, I don't know how I'd live.
Thank you so much.