Well, it means we have an opportunity.
An opportunity for what?
An opportunity
to pull off the robbery tonight.
You can't be serious.
Have you seen what's inside?
There's barbed wire,
jamming systems, bulls…
This is not the heist in Paris.
The man shot Bruce
just for setting foot inside the estate.
He and Keila are lucky to be alive!
You're right about that. Paris is Paris.
This here is Spain, corrupt and malignant.
Precisely why we need to be prepared.
Catch, Damián.
So aside from blasting our way through,
is there any other plan?
We're not blasting our way.
We're gonna walk in
through the front door.
Look. We've acquired
this beautiful set of keys
to open the gates for us.
And in the meantime,
what do you want us to do?
You and Roi… will stay and watch over him.
I mean, he is our guest, right?
First, you need to remove the pellets
from his face and clean him up,
and then tomorrow, maybe we can send
our guest home spick and span.
I'm not a fuckin' nurse.
But I can drive, and I can get you
in and out in no time.
For fuck's sake, I can be more use
to you there than here.
And sorry, but I'm better than Bruce.
Cameron, you're mistaken
if you think this is professional.
I'm doing this for you.
To rekindle the embers of your romance.
You'll see.
I can assure you,
taking care of this vermin will be fun.
One hand on the trigger,
the adrenaline… the fear…
Good enough to invigorate any couple.
Unless, of course, one of you prefers
to be the leader of the pack? Hmm?
Hey. You okay?
I'm not okay. I'm not okay, Bruce.
Because just a few hours ago,
I thought you'd been murdered.
Hey, hey.
It's okay, I'm fine.
All thanks to you.
There you were, racing across
that field like Ayrton Senna.
Huh?
Bruce, before we go back inside again,
I need to tell you something.
For a while now…
I've been having some doubts.
I had…
a moment of weakness with a guy.
It was an accident.
It only happened once,
and it didn't mean anything.
What exactly do you mean, Keila?
A kiss, messing around, or having sex?
What are you talkin' about?
- Yes.
- Yes, what? Keila?
There was physical contact,
sexual intercourse,
but it only happened once.
Today, when that man led you away,
when he pulled out that gun
and threatened you…
I… I started panicking.
Completely paralyzed.
When I understood that I might lose you…
my whole being was filled with a strength.
I realized I was capable
of doing the impossible,
like running over that man.
Bruce, if he'd done anything to you,
I swear I would have fucking killed him.
Bruce…
You are the force that moves me.
I know what I said is painful,
but I had to tell you.
What's done is done.
We're approaching the estate entrance.
Get ready. We're moving in.
The thermal sensors
show no heat signatures.
It's all clear for at least 30 meters.
Kill the lights, Damián.
Electric fence, straight ahead.
Six meters.
No thermal signatures. We're good to go.
The air vent is situated approximately
three kilometers west.
Keep going. Straight ahead.
I'm picking up infrared heat signatures.
- What direction?
- Behind the bushes, on the left.
Roll down the window.
I can't see because of the branches.
I see them. Multiple signatures.
They're following us. Get outta here!
Don't move.
They're just fucking cows, Keila.
Kill the flashlight.
You've scarred my face.
You're gonna pay for that.
You can count on it.
Shut it. Why don't you save
your energy for hunting boar?
Let her fucking go!
Let go of her, you son of a bitch!
Roi!
- Let her go, god damn it!
- Pull the trigger!
Pull the fucking trigger!
Why didn't you shoot?
I'm not gonna shoot him
for pulling your damn hair.
He attacked me for, fuck's sake!
We have to keep him alive.
That's what Berlin asked us to do!
You know what Berlin would've done?
He would've wasted him.
You think you're a big shot,
but you're just his little bitch.
What I am is loyal.
But you have no idea what that word means.
So? You got nothing to say?
That's exactly why you can't work with me.
'Cause deep down, you're ashamed.
You know what? You don't have
the courage to look me in the eye.
I warned you.
And I was completely up front with you.
Are you telling me
I put a gun to your head?
Might as well after all you did.
You crawled on the floor
and begged me for another chance.
Or did you forget?
You fucked with my head.
Messed with my brain.
You wanna know why
you didn't care about anything I said?
'Cause you're just
a fucked-up piece of shit.
You find this funny?
Yeah. Dumb bastard,
you know nothing about women.
It's clear to me she's the alpha dog.
And you're her bitch.
A real pussy, like she said.
- Shut up!
- You can't handle her. A woman like her…
- She needs a real man, like me.
- You better shut your mouth!
A few months, and she despises you.
You got a problem hearing?
I told you to shut your fuckin' mouth!
So now you've decided
to grow a pair of balls?
It's kinda late for that, don't ya think?!
You're a fucking loser.
She's the one who had the last word. Huh?
She left you pissing in the wind.
Go on, show me what you've got! Go on!
We made it.
Let's get to it.
It must be more than 40 meters deep.
I guess the duke's
not gonna roll out the red carpet.
- Good to go.
- We're good to go.
Come on down. All clear.
Bruce! Are you alright?
Are you stuck?
Bruce? Why have you stopped?
How far did you go, sexually?
- Stop, this isn't the right moment.
- Yeah?
And so what? You think it was
the right moment back there?
You're the one who decides what's right?
Keila, are we good?
Where'd you do it? In our bed?
- No, for God's sake, no.
- Did he sleep over?
No, we didn't sleep at all.
Did he make you come?
Bruce, please, stop it.
So he did.
Was he better than me?
- Huh?
- Bruce, Keila.
Get yourselves down here now.
This way.
We're about 600 meters from the cellar.
The laser alarms
could be anywhere on the property.
The tunnel or the cellar.
Both are possible.
And how do we find out where they are?
We need to create
a high-density atmosphere.
A great way is creating lots of smoke.
Keep going. Not far now.
You know what?
You can tell yourself whatever you want.
You can tell yourself
that I forced you to be with me.
But it was love, Cameron.
A love that's still real.
Berlin is right.
We're on a boat,
in the most beautiful city in Spain.
But we waste our time fighting.
If I kissed you right now,
this whole mess would be over
like that.
And afterwards, we'd hold hands.
We'd walk right off this boat.
Then, we'd paint this town red… together.
And we'd hit the bars
in the best parts of Triana.
Noisy, crazy, crowded.
Because of the music,
we'd have to move in close…
You liked it when I'd whisper in your ear.
You enjoyed the way it tickled.
And because you're fearless,
you'd start dancing flamenco.
Everyone would stare at you, hypnotized.
Especially me.
I'd do my best to try to clap along,
but you already know,
I have absolutely no sense of rhythm.
And then we'd end up kissing.
Alone, surrounded by the crowd.
Later, we'd go downtown
and do all the touristy things.
We'd pretend
to be the first to do that stuff.
We'd hit those high-end stores
on the main street.
The ones where aristocrats get suited up.
For a while, we'd pretend to be like them.
And we'd look fucking amazing.
Then we'd take a ride through Seville,
on a horse-drawn carriage,
so everyone could see us.
At the end of the day,
we'd check into a luxury hotel.
And we'd spend the night,
but we wouldn't sleep one minute.
- Cameron…?
- Yeah?
Was what happened
that night really so bad?
So bad that the rest means nothing to you?
It was you.
It was your fault, Roi.
It was you who pushed me off the cliff.
That's why everything blew up.
All you wanted to do is change me.
And save me.
And now I'm even more fucked up.
Don't pretend
like none of this ever happened.
Why not?
This was just a big mistake.
I should never have come to Seville.
Cameron!
Tell Berlin I'm done.
I gotta get outta here.
Cameron, for fuck's sake!
No, fuck you! I won't calm down!
The last stop.
It's the dome we saw with the drone.
Don't move.
Stay where you are.
A fortress of lasers.
And his art collection is inside.
There doesn't seem to be security cameras.
Why would you need cameras
when you already have all this?
These lasers work like
any other ordinary photoelectric cell.
If anything gets in the way
of the light, it sets off an alarm.
Or who knows? Something worse.
What's worse than an alarm?
Considering the personality of the duke,
I imagine something tastefully sadistic,
like a trap door and a pit full of stakes.
Bloodshed.
You're alive. Bloodshed.
Yeah, yeah. "Dead or alive." We get it.
My question is, how can we get in
now that we know he has
the best security system in the world?
Because his sophisticated system
is no longer optimal.
Not for a few years now.
Keila, all yours.
From the information that we gathered,
the mechanism was installed in 2000,
but it has become obsolete.
A few years ago,
they discovered a bug in the program.
To explain it, I made a short video.
The laser alarm allows
for a two-degree variation in oscillation.
We will use the allowance
to trick the system.
Yeah, but how do we do that?
We're going to replace
one of the lasers with our own.
One with the same power,
frequency, and caliber.
Once we can maneuver our laser
into the two-degree gap,
then we can cancel the emitter
and open a way in.
And how are we gonna know what power,
frequency, and caliber
that we need for our own lasers?
We can measure the diameter
by using the smoke.
It's easy. All we have to do then
is measure the frequency
using a spectrometer.
Two millimeters.
And once we've determined
the exact caliber of the laser…
then we can superpose
our replacement laser over theirs
if we respect the two-degree variable.
But no human can possibly do that.
This is outside of the realm
of what we can handle.
That's why we're gonna use
a neurosurgical robotic arm.
This will enable us to place our laser
at the exact point of the spectrum
with absolute precision.
Berlin, scan the room.
We need to move the robotic arm
432 millimeters to match the lasers.
And at an angle of exactly 91.36 degrees.
Set up the new laser.
We're ready.
You need to speed things up.
C3-PO could move faster than these two.
I need to make sure that all
the measurements are exact.
It's a very precise maneuver.
It takes time.
Okay. Whatever. Do it.
I have to admit,
this bastard knows what he's doing.
Wine barrels made of oak…
the floor covered in sand…
Nobody would go to this much bother
if it wasn't
for something quite exceptional.
And now for the moment of truth.
It's time for us to block
the laser alarm system.
It looks like our trick worked.
Your girl's amazing.
We did it. Our very own little door.
Shit.
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
The number you have reached
is unavailable or out of range.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Damián, I don't know if you'll get this,
but the creep got away.
I was up on deck,
so he must still be on the boat.
I'm taking the yacht out,
so he can't escape.
Damián, if he manages to contact the duke…
you're finished.
Berlin, lift your leg very carefully
through that space.
Watch out, your shoelace!
Take off your boots.
Okay. Let's do that.
I feel like one of those idiots
who's been told
to remove his shoes at the airport.
One day, I made the mistake of flying
with a commercial airline.
They actually forced me
to put on these plastic blue bags
on my feet to go through security.
Since then, I only travel by boat.
So, Keila, if you don't mind…
Ready for the big reveal?
It's now or never.
The Storm on the Sea of Galilee,
by Rembrandt.
And it's the original.
It was stolen in Boston,
from the Isabella Stewart Gardner
art museum… 23 years ago.
Poppy Flowers…
by Van Gogh.
It was stolen twice
from the Khalil Museum in Cairo.
View from… Auvers-sur-Oise…
Cézanne.
Woman with a Fan…
Amedeo Modigliani.
This one was stolen
from the Museum of Modern Art in Paris.
The Nativity…
by Caravaggio.
In all of art history,
this is the most valuable work
that has ever been stolen.
And he keeps them here… in a basement…
like some old Bordeaux.
What's up with him?
Do you think he's having a breakdown?
- It's what's called Stendhal Syndrome.
- What?
Unbelievable…
Stendhal Syndrome,
a state of euphoria, with palpitations,
and hallucinations,
caused when a person is exposed to beauty.
Okay, all right. But can he do that later?
Because we kinda gotta get outta here.
We cut the canvas
and leave the frames, right?
What do you think you're doing,
you shithead no-good moron?!
Are you expecting us
to carry all these paintings out?
No, of course not, Damián.
But all of these frames stay here.
What exactly do you mean
by "all the frames stay here"?
Damián… we're not talking
about a few million euros
in unmarked bills,
or some diamond necklace…
What you see here
are the most famous stolen works
of art in the history of mankind.
The most mysterious,
the most sought-after works of art
in the world.
But that piece of shit…
that idolater…
that narcissist has decided…
to sequester them.
The world is filled
with millions of paintings.
If they can't see these,
they'll see other ones!
Damián, please come here.
Do you realize how often I have visited
the Uffizi Gallery in Florence,
to see The Birth of Venus?
Every time that I feel depressed
or feel afraid
about the future of mankind.
And do you know
why I return again and again?
Because… simply by contemplating
this masterpiece…
I find my inner peace again.
What defines great art, Bruce?
Art is the highest spiritual expression
of humanity.
Each one of these masterpieces
was created to help reconcile
human nature with beauty…
and to ease the world's pain.
But this duke is so pompous.
Treating these paintings
like they're porn.
Flaunting his booty.
Drinking his wine,
making a call on his landline
to avoid the jammers,
ordering room service
like some cheap motel.
It's disgusting.
So what… should we do?
Give me five minutes.
I need time to think.
What are you talking about?
Does this look like a place to think?
He could be watching us right now!
Well, there aren't any cameras
down here, so…
Well, he might have motion sensors
or sonar alarms!
What if he already knows we're here?
Now look at my scars, kid.
I've got a few questions for you.
Look at me!
Tell me…
Do you like dogs?
You don't have to think about it.
Yes or no?
Yes! Yes!
Bark for me, kid.
Bark, you fuck, bark!
- Bark!
- Woof!
Good little doggie.
Your five minutes are up. That's enough.
Put that painting back down, Damián.
Why should I?
Are you gonna shoot me, or what?
Fuck you, Andrés.
You made us choose
between your plan and mine.
Because you thought my plan
in Marbella was a stupid idea.
You convinced them, and humiliated me.
And now that we've made it
behind these lasers,
you've decided we're not robbing him!
We're gonna rob this bastard.
Rob him of everything on these walls.
This Monet… it's mine now.
And I'll hang it up on the wall
behind me at the office.
Stop right there.
You're right.
And I've just had an epiphany.
Everything is clear.
All this art, these paintings,
they will all be part
of the biggest, grandest,
and most poetic robbery in history.
And we're gonna do it together.
That's the best part.
I just need you to trust me,
Damián, one more time.
Keila, is it possible to hide the number
of this landline if I make a call?
Yeah. I can do it.
Thank you.
You asked me to dress up
in your matador's jacket…
I've been waiting for over 40 minutes.
My darling,
I was busy saying goodbye to our guests.
Yeah…
Come.
My jacket fits you like…
you were born to wear it.
Maybe so.
But I'm hoping this is my only surprise.
Because…
it's my birthday.
No… No.
This is… just a whim of mine.
Your gift is over there.
Piñatas!
There is nothing
quite like the childhood fantasies
that surround our birthdays.
I love connecting with my inner child.
You may only break two piñatas.
So, choose well… my love.
Mm.
Yes?
Good evening, Duke. It's Berlin.
First, I must apologize
for calling you so late.
However, we have some very urgent issues
to discuss, you and I.
Right now? Can't it wait?
I'm afraid not.
It would be better for everyone
if we meet tonight.
You see, all my team
are beside me and want to see you.
We're not very far away…
In fact, we're on your property.
In your gallery, to be precise.
You're in my gallery?
- Yes, we'll be waiting.
- I'm on my way.
Are you leaving right now?
I am your wife.
Álvaro.
There are times I feel you prefer
your paintings over our love.
I'll be back, my love.
Keep the jacket. You look ravishing.
Let me go, asshole.
I'm putting you in with
the runt of the litter.
I'm afraid her time has come.
Let me out, you son of a bitch!
Let me out!
Give me your finger. Give. Come on!
That's it!
Easy… Well done.
You've both been nice bitches.
Time to end your suffering.
No! No! Please don't! Please, let me out!
No! Please no!
No! Please, no!
No! No! No! Help me!