(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
ظآزWandering aloneظآز
ظآزWalking far by dusk-lit streetsظآز
ظآزYour eyes are as cold as cloudsظآز
ظآزFaintly coming into viewظآز
ظآزThe city lightsظآز
ظآزLit up that single momentظآز
ظآزI can't hide or stop missing youظآز
ظآزI can't forget those momentsظآز
ظآزLosing youظآز
ظآزLike the seasons in my memoryظآز
ظآزWithout winterظآز
ظآزWalking down the long, dark streetظآز
ظآزSnow will never fall againظآز
ظآزOur old story was tornظآز
ظآزInto scattered piecesظآز
ظآزReplaying every single sceneظآز
ظآزAfter you leftظآز
ظآزAs if our documentaryظآز
ظآزLost winterظآز
ظآزThe breeze speaks of good timesظآز
ظآزPure white devotionظآز
ظآزSend out a letterظآز
ظآزCarrying my longingظآز
=The Double Game=
=Episode 6=
ظآزWhenever you come nearظآز
Having fun?
My dear sister-in-law.
ظآزStrange yet familiarظآز
What are you doing?
Putting on an act.
Stringing everyone along.
Is that fun to you?
(What does he mean by that?)
(Did he learn who I am and why?)
(No. That can't be.)
I don't get what you mean.
Let go of me.
My husband is calling me.
Lin Zhi'er,
can you hurry up?
Your husband?
If your husband knew
his wife was such a good actress,
what do you think he'd say?
What does our business
have to do with you?
Lin Zhi'er,
you want me to come get you?
Lu Tingxiao,
this is not a place to act out.
What if I insist?
ظآزEven if time could turn backظآز
ظآزAnd the story could restartظآز
ظآزI still couldn't forgetظآز
ظآزThe hidden warmth in your eyesظآز
ظآزFalling for youظآز
ظآزTook only a momentظآز
ظآزBut letting you goظآز
ظآزSomehow takes foreverظآز
Lin Zhi'er.
What's taking you so long?
Lin Zhi'er?
ظآزEven if time could turn backظآز
Lin Zhi'er,
what are you doing?
ظآزI still couldn't forgetظآز
ظآزThe hidden warmth in your eyesظآز
ظآزFalling for youظآز
Lin Zhi'er.
ظآزTook only a momentظآز
ظآزBut letting you goظآز
ظآزSomehow takes foreverظآز
I don't want you to see Lu Tingyu.
I don't want you calling him honey.
You're jealous?
No.
Then why play with me?
You're the one playing with me,
Top Blogger.
Don't push it.
Since you love role-play so much,
I'll play along.
Lin Zhi'er,
where did you go?
I've been calling you forever.
Mom's side is a total mess.
You surely know how to hide.
I just went to get some medicine,
but I couldn't find it.
I came down as soon as I heard you.
Tell me.
Did you sneak a bite?
No, I didn't.
Why would you say that?
You definitely ate some behind my back.
I didn't mean to.
Well, this...
It...
Look at you.
You didn't have enough
at the mealtime, huh?
You even smeared your lipstick
while snacking.
You're too old
to get your face so messy.
Don't make me look bad.
I'll go check on Mom.
(Lu Tingxiao,)
(who are you, really?)
(Why are you always so hard to read?)
(Why is it that when you kiss me,)
(I don't want to dodge?)
(Wen Yan,)
(you're in trouble now.)
(You've fallen for that crazy guy.)
Boss,
how did it go
after our scene?
Good.
Very good.
Congrats
on driving Xu Shulin and her brother out
and taking the project.
We're one step closer now.
But this is only the start.
Bai, you did really well
in getting those people
to target me.
(Bai Xiaoyong, secret assistant)
Thanks to your script.
After Xiao Ting pulled out,
the project blew up.
But they'd never have guessed
that you are Xiao Ting.
Someone just posted
(U.S. university)
the crypto tycoon Xiao Ting
is still a college student.
He's 20 years old and a billionaire.
So jealous.
I've heard he's at our school.
Who is that?
I don't know.
Maybe he's a handsome guy
with blond hair
and blue eyes,
just like you.
Don't make me laugh.
(Stock market)
Yes.
For the Lianxin Island project,
buy a large amount in
under Xiao Ting's name.
Chairman Lu,
Xiao Ting's representative said
he may pull his investment.
If the financing issue blows up
and draws official attention,
you could face legal money trouble.
My advice is
to find someone else to be
the legal representative.
To avoid outside suspicion
and keep things steady,
it should be a close family member.
A close family member?
Yeah.
Bring Tingxiao back.
Lu Jianchuan thought
he'd called back a scapegoat,
a son to clean up his mess.
But he didn't expect
the one he let in
would be the one to flip the board.
Ten years of lying low,
stepping into the game,
all to get back into Luzhou Group
and make those who hurt my mom
pay, one by one.
Now, Xu Shulin and her brother are done.
The next target
is that person.
Our next move
is to keep using Lianxin Island.
It's fine.
Just follow the plan.
Yes.
By the way,
when you were at the residence,
I noticed you knew my sister-in-law.
Was it Wen Yan you knew
or Lin Zhi'er?
You knew already?
Jin Chanchan
pretended to be Lin Zhi'er
for the investigation?
Only she would think of that.
Boss,
don't get Wen Yan wrong.
She means no harm.
- She just...
- Relax.
As long as she doesn't derail our plan,
I won't go after her.
Boss, don't worry.
Though I grew up with her.
I won't reveal a single thing
she shouldn't know.
After all,
when I got out two years ago,
you gave me a chance.
Without you,
I wouldn't be here today.
Bai,
I trust your character.
I'm just curious
about my sister-in-law.
How many surprises does she still have
that I don't know about?
Wen Yan lost her parents at a young age.
We grew up together in an orphanage.
She's always stubborn,
smart,
honest, and loyal.
Two years ago, I was framed and jailed.
She did everything to find
the evidence for me
to clear my name.
She runs that account
not for views.
She just wants justice.
Once she sets her mind,
she never backs down.
Watch where you're going.
You really never back down, huh?
This is my home. Why should I move?
What about you?
You saw me and still didn't move.
This is my house too.
Why should I move?
Fine, I'll make way for you.
Goodbye.
Why is Lu Tingxiao so unpredictable?
He wants distance
and then kisses me.
Now, he's pulling this again.
What is this?
He's messing with my head.
Forget it.
Focus on work.
(Proof of Lianxin Island Facilities)
(Lin Zhi'er was right.)
(The fundraising case is just a cover.)
(Behind Lianxin Island)
(is definitely a bigger scheme.)
(But where do I start)
(to get more first-hand files?)
(That necklace is
his electronic access key.)
There's no getting
around Lu Tingxiao, huh?
Come in.
Tingxiao,
I was too rash just now,
so I made you some calming herbal soup.
I want to apologize.
Can you forgive me?
Sure.
I'll feed you.
Sorry, sorry.
Are you okay?
I can't even handle this little thing.
What was that? Seriously.
(So, she wants this.)
I didn't mean to.
I'd better head back first.
ظآزThis doorظآز
ظآزLets in the sky outsideظآز
ظآزWith a voice even lighterظآز
ظآزThan how you just greeted meظآز
ظآزI know nowظآز
ظآزWhat the chill in my body meansظآز
ظآزThe moment salt hits the woundظآز
ظآزMy heart still beats so naivelyظآز
ظآزTo completeظآز
ظآزA joy that needs no brave pretenseظآز
ظآزHow cruel sincerity can beظآز
ظآزLike a door with no keyظآز
ظآزMaybe you just passed byظآز
ظآزThe tears in my eyesظآز
ظآزYou looked like you had nothing to sayظآز
ظآزThen got so good at being coldظآز
ظآزThat's why a smile feels so preciousظآز
ظآزMaybe you just passed byظآز
ظآزThe tears burned into my heartظآز
ظآزLet's say silence was just for showظآز
ظآزEven if I've grown another yearظآز