[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 26]
[Xu Miyu]
If you insist on thanking me,
how about
we have dinner together?
[Tonight]
Do you have any plans for tonight?
Come with me
to visit a restaurant.
It sounds like
you're forcing her to work overtime.
You evil boss.
You scared me.
I also want to fully support your
hard-won spring.
However,
the winter of KPIs
is coming soon.
The Golden Week has just ended,
and there are still two months
before the summer vacation begins.
[Monthly Performance Report
of Purong Hotel]
The rainy season is coming soon.
The following days
will be tough.
[Monthly Performance Report
of Purong Hotel]
[Statement of Expenditures]
[Monthly Performance Report
of Purong Hotel]
Come on.
Back then,
we took a fancy to this building
at first sight.
It's the best one
in the entire residential compound.
It really is.
Look.
The sunlight is great.
As for the layout,
it has great ventilation
from north to south, too.
In summer,
when we open the window just a bit,
there will be a breeze
in the apartment constantly.
The decoration style of your home
is so classy.
This TV feature wall
looks so grand.
Yes.
What material is it made of?
Fish Belly White Marble
imported from Italy.
So beautiful!
Come and take a look.
Come on.
Come over here.
They specifically hired someone
to design this nursery.
You guys are so thoughtful.
The baby isn't even born yet,
but this whole room
is already fully furnished.
As for this crib,
this brand is very expensive.
Sure.
It must cost tens of thousands of yuan.
My son and daughter-in-law
are both good at making money.
Not only are they willing to spend money
for my grandson,
but recently, they've also bought me
a new pair of presbyopic glasses.
Touch and feel them.
They're very light.
Yeah.
So light.
When you wear them,
it feels like you're not wearing them.
They must be expensive.
They just cost 18,000 yuan.
Mom, the price isn't 18,000 yuan.
It's 12,000 yuan.
That's right.
I have such a bad memory.
You're becoming such a humblebragger.
Just enjoy your happy life
with your son and grandchild.
Right.
We won't just enjoy the benefits
without helping them.
Since the children treat us so well,
as parents,
we should also
show our appreciation, right?
That's right.
My husband and I
have already discussed this.
We'll pay for our daughter-in-law's
postpartum care.
You are such a role model
as a mother-in-law.
It's my duty.
It's time to eat!
Hurry up!
Let's eat.
It's time to eat.
There are so many dishes.
Make yourselves at home.
What a good wife and loving mother.
I wonder if it suits your taste.
Your daughter-in-law is so capable.
It's great.
Stop working.
Let's eat.
The last dish.
Remain seated.
I'll go help her.
Okay. Go ahead.
You guys...
You guys ordered takeout again?
You should have told me earlier.
I could have come
and prepared the meal for you in advance.
Mom,
you're out of date.
This restaurant is very popular.
It's authentic French cuisine.
The most important thing is that
she was
afraid that the delivery guy
would delay it,
so even during pregnancy,
she still went to the restaurant
to fetch the food.
Don't you think that was so terrifying?
You have to be careful.
Why are you saying this?
Mom.
When I'm done with this busy period,
I'll personally make some fresh meals
for Yucheng.
Okay.
[Summons from the People's Court
of Hongkou District, Shanghai]
What's there to see?
What happened to you?
Why did you get the court summons?
What happened in the company before
has been solved.
It has nothing to do with me.
Come back.
I haven't finished speaking yet.
Well...
I noticed you didn't eat much today.
Are you hungry?
I'm not hungry. I have no appetite.
Do you think I'm annoying now?
No, I don't.
Are you not feeling well?
How about going to the hospital
to see the doctor?
None of the questions you asked
was to the point.
Are you doing this on purpose?
I...
How am I doing this on purpose?
You know I've been under a lot of
pressure lately due to my company's KPIs,
but you just won't help me.
The company's team building activity
isn't up to me alone,
is it?
You always have excuses.
I just don't know
what the use of your position
as a vice president is,
and what the use of marrying you is.
Let's not make a big deal out of it.
Alright.
I'll discuss it. Okay?
Not okay.
Not a single word you said is sincere.
You might as well say nothing.
Fine.
I promise you.
About what?
About the team building contract.
What will you do
with the team building contract?
I'll let you
get the team building contract,
and it'll be held in Purong Hotel. Okay?
That's more like it.
You're happy now.
I feel like he's kicking me.
Alright.
Get some rest.
I'll go throw the trash away.
The door is unlocked.
The door is locked.
[Summons from the People's Court
of Hongkou District, Shanghai]
[Case Cause: Marital Property Dispute]
[Summoned Party: Nie Yucheng]
[Changyang Travel Company
—Corporate Team-Building]
Be careful.
Lift it up a bit.
Okay. Alright.
Move it a bit to the right.
[Changyang Travel Company
—Corporate Team-Building]
Alright. Put it down.
It's okay now.
-Thank you, Mr. Ji.
-Thank you.
You're welcome.
Mr. Ji.
[Changyang Travel Company
—Corporate Team-Building]
Do you need to avoid them?
No need.
I can handle the reception work.
Okay.
I'm right by your side anyway.
Thank you.
Okay. Thank you.
Mr. Nie.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Xue Rui,
assistant to the general manager.
Hello, Mr. Xue.
Where is Mr. Ji?
He's waiting for you
at the entrance of the banquet hall.
Honey!
Mr. Xue.
I'll take my husband upstairs now.
Okay.
Mr. Nie, this way please.
I'm going upstairs.
Give me your bag.
They're going upstairs.
Mr. Ji.
Mr. Nie.
-How have you been?
Thank you for coming.
Don't mention it.
You don't need to thank me.
You should be thanking her.
For this deal,
she badgered me every day.
She kept badgering me
even during pregnancy.
This is my duty, isn't it?
Yes.
I just want to create profits
for the hotel.
That has always been
what I've been striving for.
Yes, yes, yes.
Come on. Let's go inside and talk.
Okay.
Ms. Xu,
please show them the way.
Mr. Nie.
Ms. Lu.
If you need anything,
just let me know anytime.
Okay.
Please follow me.
Let's go.
Please.
Mr. and Mrs. Nie,
here are your seats.
Thank you.
What are you thanking her for?
Bring us some chrysanthemum tea.
Ziyu.
Mr. and Mrs. Nie
would like some chrysanthemum tea.
Okay.
If you two need anything else,
just let me know.
-Also bring me a cup of warm water.
-Ms. Lu, are you in the banquet hall?
Yes, I am.
Just leave the banquet hall to me.
Ms. Lu,
please reconfirm this guest list.
Miyu.
There's an emergency in the kitchen.
They need you there right away.
Ask the receptionists to check
this list of yours carefully.
There are definitely some mistakes.
Okay.
Mr. Gu.
Hello, Mr. Gu.
Mr. Gu is here.
Let's go greet him now.
Mr. Gu.
Welcome.
Hello.
Come on. This way, please.
Come on.
Hello, Mr. Gu.
You're finally here.
I even saw Mrs. Gu yesterday.
Come on. Please have a seat.
Have a seat.
Mom.
Why are you throwing a tantrum again?
Didn't we agree on this yesterday?
There's no performance
at the Jazz Bar tonight.
It has been switched to the day shift.
There are 300 people upstairs
having a team building activity.
If they all eat your boat pastries,
won't that be great advertising for you?
I'll make pastries for anyone but her.
Mom, who are you upset with now?
It's all because of that Lu Zhenzhen.
No wonder
she came to the restaurant
bossing people around early in the morning.
It turns out
she's in charge of this order.
I'm not taking the order
she's in charge of.
What are you doing?
Are you driving me away?
Mom.
Lu Zhenzhen has been Purong Hotel's
monthly sales champion
for six consecutive months.
Some of her clients
would stay at the hotel,
some would get gym memberships
at the Health Club,
some would get massages here
all year round,
and some would often come here to eat.
They are all over our entire hotel.
If you can't accept it,
you might as well quit.
I'm just losing my temper, aren't I?
Gosh.
You have no idea
how much I can't stand seeing her face.
When I think about
letting her eat such delicious pastries,
how I wish I could mix some sand in them.
Mom.
Please don't talk nonsense
outside like this, okay?
If you don't
take your own specialty seriously,
you might as well quit.
You're just ruining your own reputation.
I'm just losing my temper, aren't I?
Gosh.
When I make the pastries later,
I'll close my eyes.
I won't look at
or listen to anything.
Is that okay?
That's more like it.
Then later, just stay in the kitchen
and make pastries.
Don't go anywhere. Okay?
Okay?
Okay.
It's a deal.
Isn't this...
Miyu?
Hello, Mr. Hu.
You're incredible.
Others get one year older every year,
but you're getting younger
and prettier.
Happy events bring good spirits.
Changyang is holding
such an important team-building event
in our hotel,
which is the highest recognition of
the service quality of our hotel.
Of course I will present my best demeanor
to welcome all my old friends.
Come on. This way, please.
Mr. Hu.
I'm here to welcome you personally.
Mrs. Nie.
-Please come in.
-Okay.
Please.
Here, Mr. Hu.
-Mr. Hu.
This way.
Mr. Hu.
Nie.
You did a good job on this event.
I'm flattered.
Keep up the good work.
Got it.
Why is there one set of tableware missing?
Waiter!
Come on. Please have a seat.
Miyu.
Mr. Hu.
My wife
keeps talking about
your spiced beef every day.
As for her precious son,
if he doesn't
have your spiced beef for a day,
he just can't eat his meals properly.
It's very kind of you to say that.
Actually, our Chinese restaurant has many
delicious dishes.
If you have the chance,
you can bring your wife
and child here to taste them together.
Sure.
I'll bring them here to dine
when I have time.
Please enjoy your meal first.
Let me know if you need anything.
Nie.
Did you see that?
It's only been a few months
since you two broke up.
Just see how much she has changed.
It's obvious
she has a bright future ahead.
When I walked up to her just now,
I was really surprised.
Mrs. Nie... No, no.
I mean, Miyu.
She has changed so much.
You didn't see this just now.
When she gave instructions to the waiters,
she was so sharp-eyed and quick-witted.
She has the exact vibe
of a workplace elite.
Then it looks like getting divorced
isn't a bad thing after all.
Zhenzhen.
Are you speaking ill of me?
-No.
Today is your team-building day,
and this is my home turf, too.
We need to support each other.
Absolutely, Zhenzhen.
[Homecoming, Courteous Reception]
Alright.
Okay. I got it.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Mr. Nie.
I'm sorry but I'm very busy right now.
Let's just talk for a moment.
I've received the court summons.
Is there any misunderstanding between us?
We agreed on it when we got divorced.
Why did you really sue me?
You concealed the marital property first.
I just took legal measures.
You've misunderstood me.
Honestly speaking,
I've given you everything that I could.
That investment fund is already gone.
You know that clearly.
Then where did you get the money
to buy a new apartment?
How did you find out about that?
Did you investigate me?
If you don't want anyone to know,
just don't do it from the start.
Miyu, I don't think this is necessary
since we were once married.
Going to court would be embarrassing.
If you are short of money, just tell me.
-I'll give you money.
-I just want to claim what is rightfully mine.
You weren't like this before.
What was I like before?
Nie Yucheng.
If you think I'm still that Xu Miyu
who can be bullied so easily,
I have nothing to say to you.
See you in court.
Well, I...
What do you mean by seeing him in court?
Don't talk about it here.
Xu Miyu.
Have you no shame at all?
You've been divorced for so long,
and you're still asking your ex-husband
for money?
This is something
between Nie Yucheng and me.
It's none of your business.
Let go!
I'm his wife.
Xu Miyu.
I'm warning you.
If you dare to take this to court,
I'll make sure
you can't make a living in this industry.
You bad woman!
-Don't you dare touch my daughter!
-Mom, why are you here?
Don't you dare give it a try!
You wretched hag.
-Can you educate your daughter properly?
-What are you talking about?
She's always acting like a beggar,
asking for money everywhere.
Bah!
My daughter is asking for her own money.
What does it have to do with you?
Nie Yucheng!
If you have any shame, don't play tricks.
Just pay off your massive debt!
Otherwise,
regarding your cheating scandals,
I'll shout about them so loud
that the whole world will know.
-Mom,
-Believe it or not.
Just shout then.
You'd better shout louder.
Otherwise, I'll tell the police
how you and your husband
extorted my husband.
Let's see who will suffer more.
-Just tell the police then!
-Mom!
Don't touch her.
Just tell the police if you dare!
Believe it or not...
Tell the police if you dare!
Just tell the police!
Why did you hit her, Mom?
I'm not your mom!
You call her Mom?
Here, Mr. Nie.
Mr. Ji.
After all, Zhenzhen is pregnant.
Doing this is certainly inappropriate.
-That's right.
-So I think whether...
you can give us an explanation.
Yes.
You were the ones
who upset my daughter first.
What kind of explanation do you want?
Mr. and Mrs. Nie,
you've been treated unfairly.
This matter
is indeed my management failure
as the general manager.
Please allow me
to sincerely apologize to you both.
Mr. Nie, how about this?
I'll arrange for Mrs. Nie
to go to the hospital
for a checkup as soon as possible.
All the expenses incurred
will be covered by our hotel.
Mr. Ji.
Shouldn't these expenses
be covered by the two of them?
We can cover the expenses.
Ms. Xu is an employee of our hotel,
and Chef Jiao is a cooperation consultant
of our hotel.
Their matters should be
the responsibility of our hotel.
And we'll definitely do our best
to compensate you for your losses.
But Ms. Lu,
you are also an employee of our hotel.
You should know that this is a hotel,
not a place to settle personal grudges.
So, please also respect
our hotel's principles
of handling matters.
Mr. Ji.
I don't care about personal grudges.
I am worried about the safety
of the baby in my belly.
You can't treat me
so unfairly like this, huh?
Mr. Ji, do you think this...
That's why I've told you
to go to the hospital for a checkup
as soon as possible.
We will take full responsibility.
Mr. Nie.
We've
always been good cooperative partners.
You probably don't want this matter
to affect our future cooperation, either.
Please, for my sake...
Let's...
let this go.
Okay.
Mr. Ji, I'm sorry.
My mother shouldn't have hit her.
I failed to stop her,
so it's my responsibility, too.
If you must punish someone,
just punish me.
I'll accept it all.
It was indeed inappropriate
for your mother to hit her.
But what I want to say is that
you did nothing wrong,
so you don't need to apologize.
Today,
whether you're an employee or a guest,
first of all, you are a person.
Letting others know you're not someone
who can be easily bullied
is a right you should have.
The door is locked.
Here. Change into these slippers.
If I hadn't found out about it
early today,
were you going to give her money
behind my back?
You've got more money
than you can spend, huh?
I was just afraid you would worry,
so I wanted to try reasoning
with her first.
What's there to reason with her about?
I won't allow you
to give our family's money
to that woman.
Find the best lawyer to defend yourself
against her charges in court.
Why do you keep squatting there?
Did you hear me?
I heard you.
My stomach hurts.
Could you pour me a glass of hot water?
Your stomach never hurt
until I started talking about
serious matters.
Just endure the pain.
Though that little vixen was so arrogant,
I still got to slap her face hard today,
didn't I?
You saw how she looked today.
It helped to vent my anger,
and it was so gratifying.
Tell me the truth.
About what?
You and Mr. Ji...
Mom, here you go again.
Just calm down.
You always have this attitude
whenever I mention this matter.
Because you always pair me off
with him arbitrarily.
How am I doing that arbitrarily?
Just think about what happened today.
A general manager stood in front of you
and apologized to that vixen
so humbly.
What did he mean?
Even a blind person could see it.
This matter
is indeed my management failure
as the general manager.
Please allow me
to sincerely apologize to you both.
In my opinion,
isn't that little vixen
just relying on the fact
that Nie Yucheng has a bit of ability?
That's why she can show off
in front of you.
She even dared to complain it
to the general manager.
Who does she think she is to do that?
If you and Mr. Ji are together,
wouldn't you become her direct boss?
By that time,
even Nie will have to fawn on you.
Let's see
if they would still dare to act wildly
in front of you.
But let me tell you.
No matter what happens in the future,
you can't be as impulsive as today.
Okay?
Look at you.
What a little ingrate.
I'm venting anger
and taking revenge for you.
I'm just afraid you'll get hurt.
Besides,
isn't your daughter doing well now?
Why do you always care so much about them?
They bullied you so much before.
Can you really forgive them?
Let me give you an example.
For instance,
when you're walking on the street,
a piece of chewing gum
accidentally gets stuck to your shoe.
You definitely want to get rid of it,
right?
You just can't
fight with that chewing gum, right?
Then...
Then what if they do it again in the...
If they dare to bully me again
in the future,
I just won't stand there obediently
to let them hit me like before.
Don't worry.
[High Output Management]
You're reading a management book, huh?
Mr. Tan.
So you want to be a professional manager?
I'm just setting a goal for myself.
Am I being too unrealistic?
No, it's good to have a dream.
However,
being a professional manager
is such a tough job.
Actually, you don't have to work so hard.
No matter what you do,
you are just the best in my mind.
Really.
Are you leaving tonight?
Yes.
The car will be here soon.
Oh, right.
Okay.
Then let me see you out.
I can do it myself.
Thanks.
Mr. Tan.
I haven't had the chance to thank you
for what happened last time.
Thank you for helping me so much.
And I was drunk last time.
If I did something rude,
please forgive me.
No, no.
Actually, I was thoughtless last time,
which caused you trouble.
Of course not.
You helped me.
I merely helped you out of a tight spot.
If I really want to help you,
I actually would like to take you away.
Um,
I mean,
I-I know you
really like your job here,
but the environment is still too tough.
My company is also hiring.
Would you like to come?
Where are you
flying to this time, Mr. Tan?
Hong Kong.
I've moved my business to Hong Kong
so that I can come here often.
If you live closer to the old Mr. Tan,
it'll be convenient to take care of him.
And I can also see you often.
The car is here.
Okay. Thanks.
Take care. See you next time.
See you next time.
No wonder
this girl doesn't
even like the general manager.
So this is what's going on?
Hello. This way.
Come on.
Give it to me.
Here you are.
Okay. Thank you.
Please come in.
This rainy season is so annoying.
Honey.
My shoes got wet after a few steps.
A few days ago,
I noticed that Bottega Veneta
released a new pair of rain boots.
They look pretty nice.
I want to buy them.
What are you busy with?
Why aren't you
replying to my WeChat messages?
It's damp.
Bake it again.
If it's still not okay,
just throw it away.
Alright.
Ya.
Remind the warehouse that
food easily gets moldy in this weather.
Ask them
to make sure to check the ingredients.
Okay.
Hello, Mr. Ji.
Here is the Red Bean and Coix Seed Water‌
you ordered.
I'll hang a dehumidifier bag for you.
Come in.
Thank you.
I think it tastes good.
Ask Chef Li to add a little
dried tangerine peel to it, too.
This sweet soup
can help to remove dampness.
We can offer it as a free gift
to the guests
who check in during the rainy season.
I think your idea is great.
I'll go arrange it now.
Okay.
[Purong Hotel
Performance Analysis Statistical Table]
[The Purpose of the Activity]
I'm sorry, Mr. Ji.
Our chief editor said
the rain in the suburbs was so heavy
that he couldn't make it by noon.
Then what about dinner?
It's not very safe
to travel at night.
Besides,
our chief editor
has already checked into
the InterContinental Hotel over there.
It's getting late.
We should take our leave.
Okay.
Mr. Ji,
the price we just mentioned
is already the highest one we can offer.
Mr. Ji, please
think about it again.
Okay.
We will think about it seriously.
I'll leave now.
Okay. Let me see you all out.
Should we
talk to their deputy editor again?
What they originally wanted
were two venues,
one indoor and one outdoor,
which complemented each other.
But now with the rainy season,
the garden terrace cannot be used.
It's not surprising
that they want a lower price.
We've already offered them
the lowest price.
If we accept the price they offered,
we will definitely lose money on this.
[Purong Hotel]
Mr. Ji.
You must have stayed
in the deserts abroad for too long.
Have you forgotten
the most annoying thing
about Shanghai is this rainy season?
Now look.
Without a backup plan,
our business is badly affected.
Mr. Ji.
Don't forget that
we have a VAM agreement
hanging over our heads.
What do you think we should do?
Thank you for reminding me, Mr. Wei.
I did stay in the desert regions
of the Middle East and North Africa
for a period of time.
And I interacted a lot with the locals.
Those residents
in the tropical desert climate zone
are very passionate
about watching the rain.
Our off-season
might just be their peak season.
Did you all hear that?
Watching the rain?
Are you joking with us?
Mr. Ji.
Elaborate on that.
Okay.
[North Africa Rain Viewing Group Planning]
Currently, we've established
partnerships with eight travel agencies
in North Africa.
This year, they will open up
a new route
for watching rain in East Asia.
From this week until the end of the month,
these rain-viewing groups
will check into
our Purong Hotel successively.
That's just a drop in the bucket.
Even if your so-called rain-viewing groups
stay at our hotel,
can they fill up all the guest rooms?
And what should we do after they leave?
Shall we find
cloud-viewing or star-viewing groups next?
It's a temporary expedient indeed.
But at least,
it can increase the occupancy rate by 30%.
Mr. Wei, do you have a way
to solve this issue once and for all?
You might as well bring it up
and discuss it with us all.
I...
Alright.
Let's follow Mr. Ji's plan for now.
Okay.
-Welcome.
-Thank you.
Welcome.
Human joys and sorrows
are not mutually comprehensible.
Some people would travel miles
to watch the rain,
while some would get annoyed at the sight
of this humid weather.
Having business
is better than having none.
The rain-viewing groups
can only help temporarily, not forever.
Just wait and see.
When this trend passes,
we'll be back to the original state.
Hello.
Purong Hotel at your service.
You'll check in on the night of June 6th
and check out on the 10th. Is that right?
A standard double room, right?
Yes, we have standard double rooms.
May I have your phone number, please?
Ask the guest
if he has any special requests.
Do you have any specific requirements
for the room?
You want a higher floor.
You want it to be quiet.
Don't worry.
The soundproofing effect
in our hotel is excellent.
Okay. We look forward to your visit.
Goodbye, Ma'am.
Lu Xiaoyan.
Did you also receive bookings yesterday
for June 6th to 9th?
I think so.
Check it right now.
Okay.
I found it.
There is such a booking.
The reservation is
from the 6th to the 9th of next month.
Please check again to see
whether there are other bookings
during this period.
Why are we checking this?
Yes.
I found five bookings in total.
Four of them are from the 6th to the 9th,
and one is from the 6th to the 10th.
We also need to
inform the colleagues on other shifts
about this.
Any bookings between the 6th and the 9th
or the 10th of next month
should be marked with notes.
Then send the information
to Shi Huanhuan for summaries.
You're in charge of recording it
and giving it to me every day. Okay?
Okay.
Ms. Xu,
why is that?
Think about it.
Every year,
what days are June 7th to 10th?
-The college entrance exam!
But the graded exam
for the three elective subjects
was already taken last week, wasn't it?
So we just can't miss the exam
for the three compulsory subjects.
Since the bookings
have given us enough hints,
we can't miss this opportunity.
But
what if it's a coincidence?
Our Purong Hotel is a five-star hotel.
Staying in our hotel for a day,
with meals and accommodation,
would cost over 1,000 yuan, right?
How many college entrance exam-takers'
families can afford that?
Besides,
who knows if there's an exam site nearby?
Whether it's a coincidence
or an opportunity,
we need to find out
before we discuss further.
In our area,
the "3+3" new pattern
of the college entrance exam
has been implemented for years.
As for the quantity and locations
of the exam sites each year,
we should investigate them clearly.
Hotels belong to the service industry.
We can't just wait
for guests to initiatively come to us.
We need to take the initiative to discover
the guests' needs
and provide them with the best service.
Only in this way can we stand out
in the fierce competition.
Got it?
Understood.
Let's get to work.
What are you looking at
so seriously?
The college entrance exam sites
near our hotel.
Since when have you been so obedient
to Ms. Xu's instructions?
I'm not being obedient
to Ms. Xu's instructions.
My cousin will take
the college entrance exam this year.
I'm just curious,
so I'm looking it up casually.
In my opinion,
when it comes to the tasks
of getting clients,
there should be some news
coming from the marketing
and sales departments first, right?
You and I are so well-informed,
but we still don't know anything about it.
It must be totally baseless.
Ms. Xu really
knows how to make trouble for herself.
She's not making trouble for you.
Why are you talking so much?
Hurry up and eat.
We have to change shifts after the meal.
Ms. Xu,
instead of having a meal,
what are you busy with here?
I'm doing a little research.
Why are you circling
so many spots in red ink?
Are you going to buy a house?
No.
I'm just checking where these
college entrance exam sites are.
I'd like to see if there are any of them
near our hotel.
Don't bother with this.
No college entrance exam sites
have ever been set up near our hotel.
Those exam-takers rarely
stay in our hotel.
I'll get going, Ma'am.
[Fuxing High School
Affiliated to Fudan University] [2.5 km]
[The Affiliated High School
of East China Normal University] [1.5 km]
[Xinhua Finance and Economics School]
You're at home, huh?
Why didn't you turn on the lights at home?
You also didn't reply
to my WeChat messages.
Why aren't you saying anything?
You didn't close that window, either.
It's so damp inside.
Why didn't you turn on the dehumidifier?
What's wrong with me
buying a pair of boots?
I have to
carry such a big belly every day,
and it's so heavy.
The doctor told me...
to go to the hospital tomorrow
for an enhanced abdominal CT scan.
Can you go with me?
What's wrong?