=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 6=
- Kill her!
You people are
high and mighty.
You want me to die?
If I have to die,
we'll die together!
(If you die with evil obsessions,)
(evil spirits will come
and plague the world.)
Who is this girl?
I don't know.
I...
My town, Liangzhou,
was ravaged by Chong troops.
My fellow countrymen
were killed by them.
Just now, I heard her wild remarks,
and anger overwhelmed me.
So, I was dying to kill her.
I...
Don't draw my sword casually.
Please don't blame me, General.
You contributed a lot to my army.
Sadness overwhelmed you,
and you killed her.
I will not blame you.
Bravo! Well done!
- Well done!
- You did great!
Miss He,
she hasn't confessed
how she sneaked into the granary.
You...
How could you just kill her?
Mr. Lin,
we can still interrogate
the guards on duty.
Not too much was burned.
It's all right.
Put out promptly,
the fire didn't burn much.
That's great!
Everybody, don't panic.
Later, we'll distribute food.
Distribute food?
So, we really didn't
lose too much.
Everybody, disperse.
Move, everybody.
Everybody, go home.
Break it up.
Don't worry.
We will distribute food
as scheduled.
- Go home.
- Go.
Break it up.
Why did you do that?
If He Yan had died like that,
evil spirits would prey.
Just pretend I was being nosy.
General Duan,
how on earth
did you get this sword?
That's a long story.
One day, on a bridge of Nandu,
I met an old man.
This is the truth.
Not long before I left,
I met a strange old man
on that bridge.
He said he was hundreds of years old.
He suddenly stopped me
and gave me this sword.
He also told me
it was the Deliverance.
It means dispelling illusions
and resentments of mortals.
Those struck by it
will get rid of illusions.
That's so you, Miss He.
You know everything.
I'll go investigate
the fire case.
I'll take my leave.
General Duan,
you see how oddly I behave.
Don't you suspect
that I was sent
by Duke Pei or North Chong?
Do you just take orders from people?
Judging from your skull,
you're born unruly
and you act on your own authority.
(Did he)
(get the Deliverance)
(because he was my spell bearer?)
What's up?
Great Ancestor,
I found the real Duan Xu!
How did you?
I found Du Zheng,
who served Duan Xu in Daizhou.
He gave me a portrait
of the young master
he had served.
Fang Xianye, the Censorial Counselor.
He's the real Duan Xu.
(Fang Xianye, Censorial Counselor)
Your Majesty,
there's no way.
Can we really not
deliver supplies to Shuozhou
without suffering
(Emperor of Great Liang)
any casualties?
Your Majesty.
(Yao Jianhe, Duke Pei)
Although Duan Xu has occupied Shuozhou,
(Du Yanting, Chancellor)
he disobeyed orders
and defied the law.
(Duan Chengzhang, Minister of Rites)
He sent troops
without telling anyone.
So his army has been trapped
in Shuozhou.
Now,
even 200,000 Hulan soldiers
are lurking greedily.
How can the supplies
be delivered to Shuozhou?
Are you saying
we're going to abandon
twenty thousand soldiers
and the citizens?
How can we help?
Duan Xu's life matters.
What about the lives
- of other soldiers?
- You...
Enough.
North Chong has occupied
the north of the Guanhe River
for thirty years.
Now, we're about to cross the river.
We can't just abandon Shuozhou.
However,
what General Duan's doing
is extremely perilous.
Duke Pei's concern is justified.
Your Majesty,
Shuozhou is under siege.
Supplies will run short.
Even if there's a slim chance,
we can't give in.
We understand that Minister Duan
cares for his son.
But now,
no one can fight his way
through 200,000 Hulan soldiers.
We can gather supplies
before we manage to deliver them.
Who will
take this mission?
Me.
I'll take this mission.
The court is dismissed!
You got my son exiled to the front.
And now, you want to get him killed.
(Chongde Chamber)
He Yan got the key
to the granary from Xie.
Obviously, she knew
the Lins guarded the granary with us.
She also knew very well
about the patrols and shifts.
Captain Han,
you're in charge of granary defense.
You must find out
what happened today.
Yes.
General Duan.
General Duan,
I ask for your fair judgment.
General Duan!
I'm afraid someone else
is behind Xie.
Compared to finding the spy,
we have something more urgent to do.
I've blocked the news.
But I want to be honest
with you all.
The supplies from Marshal Qin
would have been enough
for fifteen days.
But they've been burned to ashes.
All we have now is some food
Mr. Lin has collected for me.
Far from enough, though.
That madwoman...
What a mess!
Oh, it's burning me.
General, why don't we fight our way out
and die together with Chong soldiers?
The more I kill,
the more it's worth.
It's not time for death yet.
Before the enemy arrived,
I had asked my men to scout this area.
There's a secret path
on the sunny side of Mount Peng.
Tall enough for horses
and wide enough for five men.
It leads to the enemy's rear.
As people say, tit for tat is only fair.
They burned our supplies
and we'll take theirs
in appreciation.
If Chong soldiers deliver supplies,
they have to pass
through northern cities.
I have relatives there, too.
I'll contact them by pigeons,
asking them to watch the grain carts.
Then let's do it.
(The Collection of Military Techniques)
(Duan Xu)
(You're a fake.)
(You aren't an imperial relative.)
(You may even be a Chong.)
(Why did you fight aggressively)
(for Great Liang)
(and kill Chong troops with zeal?)
(Duan Xu,)
(what exactly are you up to?)
General.
What's up?
You ordered me to solve
the fire case.
But I'm confused about something.
I seek your guidance.
Go ahead.
Why are you so familiar with North Chong
when you've never been in the army?
Are you suspecting
I have a connection with them?
Yes.
I asked you to find the spy.
But you suspect me
in the first place.
Are you worried I'm colluding with them
and just pretending?
I'm not sure.
Please explain.
Captain Han, I heard
you escaped from North Chong.
You must have more connections
with them.
I don't remember what happened
back there.
You can't answer me,
but seek my answer instead.
If I suppose
an unidentified man like you
from North Chong
might be a spy,
how can you refute that?
You have the guts to suspect me.
Captain Han,
I'll pretend I didn't hear this.
Don't worry.
If Shuozhou is captured,
I will not survive alone.
(He has acute senses)
(and remarkable responsiveness.)
(He's indeed the best among mortals.)
(I think it will feel great)
(when I borrow his five senses.)
(Look at this young general.)
(What did he suffer in his childhood?)
(What lies beneath the scars)
(of the branding iron?)
(And how are they related
to his identity?)
Excellent senses.
Foxy,
you're qualified
to be my spell bearer.
(Liang)
General, you're still young.
In face of a major mission,
you were also too scared to sleep.
Don't worry.
Today, I will
scout ahead for you.
You'll be safe.
Pass the order. Call up troops.
Commandant Wu.
You should stay in Shuozhou.
What do you mean?
You don't trust me?
If I can't come back,
you will command in town.
My army trusts you.
I trust you, too.
I wrote to Marshal Qin
about the situation in town.
If tensions in Yuzhou ease,
he'll try to send reinforcements.
Then why don't you stay here?
We can go intercept the supplies.
If the mission fails
and I'm still in town,
will Marshal Qin still rescue us?
But...
We...
Han Lingqiu.
Here.
Get 800 elite soldiers.
In the mid-afternoon,
we'll depart.
Yes.
We serve the same country.
How come Marshal Qin
will not rescue us?
Commandant Wu,
take my advice.
With your temper,
do not try to be an official.
The court, right now,
is in dire straits.
Or you'll be in deep trouble.
Meng Wan, Qingsheng.
You must help Commandant Wu
defend Shuozhou.
- Yes.
Darn it.
Why do I feel
this guy is protecting me?
Foxy.
Take cover!
Hide!
Ambush! Take cover!
Captain Han.
Don't stop.
Go kill the enemies.
Great.
It really is grain.
General Duan is truly prophetic.
Move, move.
Ambush!
Hide now!
Take cover!
Hide!
So, someone is watching behind us
to hunt us.
We're ambushed.
I think they'll take you and me alive.
Prepare to fight!
As a spirit,
I didn't want to get involved.
But just now,
I made a deal with the young man
you shot to death.
He begged me to save Liang soldiers,
and I agreed.
She'll save us.
- She'll save us.
- Great.
So, North Chong soldiers,
will you do this
for my sake?
Let them go.
He Xiaoxiao,
stop pretending.
Who would dare to bully you?
Foxy,
you made an unexpected mistake, too.
Stop being mysterious!
Kill!
Do you really think
I'm asking for your permission?
Move!
Run!
Rest in peace.
Miss He,
wipe off the blood.
And then?
Then,
in exchange,
Miss He,
can you let me keep
this wondrous memory?
What?
Do I need to re-introduce myself?
I'm Duan Xu,
D-U-A-N, X-U.
Style name, Shunxi.
So, My Lady,
who are you?
By night, I carry a lantern
to guide mortals.
By day, I carry a lantern
to guide spirits.
I am
the Sovereign of Spirits.
According to legend,
at the end of the East Sea
is Fusang Tree.
Under the tree is the Void Spirit World,
governed by the Sovereign.
I thought
it was just a fabrication
from fascinating books.
So, it really exists.
If I have the chance,
I want to visit the Spirit World.
For centuries,
some information from the Spirit World
has reached the Mortal World.
But the world is way too vast.
Where can be considered
the end of the East Sea?
Just by this alone,
mortals can't make it
into the Spirit World.
Obviously,
I'm not He Xiaoxiao.
And you're not Duan Xu.
What are you talking about?
I am Duan Xu.
And my style name is Shunxi.
My grandpa and my father
chose the names.
I'm genuine.
Don't try to fool me.
Listen.
I'm here to save you
because I want
to make a deal with you.
What an honor to make a deal
with you, Your Grace.
But sadly,
I'm...
Let's not stay here.
Shall we talk about it
back in Shuozhou?
You're procrastinating.
How do you know
I'm not begging you?
People don't usually beg
with this tough attitude.
Your Grace,
I'll be waiting for you
in Shuozhou.
What happened?
Where's our enemy?
Where are they?
Yeah. Where are they?
They must have been driven off.
Clear the battlefield.
- Hurry.
- Yeah.
Let's take back the weapons.
- Yes.
General.
I'm sorry
for that.
I think the two of us
can't avoid fighting with swords.
In that situation,
I was too nervous.
Please forgive me.
Xiaoxiao.
Xiao...
She's a real sleepyhead.
Where's her jade pendant?
I knew it.
He Simu's spirit has left this body.
Once I know who this girl is,
I will know
how to restrain He Simu.
General,
you're finally back.
Commandant Wu,
I finally made it back alive
after much hardship.
Yes, yes.
General,
when you're back,
I'll have to return
the military command
to you.
You should be happy.
General.
Thank you.
Thank you
for doing that for people in Shuozhou
as well as me.
General,
you're injured?
I'm fine.
Commandant Wu.
Handle these supplies properly.
No more lapses.
Count on me, General.
These supplies
will last over half a month.
Han Lingqiu is accused of treason.
He'll be detained now
and punished later.
General,
what's going on here?
Someone sold our secrets.
During the grain raid,
Chong troops ambushed us.
We nearly got wiped out.
Then how do you know
it was Han?
Because besides me,
he was the only man
Chong troops wanted to take alive.
- Move.
But...
Xiaoxiao, you're awake.
When I was asleep,
did anyone come in?
No.
What's wrong?
Her jade pendant is back.
Did I see wrong?
Let's make a deal.
I'm all ears.
I'll fulfill
one of your wishes.
In exchange,
you'll lend me one of your five senses.
One wish
for one sense.
For ten days.
What if I refuse?
Under such circumstances,
you don't get a say.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪