What is it, man?
You called me, right?
-Didn't the work get done?
-No.
You kept saying it every day,
but I paid no attention.
No matter how much I tell him,
he isn't getting it.
He needs to be clear-headed
before he can understand.
I got him to realize.
SECRETARIAT OFFICE
Hello.
Mister!
What is it?
I'm telling you for the last time.
Sign it.
I won't.
Hey, what's your problem?
I've told you many times.
The rules don't allow you to build
another floor on your existing land.
If you proceed with illegal construction,
I'll have to prevent it.
Here, take this…
PANCHAYAT SECRETARY
I'm adding an extra ₹10 thousand
to the ₹25 thousand I promised.
Take it, sign it, and finish the job.
-This isn't about the money.
-What?
Did someone tell you not to?
Who is it?
Ethics and honesty…
they are very dear to me.
They said no.
What's with you? Feeling too arrogant?
You're getting too big for your boots.
I know very well how to make you sign.
What? Is that a threat?
Hey!
Do you know what it's
like to be threatened?
Every day…
your son goes to school
at 9 in the morning.
and at 9:30, you're at the office.
From then on, your
wife is all alone at home.
What? Did you think I'd go after her?
No… first I'll kidnap your son.
And before your wife finds out about it…
How?
Why is he saying that?
What do you mean by “how”?
How will you kidnap him?
What's with this guy?
There's nothing to it.
When your boy is going to school, I'll
wait for him at the Bangaru mettha center.
You…
Who the hell are you man?
Does anyone try to kidnap
someone at public place?
Sit down!
You filthy kidnapper!
-This is my house?
-Okay.
Here is the school.
And this is Bangaru Mettha.
-I'll kidnap him right here.
-But there will be people around, right?
-Right?
-Yes.
Between my house and the
Bangaru Mettha, there's a small alley.
-It's filled with haystacks.
-Right!
There will be no one.
Correct brother.
But he has to come with you, right?
Right. What should I say to make him come?
Show him a phone.
Tell him to make a Reel.
Once he comes…
As soon as he comes in,
just grab him,
throw him in the car
and escape from there.
Look!
You absolutely can't miss my son.
Is the plan okay?
What kind of man are you?
If anyone threaten to kidnap his
wife and kids, He'd be scared to death.
But what are you doing?
Using paper and pen to draw
a sketch and tell me how to kidnap him?
You only know there are two characters,
so you think kidnapping is easy.
I know how cruel they are,
which is why I'm not worried.
I didn't get it.
DRINKING ALCOHOL IS HARMFUL TO HEALTH.
He doesn't know my name.
Not a boy. My name is Mithil.
Son of Sriram. Panchayat Secretary.
Remember the name.
Mithil!
What's going on, Brother?
Your son is hitting him brutally!
He watched KGF last night.
This morning, he ended up
hitting someone… and saw real blood.
Plan changed.
What is it?
Your wife.
No!
You people won't be
satisfied with just promos.
You need a theatrical trailer.
Listen!
Sister, please don't.
Who the hell are you?
A thief.
What did you come for?
What else? I came to steal.
So, what should we do?
You should file a complaint
at the police station.
Right?
Then why did you file the
complaint against on us?
I mean… Sister…
-How dare you complain against my son?
-It's not that.
How dare you
-drag my husband to the police station?
-Sister.
-You…
-sister.
Look at your eyes…
the very eyes of a thief.
Forget your legs…
those eyes deserve the shock first.
Stop, sister.
When there's an attempt to kill, what
choice do we have except to file a case?
Why are you shouting?
Show me even a single scratch
on your body, and I'll agree.
Don't think I'm being vulgar.
But like an elder sister…
please open the back door just once.
-Why?
-Look at what your son has done to me.
Please, sister.
Oh my god!
Who the hell are you? You're cutting
through me like I'm just a watermelon.
Wow, my son's art is amazing.
Don't you know the difference
between art and hurt?
What kind of upbringing is this, sister?
I can bear the pain on my back,
but at the bottom…
I got hit in
a place I can't even mention, sister.
Now tell me, sister.
Isn't this a murder attempt?
Isn't your son a …?
Isn't your family a criminal family?
What a damn life…
Forget it, brother.
I don't want your signature.
I don't want to die.
What kind of family are you?
There's more violence in your
house than in the movies.
No one understands when we say it nicely.
HORSELEY HILLS
Hello!
Is it Bhukailash demolishing company?
Yes.
What can we do for you.
Yes, you need to demolish a building.
Which Building and where is it?
Little flowers high-school.
Horsley hills.
Do you want us to
demolish it or blow it up?
Anything is fine…
but make sure the teachers are
inside the school before you demolish it.
Especially Principal.
It's your choice whether you
demolish it or blow it up.
Okay, bye.
Hi daddy.
Give the phone to mom.
I'll be back.
Tomorrow is holiday.
Bunty, tomorrow holiday for school.
He never disappoints us.
Uttara.
Uttara, coffee!
Why isn't she responding?
Uttara!
What?
Didn't you hear me calling?
Are your ears blocked?
Yours only.
You don't listen no matter
how many times I tell you.
Why did you refuse the money
when he offered it to you?
What the hell are you talking…
That's a bribe.
Not a lottery ticket.
Taking a bribe is a crime.
Who asked you to take a bribe?
Consider it a gift.
Hmm…
That's right.
Hmm, we can consider it a gift, right?
Your father said he would gift
a Yamaha for our wedding.
First, look into that matter.
That's not a gift.
It's dowry.
Taking a dowry is a crime.
Stop your drama and go get me some coffee.
What if I don't?
Don't let my name go down in history
as the husband who killed his wife.
Don't give it to me.
Oh God, what a saga
for just one cup of coffee.
-Dad!
-Yes?
Diwali is coming, right?
Buy firecrackers!
When you light them,
the sound should be huge!
These small firecrackers and bombs
aren't enough for you and your mom.
-Yes daddy.
-Do one thing.
There's a big transformer at the
end of our street, right?
Go blow it up.
The whole town will hear the sound!
Superb, Dad! Okay,
I'll go blow it up then!
Hey! You useless fellow!
If you blow that up,
the police will arrest me!
Hey, Sudheer!
-Uncle!
-What's the matter?
That's not it, uncle.
The new SI has arrived, right?
I thought he'd give us some pending cases,
but he's not even coming to the station.
And here you are, playing games.
Oh, so you're feeling like you're the
only one working sincerely in this PS?
-That's not what I meant, uncle.
-Then what is it?
Actually, our old SI was better.
This guy is a bit weird.
Forget the cases coming to us,
first he has to take them, right?
What do you mean he
doesn't take cases, sir?
Have you ever gone on a raid?
We don't need that in our area, sir.
Go and check, the first
person you'll find is our SI.
Uncle.
He's always on that duty.
How's he supposed to handle cases
when he spends all his time with girls?
Don't come again.
My husband got suspicious about me.
If he gets suspicious, we can take a break
but don't ask me to stop.
Just because he got suspicious,
he put me through hell.
If it's confirmed,
he'll definitely kill me.
That's not it, baby.
Listen to me…
Enough sir…
Go…
Go!
Hey!
What is it? Looks like
Uttara is hiding something.
What's the matter?
Shh! don't shout.
Why?
Money plant.
I stole it from the neighbor's house.
Why did you have to steal it?
Does anyone buy a money plant?
Only if we steal it
without their knowledge
will it bring lots of
money into our house.
So you mean, not just my earnings,
this plant will make money for us too?
We'll get more than what you earn.
More will come?
That's great.
So, where should we put this?
That's what I can't figure out.
Ah, should we put it in the cupboard?
Yes.
Hmm.
But it might die without air.
Right?
Give it to me.
How about this?
I'll throw it just like this.
Why did you throw it like that?
Shut up.
It's theft in the first place,
and now you want to plant it in
the cupboard and get money from it?
-I didn't talk about cupboard.
-That rubbish!
You would have said the same later.
I know you.
You thief!
You don't earn enough,
and you won't let me earn.
So how am I supposed
to buy a necklace now?
What necklace?
I mean… once the plant grows,
it'll bring us money, right?
With that money, I thought
I could buy a necklace.
You threw the plant away…
so now you'll have to buy me a necklace.
Is one enough, or do you want two?
You're making me cry on a festival day.
Point number one.
Today is not festival.
Point number two.
You're not actually crying.
Point number three.
There you go, your father
Gurumurthy is calling. Pick it up.
Hi, Dad.
Hi, dear.
Hi, dear!
What happened, dear?
Did your husband say something?
Yes, Dad. I asked him to buy
me a necklace, but he won't.
Husbands will always
say they can't afford it.
Wives should insist.
If he still doesn't listen, then just
take it from your father's house.
How did I end up with people like you?
He's just like that, Dad.
You tell me.
Nothing much, dear.
Come home for the festival.
-Okay.
-Bye, dear.
Bye, father.
Did you really have to insult
my dad over the phone?
Sorry.
Next time, I'll do it live.
I'm going to the office now.
If you return early, we'll
go to my father's place.
Travel safely.
And don't rush back.
Happy journey!
What? You're not coming with me?
I need some peace of mind, dear.
You mean…
you're indirectly saying you have
no peace of mind because of my family?
I don't think anyone could've
said it more directly than this.
Of course… you think me and
my family aren't good enough.
That's why you left our family
WhatsApp group, right?
Damn!
Why do you cry over everything?
Because you make me cry over everything.
It's better to die than live with you.
Always the same torture.
Stop the fake tears.
Come and give me my clothes.
Go away.
Okay, come.
Come, come.
Sir, response.
The minister is not coming.
The program is canceled.
Alright.
Sir, please. We're running late.
Please, just let us go.
-No way. We'll lose our jobs.
-I'll take care.
Sir, please, sir.
We'll leave without disturbing
the meeting, sir. It's getting late.
Look, I already told you.
I'm telling you, it's not possible!
It's urgent, we have to go, sir.
Please. Please, let us go.
Ugh! How many times do I have
to repeat myself? Don't you get it?
Sir, sir, please sir.
Wait here. Just wait.
-Hey!
-Sir!
Okay sir.
You can go.
-Sir, sir.
-You stop. Wait.
-Just two minutes please…
-It's getting late, sir. We have to go.
Sir, everyone else has stopped,
right, sir? The SI told us to.
What do I care who told you?
No one is coming there.
Let us do our duty.
If you want, you can go the other way.
Our office is right here!
How are we supposed to go that way?
-Hey!
-That's not it, sir. Listen to me…
Sir…
What's the issue?
The minister isn't coming,
so he's asking why we're stopping them.
Why do you care?
Who are you?
Sriram, Panchayat Secretary.
To hell with your panchayat,
you can wait for 10 minutes.
Wait.
My panchayat job is far better
than the panchayats you handle.
Let us go.
Hey, what's with the attitude?
-Are you acting smart?
-Sir, sir.
The public is watching, sir.
Are you special?
Go.
Oh, so she's special to you?
Is that why you let her go?
It's my wish.
Keep your wishes inside your station.
If you show them outside…
I won't sit quietly and watch.
Then, what will you do?
-Hey!
-Sir!
File a weed case against
him and lock him up.
It's not as easy as you think
to file a weed case against me.
-How dare you?
-Sir, sir, sir… please…
He's a government employee, sir.
-Please don't sir.
-What are you getting excited about?
Everyone is recording videos, sir.
It will ruin the department's
reputation, please sir.
Hey, constables tell
them to stop recording.
Please, sir.
-Hey, what's with the videos?
-Hey, Sriram
-Turn them off, all of you.
-calm down.
-Please, sir.
-You can go, sir.
-Find out his address.
-I'll take care of it, sir.
-It is not happening, leave.
-Mister.
We've convinced more than
half the families in the village
and brought them here.
Take their signatures,
and the work will be done.
Not half.
Even if one person
disagrees, I won't sign.
You think there's someone like that?
Hey!
Does anyone in the village have
a problem with signing?
Is there?
Your vote won't be valid.
To keep your job, you have to be generous.
To be generous, I'll even give up my job.
Brother!
Why are you still here?
I'll take care of the cemetery issue.
Why should we build a
cemetery in the MLA's place?
The MLA is on the line.
Speak to him.
Sir.
MLA THIMMAPPA'S HOUSE, MADAMAPALLE
What mister?
I heard you're stopping the villagers
from getting signatures.
I'll send you a package. Sign it.
What's there in a package, sir?
The promise I gave to the
people is more important.
I promised that a cemetery nearby
wouldn't be good for the village.
Let's do it this way this time, sir.
I'm hanging up, sir.
-Hey, Prasad.
-Sir?
That Sriram must be
transferred immediately.
Sir, we've already
transferred the RI and VRO.
If we transfer someone who has public
support,
the public will not vote us again.
So let's leave him for now
and find another way, sir.
Dear, get that bag.
-Prasad.
-Sir!
Send this gift bag to the
minister, and as usual,
leave the town without
anyone suspecting anything.
It's very important.
Be careful.
Edukondalu will come at night and take it.
You just pretend you don't know anything.
Go straight, sir, straight.
Straight ahead!
Why are you turning the wheel like that?
Put it in third gear, sir.
It's fine.
Fine?
Hmm!
The car's going to stall!
Put it in third gear.
Oh no! What a man he is!
What the hell is wrong with him?
-Don't you get down?
-If we both get down, who will drive?
Damn!
Please, I kindly request you to get down.
So, you'll drive from here?
Have some shame.
It's been a month, you haven't
gone past second gear or into reverse.
Never before have I seen a teacher
break a student's spirit like this.
Sir, I don't have the
courage to encourage you.
If this car could speak, it would curse…
-I got it! It would curse me, right?
-Leave it.
That's what you mean.
Enough of this.
I don't need your fees.
Just drive in second gear.
Your neighbor Prasad has a car, right?
Convince him to give that to me.
I'll use it for my driving school.
He won't.
That is his sentimental car.
What's the point of being sentimental
about a car that isn't even running?
That's what I'm saying.
Why do you need a car that
doesn't even budge an inch?
You act like a big businessman.
Alright, I'll get down for today.
We will catch up here tomorrow. I'll
definitely drive the car in third gear.
-No doubt at all.
-He's always nagging me. Damn this life.
They're bothering me!
Send me the money!
Hey, Rajendra.
Why aren't you coming to the office?
You know our friend Venkatramana?
Yes, the guy who lives in America, right?
I think his mother passed away.
Exactly. When she passed,
he couldn't make it back,
so I hired some professional
mourners from Vellore.
Professional mourners?
Who are they?
The people who cry for money
when someone dies.
Anyway, the mourners
did their crying and left.
Now he's making me
miserable by refusing to pay up.
-What strange times we live in.
-Okay, let's go have some tea.
-No, no, I can't.
-Brother!
Just came from my driving session.
-Let me freshen up and I'll be back.
-Listen?
I'm the guy who smacks heads just for fun.
You really want to mess with me?
Be careful.
If I call my friends,
they'll smash your head.
Be careful. Bye.
This is how you should make a video!
Just you watch.
I'll make a video
that gets more likes than yours.
Smacking head?
Oh no! He's going to destroy
my peace with those stupid reels.
Hey, Sriram,
why are you messing with the MLA?
He asked you to sign, and you refused?
It's illegal, how can I do it?
But what about you? You opposed our road
construction, now you're supporting him?
What you said is correct,
but he's not as good as you think.
Okay, whatever happens, we'll see later.
By the way, I forgot…
Why is that driving school Govind
asking for your car?
Stupid fellow!
Because of his torture, I kept the
car inside saying it wasn't working,
even though it was perfectly fine.
If I get angry, I'll ram the car into him
and throw him in the trunk. Bloody idiot!
Honey, it's getting late!
Coming!
What? A tour again? Your job is great.
My mother-in-law
invited us for the festival.
Don't shout. If my wife hears,
she'll create a mess.
Right!
Prasad, will you get into the car or not?
You can go.
Otherwise, it'll ride on you.
The car… not her.
If that driving school
guy calls you again…
I'll deal with him, you go.
Let's talk on phone.
There are no signals, right?
How can we talk on the phone?
We shouldn't let her call me 'Hey Prasad'.
You are right.
-She's a tough woman.
-That's it.
Okay, I'm leaving.
Drive safely.
Leaving already?
Just stepping out for a smoke.
-Hello, boss.
-Tell me.
I came for the gift.
It will reach the boss by evening.
Be careful.
Hey!
Who are you?
What are you doing here at this time?
And who the hell are you?
KOTHAKOTA POLICE STATION
Leave me, sir.
I didn't do anything.
I'll leave you, man.
Tell me what you were
doing there at night.
I already told you, sir.
I was going to my relatives' house.
I didn't ask you to repeat
what you already said.
Tell me the truth.
What's this, sir?
You were also there at that time.
Did I ask you why you were there
and what you were doing?
Everyone has their own business, sir.
Sorry, sir.
Sir, I'm sorry.
Sir…
-Bloody scoundrel…
-Please, sir.
-Please sir, let me go sir.
-How dare you?
-Speak up!
-Leave me, sir. Please.
-How dare you talking against me? Tell me.
-Sir, please sir.
-Please!
-Get up!
Tell me.
Speak up!
No, sir, don't hit me.
I'll tell you everything, sir.
DIWALI DAY
Who is it?
Is your husband home?
He's not at home. He went out.
-And you?
-Vikram.
I'm the SI of this area.
He'll be back in a while. Come in.
Coffee or tea?
Anything you bring is fine.
You started blowing it up early in the
morning. Bombs will enter the house.
Ugh… what in the world…?
What kinds of children they are
Wait, what's this now?
Is she sulking because I wouldn't
take her to her parents' house?
Oh my god…
I swear, I can't deal with her drama.
Hello?
Hmm?
Hope she's not seriously
planning a trip to Chittoor.
My darling… "stopped breathing"?
Oh God! Are you okay?
Hey!
Who is there…?
Sir!
Hands up!
I really didn't do anything, sir.
I don't know anything, sir.
Hi, Dad.
Let's make a Reel now.
Here's the plan. As soon as I shoot,
you have to act exactly like that uncle.
Okay?
-Hey!
-What daddy?
Are you the one who shot him?
Hands up!
Uncle, you're dead.
You're not supposed to get up.
Do you think Diwali gun can kill someone?
This is a real gun.
Uncle, can I touch it once?
-No!
-Please, please, please.
I'll give it back immediately.
Please, uncle…
please…
Goodness! Why is it so heavy?
Is this really a real gun?
I'm the one who shot him, Dad.
You have to act exactly like him
and fall down. Okay?
-What have you done?!
-Mom!
No, Dad!
You're always up to some mischief!
Sorry, Dad.
-I'll kill you.
-No, Dad.
-Dear, Let him go.
-Mom, please!
-Dear, please! Let him go.
-Hey!
He's just a kid!
Are you really going to kill him?
So what?
I should beat you first.
You can hit us any time you want.
See what needs to be done now.
What should I do?
-Let's surrender to the police.
-Mom!
He's just a kid.
Not him.
It's me.
You're surrendering?
Hey, come here…
Come…
Don't you dare come into this
house until I tell you to? I'll kill you.
Go!
Why are you sending him out?
What if he tells someone?
No one will believe him.
If he stays here he'll start live
video on social media.
Forget about him.
Why are you surrendering?
That SI and I had a fight yesterday only.
Do you think people in the village
will believe that Mittu did it?
They'll think I did it.
At least if I surrender,
the punishment might be less.
Let me go.
I won't agree to you going to jail.
Then he has to go.
I won't agree to that either.
Whether you agree or not,
a mistake has been made in our house.
It's a crime if you do it knowingly…
but how is this a crime?
A crime is a crime.
Move…
If you go to jail against my word…
Kill both of us.
then it's your wish.
So what now?
You want me to cover it up?
You should have some common sense.
Let's hide it.
What?
-Yes.
-Hey!
Are you crazy?
He made a mistake unknowingly.
And knowingly I won't do any mistake.
Then go.
I'll jump into the well
along with our son.
-I'll hit you…
-Hit me!
Your son's future is less important
than your morality and honesty, right?
You always say we're the problem anyway.
If we're not there,
you can live happily as you wish.
Go.
You always say we're the problem.
Your son's future is less important
than your morality and honesty, right?
If we're not there,
you're free to live happily your way.
I'll listen to you now…
but one day this will become a big issue.
When that time comes…
you'll have to listen to me.
-Your phone?
-No.
I think it's his phone.
He plugged it in some time back.
His wife is calling.
-It's not turning off.
-Oh God, please turn it off.
-Switch off the phone.
Why did you wipe that?
What about the fingerprints?
Hold him.
Carefully.
-This way, this way.
-That way?
Let's put it under the bed.
-Is it okay under the bed?
-Shh!
I'm not shouting.
Okay, okay, let's go.
Gently… calmly…
Namaste, sir.
MR. VAIRA PURUSHOTTAM REDDY
Put your Namaste in the ballot box.
What happened, sir?
Where's the gift?
It should have been here by now.
What is this, sir?
I already sent it last night.
I don't care if you sent it, he stole it,
or the two of you are playing games.
Your work gets done
only when I get the gift.
If not… you're finished.
Nothing is more important to me
than my political future. Got it?
What happened?
Call Prasad.
The number you are trying
to reach is currently busy.
It's not connecting.
There's no signal in the village.
Hey, Madan!
-Hey, Madan!
-Boss!
-What happened?
-The Minister didn't get the gift.
What do you mean? Last night…
Why are you asking us?
You're supposed to ask
Yedukondalu that, right?
Hey, first call that scoundrel.
Did you call us for such a small thing?
You have a phone in your pocket, right?
You could have called him yourself.
-Hey, you duffer!
-Michael!
Get lost.
You're coming to my sister's place
tonight, right? I'll deal with you then.
The number you are
calling is either switched off…
Boss, his phone is switched off.
My god, he cheated us.
-Hey!
-Boss!
Tell our men to find him wherever he is.
Okay.
If he's found,
-I'll chop him into pieces
-Okay, boss.
Hey, Madan.
He has been working for us for so long.
Do you think he'd do something like this?
What do you think?
-Hey!
-Boss.
First go to Prasad's house and
check whether our gift is there or not.
Okay, boss.
What's that?
Blood spilled, right?
This prevents dogs
from sensing the smell.
Where are you going?
You asked me to hide the body, right?
If we keep it in the house, it'll stink.
That's why I'm going to
find a place to dump it.
So I should stay alone with the body?
It's difficult.
Call all our neighbors
and arrange the funeral rites.
I'll get a coffin in the meantime.
Why are all these people here?
If we go now, it'll be a problem.
Reverse the car.
First, let's go to Yedukondalu's house.
Call all our neighbors
and arrange the funeral rites.
You're here?
Go, she's over there.
Why is everyone gathered here?
Dear, please give these sweets to them.
What for?
-Well…
-What is it?
After you left, I was all alone, you know.
So?
I was scared.
And so? What have you done?
What's wrong with these chilies?
They've turned all mushy.
The peel won't even come off.
What is it? Why have you come?
Aunty… I'm scared to
be in the house alone.
Will you keep me company?
What is it, dear?
Well…
It's just… I've missed my period.
Dear!
You too…
You wouldn't even let
me live in peace, huh?
Ramu!
Having celebrations with a dead body
in the house, you shameless fool!
Enough of your romance…
just get over here.
-What is this, Sweets?
-Yes, Take this Aunty.
Sriram is quite the player.
-Here, girl. He's not a normal player.
-Hey, Sriram!
Are you distributing sweets?
Did you get a promotion?
I know, man. You're a hard worker. You'll
get what you deserve for your hard work.
Promotion? Don't be silly.
Sriram is going to be a father again.
Really?
Oh! I know. You're a hard worker.
You'll get what you deserve for
your hard work. Congratulations!
You taught him a lesson.
The daily exercise has paid off well.
What is it, Sriram? Is it Shilajit?
My foot!
Dear!
-What happened?
-Dear, our Son…
Did he come?
…is not to be seen.
Thank God!
Let's do one thing.
Will file a police complaint.
No!
I mean, why file a police
complaint on a small child?
Not on him, but for him!
Do you have any sense?
Will you make a pregnant woman
climb the stairs of a police station?
Ask them to come here.
-Good idea.
-Hey! Wait a minute, I forgot.
Auntie, Mittu sometimes goes out
and comes back late at night.
He's always pulling pranks.
Dumb! Why didn't you tell them?
Auntie… Yes, auntie, I forgot.
Oh goodness!
-Uttara! What happened?
-Uttara!
At this time, it's normal.
They just fall like that.
Come on, let the air in. Go away.
Why should we stay here? Let's go.
Sriram, let's take her inside. Come on.
Gently.
Don't worry, Sriram.
God knows everything.
Knowing that one would be lost,
He prepared another.
If you need anything, even in the
middle of the night, just call me.
-Okay, auntie?
-Take care of the girl.
-You take care too.
-Be careful.
Oh, thank God! They're gone.
By the way,
did you find a place to dump the body?
Forget about the body. Where is he?
He's eating Boost, sir.
What?
I'm the one who hid Mittu.
How many twists do
you plan to pull this time?
I mean, if the murder is revealed,
we can prove that Mittu wasn't
even in the house today, right?
For the first time,
you've done something useful.
Where is the artist?
Mummy Boost…
Slowly… slowly…
This way…
Why did you stop? Let's go.
These things are always there.
Hold it.
I'll…
After this,
we're performing the ritual, right?
I mean… if we don't do the final rites,
he might turn into a ghost and haunt us.
I've already been dealing with
two ghosts for ten years.
This will be the third.
Why did you switch off the light?
Do people move a dead
body with the lights on?
Go on…
Your criminal thinking has no limits.
Who could it be?
Don't know.
-Who is it?
-The police.
What brings you here at this hour, sir?
Some rogue boys from the next street
were fighting in a group,
causing a big ruckus.
To prevent further fights at night,
we're placing two
policemen on each street.
Our SI is also not on duty.
We're managing somehow.
It's nothing, sir. You
just switched off the light,
so you must be awake. I
came to ask for some tea.
You can come anytime, no problem.
Look, wake up your wife
and ask her to make some tea.
The ASI sir asked
for it, it won't be good.
-Otherwise, we'll make it ourselves.
-No, no, no, no.
-Come, he agreed.
-Come.
What's the matter?
Nothing sir…
Come in.
Come here…
Let's go and sit there at dining table.
Uttara!
What is it, asking for tea
in the middle of the night?
Well, when I wake her up in the
middle of the night, and asks for tea.
Oh!
Why he sits there?
Well…
The sofa springs are damaged.
That's why she's worried.
Isn't it right?
Go make some tea, will you?
-Subramayam, where has this SI gone?
-Who knows, sir.
You'll fall down.
What?
It's dark here… you
might fall and get hurt.
Come on, let's go sit over there.
Come…
What's wrong, sir? You seem
tense and worried.
-What's the matter?
-What the hell is he talking?
Is this
how you treat a government officer?
Did I come to your station,
or are you in my house?
Leave it man, leave it.
-What is this sir?
-That…
Is that your son's photo?
-Yes, sir.
-He looks like a bullet.
Not like an ordinary bullet.
He'll be a six-round bullet.
Its nice?
Hey, won't you come?
By the way, what's the issue
between you and the SI?
He is the one who grabbed my collar
-and insulted me.
-Yes.
Give me, Madam.
Thank you.
The house is nice, though.
-You've done it up well.
-What are you staring at my face for?
I just thought they might want some Upma.
-Upma?
-Hey, what are you saying, man?
-You're all still sitting here?
-We had our dinner just now.
-We just came for tea. Thanks, Madam.
-Thanks, Madam.
Thanks, Sriram.
Don't hesitate, sir. If you want
some tiffin, go ahead, eat.
-Sorry for bothering you at night.
-I'll give it to you in the morning, sir.
Anyway, we won't let it go.
Hey! Stop it.
There are cops over there!
Reverse it, reverse it!
Quickly.
Why are they sitting here
instead of doing their duty?
Hey, stop here.
Hey, turn off the light.
Yes, tell me, duffer.
We're right at the
corner of Prasad's street.
Why are you calling
me instead of going in?
How do we go? The police
are in the middle of the street.
What are the police doing there?
Shall I go and ask them?
Shut up and give the phone to Madan.
-Boss!
-You stay there
and check after they leave.
-There shouldn't be any doubt.
-Okay.
That SI has an eye on us because
we aren't giving him commission.
-Be careful.
-Okay.
Did you find out anything
about that Yedukondalu?
I said to our men. They'll find him.
We must have to take the body out
tomorrow morning, right?
Is the bike okay?
Your neighbor Prasad has a car, right?
Convince him to give that to me.
Because of his torture,
I kept the car inside
saying not working even in good condition.
302, go and check that side.
-Hey, Mahi.
-Sir?
-Go and inform the sniffer dog team. Go.
-Okay, sir.
Sir, what happened?
Some guy got drunk last night
and jumped from here.
They're investigating whether
it's a suicide or a murder.
Oh god! Police are here.
Is he saw me?
Sir, please give me the paper.
He looks like Sriram.
Sir!
Sir… Sriram!
Sir, I'm calling you, sir.
Shit! He saw me.
Why aren't you responding when I call?
Well…
But why are you here?
My wife told me not to come home
without the flask, so I came.
You came to a crime scene for this?
If I don't take this home,
it'll be an even bigger crime.
Early in the morning, just for a flask?
Something's not right.
My loving sports car!
-Sir, you…?
-Yes, its me.
I know how to drive.
I'll drive the way I want.
Damn the fate…
In the very place I
planned to dump the body,
someone else has committed suicide.
Damn!
NGO helping cremate unclaimed bodies,
showing humanity -Chittoor News Today.
-Yes, sir.
-Uncle.
-I'm checking that file only, sir.
-I'm right here at your desk, sir.
-Uncle.
Okay, sir.
I'll do it right away.
What is it?
Why are you coming from that room?
Uncle, forget that.
This case has been pending
for a long time. I'll solve it.
How many times do I have to tell you?
If the SI finds out, it'll
be a problem. Leave it.
Uncle, you can manage without him knowing.
-Hey, will you listen to me?
-That…
-Greetings, Madam.
-Greetings, sir.
-Greetings.
-Sit.
Tell them to get coffee or tea.
I don't want anything.
What is it, Madam?
Why did you come to the station so early?
Vikram hasn't been
home for two days, uncle.
And his phone is also not connecting.
So, I came thinking he
might be at the station.
He set out to handle a case.
Where did he go?
-Tamballapalle.
-Yes,
he headed to Tamballapalle
regarding a case.
He'll be back.
Don't worry.
Okay, uncle.
-Don't forget to tell him.
-Okay.
-It's a bit urgent.
-Sure.
-Fine, uncle.
-Take care.
Why are you laughing?
What do you want me to do, sir?
You know about him.
-So?
-What sir?
You wait brother.
Uncle, I'll solve this case.
Hey, don't you listen?
Don't get into these cases.
Hey!
Madam came, right?
Go find out where sir is and tell her.
She'll recommend you.
And you'll get a promotion.
What do you say?
Shit!
Who said yoga cures everything?
Why are you calling, man?
He's in shock…
how can he talk?
Shock? Why?
Won't he be shocked if there's no gift?
What do you mean, there's no gift?
Do you know something?
There's no car here.
There is no car?
Who took it?
If we were aware of that,
we would've reached out to him.
Why would I call you
about the missing car?
Under any circumstances,
I need that car and the gift inside.
Otherwise, both of you will be dead.
You will be the first one.
Remember that.
So we'll mix this body
with the unclaimed ones
and go to our parents' house
without anyone suspecting us.
I'm the guy who smashes heads just for
fun. You really want to mess with me?
Be careful.
If I call my friends,
they'll smash your head too.
Be careful.
Did you see this reel?
Mittu has acted so well.
Let's make him an actor.
He committed a murder.
What's acting to him?
Besides, the film industry has been making
heroes out of villains for a long time.
My son is not a villain.
You're right.
He's not a villain.
He's juts a henchman.
-The main villain is you, right?
-What?
Yes.
Cut it… cut it…
-cut the hen.
-Sleep my dear.
Cut!
First cut yourself,
then cut your mother's.
That would be better.
You scolding us is nothing new.
-Just look ahead.
-And what if I don't?
You could have told
me instead of screaming.
Instead of shouting at me,
why don't you go and check?
I'm this slow…
and you still dashed into my car?
Is he alive… or not?
Who the hell is this guy?
Sir…
What happened, dear?
-I think he's dead.
-What?
He's dead?
I hope no one is watching this.
Did this wretched man have
to fall under our car and die?
What do we do now?
Now…
Fourteen years for that murder.
Fourteen more for the accidental killing.
-What's wrong with him?
-And seven for hiding the truth.
-That's thirty-five years total.
-Dear.
-A lifetime behind bars.
Why are you whispering
to yourself like that?
Pack all the gold.
The chit fund money has to come, right?
Collect that too.
There are three acres in the village,
right? Transfer them to Mittu's name.
Also buy a sewing machine.
It'll take care of your monthly expenses.
Why are you talking irrelevantly, honey?
What about him?
We have no connection with him.
Let's just leave him here.
I mean, we can even put him in the trunk.
He'll keep him company.
Dad!
You are making reel without me.
The connection is established.
Did you cause an accident?
Darn it!
I missed it, Dad!
What did you miss, sir?
I just saw a live accident video.
Do you know how many views it got?
If people knew you were in an accident,
I could have made a video.
It would have gotten a million views.
I have an idea.
Let's place the body straight,
take the car to that corner,
and drive at 120 speed. Okay?
I'll record a video from a low angle.
And then we'll smash him.
It'll be a complete mess.
Okay? A million views.
You… what are you looking at?
Hey, Mittu!
Get into the car, quietly.
Please, Mom!
Just one video. Let's smash him.
-If I come, I'll beat you up. Get in!
-Just agree, Madam.
What?
Your son is just having fun… right?
Sir, are you not dead?
Of course not, sir.
Your family seems to
be planning something.
Do one thing.
Take the car back and smash it
-from the center at high speed.
-Super idea.
Sorry, sir.
-He says, "Run me over with the car,"
-Right uncle.
and she says, "Put me in the trunk."
I've never seen a family
this terrifying before.
What are you staring at?
Go and get in the car.
Sir! Sir! Sir!
-Great, man!
-Please sir.
Sorry, sir.
-Okay, okay, okay.
-Sorry sir.
-No need to touch my feet.
-Sir--
Please keep it sir.
This is fine for me.
But what about the vehicle?
Yours is a big car, right?
Let's get in that.
-You've seen enough, come on.
-Oh my God, what is this torture?
Hey, don't talk anything over with him.
-Now, It'll be fun.
-Please come, sir.
Let's go.
Ma'am, don't worry.
If your husband hits anyone again,
we'll throw him in the trunk.
There's enough space, right?
Not you!
Hey!
You fool…
Come here.
Hey!
So you thought you could betray us
and hide in jail, and we wouldn't notice?
We have informers everywhere.
Hell with them.
It was me who made the
constable call you,
-you duffer!
-Michael!
Do you think anyone would
go to jail to hide? You dumb!
Enough of this.
Where's the gift?
-The other night, I…
-I didn't ask your whereabouts.
I asked you where's the gift?
Will you move,
or do I have to make you?
You tell me.
Last night when I went for the gift,
the SI suspected me of
being a thief and locked me up.
I've been here ever since.
So you didn't take the gift.
Then how did you take out the car?
You…
The Salar Prabhas has arrived.
Now tell me.
If it's not you, then who did it?
-Please sir…
-Tell me the truth.
-Let me go, sir.
-You…
I'll tell you everything, sir.
MLA Thimmappa regularly
sends a bag to the Minister.
It's in the PA's car.
I was on my way to pick it up
when you arrested me.
Bloody scoundrel!
He got us at just the right moment.
Hey!
Under any circumstances,
SI should not be missed.
Search everywhere for him.
Okay, brother.
Does it not go beyond this speed?
It will, but not him.
Second gear…
Look over there.
What a strange family.
Hello, respond.
No.
Thank you.
-Sir, are you a policeman?
-No.
This belongs to the police.
Then why do you have it?
I need to know how much I've drunk, right?
Oh! Why do you need a test for
that? It's obvious from looking at you.
Hey!
Don't talk without knowing
the reason why I was drunk…
I only drink
when I'm doing something important.
He's not the important one.
What does he have that matters so much?
Is there anything…
…more important…
…than a missing SI?
You look like a nice, cute, small family.
But I'm the only one who
knows your true colors.
-You took him and…
-Don't talk…
did something to him.
That's what I suspect.
-No, we didn't take him.
-He came on his own.
Didn't I tell you not to talk?
So he came, did he?
Yes, he did.
Uncle and I played together too.
What did you do with
him when he came home?
We didn't do anything, sir.
Tell me!
Tell me! Are you alone,
or is your whole family involved?
What are you looking around for?
-I'm a bigger artist than you.
-Please sir…
-Did you kill him? Tell me!
-No sir.
Did you kill him and put him in the trunk?
Super shot, mom.
You hit him well.
Why did you hit him?
I didn't know what else to do.
You do something.
Damn!
-Yes, Sudheer. Tell me.
-It's nothing, man.
I'll send you a number.
Can you track it and send
me the location details?
Sure. Is it official or unofficial?
It's a family matter,
maintain confidentiality.
Okay, WhatsApp me the number.
If you find out where the sir is and tell
the madam, she will recommend you…
and you will get a promotion.
MINISTER IS ASKING ABOUT GIFT
-Hi, Dad.
-Hi dear.
What's this?
You seem to be in a lot of tension.
I deal with this kind
of tension all the time.
Sir, good morning.
-Sir.
-What is it?
-Your daughter drives really well, sir.
-Good.
-Sir…
-What again?
You said you'd give me a car if I
teach your daughter to drive, right, sir?
I'll check and arrange you
some random car. Go now.
Not just some random car, sir.
Your PA Prasad has one, right?
That sports car.
Get me that, sir.
It would be a great addition
to my driving school, sir.
He always used to say
it was sentimental and didn't work.
I saw it this morning, sir.
It's working very well, sir.
-Did you see it this morning?
-Yes, sir.
-Where?
-At Horsley hills.
That village's Panchayat Secretary
Sriram was driving it.
Bring our gift bag.
Hey, you filthy swine!
Who are you?
Why are you climbing up the wall?
Hey, old woman!
Sriram isn't at home?
You…duffer.
Are your eyes blind?
The door is locked,
so he's not here, right?
-You old fool!
-Where did he go?
Who does he have in this town
except his in-laws in Chittoor?
What is this, Dear?
There are so many good restaurants
on the way, why did you bring us here?
-Not good at all.
-I can't take a risk with both of you.
You've seen enough.
You know about my driving, right?
It's a long way to go.
Make it fast.
Tell me, Sandeep.
You sent SI Venkat's number, right?
The tower location is
showing Horsley Hills.
Thank you, Sandeep.
Sriram is not at home, boss.
It seems he's gone to his
relatives' house in Chittoor.
I don't need information!
I need confirmation!
NAGRAJ HOTEL
TEA TIFFINS PREPARATION
Where's your father?
Where did he go?
I went to the washroom.
Did you pay the bill?
Yes.
Uncle, did our SI come this way?
I saw him going toward
Panchayat Secretary Sriram's house.
-Hello?
-Hey, Sriram.
You interfered and stopped the villagers
from signing the documents.
Then I found out you're an honest officer,
and I knew I couldn't get my work done
with you around.
So, I changed my route.
But you turned into a speed bump
on that route as well.
So now, I'm going to destroy
the whole damn road.
Mark my words.
In the graveyard I'm about to build…
your grave will be the first.
You scoundrel.
Hey auto, stop aside.
Yo! Go check out that vehicle.
You! Pull it over! Right here!
Hey! Get out.
I said, Get out!
-Sir… please, sir.
-Are you dealing ganja?
Sir, open the trunk.
We are going on a vacation with my family.
-It's just luggage, nothing else.
-Hey!
-Okay, madam. First, open the trunk.
-Look into it.
Who do you think we are?
My husband is the Panchayat
Secretary, do you know that?
Sir!
Sir, they refused to open the car trunk.
Keep quiet for a while.
He is asking you to open it.
We will sir.
Open it.
Who is he?
He's my brother-in-law, sir.
He's not well.
Go open the trunk.
There's nothing, sir.
It's luggage.
Alright, madam.
Let me check.
Did he chop the body into pieces?
What is it?
Nothing, sir.
It seems there's nothing.
-Why waste our time on that? Go, go, go.
-Sir.
Get in.
Hi, uncle.
Do you also do a soft
search like movie cops?
Didn't you check the box
on top of the car?
-Hey Sanjay!
-Sir!
There's another box on top.
They already knows.
You get inside.
Sir! Gun.
Hey, It's a toy gun.
That's my gun.
Give it to me.
Okay, okay.
Keep it with you.
Give that to him.
-Place the box on top of the car.
-Okay sir.
Uncle!
Your gun is nice.
-Shall we exchange our guns?
-Hey!
I can't give this to you. It's not safe.
It's nothing.
I even played with a police uncle
using a gun like this.
I already shot him.
I mean, I have a friend
who works as an SI.
He's saying he played
'cops and robbers' with him.
-Please uncle, will you give it once?
-No dear.
Sir, sir! No, sir.
We know how to be careful.
How can I give this to a kid?
Go, go.
Where's the body?
Why aren't you answering when I ask?
Kid, take this parcel
and give it to the
police at the checkpost.
-Okay.
-No profit for us…
all we do is serve them.
-Hey, wait. Wait.
-What?
Take the cigarettes for the CI.
Otherwise, he'll bother us in the evening.
-Hey, Khan, give him the cigarettes.
-Give it to me.
Kid!
Is there a checkpost nearby?
Yes, brother.
It's at the corner after that turn.
It wasn't there before, right?
They set it up recently because ganja
smuggling has gone up, brother.
Is that so?
Okay, go.
When she died and he couldn't make it,
I called the paid mourners from Vellore.
-Rajendra.
-Sriram, tell me.
You told me about the
paid mourners recently, right?
-Do they live only in Vellore?
-No, you can find them here as well.
Why do you ask?
I came to other village for work.
There's an unidentified body
on the road here.
-I felt like helping.
-Oh no!
Alright, okay, okay.
I'm sending their number.
Hey, told them about the work?
No, they're not even listening.
It's not about drinking,
you have to work.
Brother, I need a favor from you.
Rajendra already told me.
We'll do it.
What's the payment?
Sanjay, let them go.
-Hey! Hey!
-Mittu!
-Thank you.
-Thank you sir.
Dad!
That uncle is…
Police uncle. Hi!
But what is he doing here?
The police uncle is making a reel
about
what it's like to peep from the trunk.
I'll do it, I'll do it.
-Will you?
-I don't.
-Leave me.
Go and sit.
Go!
I'll sit here.
He's growing in age, but not in sense?
So, you overacted this much
knowing there was no body in the car?
Do you know how tense I was?
Why did you do that?
Even with all my caution,
Our son was about to reveal the
information to the police.
And if you knew I was
covering all this,
how many more things would
you two have leaked?
Enough! Anyway, those people did so much,
you could have just asked them
to cremate the body, right?
You don't know anything.
Then we can directly
go to the police station.
You fool! To cremate a body
in another village,
you need permission from the Sarpanch,
the Panchayat Secretary,
and the villagers.
Now, it's not him,
the procession will be for us.
Please…
You stick to that witty mind of yours.
Just don't think like a criminal, please.
I can't.
That's enough seeing.
Get in, it's getting late.
You know my driving, right?
I don't know, sir.
They were here yesterday…
but by morning, the house was locked.
Can you call him once?
Why is he calling now?
-Hello.
-Hello, Sriram.
Yes, Mr. Murali, tell me.
Where did you go?
The house is locked.
We are going to my in-laws' house
in Chittoor for the festival.
That's the matter.
He went to Chittoor.
Going before the festival makes sense,
but what's with going after the festival?
Chittoor?
HINDU CEMENTERY - CHITTOOR
ELECTRIC CREMATORIUM
Hey, why are you throwing
all the weight on me?
Otherwise, should I
carry it all by myself?
Hold it.
Turn it.
Place it.
Hey! I have a small errand.
I'll be back after finishing it.
It's okay even if you're late.
Finish all your work and come.
In this gap, my work will also be done.
What, man?
Hey, are you bluffing?
What did I do?
Last week, because of your negligence,
wild boars tore apart and ate a corpse.
It was just a corpse they ate.
You're acting like they ate you.
This is what I don't want.
Because of your grace,
we made it to all the newspapers.
Officers can come for inspection anytime.
Understood?
So, shut up and stay quiet.
Be careful.
Let's see who has come.
Have you seen him?
He came there.
Which way did he go?
This way, towards Chittoor.
How long has it been?
How long…
It must have been about half an hour.
If it's been half an hour,
he wouldn't have gone far.
Hey, where are you?
I'm sending you a photo.
Some of their relatives are in Chittoor.
Find out all the address
details and call me.
PALAMANERU 06
CHITTOOR 48
You're driving very fast.
Can you slow down a bit?
If we had known this,
we would have started yesterday itself.
Right?
Don't irritate me.
Your dad is changing the gear.
The vehicle didn't stall.
Dad has learned to drive in third gear.
I haven't put into second gear yet.
Tell me.
Okay.
I'll take care of it.
Why are you still here?
Go fast.
Actually sir…
Without knowing who you are…
I…
It was unintentional…
I forgot to tell you.
By the way, my name is Raghava.
I am a drama artist.
-Drama artist.
-You…
Is your family full of brake inspectors?
You hit the brakes for everything?
Hello.
Let's go.
Uncle.
That…
You said you were a reporter earlier?
A reporter?
Who is he?
You said you were doing
a sting operation on us?
A sting operation?
What did you do to
warrant a sting operation?
You said the police uncle
who came to our house is missing, right?
Police missing?
Yes.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
One second.
Sir, I remember now.
A small clarification.
Before I got into the car,
did I have a small drink?
Yes, you had a small one, sir.
That's the reason.
Don't talk for sometime.
One peg is enough.
My body language changes.
What's that, sir?
I mean, I'm performing
a stage play tonight.
It's a character who catches the culprit
when a police officer goes missing.
Whatever I do, I do it naturally, right?
That's why you all got involved.
Well, ours is a family of artists.
If someone acts in front of us,
we naturally get involved with them.
-Oh!
-Interesting.
So, you didn't know
uncle was in the trunk.
Hey, shut up.
In a trunk?
-What do you mean?
-It's…
-Shut up and sit. Open your mouth,
-The thing is…
and I'll delete your Instagram.
I mean… now that he
knows you're an artist…
He's a child artist.
He's trying to outdo you.
Really?
Cute boy.
Same to you.
I have arrived at my destination,
can you pull over a bit?
Many VIPs are waiting for me.
I reached on time because of you.
-Okay sir.
-Okay, sir.
-Thank you, Madam.
-Bye, little one.
-Bye.
-Bye-bye.
Happy journey, sir.
Thank God, he got off.
Hey, shall we visit Tirupati
after this work is done?
Is the road closed?
I just made a vow, right?
What's the connection between the two?
Oh no!
How do we go now?
We don't even know the route.
Hello, sir.
Hello.
Wait a minute, sir.
Excuse me…
Sir, the road is closed there.
Which way should we go?
If you go straight, there's a village…
You should go through that village.
-So, is there no other way?
-No sir.
-This is the only way.
-Okay thank you.
Turn the volume down.
Salam Alaikum.
Welcome to Jam with Azam.
Do you know what
new reel we're making today?
Our Gun's circumcision festival.
Meaning, the circumcision ceremony.
Oh, brother.
Don't, brother.
Don't, man.
I won't let you go this time
without the cut.
Don't, man.
-Oh no.
-Put up another tent here.
What's this? They've
blocked the road here too?
Don't worry.
-What now?
-Let's see.
Inside, the chairs and tables
are all ready for the meal, right?
Yes, take care of everything.
Understood?
-Hello!
-It's getting very humid.
Why did you set this up blocking the road?
Do one thing…
Don't people need to pass through?
-Place the fans on both sides.
-Hello!
Hey, I'm talking to you.
Why have you set this
up blocking the road?
Mittu, Go inside.
What are you staring at, sir?
You… Sir! Sriram sir!
Greetings, sir! Greetings, Madam!
Meeravali! What are you doing here?
This is my village, sir.
Yes, but what are you doing here?
They're building a bridge
on that main road, right?
-Yes.
-I came this way
to go through the village.
And you're blocking the road here.
Well… today is my little boy's
Vadugu ceremony, sir.
You've come as an unexpected guest.
We'd all be happy if you came too.
Come, madam.
Meeravali, I'm going for some urgent work.
Please, can you have this removed?
That's not possible, sir.
That day, when you
registered all my lands,
you didn't take any bribe.
Today, you both must eat a few bites.
-Don't say no, sir.
-Won't be possible.
I won't listen to anything you say, sir.
Madam, you tell him at least.
Please we have to go.
This is very important work.
Dad dad!
Did you think of escaping again?
-Madam, come! Sir, come, sir!
-No dad!
-Why are they making that poor kid cry?
Let's go quickly.
Quick.
Oh God.
We've come to a function here.
Let's act like we don't know anything.
Hmm…
This is it.
Got it.
Why is he walking around the car?
Did the police get
suspicious, by any chance?
Do you want me to manage him?
What, are you scared?
I'll crush you.
Hello.
Whose car is this?
It's ours, sir.
Hmm.
-I didn't expect to find it so quickly.
-What?
What do you mean 'found'?
What's that, sir?
Why are you getting tense?
Why would we be tense?
We aren't tense at all.
This is a 2007 model, I think. Back
then, they stopped production in a year.
-He's talking about the car.
-I didn't have the money at the time,
By the way, its trunk
must be pretty big too.
Yes uncle, you'll fit too.
Hey, I'll kill you. Shut
up and stand still.
Who is this kid?
He's a young chap but very sharp.
He's my son, sir.
Is that so? Open the trunk.
How is that possible?
There's a lot of luggage.
I stuffed it all in. It will fall out.
My constable will arrange
it, but you open it, sir.
-It took two hours to arrange this, sir.
-You open it, sir.
Sriram sir!
Sriram sir! You're here too!
Food is ready, sir. Come, sir, come.
Hey, SI sir, why are you late too, sir?
Not late, bro. I got a message
that the Kothakota SI is missing.
Police get missing too? So?
I got late returning from that work.
Aha, that's fine, but do you have to come
to functions in your police uniform too?
This is the latest trend now, bro.
Oh! Nice, nice! Police shirt
on top, dhoti on the bottom.
-Oh my god, where's my gun?
-What are you searching for, sir?
-I can't find my gun.
-A gun?
Mittu isn't seen either.
I'm begging you! If that gun's gone,
I'm finished… I'll lose my job!
Please someone find him.
Sir, SI sir, a boy is
taking away your gun.
What! A kid?
Who is he?
Once he sees the gun,
there's no stopping him.
I'll take care of him.
Now shut up and sit inside.
Come quickly!
Catch him.
There! That way!
O goodness!
My heart nearly stopped.
I thought my gun had fired.
Did you pop a balloon?
By the way, where is he?
Myself Mithil.
Nice name.
Insta ID… Mental Mass Mithil.
-Oh, I see.
-I'm a big fan of yours, sir.
Thank you.
-Shall we make a reel?
-Sure, why not?
One second.
-Properties…
-Hmm.
-Oh, a Diwali gun.
-Yes.
-Yeah, one million views for sure.
-No, two million views.
-I'll give you the narration.
-Okay…
I'll hold the gun like this and shoot you.
You have to act like
you've fallen. That's it.
This is my novelty!
These are the kind of people we need.
-Proceed, proceed, proceed!
-Thank you.
Ah… but the placement…
-Where should I shoot him?
-Placement… here?
Oh, there? Not good.
Oh, here?
I already shot someone there.
Oh, better shoot here.
Here!
Then the bullet will go like this.
We can add it in graphics.
Oh my god! Mind-blowing, yeah!
-You sit down. Hey, you start.
-Shoot!
Yeah.
Hmm… turn your
face a little to the right.
Sir, you search inside,
-I'll search outside the house.
-Okay.
-Hey!
-Let's go.
Yeah, this is the heights of emotion.
Is the profile okay?
Don't move, uncle.
-Make sure the gun doesn't move.
-Wow, what an expression, uncle!
-I just did this much…
-Move aside!
Hey, focus.
Oh no!
Super uncle.
Hey, Azam!
Shh… a reel is being filmed here.
Don't disturb in the middle.
-Shoot.
-Hey, you fool!
That's a real gun,
you'll die if it goes off!
-Please don't shoot me.
-take it easy uncle. It's just a dummy.
Please tell.
-Don't listen to them.
-What should I tell?
Tel him not to shoot.
He's got the gun.
If he starts shooting, we're all dead.
They are just blabbering uncle.
-Don't listen them.
-I beg you.
-Just one bullet… let me shoot.
-Shoot him.
-Don't, don't.
They are lying.
Dad, I don't know anything!
I just found the gun there.
Oh my god!
Why he's taking the gun?
Hey, that's a real gun,
why are you laughing?
-Listen to me, son.
-Statue!
Hey!
-Dad!
-What is it?
Will you stop this program,
or should I finish it?
-Ah…
-son…
Shall I shoot?
-Thank god, you're back?
-Get in.
Hey Mittu, what are
you looking at over there?
The circumcision…
What does "circumcision" mean, Dad?
Will you shut up and get in or not?
Come on, tell me, Dad.
You know everything, right?
Do I have to tell you?
Come closer.
Now…
No, no, no, I don't want it!
-I have to tell you.
-Dad, sweetie.
Wait, wait, wait.
My dear… I won't let anyone do something
to you that you don't like.
Can I trust you?
Absolutely!
I swear on your gun,
will you give me my gun?
-For sure?
-100%.
-Here you go.
-Very good.
Take care of the gun.
Where are you going,
you little rascal? Come sit.
-Meeravali!
-Sir!
Get the things ready.
Everything is ready.
Basheer, sharpen it well.
It should be done in a single strike.
You tricked me!
Listen to me, dear. This is our tradition.
Hell with your traditions.
If you want, you get it
done, then you'll know.
He can't get it done at that age, son.
Anyway, I won't get it
done in front of my dad.
Hey Meeravali, go outside for a while.
Sir, you don't know about him, sir. He's
been escaping like this for five years.
-Hey, I'll take care of it, you go.
-Go.
It's your fate, man.
Okay, dear? You'll get it done, right?
You've been troubling us since morning.
You're going to get it today, son.
-Oh god, I'm scared even looking at him.
-Okay, you stay.
Hey, don't gawk like a villain.
The kid is getting scared.
Tell him to do it with his eyes closed.
How can he do it with eyes closed?
I don't know, tell him to do it.
Sir, shall I turn off the light?
How will you do it with
the lights off, you fool?
Sir, we've done many things
in this kind of darkness, sir.
-Are you sure?
-Sure sir.
-Then turn off the lights.
-Okay, sir.
Don't be scared, son.
-It'll be over soon.
-It'll be over.
-Hey, are you coming?
-Sir!
-Coming, sir.
-I'm on the left, the kid is on the right.
-No problem, sir, right to left.
-Left…
-Right…
-It's done.
Oh no! You killed me!
He didn't get it done this year either.
Oh god!
I'm finished… completely doomed.
Sir, will you give a
reward for the job done?
After all you've done,
you're asking for a reward?
Hey!
Oh god!
It's not that, uncle.
For some reason, I'm doubting
that Panchayat Secretary Sriram.
Have you started again?
Listen to me.
Yesterday our SI went to his house.
And they left the village.
The dots are connecting somewhere, uncle.
No, you shouldn't
suspect everything like that.
Then do one thing.
Try talking to them.
If they say no,
I'll never get involved in this again.
If you say you won't,
I will go to any extent.
Connect the call.
-Hello.
-Hey, Sriram.
-Who is it?
-It's me, Head Constable Subramanyam.
-Sriram?
-Yes, sir.
-Tell me, sir.
-Nothing, man.
Did our SI come to your house?
Your…
Your SI, to my house?
Why would he come to my house, sir?
Besides, you know we had a fight, right?
I know that.
But someone from your colony
said he came that way. That's why I asked.
I mean…
there's the house next to mine, sir.
That's where the MLA's PA, Prasad, lives.
He probably came to meet him, sir.
Maybe.
Alright, I'll check.
Okay, sir.
I'll take your leave.
-Did you see, uncle?
-I heard.
He's stuttering.
If he stutters, does it
mean something's wrong?
Hey!
He's a middle-class person.
Won't he have that
much fear of the police?
Especially when I'm talking…
Who is it on the phone?
The police…
Police?
-Why?
-I think they're suspicious of us.
-How?
-But it's okay.
It is not confirm. just a doubt.
What happened?
Damn!
My car ran out of fuel.
Why did you stop here?
The car's out of fuel.
I'll go and get it.
How can we be alone on the road?
There are so many vehicles
moving on the road, right?
I'll be back quickly.
Don't be scared.
Hey Madan.
It's our car.
Caught the idiot.
Go, go, go.
Hey, let's take the bag
and leave right away.
Is that car his own or what? If we
take the car, the bag will come with it.
Hey!
Why is there no one in the car?
So what if they're there or not?
We found the car. Take the car.
No one here means it's not locked.
Mom, it's over.
Mom!
Someone is near the car.
Why did he bring the car from
there just to park it here?
Who are you?
What are you doing near our car?
Goodness!
You're acting more than the owner.
Looks like you have a PhD in theft.
Who are you? Why do you care what we do?
Did you think I took it out
because it was poking me?
I took it out to stab you.
Give me the car keys.
I won't give them.
Is he your son?
Can he bear a stab?
Don't be such a sadist.
Who puts a knife to a kid?
You should give him an electric shock.
What, madam? Is it okay?
Please!
Don't hurt him.
Then give the keys.
You should have given this earlier.
You gave it as soon as I asked.
What about your husband?
He doesn't do anything we ask for.
Hey!
The car isn't starting.
The car is out of petrol.
Dad went to get it.
Hey!
We have it in our car.
-Tell me.
-Boss, we found the car.
We are on our way.
-Come soon.
-Okay, brother.
Where's the car?
Why don't you answer when I ask?
I am asking to you…
Dad, two uncles came and took it.
Who came?
Can't you do one thing properly?
I told you when you were leaving,
not to leave us on the road and go.
Hey, why are you blabbering
without telling me what happened?
Are you waiting for
something more to happen?
Hey, if you talk nonsense
when I'm tense, I'll hit you.
Yes, hit me.
You argued with that SI the same way.
He came to our house and argued.
Now, someone else came saying
they'll kill us and took the car.
Did anything happen to you?
Nothing happened, for now.
If you bring all the fights
from the road to our house in
the name of morals and honesty,
we'll also end up on the road like this.
So, are you saying all this
happened because of me?
Yes.
Okay.
Fine.
Where are you going?
I'm asking you.
Stop.
Why don't you answer when I call?
All these days, I thought
I was the strength of the family.
Only now I realized
I'm the weakness.
You two, take the next
bus and go to Chittoor.
What?
I've been pleading, haven't I?
That I'll surrender.
I'm going to the nearby police station.
Have you gone mad?
What are you talking about?
I told you then itself.
That on the day we face a problem,
you must listen to me.
So, will you say whatever
comes to your mind?
I don't agree.
If you don't listen to me now…
This will be the last time I speak to you.
If we go, we'll all go together.
Anywhere.
Dad, the car.
Our car is arriving, dad.
Sir!
Raghava!
Greetings, sir, greetings, sir.
Ladies!
Hey!
Get down and greet sir.
Good morning, sir.
Raghava?
How did you bring this car here?
Sorry Mr. Raghava,
today's program is canceled.
The chief guest didn't come.
You…
Will you cancel my program just because
some chief guest didn't show up?
-We'll have it next week.
-I don't want anything.
-You do it yourself. I'm leaving.
-Mr Raghava, our vehicle is there for you.
I don't want your vehicle
or anything, go away.
Hey, who is he blocking the road?
-Hey, my fan's car.
-Step aside!
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Sir, greetings.
Hey!
-Who are you?
-You block my way and ask me who I am?
You bloody drunkard.
-This is my fan's car.
-Fan?
You snatched it away.
Where are they?
Tell me, or I'll see your end.
Look at this…
I will stab you.
Oh, really?
Look that way, man.
-Get down.
-I'm getting down.
What happened?
-What's the commotion?
-He came drunk to hit the car, sir.
Sir, this is my fan's car, sir.
-He snatched it.
-Why would I need to steal it, sir?
Do you know who I am?
I'm MLA Thimmappa's man.
Hey, do you know who I am?
I'm the Deputy CM's man.
Every criminal who gets caught
says the same thing.
He's a thief, sir.
Sir!
Sir, I must say, our artists'
performance was mind-blowing, sir.
So, they weren't real policemen?
Why are you making noise?
I'll make you clean the whole place.
Idiot!
Thank you very much, Raghava.
Hey, that's okay sir.
We might forget ourselves,
but we'll never forget our fans, sir.
Hey, what are you looking at?
Go get the car keys,
put them in sir's hand,
pay respects to him, and go.
Leave!
-Uncle.
-What, dear?
That blackie stole my phone too.
Is that so? I'm here.
I'll get it to you back.
Take it.
Hey!
Did you take the kid's phone?
Why are you nodding?
Bend down!
Bend more.
Now take the position.
I will give it if you ask, sir.
Why do you hit?
You take it.
That car is ours. They stole it.
How dare you call my fans thieves?
-You…
-Uncle, uncle, uncle, uncle, uncle.
You have to stab many times
with this knife. We have a gun.
Only one bullet. Bang!
Can't you keep your mouth shut?
He's a child artist, right?
He's trying to outdo you and win an award.
He's an artist, right?
-Award!
-Yes!
You did a big favor, Raghava.
-We have work, we'll leave.
-It's okay, sir. You go.
My bag is inside the car.
Please ask him to give it.
-Happy journey.
-Hey, my bag.
Hey, my bag… my gift bag.
Reddy, we finally found the car.
Madan just called.
Here he's calling.
-Tell me.
-Boss,
that Sriram guy tricked our Michael
and took the car again.
Hey, first kill that duffer.
The misfortune will go away.
That's not it, boss.
Sriram is the one behind all this.
I thought I could forgive him somewhere.
But I won't spare him.
-Hey!
-Boss!
I'm not sure what you'll do…
but I want him.
He must die at my hands.
Okay, brother.
The upcoming left is the cemetery.
I'm getting scared
as we get closer to the cemetery.
Should we go back then?
No, it's okay. Let's go.
Don't cause any trouble here.
Just do what I told you, okay?
Let him sleep like that.
I'll go check if anyone's there.
You stay here.
ELECTRIC CREMATORIUM
CHITTOOR
Brother, where are you?
Time is running out.
We have to burn the bodies.
Are you coming or not?
Hey, I told you I was
going out for some work.
I'll be there in a little while.
Alright, fine. I'm starting.
Hey, at least listen to me just this once.
Forget it, man!
If we get late, you'll end up blaming me!
I'll be here alone.
I'm going to burn the body.
Hey, Chandra! Listen--
Is anyone there?
There's just one guy.
If we can deal with him, that's enough.
How do we deal with him?
Brother!
-What happened, dear?
-My brother…
I couldn't even see him for the last time.
O brother! My brother.
If you have a chance, what will you do?
I would have been happy, brother.
Then?
What else could I do?
I would've just cried… you fool.
What are you doing now? The same.
What's the point of this much performance?
Brother… that's not it, brother. Well…
It's not that, brother.
It's been so long since I saw my brother.
Why did your brother become
an orphan in the first place?
-One day, my father and I had a big fight.
-Okay fine.
My brother involved in between…
I left the house in anger.
But then, you would be the orphan, right?
Brother, my father also came with me.
That's it, my brother became an orphan.
Who told you that's your brother's body?
Don't irritate me… just go from here.
Brother!
What is it?
Did he stop breathing, sir?
Is he not responding?
-Does he smell?
-Yes.
Then what else?
That's my brother's body.
Oh brother…
You've matched everything well.
But it's a deceased woman
who's being burned there.
This doesn't match.
Bye bye. I'll be going. Okay.
No one comes when someone alive. It's only
after death that everyone comes rushing.
Dear, why did you stop the car?
I'm talking to you.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Why did you stop here?
It's nothing.
I'm just scared… wondering if I can
carry this burden for the rest of my life.
Dad…
I'm hungry.
There should be a dhaba nearby.
Let's eat there and then go
to your mother's home. Okay?
Okay.
Shawarma Dhaba Chittoor presents…
on the occasion of Diwali…
the Hyderabad Food
Festival, on its final day,
featuring the special attraction… Paya!
Did Trump wake up?
Again he became president
that is the magic of paya.
What are you still thinking?
I was very scared.
About what would happen to his life.
Even though the panchayat secretary
outside felt what he
was doing was wrong…
the father inside
felt it was inevitable.
Why are you overthinking?
And more thing…
Sorry.
I got scared when you
mentioned the police station.
I spoke a bit harshly,
worrying that we might get into trouble.
Sorry.
You're also emotional, right?
I can't be like you.
You can't stay without scolding me, right?
-Dad!
-Yes son?
We've been traveling since morning.
Why haven't we reached
grandpa's house yet?
-Here it is.
-Where?
I know. You took a wrong route somewhere.
Yes,
you two are always right.
Isn't it right?
Hello.
Panchayat Secretary Sriram speaking.
Can you give the phone to criminal Sriram?
-What?
-Ok fine, Killer.
Who is it?
Is your partner in crime also besides you?
Hello.
I can't hear you.
One minute…
There's no signal here.
Who are you?
You don't get scared
unless someone tells you to.
Killing a policeman and trying
to make the body disappear…
Hats off!
We'll have your family's
felicitation ceremony later,
but I have all the evidence of your crime.
If you don't want this
to reach the police,
50 lakh rupees should reach me.
Sir. Sir…
Can you give me a minute?
What is this?
You're making demands where I should be.
Okay, so be it.
Thank you sir.
Eat slowly, dear.
Who was on the phone?
That…
A friend of mine called.
You do one thing.
I can't come now.
You take an auto and go home.
I'll finish my work and come.
What happened?
Why do you worry about everything?
Will I let anything happen when I'm here?
He has some personal problem.
I'll take a look and be back immediately.
Okay then.
-Hey Mittu.
-Yes.
-Go with mom.
-Okay.
-Alright?
-Take care.
Let's go.
Watch out!
Will you come to Greamspet?
-Uttara.
-Yes.
What happened?
My wife, my wish.
Then what about me?
Come.
-Bye.
-Okay.
Is everything okay?
Bye dad.
-Bye.
Hello!
What were you saying earlier?
Why the change in tone?
Put that aside and come to the point.
What will you do if I
don't give you the money?
What else?
I'll give the police all
the evidence I have.
Tell me which station are you going to,
I'll come too, we'll both go.
What?
I did all this for my family,
without anyone knowing.
After everything is out in the open,
what is there to be afraid of?
I myself will go to the
police station and surrender.
What more can you do to me?
Wow.
Claps, man.
You're a clever one.
But…
This might have happened
if you had committed the murder.
It was your son
who committed the murder, right?
Shall we go to the station now?
Sorry sir.
Get one crore ready by tomorrow morning.
Are you in shock?
Your tone has changed,
so my price has changed.
Besides, I don't think this
amount is a big deal for you.
If you get along with the MLA…
You'll keep getting any amount.
I'm off then, bye.
G. GURU MURTHY
Hey, Jiguru Murthy!
Hello… Hello…
Babu…
Not Jiguru Murthy, not Chiguru Murthy.
It's G. Guru Murthy.
What's your name?
Michael.
What do you want, son?
Your son-in-law.
Call him.
They are not at a shouting
distance to come when you call.
They are kilometers away.
Hey, call him.
A person who calls might have love,
but the person who comes
must have time, right, son?
So, they haven't come here yet?
If he says he'll come, I won't say no.
If he says he'll leave,
I won't say go away.
It's their wish.
It's their problem.
Hey, can you please speak in Telugu, sir?
There is no caste for hardship,
no language for pain.
Om Tatsat.
What's your problem, man?
Who is this guy?
My son Prakash.
-He's been missing for three days.
-Oh!
Whoever I ask says they don't know.
If I ask the police,
they say they'll find out.
Did you tell your daughter
and Son-in-law about this?
You can share happiness.
But you have to bear the sadness.
Did you tell them or not?
Even if It is easy to say,
I can't say it easily, right, son?
What's your problem, man?
He's like that, bro.
Whenever he's down,
he ends up tormenting everyone around him.
Huh? Huh?
Hey! This is all happening
because of you, right?
What are you doing here?
Bro, Am I visible to you?
What do you think you are?
Kamal Haasan from Kalki?
Hiding in the complex like that!
With whom are you talking?
You should go to the eye hospital,
not the police station.
You are asking 'who
are you talking to'?
Your son is right in front of you.
Where?
Where is my son, Babu?
Hey, you're here, right? Then tell him.
I haven't been seen by
anyone since I died, bro.
If I want to tell someone about this,
they can't see or hear me.
Finally, I found you.
I can be seen and heard by you.
Tell him I'm here, bro.
Dear!
Come quickly!
Our son has appeared, come quickly!
Oh my God!
Where is my son? Tell me, Babu.
I will offer 100 coconuts
in your name, Babu.
-Tell me, where is he?
-Tell me son.
Tell him, bro.
Where?
-Tell him I'm here, bro.
-Where?
-Tell me.
-I'm here.
-Where?
I'm here.
Ghost! Oh my God! Ghost!
Okay, we reached the location you shared.
If I need anything, I'll call you.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
What happened, man?
-A ghost!
-A ghost? Where?
There!
Come, man!
I won't come, you go if you want!
-Come on, you duffer!
-I won't come!
Hey, come! Come!
Dad, your performance…
I bow to you, dad. Peaks! You nailed it!
Mom, come here. I never
expected this from you.
You are awesome. It's not normal.
As far as I know, this is the best
prank video on my YouTube channel.
We found a total duffer for our prank.
If he had waited a little longer,
I would have offered coconuts.
You should have offered coconuts.
The opportunity never knocks twice.
I'll kill them all.
Bloody buggers!
Shut up, you duffer.
Your son is the one who
committed the murder, isn't he?
Like some great father,
you say you'll go to jail in his place.
How can I let you go that easily?
I'll reveal the evidence
and send your son inside.
Once someone's labeled a criminal,
it's like dying a little every minute.
After seeing all this, he'll feel that
being inside is better than being outside.
He'll commit another crime.
This time, whether he goes into the jail,
or end up dead in an encounter.
To have a future, one
has to be alive, right?
Dad, shall we go for a ride?
I love you, Dad.
That's a minus.
You don't know how to play.
Here, Sriram.
My husband and my son…
…should be better than
anyone else in this town.
Sorry, Uttara.
That day, I couldn't give
you what you asked for.
But you never left me.
But I…
…promised to be with you until the end,
and now I'm leaving you midway.
I don't know if I was a good
husband to you or not…
…but you were a good wife to me.
More than that…
…you were a good mother to Mittu.
From now on…
you're like a father to him.
I love you.
Sorry, Uttara.
My name is Sriram.
I am the Panchayat Secretary
of Horsley Hills.
A few days ago, Kothakota SI Vikram
and I had a fight.
He held a grudge and came to my house.
He misbehaved with my family.
I shot him during that fight.
I also burned the body.
Please don't drag my family into this.
Please.
This is my dying declaration.
What is it, Sriram?
What brings you here?
Well, uh…
One minute, sir.
-What is it?
-Sir…
-Can I have some water?
-Yes, drink…Take it.
Yes, tell me, Sriram.
What is it?
You look tense.
Actually…
I've come to file a complaint, sir.
About what?
It's… my bag was stolen, sir.
Oh, a theft case?
What was in it?
-One crore rupees, sir.
-Crore…
One crore rupees?
How did you get that much money?
I… had some urgent work, so I
borrowed it from someone I know, sir.
What was so urgent?
Well… someone was blackmailed me, sir.
What? Blackmail?
Who?
I don't know, sir.
Then you should file a
complaint against him!
Why are you saying it's a theft case?
If I file a case, he's threatening
to demand two crores, sir.
One crore is better than two, right, sir?
How can you just give it to him?
We're here, aren't we?
You don't understand my pain, sir.
First, call that SI.
I'll explain it to him.
It's been two days since he came to
the station. We're also looking for him.
Don't look for him, sir.
He won't be found.
What do you mean?
I'm the one…
…who killed him.
Killed?
Have you gone mad, coming to
a police station and saying such things?
This is Vikram's gun.
I killed him with this.
Why did you kill him?
Well… you know, right sir?
That day the minister was visiting…
he and I had a big fight.
After that, he came to my house.
He misbehaved with my family.
In the ensuing fight, I shot him.
I also burned the body.
Uncle, I've been telling
you since that day!
I was suspicious of him,
but you didn't believe me!
You commit a huge crime,
then file a complaint about stolen money?
What are you trying to do, Sriram?
Just tell us what you want.
Nothing sir…
-I need a favor from you.
-What is it?
Since I came and surrendered myself…
I was hoping you could
reduce the punishment.
That's not in our hands.
Then what is in your hands, sir?
Right now throwing you
in a jail is in our hands.
In that case…
I didn't kill him, sir.
What are you talking about?
Didn't you just come here and
confess to the murder yourself?
Now you're saying you didn't kill him?
I'm telling you again, sir.
It wasn't me who killed him.
The killer was…
my son.
Are you playing with cops?
Yes, sir.
My son killed him while playing.
Sriram, whether you
killed him or your son did,
a case has to be filed
and submitted to the court.
Tell us what happened
so we can write the FIR!
I'll tell you, sir.
But before that I have a small doubt, sir.
What is it?
Well… is murder a bigger crime,
or is blackmail, sir?
Both are crimes.
I'm asking which one is bigger.
Murder, of course.
No… no, sir.
As far as I'm concerned…
blackmail is the bigger crime, sir.
How so?
Because…
it's only because he blackmailed me, sir…
that I discovered someone else
was the real killer.
What? Someone else?
Hey!
We're speaking to you respectfully
because you're a government employee.
Are you playing games with us?
No, no.
No, sir.
If my son and I had really fired this gun…
there should be fewer
bullets in the revolver, right?
But the magazine is full.
Which means…
The gun didn't fire.
I had a doubt.
It's so hard to even pull off…
then how could Mittu have loaded it?
I opened YouTube and searched,
"How to open a magazine?"
I found out how many bullets
a full magazine holds.
That's when I got some clarity.
Only then did I realize that
if the gun is locked… it won't fire.
My son didn't kill him!
He could have been shot with another gun.
How can I maintain the gun count, sir?
I'm not a…
policeman, sir.
Like you.
What, uncle?
Why are you talking politely with him?
Throw him in a cell and give
him our special treatment.
He'll spill the truth.
I'll make him talk.
Should I lock him up?
Wait, sir, wait, wait, wait.
Yes, you should throw me in the cell, sir.
You definitely will.
But before that, I need to
send a little message to your sir.
Sir, I sent it to your WhatsApp number.
Please check it once.
The funny thing is…
at that very moment,
I got a message from my son.
Hi Dad! When will you come?
Ayaan sent a Reel.
He says he did it better than me.
You watch it once and tell me.
What is it, Uncle?
You look at it.
One small piece of evidence
got you caught.
I'm the one who killed him.
I… killed him.
Move aside a little.
Move, sir.
Hey!
-Why are you sitting in my seat? Get up!
-Huh?
Why are you sitting in my seat?
Get up!
You couldn't even control your anger
for a second while sitting in your seat…
but he came to my house…
on my bed…
…and slept with my wife.
How was I supposed to bear that, sir?
Don't come again.
-My husband got suspicious about me.
-That's not it, baby.
-Listen to me…
-Go…
Go!
I made my decision.
I followed him, waiting for the
right chance to kill him.
With the information from Edukondalu,
he was on his way to the
MLA's PA's house for the gift bag…
He saw your wife in the house next door.
Because of his lust,
he followed you wife.
I thought I missed my chance.
But fortunately…the gun
ended up in your son's hands.
Outside, firecrackers were bursting.
In my hands, the revolver went off.
Without any effort from my side,
you walked right into this.
To hide the crime,
you crossed the town with the body.
To frame you for this murder…
I started my work.
Wherever possible, I planned
things to make you look suspicious…
and turned the story against you.
There's one more thing none of you know…
I killed my wife as well.
As for the blackmail…
These murders will
eventually come to light.
Before that, I have to leave the country.
And for that, I need money.
You can only threaten someone
who's already scared, right, sir?
So now what?
You're going to throw me
in a cell with this flimsy evidence?
Put your emotions aside for
a moment and think a little logically.
To prove that the bullet that
came from the gun I used…
is the one in the SI's head…
you need SI's body…
What, Sriram?
You need the body, right?
It must be burned down into ashes.
The body is right there.
The body is right there, Sudheer.
My son didn't kill him.
Oh my God!
I have to tell Uttara.
In the relief of knowing
my son didn't kill him,
something else came to mind.
Oh my God!
Vikram's body…
I rushed to the crematorium for that body.
Brother!
The unclaimed bodies that were here
earlier… have you burned them?
I burned them. Why?
-You burned them?!
-Yes.
Amid that shock, I received
a call from MLA Thimmappa.
-Hello.
-Hey, Sriram.
Bring my gift bag and come here.
Your mother-in-law, your father-in-law,
and as a bonus, your brother-in-law…
are all here with me.
You take time until morning.
Give me my bag and take them away.
I felt trapped from all sides.
But… that's when God
gave me another chance.
I saw the unburnt body of SI Vikram.
When people have a problem,
they go to the police.
But if the police themselves are
the problem, who do we turn to, sir?
Enough now. Come on.
Let's go.
Whatever happened, Sriram,
what you did was still wrong.
It was a mistake, sir.
But for the sake of my family,
I had no choice, sir.
Please forgive me.
Okay. You must come
whenever we call you.
You can go.
-Hey, constable!
-Sir.
Okay, sir.
-Okay, sir.
-We've brought the body, dear.
What do we do now?
Don't try to think of anything new.
Just do exactly what I told you.
It's true that I took your car.
But there was no bag in it, sir.
However, I do have something you want.
Check your phone.
For the last time, if you have
something to say to your daughter,
now is the moment.
What is it?
-Leave them. Send them away.
-Okay, boss.
You missed one small logic, MLA sir.
If you're this tense,
it must be something
that could cause you trouble.
You've known me for years.
If I had found something that serious,
you would have been behind bars
the very next minute.
Actually, I didn't put
that gift bag in the car.
Yes. Generally, when we handle
these kinds of illegal transactions,
I put the bag in my car's trunk
and leave for a trip with my family
the same day to avoid raising suspicion.
But that day, I needed the money,
so I took the bag with me.
I assumed the crime would be blamed on
whoever came for the money.
Unexpectedly, he got arrested,
SI Vikram came to your house
instead of mine looking for the money,
and then he died.
Everything happened one after the other.
I'm really sorry, Sriram.
Sorry. Really sorry.
It's alright, sir.
-Eat, son.
-How much will you eat?
If you eat any more, you'll die.
That's okay, Dad.
Boost is the secret of my energy!
So, what now?
I'm hungry too.
I haven't eaten in three days.
Go away.
Okay, come.