♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my playful charm♪
♪Just to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for you♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
(Ten years ago)
(Jiang Xiaodi, Jiang Niannian's Brother)
I can skip meals,
but Xiaodi's still little,
at least let him eat something.
Eat?
Where would we get the money
to feed two useless mouths?
If you ask me,
you two shouldn't even go to school.
Talk to them properly.
Niannian is sensible.
As for school,
you're not going anymore.
Why can't I go to school?
Because Qingqing
needs to live well in France.
She needs brushes and paint.
And she has tuition to pay.
Did you wire Qingqing the money?
Yeah, it's sent.
Our Qingqing
(Jiang Qingqing Amount)
will be a great artist.
Your family got such a good kid.
That's your ancestors' blessing.
(If I had money,)
(I could take Xiaodi away.)
(Why don't I have money!)
90 million, going once.
=Episode 6=
=Tears of a Fool in Love=
(Jiang Qingqing, Jiang Niannian's Stepsister)
90 million, twice.
100 million.
100 million!
The top bid has hit 100 million.
Any higher?
I didn't expect
you'd bring me to such an elite auction.
Because you're a top student
from Saint Martins in France,
and also my mother's alumna.
You're worthy of being my companion.
You're so good to me.
100 million. Sold!
Congrats to that gentleman.
Next,
let's welcome the host and his companion
to present the crown
to tonight's most valuable "item."
(I shouldn't have brought her)
(to this filthy place.)
(But I couldn't resist
watching her suffer for me.)
(Ye Lang.)
(You brought Jiang Qingqing here on purpose.)
(Was it all to shame me?)
(Why does punishing her)
(make me feel bad?)
(I want everyone to see clearly)
(the woman by Ye Lang's side
will only be me.)
Sir.
You can enjoy your auction item now.
No rush.
The night's still long.
Let's take our time.
The bed's too soft.
Look at this table.
Isn't that more exciting?
Go wait over there.
The hosts sent something over.
Want to come take a look?
You just said I could enjoy myself.
Why act all proper now?
Put me down.
Put me down!
Young Master,
you tricked me into coming here.
Wasn't it just to test my feelings?
Where did he kiss you just now?
You guess.
♪Bit by bit, marking you with kisses♪
♪Like shadows entwined in the night♪
♪You are mine♪
Ye Lang!
I'm your companion tonight!
Let me out!
♪I love you, with no limits♪
♪Crimson bite marks♪
♪Like I need you, and can't stop♪
If I hadn't come,
would you have...
♪The night melts♪
I belong only to you.
♪A tender dream♪
You belong only to me.
♪There's clearly no breeze in here♪
♪Why is the fire slipping out of control♪
♪The heat is rising♪
Jiang Niannian!
Ye Lang is mine!
Hands off him!
(Jiang Qingqing.)
(A man I don't want)
(isn't yours either.)
(Since the Li family
has no clue about Xiaodi,)
(I shouldn't stay in this den of danger.)
(I'd better leave now.)
(Ye Lang.)
(This time)
(I truly have to say goodbye.)
(Kill Ye Lang, Jiang Xiaodi will be back.)
Mr. Zhong,
let me handle it.
Ms. Jiang,
why are you still here?
From what I know of Young Master,
trying to please him like this won't work.
As long as
he hasn't driven me away,
I'm still his wife.
Good luck then.
You shameless girl,
you still dare show up?
Watch your mouth.
You're nothing more than a plaything.
Let me remind you,
the Li family
sent an invitation to the Jiang family.
Besides,
that day's auction
was just a little game between us.
You got locked in the restroom.
Isn't that clear enough?
So what?
My background is spotless.
I'm more fit for the Li family than you.
But now,
I'm the one who married Ye Lang.
You...
Honey,
you're here.
You sent the people
who raised you to prison,
you don't deserve to be his wife!
I'm the one who sent them to jail.
Ms. Jiang.
The driver is ready.
Please leave.
The outsider's gone.
Young Master.
Time for your medicine.
(Jiang Niannian.)
(So you really are giving up on me?)
Your carotid pulse frequency
is 0.3 Hz slower than before.
Your physiological data
has fully returned to normal.
Your muscle fibers
are 24% better than average.
Relax.
When I die,
I'll lie on your table, nice and still.
But now, you need to tell me
if Jiang Niannian poisoned it or not.
That bowl of medicine you sent
was different from the last one.
The sedative content increased by 33.3%.
As for this snowflake crisp,
its sweetness,
texture,
and cream ratio
are all decent.
But if this were to take you down,
based on your weight,
you'd need to consume
at least a ton of it continuously.
And what about the scented oil report?
I'd actually advise you to use less of it.
Why?
The sedative components in the fragrance
interact with your medicine.
If your sleep improves
and you live a few more years,
how long will I have to wait to dissect you?
(Jiang Niannian.)
(Are you just someone's pawn)
(or the one playing the game?)
(Did you ever truly love me?)
Have you been under too much stress?
Are you getting paranoid?
Want me to
give you some counseling?
I bet you want my heart out for that.
So you figured it out.
Jiang Niannian.
Niannian?
Find Jiang Niannian right now!
It's Bloody Peony.
She hasn't shown up for a long time.
I heard she got married again.
I heard it's the Li family.
Who would marry a widow
who's "killed" three husbands?
Always flaunting herself,
dreaming she'll rise to the top.
Waiter.
This is so dull.
The wine's
as bad as the people here.
What about this one?
What a gorgeous drink.
What's it called?
I made it just for you.
Because it's me.
Jiang Niannian.
I thought I'd never find you.
You've got the wrong person,
handsome.
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
Jiang Niannian.
Why do you always leave me behind?
Ye Lang.
We were never meant to walk the same path.
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
You don't know
what kind of person I really am.
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
I... I don't need to know.
As long as it's you, that's enough.
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪
(Ye Lang.)
(Sorry.)
(Before I find Xiaodi,)
(I still need to use you)
(to find who's behind this.)
♪La la la♪
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪