[A Splendid Match]
[Episode 25]
My Lady,
did Third Master Chen come there
to ask for your hand in marriage?
He said
he came back from Tongzhou.
Then he must've asked Old Madam Ji
for permission to marry you!
Did she agree?
That's wonderful!
I didn't expect you...
to actually be getting married.
It all feels like a dream to me.
Me too.
I don't know, but something feels off,
and I can't really explain it.
Right now, I still have
a tricky matter to handle.
[Marquis Changxing's Mansion]
Okay, I got it.
Thank you.
My Lady.
How was it?
The gatekeeper said
Young Lord Ye has been on duty
in the palace these days
and won't be out for a few more days.
Of all the times to be on duty...
But Guard Li came back once
to collect a change of clothes
for His Lordship.
My Lady,
why don't you write a letter?
I'll find a way to pass it to Guard Li
so he can deliver it to His Lordship.
No.
I must
tell him myself about this.
Otherwise, it would be disrespectful.
It's all my fault.
I should've told him earlier.
Lie down.
Here.
Ye Xian,
you always have a way.
Since you've been here
these past few days,
Shuanghua is
getting better day by day.
She's eating and sleeping well,
and can even run and jump again.
I think
she's simply fond of you.
Your Majesty flatters me.
As I see it,
she hasn't taken a liking to me.
She's taken a liking
to the jerky I brought in
from outside the palace.
Come on, Shuanghua.
Looks like she's grown tired of
palace food
and is craving something new.
Even a dog is like this,
let alone people.
Speaking of this,
it reminds me of
something rather strange.
The other day, my throat was itchy,
and I wanted some pear soup.
But after giving the order,
I had to wait an hour
for it.
Yesterday,
Mr. Fu came to give me a lecture
and also wanted pear soup.
Yet it was served
almost immediately
and even at just the right temperature.
I found it rather strange,
so I ordered someone to look into it.
Guess what?
Turns out that the Huangji Palace's
small kitchen has been preparing
pear soup and lamb broth
for him all along.
That is indeed strange.
Speaking of which,
I've also encountered
something strange over the past few days.
Go on, then.
Does Your Majesty know
that the Penal Court
has a file storeroom?
The late Emperor told me about it.
The Penal Court
keeps all its oversight records
on court officials there.
Yes,
the records for every official are there—
except for
one particular person's.
Your Majesty, tell me,
isn't that strange?
Strange.
Yours is even stranger.
Jiuheng, rest assured.
Leave this matter to my wife and me.
Okay.
Then I will leave it to
you and your wife, Zhonglu.
I really envy you, Jiuheng.
You're so carefree,
and yet another great blessing in life
is coming your way.
Unlike me—
ever since Grand Secretary Fan Chuan
left the Hall of Literary Profundity,
and now with you gone as well,
I've been run off my feet.
You have no idea.
The memorials are stacked so high now.
Just today, I was urging
the Senior Grand Secretary
to bring you back as soon as possible.
Oh, you.
[The Emperor Establishes Supreme Order]
I can see that all you officials
of the court have served diligently,
each fulfilling your own duties,
loyal to the nation,
and exhausting your minds and efforts.
I am very pleased.
Therefore, in consideration
of your tireless efforts,
I hereby abolish the post of
Inspector of the Penal Court.
Let us henceforth be united in purpose,
working together on affairs of state
to secure peace for the people
and stability for the realm.
Your Majesty is wise!
Long live the Emperor!
[The Emperor Establishes Supreme Order]
[Gu]
My Lady.
How did it go?
Did you manage to see him?
A fire broke out at the Penal Court,
burning much of it to the ground.
Young Lord Ye is so busy
he can't get away.
I heard my husband say
that after the court session,
the Senior Grand Secretary's face
was black with fury.
It seems
even the Senior Grand Secretary
had no prior knowledge
of His Majesty's intention
to abolish the post of
Inspector of the Penal Court.
Old Madam,
Second Madam,
Madam Yao has arrived.
She wasn't expected until noon.
She's early.
She must be
eager to move forward with
Lian and Yao Wenxiu's wedding.
You should hurry over.
Mother, please come along.
For such an important matter,
we need you there to make the decisions.
That's true.
Xiuju? Xiuju.
Go listen in over there.
If anything happens,
hurry back and tell me.
Yes, My Lady.
What should I do?
Madam Yao is likely here today
to set the date
for my wedding
to Wenxiu.
We're late,
Madam Yao.
-Old Madam Gu.
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
Not at all.
I was early.
Please take the seat of honor.
I came today
for Wenxiu and Lian's
engagement.
Right.
After the new year, Wenxiu will be 18
and Lian 17.
It's time to set a date.
Have you found someone
to pick an auspicious day?
What?
Is there something wrong?
Do you think it's better to have it
at the end of the year or next spring?
I'd prefer next spring.
After all, the weather will be warmer,
and the wedding attire will look lovelier.
I've heard that life as a new bride
can be quite difficult.
You two are lucky—
you don't have to worry about such things.
After all,
one has too poor a reputation,
and the other's
birth mother misbehaved—
neither of you is easy to marry off.
Are you stupid or what?
What did you say?
Are you genuinely ignorant,
or are you playing dumb?
Although Lord Yao is
the Vice Minister of Justice,
he has four sons.
And Yao Wenxiu
is the youngest.
By the time their family's assets
are divided down to him,
there'll probably be next to nothing left.
And he has no particular talent either—
to this day, he is only a xiucai.
If he still fails to enter officialdom
in the future
and his family provides no subsidy,
once you marry him,
he will depend
entirely on your dowry to get by.
If I were you,
I'd be worried sick.
How are you still able to look so pleased?
Gu Jinzhao, you...
Don't think that just because you have
a bit of money
you can flaunt it in front of me.
I'm telling you,
once I marry Wenxiu,
I will make sure every one of your shops
is driven into the ground!
You dare laugh at me?
I didn't.
How would I dare to laugh at you?
I... I envy you, if anything.
Why are you acting so weird?
Are you up to something?
My Lady!
How did it go?
Did they decide on the end of the year
or next spring?
Neither.
Madam Yao said...
She said she wants to
break off your engagement.
Break off the engagement?
Why?
I don't know.
Are you an idiot? How could you not know?
The moment I heard them mention
breaking off the engagement,
I hurried back.
I didn't hear anything after that.
No.
I need to go over there and ask why.
My Lady, you can't go!
Why can't I go?
They're talking about
breaking off your engagement.
If you go now,
how humiliating would that be?
Was it you?
I know it.
It had to be you.
Because only you
would be capable of such tricks.
You hate me,
so you came up with some schemes
to make the Yao family
break off the engagement with me!
Tell me, wasn't that it?
If the Yao family calls off
the engagement with you,
it'll bring shame
to our entire household!
What good would that do me?
Unbelievable.
Lan, let's go.
You're not going anywhere!
Even if it wasn't because of you directly,
it was still your fourth branch—
you got my father thrown in prison
and his reputation ruined—
that's why the Yao family is withdrawing!
I knew it.
Ever since you lot moved back,
this household
has had nothing but bad luck!
Nothing but bad luck!
You...
You're nothing but a bunch of jinxes!
Bringers of misfortune!
If the Yao family
truly breaks off your engagement
for a reason like that,
then not marrying into
such a snobbish family
might actually be a blessing for you!
Oh, a blessing
for you!
You can't get yourself married off,
yet you're jealous
that I've made a good match!
Maybe it's simply that Yao Wenxiu
never liked you
and has been
looking for a way out all along.
Nonsense!
I'll rip your mouth apart!
Zhao!
I'd like to see who dares bully my sister!
In any case,
our Yao family has wronged yours.
As for the betrothal gifts,
we have no intention
of taking them back.
Just consider them compensation.
But no matter what,
this marriage
must be called off.
Old Madam, Second Madam,
[Embrace Simplicity
and Maintain Innocence]
trouble! Trouble!
Second Miss, Eldest Miss,
Third Miss,
and Young Master Rong
have all broken out into a fight!
Second Miss hit Third Miss,
and Young Master Rong...
Useless thing!
Get out!
You ill-mannered brat!
Lian even hits people now?
With such a temper,
who could possibly endure serving her?
Well.
I've made my intentions clear today.
I trust you will come to a decision soon.
Don't drag it out.
Old Madam, Second Madam!
Hurry! Hurry!
Outrageous!
Every single one of you, outrageous!
Old Madam, Second Madam, please calm down.
It is not that this servant intentionally
broke the rules.
It's just that...
Madam He
has already arrived at the gate.
Madam He?
Which Madam He?
The wife of
He Wenxin,
Grand Secretary He.
Madam He is here?
Oh?
Does Madam He also associate
with your family?
Hurry, hurry.
Open the main gates to receive her!
Yes.
We're too busy today,
so we won't keep you any longer.
Cuilyu, see our guest out.
True.
Receiving your distinguished guest
is more important.
As for canceling the engagement,
I'll go back and discuss it further!
We should take our time to consider it.
My... my stomach
is feeling a little unwell.
Please take me somewhere to freshen up.
Yes.
Please follow me, Madam.
Welcome, Madam He!
This way.
Please, this way.
Properly speaking, I should have sent
a calling card first.
But since our two families
rarely interact,
I worried that sending a card ahead
would only cause you unnecessary trouble.
And I am
an impatient person,
and the person who entrusted me
with the matter
is even more so.
So
I simply came to visit directly.
Please don't take offense, Old Madam Gu.
Not at all.
Your presence in our residence
is a great honor.
Though I wonder...
to what do we owe the visit?
Old Madam Gu, please sit down first.
It's naturally a joyous matter.
Someone has entrusted me
with the task of
proposing a match for your Eldest Miss.
Zhao?
May I ask
who has such great prestige
as to ask you to act as matchmaker?
Who else could it be?
Naturally, it's none other than
the youngest
and most capable official
in the entire country—
Lord Chen Yanyun.
What?
Third Master Chen is proposing to Zhao?
Yes.
Lord Chen
has asked Grand Secretary He's wife
to be the matchmaker.
Old Madam and Second Madam
are receiving her right now.
Old Madam specially
sent me over
to inform you
so that you are aware, My Lady.
Congratulations,
My Lady!
What did you say?
Chen Yanyun is proposing marriage
to Gu Jinzhao?
And he's even asked
the wife of Grand Secretary He
to be the matchmaker?
My Lady, My Lady!
Please don't be angry anymore!
Be careful not to ruin your health!
Don't be angry anymore!
What did you say?
Chen Yanyun wants to marry Eldest Miss Gu?
That Gu Jinzhao?
Did you hear it clearly?
I heard it clearly with my own ears.
Absolutely no mistake.
This is bad.
Well...
How did things turn out like this?
We've handled things badly today.
It seems the Gu family
is not one to be trifled with so easily.
Madam,
but hasn't Lord Chen
already stepped down from his post?
The Master is
the esteemed Vice Minister of Justice.
Do we still need to be wary of him?
What do you know?
Chen Yanyun's so-called "idleness at home"
is merely a way of lying low
until the storm passes.
The moment it passes,
he'll be right back where he was.
He's the true favorite,
valued by the Senior Grand Secretary.
My husband cannot compare to him.
[Eternal Glory]
Take care, Madam He.
I really didn't expect this.
But Chen Yanyun
really had someone come to propose.
Even now,
I still feel the whole matter
doesn't quite seem real somehow.
Look at Zhao—
whether in terms of family background
or her own temperament and disposition,
how does she deserve to marry into
such a prominent family?
At this point,
we have to accept it
even if we aren't pleased.
Old Madam Gu, Second Madam Gu!
You haven't left yet?
Madam Yao, why are you...
Earlier, my stomach felt somewhat unwell,
and I felt a bit dizzy,
so I rested in your mansion for a while.
Knowing you were entertaining the guest,
I didn't have the servants disturb you.
Has Madam He left?
Yes.
Since she's left,
it's time to talk about
our two families' matters!
Just now, I gave it some thought,
and I feel the idea of breaking off
the engagement was indeed rash on my part.
Our two families
have been close for so many years,
and Wenxiu and Lian
have grown up together since childhood.
If we hastily break off the engagement,
wouldn't that be like
tearing apart a pair of lovebirds?
Madam Yao,
listen to yourself.
Our Lian is a young lady of good breeding,
not some wild bird.
Yes, yes.
I misspoke.
But regarding their marriage...
What do you think, Old Madam Gu?
Since
things have been said so plainly,
I will be direct.
Wenxiu and Lian's wedding
has been dragging on for far too long.
If your family is truly sincere,
then show us.
Thank you, Old Madam Gu, my future in-law.
I'll go back and prepare right away.
Mother,
the Yao family has treated us
so despicably.
Are you still willing to let Lian
marry Yao Wenxiu?
What choice do we have?
Say what you will about the Yaos—
they're still an official household
of the 3rd rank.
[Generations of Excellence]
My Lady,
with each autumn rain,
a deeper chill settles in.
Do be careful not to catch a cold.
My Lady, what's wrong?
Third Master Chen's proposal
is such wonderful news.
Why are you sighing?
I don't know.
I knew all along
that he intended to propose marriage.
But now that it's really happened,
it somehow doesn't feel real.
Am I...
really getting married?
Second Madam, Second Miss, greetings.
Why are they here?
Zhao.
Zhao,
congratulations.
You've made
such a good match.
When your second uncle heard the news,
he was overjoyed.
Right now,
he's drinking with your father.
Zhao,
regarding everything
that happened before...
it was because of my narrow-mindedness
and short-sightedness.
I apologize to you here.
I cannot accept such an apology.
And Lian...
I heard she quarreled
with you again today.
Lian
has been spoiled by me since childhood.
She speaks without thinking,
but deep down she regrets it.
Right, Lian?
I apologize to you.
I ask for your forgiveness.
You don't need to apologize to me.
In this household,
you can't bully me.
But Lan
has been bullied by you
time and time again.
She is the one
you should be apologizing to.
You...
Yes, yes.
Lian knows she was wrong.
We were just talking about
going to
Lan's place in a while.
We're going now.
Let's go.
My Lady,
Second Madam certainly
changed her tune fast.
I want to see Third Master Chen.
♪ In the bustling crowd,
every step foreshadows this meeting ♪
♪ Smiling, you remark
that no beautiful scenery in the world ♪
♪ Can match this destined encounter ♪
♪ Time passes quietly,
and this meeting feels like fate ♪
♪ A lifetime spent answering this riddle ♪
♪ If a story's beginning
requires courage ♪
[Glowing Bloom]
♪ I'm willing to take the brush first ♪
♪ With a true heart, paint a scene of us
together through days and nights ♪
If you ever run into trouble again,
♪ I'll always stand here,
quietly guarding ♪
you can blow this whistle.
♪ That very moment
of our first encounter ♪
♪ Whether it is fate or divine will ♪
♪ There is no need to analyze it anymore ♪
♪ When you look back, the wind rises ♪
♪ Gently stirring heartbeats and breaths ♪
♪ Only your palm remains warm as before ♪
♪ Warming my wandering, lonely soul ♪
Will you
♪ Everything exists because of you ♪
marry me?
♪ Every step together brings joy ♪
♪ Day by day, side by side ♪
If I ever
run into trouble at court in the future,
♪ Whether it is fate or divine will ♪
you can take
this letter of amicable separation,
♪ There is no need to analyze it anymore ♪
fill in the date,
and leave whenever you wish
without telling anyone.
♪ When you look back, the wind rises ♪
Or perhaps...
if one day you grow tired of me,
♪ Gently stirring heartbeats and breaths ♪
you may use it then as well.
♪ Year by year, side by side ♪
It's raining.
Why aren't you taking shelter?
Don't you know you'll catch a cold?
Let me check.
Your hands are cold, just as I thought.
What happened?
Why are you in such a hurry to see me?
I...
I think I must be losing my mind.
Losing your mind?
Originally, when you asked Madam He
to come propose marriage,
I was truly very happy.
But then, somehow,
I began to feel
a bit worried.
It all feels a little unreal.
I'm scared.
Was I too impulsive?
Could it be
that I made the wrong decision?
The wrong decision?
Let me finish.
At first,
I felt a bit uncertain and insecure.
But
when I saw you walking toward me just now,
for some reason,
I suddenly felt
that perhaps...
I could try
taking a chance.
You gave me such a fright.
I thought...
You thought I was going to back out?
Really?
So, Lord Chen, even you
would feel insecure?
That's right.
This is my weakness.
So you must keep it a secret
and not let anyone else find out.
Weakness?
Me?
Yes.
You.
Chen Yanyun,
I like you.
♪ Ask the passing time
whether it has forgotten ♪
♪ The moonlight of our first encounter ♪
♪ Year after year,
it etches your likeness ♪
♪ Count the faint shimmer
of the starry river ♪
♪ Yet none compares
to the gentle light in your eyes ♪
♪ At last, I see the galaxy
shimmering and swaying ♪
♪ Reflected in our eyes ♪
♪ I'll be with you forever ♪
♪ And enjoy
the beautiful scenery with you ♪
This is my favorite hairpin.
Grandmother gave it to me.
I'm giving it to you
as an apology.
Since it was a gift from Grandmother,
you should keep it.
I've already lowered myself enough.
What's with your attitude now?
Still putting on airs?
You're truly...
Forget it.
Anyway, I'm leaving
this hairpin here for you.
Wear it if you want.
If not,
you may throw it away.
Either way, I've apologized.
Xiuju, let's go.
Lian!
What?
I heard
that Yao Wenxiu
is not a good man.
Even though the engagement is set,
you should still look into him further.
What do you mean by that?
Wenxiu and I
have known each other since childhood.
How could I not know
what kind of person he is?
I see now.
Zhao is going to marry Chen Yanyun,
and I am going to marry Wenxiu.
You're the only one left,
without any prospects.
You're jealous,
so you're deliberately trying to upset me.
Isn't that it?
I've said all I have to say.
Believe it or not, that's up to you.
Instead of sticking your nose
where it doesn't belong,
you'd better worry about yourself.
Otherwise, you might end up
marrying some penniless nobody.
By then, how could Lord Chen and Wenxiu
possibly be brothers-in-law to such a man?
Second Miss speaks so harshly.
She took your good intentions
for ill intent.
Let her be.
I have said my piece.
As her sister, I have done my part.
[Ji Mansion]
Look at
this heartless girl.
Third Master Chen came to propose,
but she'd never even written a letter
to tell me beforehand.
Grandmother!
[Bound by Honesty]
Oh, my dear Zhao.
Come on, let me take a good look.
Grandmother.
My precious.
He said he'd ask Grand Secretary He's wife
to act as the matchmaker
and
have the Senior Grand Secretary
officiate your wedding.
I didn't expect him
to value this marriage so highly.
Third Master Chen is honoring you
in this way
because you deserve nothing less.
Our Zhao
is the finest young lady in the world.
Just let him.
That day,
Third Master Chen
suddenly came to propose,
[In Full Radiant and Flourishing]
which gave your uncle, aunt,
Yao, and me quite a shock.
Your uncle and aunt aside,
Yao and I
actually disapproved deep down.
The gap in status is too wide.
Moreover,
our Ji family
still bears the name of
his household servants.
The Chen family has produced officials
for generations.
They're highly prominent.
I was afraid that after you married,
you might be bullied.
Even knowing you're not worried,
there are some hardships in life
that are best avoided if possible.
No need to invite trouble.
But who would have thought
he would bring
a letter of amicable separation with him?
Well, who in this world brings
a letter of amicable separation along
when proposing?
It left Yao and me
at a loss for words.
[Ji Mansion]
[Glowing Bloom]
You've made up your mind?
You really want to
marry Third Master Chen?
I've already said yes.
So what?
If you feel forced
and want to back out,
I can help you
call off this engagement.
Aren't you afraid
of offending Third Master Chen?
What's there to fear?
The worst that can happen is
we lose the business.
He is our family's patron
and a Grand Secretary.
If you offend him,
you might lose
more than just the business.
You might
even lose your life.
You...
Gu Jinzhao!
What?
This is the most important decision
of your life.
I'm worried about you.
Forget it.
Yao.
Don't be upset anymore.
I spoke poorly.
I shouldn't have said those things.
I won't say them again.
Then I'll ask you one more time.
What exactly are you thinking?
Do you really want to marry him?
Yes.
You've thought it through?
You love him that much?
Yes.
You really are...
Grandmother!
Yao
just can't bear to part with you.
"A grown daughter cannot
stay home forever"—
that saying was meant for
girls exactly like you.
Even after I marry,
I'll still come back often to visit you
and Grandmother.
I've also read
that letter of amicable separation.
It appears to give you a way out,
but I know
if one day
something were to happen
to Third Master Chen,
with your temperament,
you definitely wouldn't abandon him.
If I couldn't bear to leave him,
wouldn't that only prove
that I've met the right man?
Grandmother.
Yao.
You two are my closest family
in this world.
I don't want to hide anything from you.
Yes,
I'd already made up my mind
and would never marry.
But
the moment Third Master Chen
told me he wanted to marry me,
my heart
began to change.
Just like Yao said,
if one day
something really happened to him,
I'm really not sure
that I'd have the heart to leave him.
But right now, there is one thing
I am sure of,
and that is, even if that day truly came,
I would still be able to
live my life well.
As for right now...
I'm willing to take that chance.
Since you've said as much,
Yao and I
can set our minds at ease.
This bracelet
was a gift from your grandfather
when he first came to
ask for my hand in marriage.
It's been with me for decades.
I'm giving it to you.
Wear it,
so it may
remind you on my behalf:
if you ever encounter hardship,
come back to Tongzhou.
This will always be your home.
Okay.
Take care of yourself.
[Great Yan Bank
General Circulation Banknotes]
Here's half of your dowry.
This many banknotes?
[Glowing Bloom]
My Lady, you're back.
Were there any letters for me
these past few days?
No.
Earlier, Old Madam's servant came by
to say that she wishes to see you
when you return.
Got it.
Why hasn't Ye Xian left the palace yet?
I'll head out later
and ask Guard Li again.
Okay.
[Crystal-Clear at Heart]
Zhao, come here.
This
is the dowry list
your mother left behind.
[Ji Family Dowry Register]
At that time,
your fourth branch
had just split from the main family
and rented a
modest three-courtyard residence.
It was too small
[Fine White Jade Bracelet]
[Huanghuali Desk]
to store all these things.
[Song Edition
of The Collected Works of Tao Yuanming]
So they've been kept in my storehouse,
under my care.
Now that you're getting married,
your mother's dowry
should naturally be returned
to you in full.
No!
All right.
I'm a bit tired.
You all may return to your rooms.
Zhao.
Keep it safe.
Thank you, Grandmother.
What?
Seeing me hand
all those properties over to Zhao
made your heart ache?
I originally thought
you'd return at most half of them.
I didn't expect
you to return them all to her.
Those properties
belonged to Dezhao's wife
in the first place.
If I insisted on keeping them,
would they not come
demanding them eventually?
Better for me to return them openly
and generously to her.
That way, everyone gets to save face.
If we waited until the day
she came to demand them back,
by then, not even
a word of gratitude
would be left for us.
But what about Lian?
Many of those items were already
included in Lian's dowry list.
If the Yao family were to
make a fuss about it...
If they were to make a fuss about it,
just talk back.
Tell them
those things
have all been given to Zhao.
If they've got the nerve,
they can go ask Chen Yanyun for them.
Seriously.
[Crystal-Clear at Heart]
What are you afraid of?
Don't be fooled by Chen Yanyun's
current idleness at home.
With his abilities,
his reinstatement
is only a matter of time.
In the future, Zhao
will be the wife of a Grand Secretary.
As for you, teach Lian more
so she learns proper manners.
Let her maintain close ties
with her elder sister.
Let's see if the Yao family
dares to mistreat her then.
You're right, Mother.
My Lady, you've always seemed
absent-minded these past few days.
You noticed it too?
I haven't slept properly for two nights.
Well, what if Xian finds out
that Zhao is marrying
the Third Master of the Chen family?
The thought of it makes me anxious too.
But His Lordship
will find out sooner or later.
Yes,
he'll find out sooner or later.
But with his temper,
there's no telling
what he might do.
Fifth Aunt!
Zhao.
Fifth Aunt,
are you free right now?
I have something to say to you.
I'm free.
I also wished to have a talk with you.
Let's go.
[The Penal Court]
My Lord.
Miss Gu has been looking for you
these past few days.
She asked if you would be free tomorrow
and said she wanted to see you.
[A Splendid Match]