"Episode 8"
(I'm home!)
Arashi?
What's going on? Arashi?
Ah! Help!
Arashi!
Arashi! Arashi!
(I'm home!)
Thanks for everything last night.
And now you're even seeing me off.
Of course. After all, I got to kiss you.
That's hardly a fair exchange.
Everyone values things differently.
To me, you're priceless.
Anyway, I'll pick you up again
this evening.
After tonight's race,
I'll tell him everything.
Once I do,
I won't have to be afraid anymore.
Good morning.
Is Rei running late?
Umm...
He said he'd be working on
assignments last night.
He might've fallen asleep again.
Hey, senpai? What's up?
Oh!
Just now at the gate,
a tall, handsome guy stopped me
and told me to give this to Kai-kun.
A hotel room key?
What? Oh, no, it's morning!
It's obscene!
No, I won't accept it.
He must be a real playboy to
ask someone out like this.
What if it was Fuma-san?
Huh?
So you know him?
My boyfriend.
- Whoa! This is spicy! Hot, hot!
Geez.
- Four in the evening.
To go to that location?
And right before the race, Fuma-san...
- Hey, hey, really? - I don't know.
- It's still early. - That's right.
An acquaintance, huh?
What's wrong?
I can't get through to Rei.
What? Since when?
He texted me last evening
that he had arrived home.
When was the last time you saw him?
Like, two minutes before that.
Huh?
Whoa... Isn't that a bit strict?
He's coming to watch
the race tonight, yeah?
Yeah.
Haa...
Ah, maybe I can finally get
serious about tonight's race.
Him again? Doesn't he ever give up?
Oh, look who it is!
The shady mechanic
and his side character.
Huh?
Hey, hey.
Isn't your expression a bit dark?
Are you worried?
- Come on. - What is it?
Nothing. It's just...
I just picked up a kitten.
Help me, Arashi!
Arashi!
If you value your life,
give me back my boyfriend.
You might want to rethink your tone.
What if one of my guys
decided to cut that pretty face of his?
What do you want?
Step into the race instead of Fuma.
I want to beat you and drink good sake.
You want me to lose on purpose?
If you involve the police,
outsiders, or the organizers,
I can't promise he'll be safe.
But if you do as I say,
he'll walk away unharmed.
Not a bad deal, right?
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love-"
Man, I hate that guy so much.
He pisses me off!
What the hell are you looking at?
Ah, right,
you can't talk.
Arashi won't lose.
Even if you use a dirty method,
do you think you can win?
You're just a loser who couldn't
win even when you cheated!
Hey, just keeping him
confined is enough.
What are you scared of?
Kidnapping him's already bad enough.
Therefore...
Here, cool, right?
I want to see your expression
when he loses.
Your beautiful face.
Keep it safe.
Arashi won't lose!
Not to someone like you!
Aki.
Arashi won't lose!
Don't worry.
If it's Fuma-san,
he'll surely accept it.
What?
Alright.
We meet again.
Let's have some fun tonight.
Let go of me! Let go!
Don't say stupid stuff.
Stop it!
You've grown defiant, haven't you?
Still as cold as ever.
Wasn't he your boyfriend?
Boyfriend?
He was just a toy!
A toy I broke
and threw away.
There it is,
that victim act.
You enjoyed being with me, didn't you?
Pretending you hated it,
but you were always happy
to come to be hugged.
No.
I just wanted to be a good boyfriend.
You laugh too much.
Because I feel sorry for him.
And now his ‘new boyfriend' is
going to dump him too.
- Huh? - Ah...
Shocked?
Should I show him
those pictures, videos,
and many other things
of you from back then?
Liar.
- You're lying. - It's the truth.
What do you think
your boyfriend will say?
"I don't want the something dirty."
"Take it back."
It's a lie.
It's already been many years,
but it's still the same as it was then,
Naive and dumb Kai-kun.
Just right for killing time.
How nice.
Kai and Rei seem so happy these days.
Yeah, totally.
You two...
Are you friends of Sorano Kai?
Uh, yes.
Is he still in the classroom?
No.
Seemed like his boyfriend
called him to go to a hotel.
So,
- no flirting allowed... - Wait.
I'm his boyfriend.
Wait. But I met him this morning.
Fuma-san has a piercing right here.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm afraid his shoulder will dislocate
or a bone might break.
So I asked him.
That guy...
- Which hotel? - Huh?
Kai's in danger. Please, just tell me!
Umm... Which hotel was it?
What? I don't remember!
- Neither do I... - Please!
When Fuma comes,
I'll ask him to let me race instead.
Are you really going out there to lose?
There is no other way.
Because Rei is the most important.
I've never done any maintenance to lose,
will it go well?
Do the maintenance as usual,
as a mechanic should.
Umm...
I'm sorry!
Please stop him!
Hey, hey, are you lost?
Stop!
Because of that weakling,
the plan was all ruined.
- Let my boyfriend go!
- If I let him go now,
you won't do as I say, will you?
Hey!
This 'love' thing is so hilarious.
Oh right.
Since we're all here,
let's have some fun.
Get on your knees.
Hurry up!
Brilliant. Like an obedient dog.
Makes me want to keep you as a pet.
Next up.
Bow your head to the ground.
Arashi, don't!
Not there!
Crawl to me.
Arashi!
- Let my boyfriend go!
- Don't be so impatient.
Now, a commemorative photo.
Alright, so miserable. Yay.
You've been mocking me a lot!
Fighting back?
Do you want to see your boyfriend hurt?
That's better.
That's how it should be.
- Kurosaki-san is so stubborn.
- What are you talking about?
What the hell?
Take that!
You...!
Ah, you're misunderstanding.
He invited me here. Stripped himself.
We were lovers once,
so occasionally, things like this
happen between us.
Kai!
Look at me.
Fuma-san.
I...
am not yours alone.
I'm dirty, ugly, and defective.
So I can't belong to just you.
You can. Of course, you can.
You're so beautiful, so good.
It's all right.
You're mine, Kai.
- He'll die! - Good!
Fuma-san.
Let's go home, okay?
Mm.
Cut it out, you coward!
Huh?
You can't win on your own,
so you use your gang,
and even using a knife.
If I were you, I'd die of embarrassment.
You coward!
You little...
Stay away from my boyfriend.
You weakling! Coward!
I said stay away!
Dammit!
Stop! Don't hurt Arashi!
Ah! Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
Oww!
- Tomaru-san. - Shut up!
Hey, you lot!
Don't lose and take care of this guy!
Otherwise, I'm not paying!
Hey!
You lot... Ouch!
The hell you doing?
Hey!
What?
What are you trying to do?
Don't do it. Hey, look!
This is for hurting my boyfriend.
I got it. How much do you want?
I said I got it! Don't!
Arashi.
The race went off without a hitch!
Even though those guys were
caught during the competition.
As for the situation,
the organizer will handle it later.
From now on...
Thanks.
- You were worried, huh? - Not at all.
I knew if anyone could handle it,
it'd be you, Arashi.
In the past...
I used to date that person.
He was kind to me at first.
But then, he suddenly started to hit me.
It became more and
more intense day by day,
and it left scars.
Even though my friends
told me to leave him.
But I didn't listen to them.
I thought it was because I was bad
and I thought he loved me.
One day,
I was tied to the bed.
Took off my clothes,
he brought his friends,
and they raped me.
After he laughed
and played,
he said he got tired of me
and threw me away.
Why are you crying?
Because Kai doesn't cry.
If Kai can't cry, I'll cry for him.
If Kai suffers, I suffer with him.
If Kai is in pain,
I'll endure the pain too.
Therefore...
Don't carry it alone anymore.
You're allowed to cry when it hurts.
I'm here for you.
I will wipe your tears
and take care of you.
So,
cry,
Kai.
Fuma-san.
Can I...
love you?
Don't ask me that.
My greatest wish
is for Kai to love me.
I'm sorry.
If we had met sooner,
I would have been able to protect Kai
before anything happened.
But...
we met now.
These tears...
they're happy tears.
Thank you
for saving me
from my nightmare.
It should be me
thanking you for telling me.
I'm happy too.
I'll show you by my actions
from now on, not promises.
I will make Kai so happy
that everyone will envy him.
I'm afraid of more happiness.
Then, I will make you so happy
that you forget the fear.
I will make Kai smile all the time.
Me too.
Again.
No, no.
- Again. - Hey.
Mm.
No.
Does it sting?
I'm fine.
When you tried to help me,
I fell in love with you again.
Have you ever fallen
in love with me before?
Can't you hear my heart?
If you don't tell me, I won't know.
I love Rei.
Me too.
What's the same?
Don't cheat.
Rei loves Arashi.
The weather.
Hmm?
Well,
when a storm comes,
rain always comes with it.
This is my new design.
(Love)
Mmm...
- Hey, how is it... - Ignoring me?
Always treating me like this.
- It's so tasty. - Really?
Oh, here they come in a pair.
They're always so dazzling.
Ready to go?
Mm.
Hey, Rinka...
Rei. Congratulations.
Thank you.
Honey!
Dammit!
I told you, stop calling me that.
They're flirting again.
Those two are amazing.
They're really intense.
You've been listening to
Love in the Air.
May you all enjoy
the unpredictable weather
and the wonderful days ahead.
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love-"