Memories are weird.
They make you laugh.
They make you cry.
Such is my life.
Like the ocean.
What you see on the surface,
is not real.
It conceals dozens of secrets inside.
My job is to clean the ocean,
in a dredging company.
I am trying to find myself
while cleaning the ocean.
I am trying to uncover the secrets
hidden underneath this quiet ocean.
My life is similar to this.
Calm and simple on the surface.
But dark, chaotic,
and complicated on the inside.
Ronnie.
Have you guys reached there?
Where is Tara?
Tara!
Martin. We've just finished the job.
We don't have enough oxygen.
Tara, the Navy is already on the spot.
You just have to assist them.
And report to Captain Aman Sharma
for briefing.
Okay? Thank you.
Martin!
This is Tara Salgoankar.
CO of Maria Sea.
Do you copy?
Hi, this is Captain Sharma.
You came right on time.
How can we help, Captain?
There was a blast.
I need you to dive in with your men,
and gather the remains
of the dead crew members.
Of course.
Copy that. Over and out.
I know this is your first time.
But you'll be fine, okay?
As you all just saw,
there was a blast in the hull.
And we're assigned
to excavate the remains
of the dead sailors from the sea.
Look, we do not have enough oxygen
or light here to be negligent.
So we're going to be intelligent,
resourceful, and fast.
And I really need you guys
to follow my lead.
Now, does any one of you
have a cold or congestion?
-No.
-Is any one of you… drunk?
-No!
Great.
You guys already know the rules.
Just follow my instructions
at all times.
Do not panic.
And lastly, don't forget to breathe.
Another one…
down there.
Stuck in the rubble.
We'll need a crane.
Okay.
You notify the Coast Guard
-and send them the coordinates.
-Yes, sir.
I hate you.
I hate you, Tara.
Why don't you quit drinking?
Stop.
-Leave me.
-Look at yourself!
-Look at your condition!
-Shut up!
-Shut up.
-Get out of my life…
I will slap you.
-Do not talk like my father.
-Shut up! Shut up!
-Are you… You don't…
-Shut up!
-care anyway!
-Mom, please. Please don't fight. Stop it!
-Tara. Go back.
-Please, Mom!
-Tara, go back to your room.
-Stop misbehaving with the child.
-Learn to behave.
-I am!
-You be good to me!
-What are you saying?!
Stop!
-I will slap you.
-Let go of my hand!
-Let go!
-Leave my hand!
Are you crazy?
You will die.
Hey…
Tara.
Kabir!
Tara!
Are you okay?
Can you breathe?
What the hell is this?
Are you insane?
If I hadn't arrived on time,
you would have joined the dead.
Take her to the medical room.
Tara…
Do you want to get my license canceled?
Your job is only to clean up.
Rescuing is the Navy's job.
Why were you trying to be a hero?
Someone has died.
How can you be so careless?
Call me back.
-You've debriefed them?
-Yes.
-It's done?
-Good.
-Can you tell us about the blast?
The blast happened in a fishing vessel
coming from Italy.
Any casualties?
Unfortunately,
we lost five crew members.
Some minor casualties
and minor injuries.
But the Navy has rescued the others.
No credit to us.
We were there, as well.
Forget it.
Are you okay?
If you are genuinely concerned,
then get your equipment fixed.
Point taken.
But you should have behaved
more responsibly.
If it wasn't for Captain India,
then the matter could have escalated.
Kabir.
Evening, we have an assignment.
-You are coming with me.
-Yes, sir.
There's mass at 7:00 p.m.
You've to attend it.
Another one of your dramas!
That's an order.
The investigation is still going on.
As soon as we get the final reports,
the Navy will release
an official statement
very soon.
Excuse me. Thank you.
Hello, Captain.
Martin. From Martin's Dredging.
Hi. Captain Aman Sharma.
I just wanted to thank you
for saving my mermaid.
Tara.
Oh.
I've heard a lot about you.
Gold medalist.
More than 100 successful missions.
Thank you.
But the Navy's salary
doesn't justify your skills.
Ever thought of joining a private firm?
I never really thought about it.
Just in case.
Hey.
Hey, Captain.
How are you now?
I am good.
Good.
You shouldn't be drinking so much.
And you shouldn't be yelling
at people without a reason.
It hurts.
David.
Get me more, please.
-Sure.
-Thanks.
Can I sit?
The seat's empty.
At your own risk.
To the fallen.
I am sorry.
Why?
I shouldn't have misbehaved publicly.
You mean if you were alone,
it was okay.
It's not what I meant to say…
And what if you are in bed,
and she really wants it?
Are you flirting with me?
What do you think?
Here you go.
Hi, Captain.
-Hi.
-How are you, man?
David.
You know our Captain
is such a good boy,
that he won't even spank a girl
in bed.
-Why not?
-No, I was…
You're disgusting!
Sorry, Father.
What are you doing?
Can we go someplace else?
Where?
Somewhere away from this boring mass.
-Are you…
-Come.
Where?
Come on. I'll tell you.
What?
Aren't you scared?
Like to… live with the dead.
People who are alive scare me,
not the dead.
But still.
A girl like you… in this profession?
Because…
I am good at it.
Martin…
I mean, Martin doesn't have
a sound track record.
Who cares how Martin is
as long as he pays well
and on time!
Enough about me, Captain.
Tell me something about yourself.
First of all, stop calling me Captain.
My name is Aman.
There isn't much to tell.
My great-grandfather was from Goa.
He settled down here with
a Portuguese sailor.
He settled down here.
I was born here.
I visit India sometimes.
Nothing else has happened
that's worth mentioning.
Nothing special…
An entire ship drowned.
You should give some kind
of credit to life.
Not many witness such an event.
Sorry, I didn't know
we're counting traumatic, as well.
Life consists of everything.
Little water, little sand.
Some clouds, some soil.
The rains, the high tides.
A bit of love.
A bit of chaos.
Nice. That was really good.
You wrote it?
My dad wrote it.
He's a writer?
No. He's retired.
He does everything he wants to.
And mom?
Dead.
I am really sorry.
It's okay.
It was… a long time ago.
Are you feeling cold?
I am okay.
Leave me. I am fine.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
Wow!
So many aquariums.
It's illegal.
Is this your side business?
Shut up.
I love aquariums.
They help me…
relax.
Grandma doesn't like that I drink.
That's why…
I keep a water bottle…
filled with vodka.
Cheers.
Oh, pickle.
Can I have some, please?
-No.
-Only a little, please?
We just put it to dry yesterday.
If you open it, it will be
ruined. And grandma will be…
Make yourself at home.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Captain,
ready to sail?
What are you doing?
What do you think?
That you are drunk?
So…
don't you want this?
Captain.
Tara?
What will you do
with all these pickles?
Have you been selling them?
No. Only four of these are for me.
The rest are for Monu,
Bittu, Nanu and Bhoomi.
Why don't we buy ready-made
pickles like the rest?
It's not all that bad.
Oh, no… readymade pickle!
I wonder what ingredients
they use to make it quickly.
Pickle is the sweet fruit of patience.
Hard work.
Wait.
Lots of spices and sea salt.
The saying goes,
"Whoever's body the sea salt touches,
is blessed with a long life."
Take me for instance.
I'll be turning 72 soon.
No! Not at all!
Do you mean you were a diver like me?
Absolutely.
As a kid, I would dive right
into the ocean.
I was the best swimmer in my village.
Mom, can I taste it?
Go ahead.
Did you cover it with sugar or something?
-Tastes weird.
-Why will I add sugar?!
Check, dear.
It's so nice.
Unnecessarily…
And who do you think
you take after?
Your father is an earth lover.
Like your grandpa.
But we Salgoankar women
are daughters of the ocean.
God. I am late.
I've to get to work.
Why don't you quit this job?
I am the daughter of the ocean.
Remember?
But you've to live on earth.
You will have to return.
I will and I will make
the best pickle like you.
But not now.
-Understood!
-I'm having another one.
It's amazing.
-Bye.
-Good morning, Tara.
-Good morning.
-Good morning, David.
Heard about the incident.
How are you?
I am good now.
Thanks.
So…
So, what?
How was your date?
We're going for the office picnic.
I can't come.
But it's compulsory.
Says who?
I did.
This is an office, not a school.
And anyway,
I've to clean my fish tank.
I can't come.
Clean your fish tank on Sunday.
The picnic is on Saturday.
And you are coming.
We've already made the booking.
I've five and not one.
The largest tank is ten feet tall.
Takes time.
And if it's too much trouble,
then deduct it from my salary.
I am not running a corner store,
to deduct your salary.
Don't come if you don't want to.
"Deduct my salary!"
That's all I had to hear.
-Hi.
I've come to see Tara.
I'll call her.
What exactly happened last night
that the Navy landed up
on our doorstep in the morning?
Shit! Damn it!
-Hey.
-Hi.
What are you doing here?
This is for you.
I hate flowers.
I love flowers.
This is my workplace, Aman.
You passed out last night
before giving your number.
I could have gone to your house
or here.
And anyway, I feel it's too soon
to meet your family, right?
What say?
Can we continue last night's date?
-You know, I…
-Forget it.
Your receptionist seems nice.
I'll… ask her.
-You dog!
-What…
The world's so cruel
You are like the soother in my life
When we met
I felt closer to God
Seems like I am in love
My heart goes out to you, beloved
Can't live without you
I've renounced the world in your love
I've become a wanderer
My heart goes out to you, beloved
Can't live without you
I've renounced the world in your love
I've become a wanderer
Can't see anyone beyond you
All your wishes have been answered
You are the one I see
You dwell inside me, beloved
My days and nights
Are spent talking about you
With you, I want to be
Forever and ever
-Where are we going?
-I have a surprise for you.
-Can't live without you
-Come.
I've renounced the world…
Come, I want to show you something.
Come. It's a surprise.
Look.
Does the mermaid look familiar?
It's a tribute to you.
Tara.
Tara!
Calm down.
It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay…
Thank you so much, sir.
-I am really sorry.
-Please be careful.
Yeah, fine.
What drama was that?
-I was doing a drama?
-Was it me then?
What is this?
Look, I am really sorry about this.
But why did you have to do all this?
And was this your surprise?
A ship that was littered
with dead bodies?
You were there.
I just wanted
to do something nice for you, Tara.
By recreating a tragedy?
Wow. Genius.
It's my fault…
that I loved a drama queen like you!
Do you even know…
Ramesh.
Look.
Your daughter made us proud.
Come on, Mom.
Don't start this in the morning.
People are saying
Tara was completely out of control.
Like she was possessed.
Mom…
we are gearing up to go on Mars.
And you are still stuck
on ghosts and spirits.
Everyone in the family knows.
They are all talking about it.
Like mother like daughter is
what they are all saying.
Not your daughter.
If you can't stand me, then I'll leave.
Like Mom did.
Then you can take care of your "family."
Forget it.
You know Mom's nature.
See how audacious she is!
Mannerless!
You please calm down, Mom.
I will calm down,
but what about the world?
I didn't do it intentionally, Grandma.
I know.
This is why I kept saying,
stop hanging around dead bodies
and join me or your father.
Now you've brought
some spirit back with you.
I can't deal with this.
Tara.
What is this, Mom?
You say such absurd things.
Think before you speak.
Why did you have
to bring Sukanya into this?
Hey.
Hi.
So, what did you find?
Straight to the point as always.
So, Leslie Fernandes used to work
for the Indian Embassy,
but now he's retired.
And after some digging,
I found a trail to Sicily.
So I am going to go there
and do some more digging,
and let you know what I find there.
But as always,
I am going to need some more cash.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Always a pleasure, Tara.
Hi.
Hey.
Indian?
Wow. Me too.
How can I help you?
Hi, I'm Neil.
Tara.
Actually, I needed a pond cleaned.
Sorry, we're booked
for the entire month.
I can't help you.
Thanks.
-The entire month?
-Yeah.
Because of the carnival.
It's a busy month.
Please help me out.
In fact, I can pay you extra
if you want.
Is it an emergency?
A big emergency.
It's an unattended pond.
If anyone falls in it,
it can be an emergency.
-Very funny.
-It's a life risk.
Call me when someone falls in it, alright?
Thank you. Please.
I am busy.
Tara, I am planning to throw
the grandest party in Malta's history.
But a dirty pond
will make it impossible.
My reputation is at stake.
-A party!
-It's not an ordinary party.
The grandest party.
Ever!
Please give me your address.
-Yeah, sure.
-Yeah.
-I'll see you then.
You? You don't have to come.
You can send any diver.
I am the diver.
Wow.
Do you know what's happening?
What do you mean?
He's trying to replace you.
Rubbish!
You say such absurd things, Kabir.
Navy boy Aman.
I've heard rumors.
Aman? He hates Martin's Dredging's.
He was telling me to quit.
So that he can take your place.
Why would he quit his job in the Navy
and clean garbage
from the ocean with us?
Does not make sense.
Money, Babu bhaiyya, money!
It's a curse!
Tara, are you really leaving?
Yes. I'll be back in a couple of days.
Don't take offense
to what Mom said, please.
Keep feeding my fishes, please.
Okay.
What do you want, Aman?
Forgiveness.
I acted immaturely.
It's okay. It's all in the past.
You are the best.
I have something to tell you.
You are quitting the Navy.
How do you know?
That Martin…
I told him to keep it a secret.
I wanted to surprise you.
Listen, I don't want
any more surprises, okay?
Your surprises give me nightmares.
I thought you would be happy to know.
Come on, stop pretending.
As soon as you found out I was not fit,
you came to take my place.
You didn't even like Martin.
You were telling me to quit.
So what changed now?
Tara, calm down.
I've no interest in taking your place.
Martin told me to do it.
He needed help.
He begged me.
Kabir heard something else.
You trust someone
else's word over mine.
Listen, I've got to go.
Tara.
Yes?
Martin's Dredging.
Oh, yes, Neil told me about it.
Please, come in.
Neil will be with you in a minute.
Please, make yourself at home.
Bathroom.
Just down there, to the left.
Thanks.
Often I feel
There's a secret in my heart
I want to reveal
But I can't
Conveys through the eyes
What language is this
That silence speaks?
I heard what she never said
Could this even be possible?
Tell me, God
Is this how love happens?
Hi.
-You sing really well.
-Hey!
Really? Did you like it?
I loved it.
Thank you.
Please sit down.
Oh. Thank you.
-I recognized you right away.
-I see.
I've heard a lot about you.
Heard what?
That you are a spiritual
and music Guru.
And all these people from around
the world come here looking for you.
I am not a Guru,
but I am a student of this universe.
Like you.
Do you feel that way?
Everyone in this circle
has their eyes on you.
They are like lost souls.
We are all looking for something.
Searching for something.
Don't know what it is.
Recognition.
Happiness.
Fame. Power. Money.
Love.
Lust.
Look at yourself, for example.
Away from home, from friends,
you're here, among strangers.
Ever asked yourself
what you are looking for?
I don't know.
What do you see here?
Nothing.
Close your eyes.
Now… focus on your breath.
Listen to your breath.
Just…
surrender to the moment.
Relax.
Now you can hear…
what this moment is saying to you.
Wow.
There is so much here.
Yes.
It's amazing.
Just because you can't see the ocean,
doesn't mean it's not here.
We just aren't looking for it.
Not focusing on it.
We always… cover our eyes
with a layer of lies.
The future, the past…
is not in our control.
And yet the world carries
them on their back.
And this burden of memories
and dreams…
breaks their backbones.
And then they come here
looking for that moment of peace.
Hoping that someone will make
them hear their voice.
They don't know that finding the truth
isn't hard at all.
Just close your mind…
and open your heart.
And then ask yourself,
what your eyes are searching for.
Oh, you're here!
Thanks for coming.
Come, I'll show you around.
Arlo's a fantastic person.
People from all over the world
come to learn meditation.
The center is close by.
He used to party in Goa as well.
Long ago.
Twenty-years ago.
I've heard he hosted
George Harrison back then.
Just imagine… it's a big deal.
The pond is right there.
This is our little home.
And that's the pond.
It will take a lot of time
and money to clean.
It's not possible. Sorry.
No. This is the reason
we bought this mansion.
Don't worry about the money.
But please get it done in a week.
Can't be done in a week.
Hire someone else.
You can at least try.
-I said it's not possible.
-But…
You can only control your actions,
not the result.
Try.
Don't worry about the result.
And anyway,
you don't look like someone
who easily gives up.
Take care.
If she needs anything…
-Okay?
-Sure.
I think it could be managed.
You can talk to the people.
Come, Kabir. Let's do this.
The number you're trying to reach…
It's done!
You said it can't be done even
in a week.
It's just the surface.
We've to drain the water
and clean the pond floor.
That's a time-consuming job.
I see.
Here. You must be tired.
-Thanks.
-Chilled beer.
By the way, what else do you like
other than diving?
Being quiet.
Come on.
Don't be a sad
and mysterious sourpuss, please!
You can be my friend.
Listen, I am not your chum.
I work for you.
And I would really appreciate it
if you keep it that way, please.
Why are you so rude?
Did you get extra love
in childhood from your parents?
I am sure you are the only child.
Yeah, so?
I knew it.
These "only child" kids
have a lot of tantrums.
They get spoiled with love and care.
Look at me.
Youngest of three brothers.
I've been beaten up so many times,
that I've no qualms,
shame, or fear in life.
Once as a kid, my brother
punched me in the chest,
and I went flying through the air.
What the hell!
"What the hell", exactly!
I swear on God,
I couldn't breathe for some time.
Didn't your parents yell at your brother?
It never got to that.
We made a deal.
For an entire year,
a chocolate every day.
So… you and Arlo are family?
You can say that.
He is my guru.
Actually, I am learning music
from him.
I am a singer.
A singer?
A very good one.
Someone thinks highly of themselves!
"C'est La vie."
Know what it means?
"It is what it is."
Well, I've to get back to work.
Thanks for the beer.
And unless you want to help me out…
I…
Shit. I've some urgent business.
I don't know what I am doing here.
I'll see you, okay?
Crazy!
-Okay. You can go.
-Goodbye.
You are still here?
I am almost done.
Just leaving.
Your hard work is clearly visible.
Thank you.
It's pretty late.
Why don't you have dinner with us?
Thanks.
I don't like to impose.
No formalities.
You must have dinner.
I insist.
Here you go.
Thank you.
No one else is eating?
These foreigners eat at six
and turn in early.
And Arlo?
He's conducting the evening
meditation sessions.
Why? Do you have a problem
with my company?
Yes. A little.
But I will manage.
Return the beer.
You took it to your heart!
I was joking.
You don't meditate?
Booze and drugs.
What?
I can't stay silent and calm.
I can see that.
The food is delicious.
Who made this?
Do you see anyone else here?
The most talented.
Arlo?
-Give me my beer.
-Okay.
I would rather eat alone.
You really are a good cook.
It's really nice.
I sing even better.
Then why are you here with Arlo?
Okay, sorry.
No more jokes, I promise.
I am good at music,
but Arlo is something else.
He's truly blessed.
When he sings, you feel like you are…
Possessed?
Yeah.
Have you ever heard him?
No.
I've heard from people.
You should hear him play.
He is…
damn good.
I would love to hear you instead.
Are you flirting with me?
You wish!
My gorgeous personality
is affecting you.
Play something, seriously.
-Pay me.
-What?
If you're good at something,
never do it for free.
That I agree.
So, how much?
Well, how about an exchange?
I will play for you,
you teach me how to dive.
What do you say?
Done deal.
God conjured this beauty that's tanned
All the boys are my fans
Some call me hot
Some say goddamn
You are the one who stole
My peace and sleep
God conjured this beauty that's tanned
All the boys are my fans
Some call me hot
Some say goddamn
You are the one who stole
My peace and sleep
Hear, O beautiful one, your brown skin
All the boys in my
Town are crazy about you
Hear, O beautiful one, your brown skin
All the boys in my
Town are crazy about you
They don't go to work, don't eat
No one looks
At the fair ones anymore
They don't go to work, don't eat
No one looks
At the fair ones anymore
Who…
Who will you keep running from?
God's made you this beautiful
Black is your Gucci bag
And red is your Prada
Where are you going beautiful
Looking like this?
All the boys keep telling me
You are everywhere
From Star News to BBC
Brown-brown skin
Let me tell you one thing
Swear on God, you are so… sexy
Intoxicating eyes, curvy figure
At first sight
You became my lover
I know all about you
You can't be patient
Intoxicating eyes, curvy figure
At first sight
You became my lover
I know all about you
You can't be patient
Let me tell you one thing
I never-never
Touch anything sub-standard
Although, I have a big score
But white chicks
I don't like them anymore
Be my hoe
I mean be mine forever
I know you look at me
From the corner of your eyes
I know…
Don't say no-no.
I am your Yo-Yo
Just say yes
And I'll talk to your father
Hear, O beautiful one, your brown skin
All the boys in my
Town are crazy about you
Hear, O beautiful one, your brown skin
All the boys in my
Town are crazy about you
They don't go to work, don't eat
No one looks
At the fair ones anymore
They don't go to work, don't eat
No one looks
At the fair ones anymore
Hear, O beautiful one
Hear, O beautiful one, your brown skin
All the boys in my town
Are crazy about you
Hear, O beautiful one, your brown skin
All the boys in my town…
Are you okay?
I shouldn't have come here.
What happened?
I have to go.
-Tara, relax.
-I have to go.
Tara, relax.
You are on a bad trip.
Happens to everyone.
Just calm down.
You don't know.
This lifestyle of mine
is why I lost my mom.
What?
My partying killed my mother.
What did you do at the parties?
Sorry. Continue.
Every weekend I would travel
from Mumbai to Goa with my friends.
How could you be this careless?
What were you thinking?
You didn't even think about us!
Calm down, please.
-Who's the father?
-Sukanya.
Who is the father?
I am talking to you!
Answer me!
I met a musician
at a party in Goa.
All you want to do is
have sex, drugs, parties!
Is that all?
-Sukanya.
-Leave me.
-What are you doing? Are you insane?
-Let go!
I would have rather
not given birth to you.
-I hate you.
-Sukanya.
Sorry.
Sorry!
Take her to a doctor.
Go. Clear this mess. Go.
She left a letter behind before she died.
She wrote that I am the result
of a mistake she made 22 years ago.
Twenty-two years ago,
my mom went to Goa with her friends.
In the last ten years,
I've asked all her friends
what happened in Goa.
But no one knows.
Only one last hope is left.
Leslie Fernandes.
I am sorry, Tara.
I am so sorry to hear this.
My partying killed my mother.
-I killed my mother.
-No, you didn't! Don't…
Don't think like that.
I killed her.
Don't blame yourself.
Tara.
Good morning.
You are home.
Can you stay with me tonight?
If any other girl had asked me this,
I would have instantly said yes.
But you are a friend.
And in this condition,
you can't choose between right
or wrong.
I am sorry, Tara.
Yeah.
Hold on
Even if the walls are caving in
This time… it's harder now
Then it has ever been
Don't leave me out in the ocean
Hold on
It's harder now
Don't leave me out in the ocean
Hold on
Kabir.
-Yeah.
-Hi.
Just give me a hand.
Hey, Martin.
Look, I know what happened was wrong.
But before you say anything,
you need to understand
that I was very high.
It's not funny.
Everyone thinks I am going crazy.
You are a bit crazy.
Just a bit. Right?
Grandma thinks I am possessed.
What? What was Grandma saying?
That I brought some spirit back
from the boat.
That's rubbish!
These things happen in our field.
Don't worry.
Panic attacks.
Nightmares.
PTSD…
And sometimes terminal…
Carrying life on your back every day,
and scanning the depths of the ocean
is not easy.
We divers know this.
But everyone's laughing at me.
What is this?
What keys are these?
To my guesthouse.
In Sicily.
Amazing view.
Go and enjoy.
-Take a break.
-I don't want a break.
I need work.
I really need to get this thing
out of my mind.
I am giving you work.
It's a paid leave.
Take your dad and grandma along with you.
I would rather check
into a mental asylum. Never!
Fine.
Go alone. Or with a friend.
You choose.
But just go!
Okay?
And Tara,
immerse the spirit in the ocean.
Hold on
Even if the walls are caving in
This time… it's harder now
Then it has ever been
Don't leave me out in the ocean
Hold on
It's harder now
Don't leave me out in the ocean
Hold on
You swam all the way out here.
You?
What are you doing here?
So finally,
Arlo chucked you out of the house.
You wish!
Excuse me.
Can I have two beers?
Some fries and sandwiches.
Tuna for me, bacon for you.
-Yeah.
-And, wait.
-Yes, sir?
Please make it quick.
-I've to go on stage.
-Sure, sir.
He will get it if you let him go.
What brings you here?
I am on a little music tour.
Heading to Sicily next.
Really?
I am headed there, as well.
To look for Leslie?
How do you know?
You told me. Remember?
I don't remember anything.
Shit. These bloody drugs,
they really mess up
with my mind.
You know, why don't you come with me?
I am headed to Sicily.
You can have your vocation, as well.
Thanks. But I don't like to impose.
What impose?
Let's go together.
We'll have fun.
Shall we?
Let's go. Let's go.
Ladies and gentlemen,
put your hands together for Neil!
Are you ready?
Let it go… just let it go
Don't be so stubborn
The world's before you
Dive right in
Don't stop yourself
The world calls out to you
Let yourself lose
Get destroyed
Do this crime without a thought
Let yourself lose
I've let myself go
Get destroyed
Do this crime without a thought
Let yourself lose
Look for no excuses
I've been waiting for you all this while.
Where are you?
Tell me now
The world's calling you
-Hey, bro!
-Hey!
-How are you, buddy?
-You good?
-Yes.
-Tara.
-Meet Fred. Tara.
-Hi!
You're a fantastic artist.
I really loved your work.
-Thank you.
-He's amazing.
So, buddy, we want this.
Where do you want to get it?
Not me. Her.
What? Me?
No way.
Tara, you always wanted
a starfish tattoo.
You told me at the party.
I never said such a thing.
I am very scared of needles.
No.
Decide quickly, guys.
I have some other work to do.
Yeah, please carry on.
No, please wait.
Tara.
We have only one life.
It won't hurt. I promise you.
How are you feeling?
I hate you for this.
It will be gone by tomorrow.
Here.
I need a painkiller.
This is to celebrate your first tattoo.
First and last for sure.
Everyone says that.
Yet they get more.
My life is painful as it is.
I don't want any more.
Just like this tattoo,
we choose all the pain in life.
Let yourself lose
Get destroyed
Do this crime without a thought
Let yourself lose
Look for no excuses
Tara.
I can't do this.
Just shut up.
You made me get a tattoo.
Now it's my turn.
Come, let me show you my world.
-But I don't know diving.
-This will be fun.
I am scared. I can't do it.
Don't worry. I won't let you die.
Okay, these are some signs you need
to remember.
This means go straight…
This means no oxygen.
This means danger.
This means okay.
Let yourself lose
Get destroyed
Do this crime without a thought
Let yourself lose
Get destroyed
Do this crime without a thought
Do this crime
-Nice place.
-Yeah.
Way better than
what I expected from Martin.
Does Martin make this kind of money?
Doesn't look that way.
Booze.
So… the star is here.
I am pleased and honored
to welcome the new director of diving.
Aman Sharma.
Welcome to the family.
Thank you.
Welcome, Aman. I am Lara.
Anytime you need me, call me.
For you.
Thank you.
A big clap for him.
-Kabir.
-Yes, boss?
Show him around.
Please.
Back to work.
So… this is your cabin.
Your chair and desk.
Oh, nice.
Let me know if you need anything else.
Sure.
This belongs to Tara.
Come, I'll apply.
No. I will manage.
I can see that.
Give it.
Cool.
Kabir.
Did you have a word with Tara?
She isn't picking up her phone.
I spoke to her the day before yesterday.
She seemed okay to me.
Anything wrong?
No, she isn't picking up her phone.
Where is Martin's guesthouse?
You don't need to worry.
She doesn't use her phone much.
I think she is fine.
-Is this the one?
-Yeah.
I would have come inside,
but I am getting late for my performance.
It's okay.
I'll see you there.
Tara.
Don't get lost this time.
Please.
I'll see you there.
The last time I saw you,
you were only two years old.
How are Ramesh and Sukanya?
They didn't come along?
Dad is fine.
But…
mom is no more.
What?
She passed away ten years ago.
How?
Suicide.
Oh, God!
Sorry.
I am so sorry.
It must have been terrible
for you and Ramesh.
I want to ask you something.
What happened in Goa 30 years ago?
Whatever it was, just forget it.
Please, sir.
I really need to know…
why she killed herself.
Are you capable of hearing the truth?
That's why I am here.
You are Sukanya's daughter…
but not Ramesh's.
What nonsense!
And what are you even saying?
How dare you even
say something like this?
Why did I come here?
I am leaving.
After hearing only half the truth?
Me, Sukanya, and our group,
we all went to Goa.
Thinking we might meet George Harrison.
We went to Goa but no one had
any idea how to meet him.
For a week we searched every lane,
every alley, and every beach in Goa.
But we couldn't find Harrison.
But the next day…
You think we will find him here?
I hope we do.
It'll be really amazing.
Sukanya, I am telling you.
This is the last party we attend.
After this, we are heading home.
-Hey.
-Hey!
Shall we?
I have to go.
Go where?
Well… actually,
I am looking for someone.
Then stay.
Maybe this is where your search ends.
Right?
-Let's stay for a while…
-It's okay.
You enjoy.
Wait. Leslie.
Your boyfriend seems
pretty possessive.
He's not my boyfriend.
-Really?
-No.
Then what are you doing
with him in Goa?
If I tell you, you will laugh at me.
Then you must tell me.
I want to meet George Harrison.
You're laughing at me.
-You're laughing at me!
-Sorry. I am sorry.
You want to meet George Harrison?
Yeah. Wait!
You know George Harrison?
Of course.
-Oh, my…
-Look at this guitar. George Harrison.
Oh, my God.
Can I touch it?
You can play it.
-Here.
-Okay.
Be careful with this.
KAILASH
What is your name?
Sukanya.
I am Kailash.
Hi, Kailash.
After coming back from Goa,
Ramesh and Sukanya got married.
This can't be true.
You are lying.
Because my mom chose my dad,
and not you.
I read in the diary.
You are just lying.
You are lying, right?
Yes, you are.
I don't know why I came here!
Like a dream she was
A broken star
-Where do I look for her now?
-30 years ago, when Arlo lived in Goa,
he hosted George Harrison.
It was the heart's wish
To let it go
I wonder when the sky turned dark?
What I got
Isn't what I had imagined
In exchange for my dreams
All I got was deceit
Like a shadow in these empty hands
What we got
Isn't what we had imagined
On a blank paper
I painted your smile
Carried away by the wind
Couldn't complete this story
That I was once narrating
Which was once our story
What I got
Isn't what I had imagined
In exchange for my dreams
All I got was deceit
Like a shadow in these empty hands
What we got
Isn't what we had imagined
Return those moments to me
I call out to you right now
The world we existed together in
Can someone return that world to me?
What I got
Isn't what I had imagined
-In exchange for my dreams
-Like a shadow in these empty hands
-What we got
-Isn't what we had imagined
Tara.
Oh, God.
Everyone, please step out.
I think she needs rest.
Sorry, Dad.
Sorry?
Do you have any clue
what you are doing?
Any clue at all?
If Aman hadn't arrived on time,
do you have any clue
what could have happened?
-It won't happen again.
-Quiet.
Don't utter a single word!
I always stood up for you, child.
I sold everything I had in India
and came here for your sake.
I supported you. Fought for you.
And you…
You don't care about your own life.
I've had enough of your drama.
You are going nowhere.
Understood?
You're done scavenging the oceans.
Enough!
Your grandma has chosen
a suitor for you.
Take up the responsibility if you can.
Otherwise, you can just abide by it.
No.
What?
I don't want to get married.
Do you want to be alone then?
What did you get out of marriage?
Pain. Loneliness. Humiliation.
-Where is Mom?
-Don't cross your limits, Tara.
You don't know, Dad!
Mom betrayed you.
What did you do?!
What did you do?
Look, Tara.
If…
you can't do it, just tell me.
I will let go, as well.
Tara, I cannot handle this anymore.
I am sorry, Dad.
I will do as you say.
Tara.
I am tired.
I will never forget this favor, son.
Don't say that, uncle.
Tara isn't just my colleague,
she is also a good friend.
So, why don't you turn this friendship
into a relationship?
What are you saying?
Aman is a nice boy.
He likes Tara.
He even understands her job.
He's also from a good family.
He's a Sharma. Brahman.
Don't make a wrong decision
in a fit of rage.
The solution to your problem is right
in front of you.
Why take the pain of sending
your daughter to Mumbai?
On top of that,
if Tara and Aman accept my proposal,
then I will make them partners
in my company.
I've no children.
And life is unpredictable.
Someone will have
to look after Martin's Dredging.
Who better than these two?
Can the two of you handle it?
-I accept it.
-Good.
Let's ask Tara.
We do too.
Tara.
You!
What are you doing here?
I should be asking you this.
What are you doing, Tara?
Where were you, Neil?
Me?
You left without saying anything.
Let's leave.
I have a lot to tell you.
But first, let's get out of here.
Let's go.
Come.
I've so much to show you.
This will be our house.
This place will be
for your fish tanks.
You design the place.
How is it?
It's beautiful.
Baby!
I got the contract.
-Really?
-Yes.
Wow. I am so happy for you.
Thanks.
What happened?
I am sorry.
It's too late, Neil.
Tara.
Ramesh.
-Hi. How are you?
-Hello.
-Excuse me, please.
-Go ahead.
What happened?
Where is Tara?
Tara must be in her room, Mom.
She isn't.
-Did you find her?
-No, Mom.
Good God. Did she run away?
That's absurd.
She must be around.
Let's go check.
Tara.
What are you doing here?
It was too crowded inside.
So I came out here.
This is your wedding.
This isn't some wedding
we're attending
which you can leave from.
Sorry, Grandma.
Tara, are you alright?
Yes. Just feeling a bit dizzy.
You've been busy since morning.
Must be tired.
Go to your room and get some rest.
The brides must not venture out
at night alone.
Come on.
Wish you all the happiness in the world
May God fulfill all your wishes
May everyone shower their love on you
You become the light of their life
You're my grace
Now leaving us behind
Don't forget those stories
I told you
Milk churner
Oh, my great God
Whom are they born to
And who would take them away
Oh, my great God
Whom are they born to
And who would take them away
Milk churner
May the fairies dress you up themselves
The sun and the moon
Ward off your evil eye
May the fairies dress you up themselves
The sun and the moon
Ward off your evil eye
May you only shed tears of joy
And leave behind insignia of love
Milk churner
By giving the box of memories, my dear
As you leave your friends behind
May God bless you with every happiness
I'll keep some of your memorabilia
Milk churner
Hello. Can you connect me
to the Coast Guards?
What happened?
Nothing.
Is everything okay?
Jax took some
archaeologists to the shipwreck,
for research.
They're stuck there.
Why did you send Jax?
-He is new.
-What option did I have?
Everyone is busy here at the wedding.
Let's just leave.
We must save them.
Let's just go.
Are you out of your mind?
It's your wedding.
-I'll arrange. I'll arrange something.
-I don't believe this.
Is my wedding more important
than someone's life?
She is right.
I'll come along, as well.
Help! Over here! Help!
Help me! Help! Over here!
Help!
Wait. We're coming there.
-How many?
-Three.
-Divers?
-Only one.
The rest two are archaeologists.
-How long has it been?
-One hour.
-We have very little time.
-Yeah.
They are running out of oxygen.
-Let's go.
-Yeah.
Don't leave me behind with your memories
Don't shatter the few that I have
Come to me
The house is lonely
Lonely are the beds
Where do I look for you?
Where do I come to pacify you?
Come to me
While searching for you, beloved
My life has become a long night
Why have you become
Just a memory for me?
Let go of the nights and days
But never let go of your beloved
Without my beloved
These moments
Have turned into ashes
Why have you become
Just a memory for me?
My world seems lost
Since you became aloof
Come back to me or just tell me
How do I live without you?
While searching for you, beloved
My life has become a long night
Why have you become
Just a memory for me?
Let go of the nights and days
But never let go of your beloved
Without my beloved
These moments
Have turned into ashes
Why have you become
Just a
Memory for me?
Are you okay?
Tara.
What happened?
You killed my mother.
What?
Remember Sukanya?
Year 1992.
She went to Goa with her friends.
To look for George Harrison.
Look.
How would you remember?
Girls are just a toy for you.
My mom broke free by killing herself.
But Dad…
has been loving someone else's daughter
as his own for the last 30 years.
I am your curse
that's come down hard on my family.
Do you even remember who I am?
Tara Salgoankar.
Year 2012. Calangute Beach.
You came there with your friends.
You knew.
I knew it the moment I saw you.
You were skirting eyes.
I thought maybe…
you wanted to forget that moment.
So, I didn't mention it.
I don't forget faces, Tara.
And I can tell you…
that this face…
I've never seen it before.
You are lying!
Jazz Club, London. 1992.
I wasn't even in Goa at that time.
Your name is Kailash.
How is that possible?
Why did Mom commit suicide?
Tara…
I don't know why…
people run, not from their mistakes,
but the truth.
They dig a grave of lies
in their mind
to bury the truth.
And then that same
truth haunts them forever.
That's where lives are lost.
Maybe…
that's what your mother did.
It wasn't her fault.
Attraction isn't a sin,
neither is lust.
We are humans.
Illusions, delusions, lust…
It's a part of life.
You can't run from it.
We cannot escape from it.
Your mother made only one mistake.
She didn't think her
life partner was worthy
of sharing her pain with.
Tara, you have one such life partner.
Neil.
My life is just too messed up.
I am getting married to Aman.
He loves me a lot.
And I am pregnant with Neil's child.
I really love him a lot.
I don't know what to do.
Please help.
Can you tell me what to do?
Tara, when the time comes,
face the truth.
You don't need to run anymore, Tara.
Did you know
that starfish can heal itself?
It doesn't die even
if it's cut into pieces.
As for us, we are always caught
up in our past and future.
But life never stops.
You think we're caught
up in the wave of memories.
But life always finds its way.
As I have found my…
love.
Love heals every wound.
Love erases all that needs to be erased.
Love makes you live… again.
So don't be afraid to wander.
Because, in this sea of memories,
everyone needs to take a dip.
So don't be afraid of drowning.
Because life will take you ashore.