We just sex partner.
We satisfy each other's needs.
Without any feelings involved.
You.
Hmm?
I’ve got gossip.
Last night, the place I went to—hot Korean guys, seriously.
Whoa! You went without even thinking of inviting me?
What’s your heart made of, huh?
Oh please, even if I invited you, like you’d actually come.
You just watch Chinese dramas all day. Look at you—not sleeping at night, your eyes are all dark.
Really?
Totally. You need fillers already, babe.
But the lead actor is so handsome. I can’t get off the Great Wall of China!
Hey, the Great Wall is tall, okay? Be careful or you’ll fall to your death. Don’t say your friend didn’t warn you.
Are you cursing me?
I’m not cursing. I care about you, duh.
Care, my ass. You love me so much, right?
She’s here—Praew’s here.
Jun!
Oh, hi.
Hey there. Where’ve you been? Walking in like that, eyes all droopy. Did my love hit your eyes or something?
Oh please, stop harassing him.
I wasn’t harassing him at all!
Sorry, okay?
Oh, it’s alright. No worries.
So sweet. He’s not mad at me.
Jun, he’s like… whoa… like rawr! Just like that, right, Praew? Spot on, told you! Haha—so spicy.
Haha—so spicy.
I wanna be a hyena so bad—so I can bite your neck! Rawr!
That’s enough. Get back to work.
Ughhh.
Shit! P’Son!
- What are you doing?!
- Hey!
Geez, you came out of nowhere! You scared me!
You’ve got such a weak heart.
It’s your fault—this bite mark!
P’Korn and P’Praew saw it already!
It’s just a mark, right?
But they saw it, didn’t they?!
Want me to do it back to you? It’s embarrassing, you know!
Then do it back, why don’t you?
It hurts, Jun.
So what? My neck hurts too.
Son! Hiding out here, huh? P’June was asking for you.
Hey, boss.
So, did P’Sorn mess with you or anything?
I didn’t mess with him at all.
And you? Did you mess with him?
You used to be pretty spicy, didn’t you?
Come on, boss. Who’d dare mess with him?
He’s supervising my internship—if I fail, I’m screwed.
Yeah, good. Keep things smooth. Son’s got a sharp tongue but a kind heart. If you're good to him, he’ll take care of you for life.
Him? Kind-hearted? Really?
Yeah! Keep fighting, bro!
He’s only kind to ghosts.
Hello, Jun!
Oh! P’James!
Having coffee?
Yeah.
So, Jun has to go to the… rong-ngang jad-song… or something. (mumbling)
What did you just say?
Rong-ngan! Don’t you get it?
Oh! The factory.
Right—the factory.
Exactly.
Going to see Win too, right?
Exactly, With Sorn.
Okay, With P’Sorn?
Yeah.
I’ll head over after I finish this.
Here—want some?
Thanks.
How do you feel, man?
I’m excited!
Yeah.
I couldn’t sleep at all last night.
Whoa, that bad?
Of course it was, friend.
Let me play it for you. Yeah.
Jun, sit in the front.
Go on, just go.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
You guys going to the factory?
Yes.
Let me come too—I was just about to see Khun Paisan.
The employee documents on their side are still a mess.
Take the front seat, please.
Thanks, sweetie.
Don’t.
No one’s gonna see.
The kids in the back!
They’re all asleep already.
Alright, I’ll go see Khun Paisan first then.
Okay.
It’s massive.
Seriously, it’s freaking huge.
Whoa.
Hey Jun, Aey, wanna go check that area out?
Where are you guys going?
We’re just walking around the factory.
You guys can’t just wander around here, it’s dangerous. Some areas are off-limits, and others need a guide to enter.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Jun!
Win!
Missed you so much.
Seriously missed you, man.
Big smooch!
Calm down, bro.
Oh! Hey P’Son, hello!
Oh, so Pe and Aey came too?
No way we’d miss this!
How’ve you been? All good?
All good, you bastard.
Just kinda lonely—no one my age around.
Yeah, I get that.
Come on, let’s head to the break room.
Is there aircon?
Yup, icy cold.
Alright, let’s go.
It’s scorching hot.
Help yourselves to the snacks, guys.
Thanks, bro.
Hey P’Son, bring Jun to see me more often. I’m all alone here—no one my age!
Didn’t I hear you’re playing sepak takraw with the mechanic team?
Yeah, I am.
I’ve got a match next week. Wanna come watch?
Wait a sec, Win—are you here for your internship or training for the national team?
Hey Win, but we’re not sure yet. If there’s work at the office, then maybe…
I’ll bring them myself.
Hoo! Count me in too, P’Son.
Yeah, I’ll bring you guys.
But I gotta get back to work first.
Okay, sure.
Does P’Son have a girlfriend?
Why you asking? Got a crush on him?
Nooo, just curious!
Just answer already.
Not really. Since I’ve known P’Son, never seen him with an actual girlfriend.
What a shame! I thought he was dating P’Penny—they’ve got such good chemistry. I totally ship them.
Pfft, you just imagine things. They might just be close friends—doesn’t mean there’s anything more. All in your head.
You never know. Maybe there is something.
Someone as pretty as P’Penny? Of course all the guys like her.
But usually… he doesn’t really act flirty with anyone.
Right, Jun? You work with him, don’t you?
Uh… nope, nothing going on.
See? Told ya!
Next time you come to the factory, I’ll introduce you to this technician—he’s insanely good at takraw.
Is he as good as Aey? He just went ice skating—super intense. I’ve got a clip, let me show you.
You better do it properly.
Here, look at this... this one.
He’s flying like that—I thought it was Iron Man!
So slick.
Cool, right?
Yeah, Win, I’m telling you—this place has tons of activities. I’ve changed my mind, I wanna intern here. Can I switch?
If you can switch, let me come too.
No way. I won’t let you.
The international department interns at the city office. If you move here, what would you even do?
Might as well go home.
Has P’Son gotten stricter lately or what?
And harsh, too.
Thank you, P’Penny, P’Son.
Sure. You coming?
Hey Aey, do you think P’Penny actually wants you to do this kind of thing?
Maybe not, but I want them to spend time together, you know?
Busybody. Meddling in things that aren’t your business.
Come on, let’s go.
Why you meddling?
Hey Jun, let’s go!
Alright, alright, I’m going.
Hey, how do you press this? Help me out.
Watch this.
Just like that.
Awesome.
Mhm.
Thank you.
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
You and P’Son—have you known each other long? You guys seem really close.
I wouldn’t call it close. We only talk like two or three sentences a day.
Why?
Can’t you tell?
Me and P’Son just argue all the time. I’ve never liked his face.
Even though you “don’t like him,” he still takes care of you.
Look at today at the factory—when you said you wanted to join the sports event, he actually took you there.
You’re exaggerating.
No, it’s true!
Have you seen P’Put?
I think I saw him—looked like he was walking this way.
Still hasn’t come to collect his stuff.
How’s it going, my dear junior?
There he is, speak of the devil. All done, bro.
Let me see.
Let’s check it.
Only one file?
Here, there are two.
Oh wait, this one doesn’t count, right?
Okay, all set. Thanks a lot.
- See you around.
- Goodbye.
Hey, what’s up, Piang?
Why do you keep disappearing, P’Jun? I have to keep chasing you down.
Ugh, I’ve been super busy lately. What about you—what are you doing?
Just lying around under the building. I went to grab some snacks.
Um! Are you free this evening, P’Jun? Wanna catch a movie?
Hmm, a movie? Yeah, sure, I’ll go.
Hey… let me ask you—was the guy who owns the bar we went to named Franz?
I don’t remember his face, just that he was hot.
Hmm. Now that you know your type, you can’t stop complimenting him, huh?
So? Are you going to tell me who that guy Son is—the one who came to pick you up?
He’s just like I said—an older guy I know. Nothing more.
Now I wanna know even more. I asked P’Franz, and he wouldn’t say a thing.
He said something like, “I can’t get involved in this,” acting all secretive.
Come on, there’s really nothing going on.
Let’s just meet at the cinema, okay?
Okay, that’s all for now. My friends are here.
Wow, just hung up like that?
Ugh.
Geez, what the hell are you doing, man?
And what are you doing here?
Where are you going?
Just going to the movies with Piangrak.
Didn’t I tell you not to talk to her?
Oh please, I’m just going as her friend.
So who are you texting? Franz?
You want him to get you drunk again?
I’m the only one getting myself drunk.
Hoping you’d end up in his bed, huh?
I just wanted to prove that I…
I...
Wait, are you seriously gonna sleep with him?
He’s really pushing it, insulting me like that.
Hey, I’m just going to chill, that’s all.
I’m not hooking up with anyone.
Then why waste your money on it?
Can you even earn your own money? Spending it on nonsense.
What’s your problem, seriously?
Yelling like this—did you fight with P’Penny or something?
What’s Penny got to do with this?
You think I didn’t notice?
There’s nothing going on.
Penny was just messing around, that’s all.
Is that how people tease each other these days?
Whatever. Up to you.
I’m not dating Penny. I don’t have a wife.
Then… do you have a girlfriend?
I don’t have a girlfriend either.
You little brat.
No one owns me yet.
Wanna grab a drink, huh?
Same place as always.
Oh.
Watch my phone for me.
What are you doing here?
Are they about to fight?
I’m just training Jun.
Oh, right. You’re really dedicated, huh?
It’s after work already, look at the time.
You could’ve gone home, you know? Jun probably wants to go too.
Something urgent came up.
They’re kicking us out—let’s go.
Then I’ll leave this work with you.
Please take care of it.
Then I’ll take my leave.
Goodbye.
Let’s go, Jun.
Jun, come on.
Damn, my heart nearly jumped out of my chest.
Feel it—my heart’s pounding like crazy.
Whoa, what’s up with you?
Penny.
Yes? Is something wrong?
Do you realize you’re behaving inappropriately at work?
Inappropriately?
How so?
Going off with Son during work hours—and acting like you own him.
Aren’t you afraid people in the company will think badly of you?
Is that all?
If that’s all, I’ll excuse myself.
Why haven’t you gone home yet?
I called a ride, but no one’s picked it up yet.
I’ll give you a ride.
Uh, well…
C’mon, I’ll take you.
But I’m stopping by the mall first.
Huh?
Which place should we eat at?
Oh, Jun! Wanna have dinner together?
I was going to treat Son to thank him for giving me a ride to the factory.
Thanks, but I’ll pass. I already made plans with a junior.
Which floor are you meeting this junior on?
P’Jun!
Oh, Piang!
Let’s go, Piang.
See you later.
That place looks tasty too.
Come on, let’s eat.
Hmm… I wanted to go to that place…
What’s wrong?
Oh, let’s go to a different place.
Nothing.
P’Jun,
Why’d you drag me here? You didn’t even say hi to him yet.
No need to say hi. It’s not like we’ll see him again.
Don’t come home late. Tomorrow morning, I’m making you join the meeting too.
Hmm, nothing.
Don’t be a smartass. Read it and reply.
I’m going to hang out some more with Piangrak.
Where the hell are you going?
Oh, hi P’Son!
Ugh, Praew—he’s in a bad mood again. I even greeted him and he
scowled at me.
Oh no, drama incoming.
Just wait.
So, what now? What do you think? Yeah, exactly.
Hi Jun! What did you buy?
Grilled sticky rice. Want some?
Can I have a bite… of your heart?
Oh, come on.
You cheeky thing.
Hey! Hello, P’Champ.
Hey, what did you buy to eat?
Grilled sticky rice, bro. Want one? Got different fillings—pick one.
Oh, I saw Win yesterday.
Oh right, I forgot—I was gonna throw him a birthday thing.
I’m probably free next week. I’ll call him.
Sounds good.
Tai’s back too—perfect timing for a get-together.
I’m in, boss.
Look at us—just work all day. So stressed out.
Jun, you’re coming. That’s an order.
P’Champ, can I even say no?
When it’s free, I’m in.
But can you afford me? I eat a lot.
Bro, don’t worry—I got you.
Let’s go, bro.
You’re my favorite, after all.
Don’t forget drinks too.
Go all out.
Here you go.
You’re early, man.
Thanks, thanks.
One each.
Go print and copy 15 sets of this—collated. I need it in 10 minutes.
I’m still eating… haven’t even had breakfast yet.
It’s alright, I’ll do it, P’Son.
Pe, don’t do it. Jun will.
I want it done by 8:50.
I’m gonna tell Tai. When he’s back, you’re screwed.
You breathe Tai’s name. He’s not even here, and you’re still talking about him all day.
Well, you keep picking on his boy. Don’t let me catch you doing it again, jerk.
I’m not picking on him—I’m making him work.
You dumbass. Who’d believe you? The kid’s eating and you make him work, but you never ask Pe or Aey to do anything. Damn.
It’s work time, not mealtime!
Idiot.
Shit—it’s jammed! Damn it! Why’d it shut down?!
Jun.
is it done yet?!
The machine’s frozen—shut off. Give me a second.
Can’t even finish this simple task?
How are you gonna survive.
Jun? Is anything done? If not, don’t bother.
Well… I’ll just go work in P’James’s office then.
Look in the folder. These are the orders we’ll need to…
Sorry, I brought the meeting documents.
The printer here broke down, so I’m a bit late—my apologies.
Jun, P’Son told you to prepare these yesterday.
Huh?
Are you done.
Jun? Please step out—it’s meeting time now.
Sorry.
Okay, let’s continue. These are the rush orders, the client’s already following up. If you have any questions, feel free to ask.
Champ, have you seen Jun?
How would I know, idiot? You’re the one pulling dumb pranks, jackass.
Don’t start yelling—help me find him first. He disappeared.
James!
What?
Have you seen Jun?
I think P’June asked to talk to him—he went that way.
Jun.
Jun, look up.
Don’t bother me. Just leave.
Calm down.
Calm down?
For what? What the hell have you been doing to me?
All those pranks—and now P’June called me in just to scold me because of you. Dammit.
Jun, I’m sorry. Please don’t cry.
Son, P’June wants to talk to you.
Yeah, I’m coming.
What’s up?
Are you busy?
For you? I’m always free.
Your dear friend caused trouble again.
He teased the kid so much P’June ended up
scolding him. Too much.
"Work stuff?"
Yeah. I wouldn’t say anything if it was something else, but Jun looked crushed—like a kicked puppy. Call him and cheer him up.
Alright, alright. I’ll call him.
You going out tonight?
Nah.
I’ll call you later then.
Okay.
Yes, boss.
Heard you got pranked by Son? What happened? You two seemed to be getting along.
It’s fine, bro. He always messes with me.
I’ll deal with him.
No need, really.
I don’t want it to blow up. Besides, P’Son already apologized.
Alright, I’ll still sort it out. Champ told me already.
I’m heading back in a couple of
days—anything you want? Win gave me a whole wishlist.
Win again? Hmm… nah, I don’t want anything. Nothing in particular.
Okay then. I’ll get back to work. We’ll talk later.
Alright, bro. Thanks.
Bye.
Who else just showed up?
The grilled sticky rice is here, guys.
Be careful or P’Son's gonna scold you.
Why would he? I asked him to buy it for me.
Still, I bought it for you first, okay?
So what now? Are you gonna move out or what?
I can't afford the rent, man.
Then just come stay at my place.
And don’t even worry about it — you’ve crashed there before anyway.
Jun.....
I want it.
P’Son...
I’m not feeling so good...
But I do know how to make you feel better.
Why are you eating so fast?
If you rush like that, you're gonna get a stomachache.
I’m just super hungry!
Finish chewing before you talk, man.
If I closed my eyes, I’d think I was eating with my dad — you nag just like him.
Well, maybe if you didn’t act like a kid, adults wouldn’t have to nag. Try listening for once.
Yesss sir, Grandpa.
Thanks a bunch.