(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
[Disclaimer: This series is entirely fictional
and solely for entertainment purposes
with no association or reference
to any individuals, places, or events.
There may be inappropriate behaviors
and vulgarity based on the character's persona.
Viewer discretion is advised.]
To me, a home
isn't merely a shelter,
but an energy system and a field of forces
that affects the residents
and holds the power
to define the life they will lead.
Human beings have long lived with beliefs.
We searched for ways to foresee the future
by reading the stars,
wind direction,
and even symbols on stones.
Hey,
do you know
that Ritt is writing a thesis
on beliefs and superstitions?
No kidding?
Is that even gonna work?
It sounds too much like a daydream.
I guess
he is giving up on graduation.
I guess so.
People might call me a daydreamer,
but this exact dream
might just be the beginning
of an unexpectedly long journey.
These things
are used in fortune-telling to predict
if something will flourish
or wither.
Oriental divination art
has feng shui to assist in designing,
and the Western art
has runestones...
Whoa...
[Algiz: Safety]
These stones
are my biggest challenges at present.
Rune
is not only a symbol used for divination,
but it also reflects humans' beliefs,
hopes,
and fears.
If we reinterpret those into home design,
we might be able to create
a space that's not only beautiful,
but also fulfills one's vitality.
And this...
is what I've decided to prove.
♫Is it pure coincidence?♫
♫Or is it destiny that decides?♫
♫Is someone above drawing all these lines?♫
♫Or playing matchmaker in disguise?♫
♫What if the stars shift in their place♫
♫Slightly out of line,♫
♫Will our orbits still align?♫
♫Try answering (if) your world
will cross with mine♫
♫Though the destiny between us
is differently defined♫
♫And I believe our love has power♫
♫I believe the love of us♫
♫Will realign the stars back
to the line where they should be♫
Please wait up.
Thank you.
Sorry.
May I get through?
Hello, I'm Ritt.
Today, I am going to present
to you my project
named
"House Architecture Design
with a Combination of Energy
from Runestones and Healing Stones."
There are 24 runestones,
which resemble the English alphabet.
For example...
So...
That concludes my presentation.
Thank you.
Alright,
overall, I must say
it's okay.
There are many groups
that led an intriguing presentation.
But for those
whom I have given some feedback,
try revising it,
and we can revisit it next time.
In this semester,
many of you
probably have only a few credits left.
Some might only have
their senior project left to work on.
Therefore,
give it your all!
Your all!
Make some noise!
Show me your hands, too!
- My all!
- My all.
Good!
- I'll give it my all!
- Yay...
If there are any questions,
you can come see me
anytime at our department.
Catch you later.
Class dismissed.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Working in this field,
you need a keen eye.
Yes, Professor.
[Thurisaz: Caution]
Pure, where are you?
Help me check this out.
The LED light of the bar sign
won't turn on again.
We've barely been open a month,
yet everything is already falling apart.
Will it survive?
Jeez,
what's with all the yelling?
Check the outlet, see if it's loose.
It's not. I already checked.
See?
Is this business gonna survive?
We barely have customers as it is.
No,
don't say something ominous,
my beloved freaking sister.
You're right.
What's wrong with it?
What did you do?
You plugged in the wrong thing.
That was for the air purifier.
You didn't even bother paying attention.
Are you the CEO of complaining? Huh?
Huh? Huh?
Pure,
it's been almost a month
since we opened our bar,
yet lots of thing still don't
seem to fall into place.
Patience, Ploy.
Slow and steady
win the race.
This bar
isn't like any other ones out there.
It sets out to become a legend.
Hello, Magic Move.
Your first customer of the night
has arrived.
Welcome, your VIP ass.
Where would you like to be seated?
May I suggest
on the floor or the floor mat?
Look at you.
With that mouth,
you're gonna chase away all the customers.
Right, Ritt?
I'm so scared we'll have to count
down the days until we close down.
Both of you
just keep spitting unkind things.
How about some positivity around here?
My gut is telling me
that this bar
will go viral.
So what drink can I get you, Mr. VIP?
Alright, alright, alright.
And before ordering,
please remove your school uniform.
This bar doesn't allow
university students in uniforms
or those under 20 years of age.
Here.
Are you gonna check my ID, too?
No need.
I can tell from your face,
that you're a fossil in university.
If I'm old,
wouldn't you be as old?
But I've already graduated.
I'm a newly graduated, you see,
unlike someone still in school like you.
That's because I majored in Architecture,
not a 4-year Business program like you.
Right,
so how did it go,
presenting your
senior project to the professor?
Did you pass with flying colors?
It's fine.
Hey,
I have a story for you.
What is it about, Ritt?
Let me in on it.
You're so quick with this kind of stuff.
Water?
It's still bright outside.
You could get drunk.
So today,
I had an immensely
impressive moment with someone.
And that person was...
Was...
- Was...
Okay, then.
I'm out.
I'd rather go organize the stockroom.
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
I'll tell you now.
So today,
I met the campus's finest.
Itthi,
Itthiphumi Pongpanyalert.
Who's that?
Well,
he's the sole heir to a top-tier
massive real estate business.
Itthi...
He just graduated from my faculty.
He sure did.
Who in the world
could be so perfect?
His hair delivers.
His eyebrows deliver.
His eyes deliver.
His lips deliver.
His cheeks deliver.
His face delivers...
And the man delivers...
Ice!
The ice delivery is here.
Can you go check?
What a total buzzkill.
Ploy, you go.
What? You go. I'm gonna listen to him.
Hey,
we'll have the same amount as yesterday.
Deliver it to the backroom.
On it, sir.
So what else?
Where were we?
So how did that moment happen?
So what happened was...
Thank you.
Man,
that was enough to
make me freeze, alright?
I've had a crush on him since
freshman year until now, as he graduated.
This is the first time
I've been this close, like...
face-to-face.
You're so fucking dramatic.
I saw him all the time
at the faculty building.
Easy for you to say.
Pure, just stop interrupting.
So what happened next, Ritt?
All of a sudden,
a swarm of people from who-knows-where
rushed into the elevator
and squeezed Itthi
until he was right in front of my face!
Dude...
That was almost enough
to make me go insane.
Our faces were so close together
that I could feel his breath,
his faint cologne,
and a vivid sight of his face
in front of my eyes.
And all of a sudden,
the elevator jerked,
and he...
Sorry.
It's alright.
Are you sure you're alright?
Yes.
What about this?
Would it be alright?
And his naughty hands
slid up to unbutton my shirt.
I didn't know what to do,
so I unbuttoned his shirt in return,
and after that...
Close your ears.
- This is inappropriate for children!
- Ugh!
So what happened next, Ritt?
Weren't the people in the elevator
at least taken aback by it?
You're right.
There were other people.
I forgot.
What are you saying?
To be honest,
he just accidentally kissed my forehead.
I just added
some teeny-tiny detail to spice it up.
Jeez, Ritt!
There.
Here's another kiss for your noggin.
You really had me there.
The first touch between him and me...
Now you're just daydreaming.
What a waste of time.
Come on,
open up the first tab
for Magic Move. Order up.
I'll have my usual, Ployplern.
Go ballistic on that mixer.
But I'll have some food first,
or else I'll get drunk.
I'll have fried pork
with garlic and pepper like always.
Sure, with no cilantro,
cucumber,
and with one over-hard fried egg.
You got it.
Jeez,
you know me too well,
unlike this brother of yours.
Whatever his deal is.
Are you full, Itthi?
I am, Grandpa.
Why did you eat so little?
Isn't it delicious?
It is delicious, Grandma.
But I'm just looking out
for my health before I get a potbelly.
Alright, bring Itthi some bua loy,
and also some for the tycoon and me.
Yes.
And do you still have to go
to the university after graduating?
Oh,
I have to go in to apply for graduation.
Mm.
Also, I'm preparing
documents to further my studies.
Right, furthering your studies.
You should do that.
Get right into it after graduation
because if you leave it on
for too long, you'll get lazy.
- Mm.
Good for you.
Thanks.
Here.
Let's take it easy.
A family filled with happiness,
love, and harmony.
Tomorrow, after you wake up,
don't forget
to celebrate Guanyin's birthday.
What is it, Grandma?
Oh, it's the Goddess of Mercy's Birthday,
of course.
Didn't we just celebrate the occasion?
Guanyin's Birthday
is celebrated three times a year,
on the second, fifth,
and eighth lunar month.
I already have the stuff prepared.
- Oh, this smells nice.
- Look,
you have to finish the bua loy.
It's auspicious.
When you have time
while waiting to further your studies,
you should visit the office sometime.
Get to know the employees
because after you graduate, you'll have
to take over the business from me.
Yes, Grandpa.
And tomorrow,
after you're done with your errands,
rush back home if you can.
I've made an appointment
with the masters for fortune-telling.
How many people
have you made an appointment with?
Just everyone who can make it.
Let's check them all out
so we can be sure.
It's to be on the safe side.
Nice, nice.
Of course.
Here are some orange.
Have a slice of it for good luck.
Aren't the tastes
going to clash in his mouth
since bua loy is sweet
and the orange is tangy?
- Just eat it. It's for good luck.
- Alright, alright, alright.
Twice the luck.
Whoa...
Bottoms up, Ritt?
Get me one more...
I think that's enough.
You're already drunk.
Sowilo: Light and success.
What's that?
The stone is saying...
that I can drink until dusk
since success awaits...
Is that so, Ritt?
Did you just make things up?
What did I do wrong?
Do I not look good enough?
Hello, there.
Heard you're heartbroken.
Do you believe in prophecy stones?
Concentrate well,
deeply bond with your query.
They reveal the reality
and settle your doubts
according to your destiny.
Think of what bothers you
and pick up three stones.
The stones say
that what's yours
will always be yours.
I ran out.
Fill it up.
Quick.
Hey,
can I have my fortune told, too?
You're majoring in Engineering, right?
Whoa, how did you know that, Master?
Close your eyes
and pick up three stones.
You don't
really pay attention in class, huh?
Sir, could you please
visit our table as well?
The stones reveal the reality.
Concentrate well.
The stones say you read into it wrong.
Deeply bond with your query.
That's good.
You'll be in a relationship by next week.
Certainty
is uncertainty.
The stones reveal the reality
and settle your doubts...
according to your destiny.
Ritt, are you alright?
I am.
Call me a cab.
Drop me off at my dorm,
not my house, or Mom will scold me.
Gosh, this friend of mine.
Completely wasted.
Why the hell are you cuddling with this?
It's not a pillow!
There.
There goes his leg.
Mm.
Go on.
Concentrate well,
deeply bond with your query.
The stones reveal the reality
and settle your doubts
according to your destiny.
- Hello...
- Ritt,
don't you think you should wake up?
Why are you calling so early?
Early, my ass.
This is almost the afternoon.
Don't you have any classes?
No.
I just...
have to go in to discuss my project
with the professor this evening.
Why did you call?
I'm having a massive hangover right now.
Look how much you drank last night.
It'd be a surprise if you didn't.
By the way, I sent you a link to a post.
Have you seen it?
What post?
The one about Ritt,
the Prophecy Stone Master.
Huh?
Go check it out now.
What's happening?
[Alrighty! I'll give you
a review on the famous fortune teller]
[The Master from Magic Move told me
that I'd break up with my partner,
and I caught them cheating this morning,
how accurate #MagicMoveFortuneTeller]
[The fortune teller from the bar
behind the uni is on fire; check him out]
[Dead-on prediction;
thought that hottie was making things up,
but he actually ate
#RittTheProphecyStoneMaster]
[Check him out
at Magic Move behind the Uni!]
[I've had my fortune told everywhere,
and this was so detailed]
[He was precise about love prediction,
and he was so friendly and handsome]
[We don't gatekeep on hot fortune tellers,
the puppy-type bot who's also accurate!]
[If he were even more accurate,
I'd think he lived in my shadow]
[So fetch! So spot-on! Perfect!]
[The Architect-majored fortune teller
was so dead-on!]
[I met him last night;
it was so accurate that I got goosebumps!]
Shit!
Dude, look.
Here he comes.
Since when did Ritt
become a fortune teller?
Right?
He even used the prophecy stones.
Yeah, that's quirky.
Here,
I'll try having him tell mine.
Hey, Ritt.
It's gonna be just a second, my guy.
So...
Can you tell my fortune?
I heard your reading is spot-on.
Uh, maybe later.
I'm in a hurry.
I have a meeting with the professor.
Wait, what meeting?
It's only gonna be a second!
Uh, regarding our project right now,
in terms of the external structure,
around 80% of it has been constructed.
And the interior work
is around 50% done.
The interior system,
be it the electric system,
sanitary system,
or air conditioning system,
is now also
approximately 80% constructed.
For the building supplies,
we have ordered them
per the approved specifications.
It's definitely
up to standard, though...
we have purchased them
at below the market price.
Alright.
When it comes to the structures,
we've precisely constructed them
according to the architects.
I'm certain we will be able to deliver
the project to the client in time.
Not only is a home a residence,
but it's also a space that nurtures
the beliefs of the people living in it.
If we organize it
according to a lifestyle,
it naturally brings about
peace of mind; for example,
a kitchen located in the East
to welcome in the morning light,
and a pathway with
proper airflow for ventilation.
Also, a proper space
to worship the deities
is one that doesn't disrupt
the resident's daily life,
because if it were set up where
people would walk past on a daily basis,
it would be akin to
the deities getting in the way,
when their duty
should be to support,
not to hinder.
Therefore, a good home
is one where beliefs
can coexist without interruption,
and where you can still feel the power,
peace,
and faith right beside you.
That's such a great idea, Ritt.
But I wish there were
more scientific evidences
to support your claim.
For example,
the data about temperature,
natural light,
air ventilation,
and their effects
on the state of the residents.
Collect more case studies,
then you can give me an update next week.
Do you understand?
Sure, Professor.
I'll provide the data set
and wind direction simulation.
As for the art of
prophecy stones and all the energies,
what do you think?
Good!
Being a designer,
apart from the ideas,
you also need academic information.
Of course, Professor.
Alright, next group, please come up front.
Make it quick.
Right over here.
Very well.
Okay.
Thank you, everyone.
This project...
As soon as it's launched,
it'll be fully booked for sure.
Any questions, Itthi?
No, Grandpa.
These days, Itthi, my grandson,
has been assisting me with some projects.
Well,
please look after him
so he gains some experience while he's here,
because he'll be going abroad to study.
I'm entrusting him to your care.
Thank you very much.
A lot of customers today.
If she can't keep up...
Go help her out.
Pick everything up.
Hey, that's Ritt.
Ritt, could you read my fortune for me?
Can you do a love fortune reading for me?
What's happening today?
Why is it so crowded?
Oh, so you've arrived,
Ritt, the Prophecy Stone Master.
You're just going along with them, huh?
What's going on?
Why are there so many people here?
They're here to get readings from you.
Get ready.
It's your show tonight.
What are you talking about?
You know I was drunk last night.
What? I thought you knew for real.
Last night I saw you rambling on
like you saw it yourself
as if someone whispered it to you.
I made it all up.
Alcohol did it, not me.
I don't know about this.
These people came here
because they want readings from you.
Huh?
What did you tell them?
I said, "Sure.
But you'll have to wait until after 11."
Unbelievable.
How am I going to read for them?
And why does it have to be after 11?
Well,
so my store can make more revenue.
Besides,
after 11, you should be so drunk
you can do the fortune-teller
thing like last night.
No way.
I'm not doing it.
Hey, come on.
These people have been waiting for you.
Besides,
I promised them.
Pure.
Can we take two more?
They said it's urgent.
It has to be tonight.
Go for it, Ploy.
Make it the last queue tonight.
Pure!
Come on. Drinks are on the house tonight.
Courtesy of Magic Move
for Ritt, the Prophecy Stone Master.
Concentrate deeply.
Set your mind on what you wish to ask.
These stones reveal the reality,
and settle your doubts
according to your destiny.
Close your eyes and pick three stones
that attract your heart the most.
Someone's crushing on you, you know that?
Not too close, not too far.
What you've been waiting for
will appear
in due time.
Your mind is occupied these days, right?
Every beginning
has an end.
And every end
leads to a new beginning.
What you're too afraid to ask now
has the answer in itself,
you know?
Once you've chosen a path,
you can't go another way.
So,
think carefully before deciding.
Pure,
is Ritt really talking nonsense?
I'm starting to think that
he's right on the money.
Talking nonsense or
being right on the money,
he's the one raking in customers.
I'm okay with this.
See? Faith-based strategy.
It's not just marketing,
but it's...
Market-telling.
Grandma, Grandpa.
Hmm?
We should use electric incense sticks
so there'll be no smoke.
If you use smokeless incense sticks,
how will the gods know
that you're worshiping them?
Those blinking LED lights
don't look very respectful to the gods.
If you want to communicate with them
using electric equipment,
you'll have to wire it up all the way to heaven.
Will the gods understand?
Besides,
if you use electric lights,
how can you tell when to remove the offerings?
You know, we can only remove the offerings
after the incense sticks burn out.
Once they burn out, we bid farewell,
then share the offerings.
- Yes, Grandma.
- Mm.
Hello, handsome Itthi.
Today, your friends are here for free food.
Looks like nobody's home.
The mansion is ours.
Itthi? Itthi?
Itthi? Where are...
Didn't he say nobody's home today?
Hi, Grandma. Hi, Grandpa.
Hi.
Are you waiting for free stuff?
Yes.
Wait here.
You can have it after the sticks burn out.
You'll be blessed with fortune
if you eat after the gods.
Itthi.
Be careful who you hang out with.
There's an old saying...
"Jin zhu zhe chi,
jin mo zhe hei."
If you stay near vermilion, you'll turn red;
if you stay near ink, you'll turn black.
What does it have to do with vermin?
Not vermin,
it's vermilion, the red color,
the red pigment.
It's a Chinese saying,
which in Thai is
"Bad company leads you astray;
good company leads you to success."
Oh, that means we are good company.
We're good friends, Grandma.
- Really?
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- Okay, okay.
Well, take care of Itthi for us.
Go on, take your friends to wait in the room.
I'll give you some snacks first.
Okay.
Hey, Itthi, didn't you say
they'd go to worship at Tai Hong Kong?
They got the date wrong.
The fortune master said
it should be tomorrow.
Did you know
that Ek and Max
got interviewed for jobs?
Really?
How many applications have you sent?
I haven't applied for anything.
I told my family that
I've been in school since I was a kid
and haven't had a chance to rest.
I asked them for a few months of rest.
Guys, have you seen this?
There's a fortune teller
at a bar behind the campus.
He's really good.
Right. The girls said that
he's an architecture student.
Should we go try and
see if he's actually good?
Sure. When?
Tonight.
I feel bad for her.
For whom?
For Pitcha,
a trainee from JJV
who almost made her debut,
but was injured first.
Right now,
let's feel bad for our bar first.
People are already here.
Where the hell is Ritt?
Don't use that tone with him.
He's Ritt,
the Prophecy Stone Master of Magic Move.
Yeah, right.
He doesn't answer my calls.
Oh, finally.
Where are you?
A lot of people have been waiting for you.
Okay. Hurry.
See? This is why they say,
"You can't just rely on smart,
but the right time and place, too."
Like our bar,
it can't just be good,
but it needs support from Ritt.
This project
needs a supporter.
Come again?
It can't happen on its own.
It needs help from many departments.
Are you saying
we should invest in this?
Well...
It's the family's big project.
What's the risk?
Pick another stone.
Let it speak to you.
[Kenaz: Fire, brightness]
Fire...
Will there be light or darkness?
It depends on you whether
it stays on or goes out.
Which means...
Happiness, okay?
Happiness?
Hey.
Your next clients,
behave well around them.
Why?
The two guys on that table
are friends with Itthi,
who sucked your lips in the elevator.
It was an imagination.
Yeah, right.
How do you know
they're friends with Itthiphumi?
"Itthiphumi," huh?
Alright, how do you
know they're his friends?
I'm also a business student.
I see them at the faculty often,
but we're just not close.
Okay, sure.
Are you okay, though?
You're not drunk, yeah?
Hey!
I'm good.
Tell them to get more mixers.
I'll follow you
after getting another one.
"I'm good."
Well...
What do you want to know about your fortune?
You...
You've recently completed
or accomplished something, right?
I've just graduated. How did you know?
Concentrate deeply.
Set your mind on what you wish to ask.
These stones reveal the reality
and settle your doubts
according to your destiny.
Go on.
Pick three stones.
Whatever you do, things will go your way.
Just be focused and determined
and never give up.
Erm, well,
My family wants me to continue studying,
but I want to work.
You want to work, no problem.
But you must apply for companies...
with a building and stuff.
If you continue studying,
you'll be away from home,
and you'll have to travel.
One more thing...
I see...
[Gebo: Relationship]
Equality...
There's giving and receiving.
Be fair.
Oh.
One second.
I have to use the toilet.
I'll be right back.
Hey, why is Itthi so late?
He'll miss the reading.
He texted me that he had arrived,
but I don't know where he is.
Hi.
If I want to have my fortune read,
how much do you charge?
Erm...
Well...
I'll wait for you at the table.
What do I have to do, Ritt?
Erm...
Pick 3 stones.
[Eihwaz: Patience, Transition
Kenaz: Torch, Light]
[Algiz: Guardian / Protection]
What do you wish to ask?
I've just graduated.
I want to know my future.
Mm.
Good.
That's good.
Whatever you do is good.
What does that mean?
Well... It's good.
Very good.
No problems.
And...
What about the elders in the family?
Well...
They should watch their health.
They're seniors, you know.
Anything to be careful of specifically?
Nope.
Nothing.
Very good.
It's all good.
I have one more question.
It's about the past.
Then...
Pick a new set of stones.
[Perthro: Secrets / A turn of destiny]
[Wunjo: Happiness / Fulfillment]
[Gebo: Presents / Soulmates]
I used to have...
He used to have a sweetheart.
They were very close back then.
Always side by side.
That's true.
And after that,
he disappeared, and
I couldn't reach him anymore.
I'd like to know
if I'll ever see him again.
Wait, you studied at an all-boys school?
Where did you study?
What's your name?
Are you Itthi?
Itthiphumi Pongpanyalert.
Do you remember me?
I'm Ritt.
Like something out of a series...
Reaching over to fasten my seatbelt...
You're sitting so close to me.
Do you want to be
the lead or the love interest?
You're moving so fast, my friend.
Have they hooked up?
Haven't you told him yet
that you're not the real sweetheart?
So he still thinks that
you're his childhood sweetheart?
Or do you really look like him?
[Watch Magic Move Uncut version online
only on iQIYI and iQ.com]
♫Is it pure coincidence?♫
♫Or is it destiny that decides?♫
♫Is someone above drawing all these lines?♫
♫Or playing matchmaker in disguise?♫
♫What if the stars shift in their place♫
♫Slightly out of line,♫
♫Will our orbits still align?♫
♫Try answering (if) your world
will cross with mine♫
♫Though the destiny between us
is differently defined♫
♫I believe our love will change our♫
♫Destiny, rewrite prophecies♫
♫Even if they are against our destiny♫
♫(But we’re gonna try… try… try! )♫
♫And I believe our love has power♫
♫I believe the love of us♫
♫Will realign the stars back
to the line where they should be♫
♫(And we’re gonna try… try… try! )♫