Amazing!
I’m glad you thought of coming home.
Don’t get mad right now, please.
Okay? Forgive me already.
Whatever, you owe us an explanation.
Okay… Okay!
He brought me to his condo.
I slept at Kalix’s place.
I puked all over his bathroom.
Look at this.
Do you think they’re together?
They look like they’re just friends.
I'm not sure.
They’re always together.
So? We’re always together, too. But–
Hi, Kalix!
Ah, this is Sevi, my friend.
Sevi, this is Kalix.
Hey bro, Sevi.
You’re Sevi.
- Are you in a relationship? - What?
Do you have a crush on Amethyst?
I have to go.
Thanks for the dinner.
Why? Are you mad?
You’re confusing me, Luna.
A good relationship is built on honesty.
So, that’s why as early as now, I might as well ask about him and Amethyst.
Kalix.
I like you already.
Ke, I’m about to leave the condo.
Huh? You’re still in the condo?
Yes, why?
Oh, nothing. It’s just that–
Surprise!!!
I missed you!
I missed you, too!
I missed you, Sam!
Hey! It’s been so long.
You should have told me that they're coming for dinner.
I'm not prepared.
Wow! You call this unprepared?
Hey!
Pre-game first.
Wine from Spain.
Woohoo! You know it!
Let's settle down.
Besides, it won’t be a surprise if we told you.
Don’t you have a shoot today?
It got canceled, but I was already out of my house
so I asked the girls if they’re free for a surprise visit.
Yes, the timing's perfect. I just got off my last flight this morning.
You know how the life of a flight attendant is,
it’s so hard to find time.
I’ve been awake since morning.
Still jet-lagged?
Yes, I still haven’t adjusted. But–
That’s okay. What’s important is…
- We’re all together, finally! - That’s right!
Welcome back home, our architect from Spain.
Yes!
But, first order of business–
What’s up? I heard you have some news.
Oh my god, seriously you guys.
Did you all just come here to gossip? Can’t we have dinner first or something?
We’re not hungry yet. Spill the tea first!
Wow, such a deep sigh.
I want to resign.
Bitch, how?
What’s the issue? Is it because of work or is it about your past?
It’s crazy ‘cause it feels like the universe is playing tricks on me, you know?
It’s been years since I last saw Kalix, right?
Now, everywhere I go
no matter how I evade, I still bump into him.
Why? What happened?
¿Por qué?
This is what happened…
Let me help you.
Do you need help with that?
No.
Why are you here early?
The early bird catches the worm.
Right?
I have an early meeting and I have to review some documents.
Okay.
But this is what I couldn't stand–
I went to Dad’s office.
When I opened the door, guess who I saw?
Maybe he was there for a project?
Girl, do you know what they were talking about?
I don’t think you can beat me in golf.
Well, I just started but smy skills are pretty good.
Skills, you say? I’ll set our game.
Are you all right with that?
Deal.
It’s just so annoying that it feels like
he’s invading my personal space, you know what I mean?
He has his own office, so why can’t he just stay there?
Relax, come on.
Maybe he was there for a meeting.
Besides, you never told us the reason why you guys broke up.
Right! You just said that you both can’t focus on your studies.
Look at them now, they’re all in for the both of you to work together.
Come on, I don’t really need to tell it all in detail.
I don’t wanna relive the pain again.
Besides, it's emotionally draining.
And I don’t believe Dad actually needs him all the time.
Maybe he’s actually going there just to see you.
Bitch! He doesn’t need anything from me.
He seems happy, now that he has moved on.
The type who has forgotten everything that happened in the past.
Is that bitterness I’m sensing?
What bitterness?
Of course, not. Besides, I don’t care about him anymore.
You know, I just don’t want to feel the way I felt back then
when I was cheated on. It really hurts.
I guess that’s just the way it is.
The person on the receiving end
is always gonna remember what happened.
While the person who caused the pain, tends to just forget about it.
It’s so unfair.
Luna, do you still like Kalix?
- I think you still do. - No!
- Of course not. - You don’t?
I don’t! I really don’t. All I feel for him is anger.
Hey, calm down.
We know how pissed you are.
You know what? This wine is actually good for the heart.
Cheers!
- Cheers! - Cheers!
The ground should just open up and swallow me.
I am so embarrassed. I don’t know why I did it.
Calm down, its okay.
What happened anyway?
Okay, this is what happened…
I think…
I like you already.
Just kidding.
Did you actually believe me?
You know I like making jokes.
I'm not feeling well.
Maybe we should reschedule our study session.
I’ll just go home.
You sure?
You gotta rest.
So there! I actually got a stiff neck just to avoid facing him.
Besides from not saying “I like you” back, he didn’t even have any reactions at all.
I really have no idea why I did it, it’s so embarrassing!
You said you like him then you say it was just a joke?
That’s weak, Luna. You shouldn’t have taken it back.
Well, he didn’t have any reactions.
Of course, I just turned it into a joke ‘cause I was so ashamed.
This is weak.
You shouldn’t have stepped back.
If you were firm, we wouldn’t be having this problem.
She’s not like you.
Kalix’s actions are really confusing.
Based on her stories, it really seems like Kalix is into her, right?
But why didn’t he say, "I like you too"?
- Right? - Yes.
Isn’t he really confusing?
But wait–
Maybe he’s also confused with your actions.
Maybe he wasn’t sure if you were serious or not, right?
My goodness!
Let’s just stop talking about these boys.
This night is ours. Okay?
Let’s cheers!
Okay, fine.
Cheers!
- Okay, stand up. - You sure you can manage?
- Of course. I can take care of this. - Take care, okay?
Are you sure you guys will be okay?
- I’ll be fine, I’ll carry her home. - Hey, Yanna, your skirt!
Hey! My skirt’s just right here.
Hey!
- Careful! - It’s okay.
Left, right, left, okay.
- Take care! - Buh-bye!
Hey!
Bye!
Okay, let’s go home.
Kalix hasn’t texted me.
I know I’m not his girlfriend and I shouldn't be expecting his message–
but it still pisses me off that he hasn’t reached out to me yet.
Let me check his socials.
Maybe he really doesn’t like me.
Maybe he’s ignoring me because I keep making jokes.
What do you think, Ke?
Hey!
Who’s that “M?”
Nothing, no one.
Me-members. Group members.
- Nothing, no one? - We were just joking around.
That smile is giving you away, you flirt. I know that smile.
Kalix: you free tomorrow? let’s study.
- Oh? Wha– what happened to you? - Ke!
Why are you suddenly shrieking? Sit down.
Lord, thank you! Thank you.
Luna: Kalix, you still coming today? Looks like it’s gonna rain.
Kalix: Yes. It’s just the rain. I can handle it.
Luna: Okay :)
Kalix: And I already made this
Luna: Omg you cooked? That looks good! What is it?
Kalix: Shrimp Marinara with homemade pasta.
Kalix: It’s decent.
Luna: Perfect, I’m kinda hangry.
Kalix: You look so pretty for someone who’s hangry.
Kalix: On my way now.
Luna: Take care!
Don’t look at this.
But it’s good.
It’s not finished yet.
Look at this instead. Go ahead, give your compliments.
Pretty, right?
- You made that? - Yes.
This is my dream house.
This is my driving force to do good in school.
Someday I want–
to build this with my hard-earned money.
I just have a simple dream.
To be a successful architect, just like my parents.
And to live a comfortable life with my family.
Have you always wanted to be an architect?
Yes. I really want to.
When I was young…
my parents would have clients
and then they would bring me to the site once the project is completed.
The family would be there and they would see their new house.
You could really see their happiness,
that’s the feeling I like.
To be able to provide happiness to others.
That’s good.
It’s really nice, actually.
At least your dreams are in sync with your parents.
Why, aren’t yours the same?
If you don’t want to talk about it, it’s okay.
No pressure, okay? No pressure.
They want me to become a doctor.
Especially my mom.
Good thing they’re okay with you taking Law.
Not really.
We made a deal,
I have to keep my grades up and be in the dean’s list every single semester
or else, she’ll send me to med school.
That’s hard.
Yeah.
There’s constant high pressure and expectations.
It’s like, I can’t even make a single mistake or I’ll lose everything.
You know what, Kalix?
You’re doing well.
Just don’t forget to rest
so that you’ll have energy next time.
Kierra: I'll just stay here at Tanya’s dorm. The rain is so strong, España is already flooded!
Ke can't come home.
Roads on the way here are already flooded.
I don’t think the rain will stop anytime soon.
It’s dangerous to leave, Kalix.
Do you want to stay here for the meantime until the rain subsides?
Let me check socials. Then let’s see.
See, the roads have been closed.
You pass through here, right?
Is it okay if I spend the night here?
I’ll sleep on the couch.
Of course, it’s okay.
But, I don’t think you’ll fit in the couch. You're too tall.
How about this…
You stay in my room. I’ll stay in Ke’s room.
Ke’s room is locked.
You know what, it’s fine. Look, I’ll just drive home.
Come on, Kalix, it's not safe.
You might end up stranded.
Let’s just do this...
Let’s just sleep together in my room so that we’re both comfortable.
Are you sure?
I won’t do anything to you, Kalix.
Let me just fix the room.
I’m sorry. I usually sleep on this side
I'm not used to sleep on that side.
Don’t worry, I’ll put this here in the middle so that you’re safe.
Lights on, lights off?
Any.
I can’t really sleep with the lights on.
Could you turn it off?
Hey! Put a blanket. It’s cold.
Move closer here.
It’s okay.
Don’t you feel uncomfortable in your position?
Maybe, just turn towards me.
Just sleep, Luna.
Kalix.
Hey!
Hey, Kalix!
He fell asleep.
Now I can’t stare at him.
Hey, Kalix!
Good night, Luna.
Good night, Kalix.
Hurry up! He’s in the parking lot.
Wow, you went all the way here– fourteen kilometers from your school to my school.
Are you picking me up?
I don’t know.
Maybe.
I really came here to see you.
Hop in.
Okay, thank you!
Take care.
Kalix: Done stalking?
Luna: Huh? I am not!
You like milkshakes?
Yes. How about you?
I love milkshakes.
Ah, perfect!
We’re a perfect match.
Out of milkshakes?
Yes! We really are a perfect match.
Luna: I accidentally liked it. Hehe.
Kalix: that’s the only picture you liked.
Luna: and so?!
Kalix: it means you only like me when my shirt’s off.
Perfect! There you go.
Now I have something to post when we become official.
Are we gonna be official?
Yes?
Oh, stop. I’m not ready yet.
Just kidding.
Are you two together, now?
Huh?!
Are you two together already?
What an interrogation.
No.
Not yet.
Even if you chat everyday?
He always picks you up from school?
Even slept on the same bed?
I hope you don't get stuck in the friendzone.
Okay, fine.
I-I don’t know what we are.
Sometimes, I feel like we’re more than friends.
‘Cause he really makes me feel special.
But sometimes,
I think I’m just putting too much meaning since he’s my happy crush.
In short, you’re confused whether he likes you or not.
Exactly.
Why don’t you just confess, not as a joke, okay?
Like, tell him how you really feel.
I mean, you’re used to making the first move.
I can’t.
Since when did Luna Valeria ever become a coward?
I’m not a coward, Ke!
I’m just worried that it would ruin our friendship.
What if I confess,
and he doesn't feel the same way?
That would make things awkward.
I might regret it.
So, you’re scared to lose him?
Ke, I’m not scared to lose him.
I just don’t want to ruin our friendship.
Besides,
my feelings for him aren't that deep.
I’m just enjoying what we have.
Just a happy crush.
What?
Nothing…
Your happy crush just texted!
Kalix: are you free later? let’s study together.
Okay, I'll come over.
I’ll bring food.
Weak!
May I take your picture?
Just pretend it’s candid.
It’s fine.
So handsome.
Is it okay if I make this my wallpaper?
You can do whatever you want.
I hope you don't get stuck in the friendzone.
Why don’t you just confess, not as a joke, okay?
Like, tell him how you really feel.
Isn’t it weird?
What’s weird?
To make you my wallpaper even if you’re not my boyfriend?
Bro, why weren’t you answe–
Sorry, we didn’t mean to intrude.
We didn’t know you’re here.
I’m sorry, are we interrupting something between you and…
What’s your name?
She’s Luna.
Ah. So, do you want us to leave?
‘Cause you haven’t been replying so we didn’t know if you had company.
I’ll just go, Kalix.
No.
Everyone stays.
Let’s just fix whatever you guys brought.
- Come on. - Sorry Luna, we didn’t know you’re here.
Let’s just drink!
Okay guys, fix it up.
Alright.
Bro, we don’t have any ice.
What are we gonna do?
We can go to a convenience store. Come on.
- Perfect, I can buy cigarettes. - Come on, let’s go.
Can I sit here?
I’m Amethyst by the way, I don’t think we’ve met yet.
Luna.
So, you’re an Archi major.
So what did Kalix say about your designs?
He’s not really a drawing and design kind of guy.
It’s not really what he’s into, as far as I know.
Nothing.
But you guys are pretty close. Considering you both don’t have a lot of similarities.
Yes, we’re close.
Nice!
I’m happy it’s working out for you.
Although, he almost always tells us
if he’s seeing someone…
Seriously, I mean.
So it’s funny that he hasn't mentioned you to us, like at all.
Well, KJ you know,
he’s really serious about his goals to become a lawyer
so maybe he's not looking for anything serious right now.
We’re going to play truth or shot.
If you can’t answer, take a shot.
- Game! - Let’s do this!
Luna, don’t be shy.
If you can’t take the shot, let Kalix take it.
Jeez! These are just shots.
Maybe I’ll take the shots for him.
Just don’t get drunk.
Don’t worry. I don’t get drunk easily.
All right then,
don’t underestimate Luna.
Okay, let’s start!
All right!
First bottle goes to…
- Adi. - Adi!
Truth or shot?
Truth, of course!
Why’d you turn down Sam?
She’s friend material for me, bro.
You bastard, too bad!
Sam’s a total catch!
Too bad about Sam.
Once she’s decided to move on from her crush,
there’s no going back.
- Okay, next? - Okay.
Okay, so who’s gonna ask Kalix?
Me!
Okay, Kalix.
Do you still
think about...
our first night together?
Okay!
Deflecting the question, I see.
- Okay, spin the bottle? - Yeah!
Okay, next round!
Ah!
Guys, my parents just texted me. They’re asking me to go home.
You have to leave now?
Stay for a bit!
Luna, we’re just getting started.
It’s still early!
No, my head’s been hurting as well.
I’ll drive you home.
No need.
They might think I’m your girlfriend.
I don’t wanna explain.
Besides, if you drive me home, you’ll get stuck in traffic.
Just play spin the bottle with them, it seems like you’re all enjoying it.
- Take care, Luna. - See you!
Bye, Luna!
Wasn’t this supposed to be just a happy crush?
Why am I feeling this way?
Luna!
Happy birthday, Sam!
Thank you so much, everyone!
I love you all!
Let’s enjoy the night!
Happy birthday, Sam!
Fuck! Unlimited drinks, unlimited hotties!
So, unlimited flirting for me!
Hey!
Luna, you might get drunk again and suddenly disappear! Take it slow.
What’s the problem? What happened?
And wow, why are you looking for guys?
Don’t you already have one?
Excuse me!
I’m very much single right now.
Bitch is heartbroken!
Hey, what’s that?
Come on, you’ve been ignoring Kalix.
You weren’t answering his texts and calls.
I didn’t ghost him! I’m just ignoring him.
But why?
Did you two fight again?
Let’s just stop talking about someone who’s not even here.
Come on, let’s party—
I invited Kalix though,
but he said he might not come.
Well, he really shouldn’t come because I don’t want to see him.
Come on, let’s party!
Hey, Via!
We’ll just go to the bathroom, we’ll finish all these later.
You better be back.
Hey, it’s the guy you ghosted.
Oh no.
They even came together.
Sam! I thought you didn't invite that girl?
I didn’t invite her,
maybe Kalix just brought her.
Come on, chill!
This club is huge. Let’s just have fun!
Luna, wait, I just need to answer this.
Wait, wait! I’ll be back, just a sec!
Hey, come on! Let’s greet the birthday girl.
S-Shan!
Shan, Shan! Luna.
Didn’t know you’re here.
Sam, wait a minute. Let me sit, my feet hurt.
Just a minute.
Sam! Happy birthday!
- Sam, happy birthday! - Hi! Thank you.
Thank you!
Thank you, Amy.
- Hi, Kalix! - Happy birthday!
Wanna get a drink?
Hi!
Wanna take a shot?
Sure.
KJ, why aren't you drinking?
Cheers birthday girl!
Cheers!
What’s up?
Why are you here?
Let’s kiss.
Sure!
What?
You okay?
Ke! Where are you?
I’m so pissed! You gotta know what happened!
Bitch! I’m back inside, where are you?
I’m outside since it’s so noisy inside.
But fine! Wait for me there, I need to tell you what happened.
Glad you came.
Sam told me you're not coming.
Kalix?
Luna, fuck!
Do not play with me, please.
Kalix!
For fuck’s sake!
What is your problem?
Nevermind.
What the hell, Kalix? What is wrong?
I just don’t get you. You’re so confusing!
Can’t you just explain to me what exactly is happening?
Me?
Are you serious?
See? You can’t even answer me.
I get it now.
I guess that’s just how you act with everyone.
What did you just say?
Maybe it’s my fault for assuming things.
Can you just please leave me alone for now?
You’re so confusing, Kalix! So confusing!
How, Luna?
Okay, how?
One moment, you treat me special
and then the next, you act so sweetly with Amethyst.
So what is it? I’m so confused.
I have no idea if you like me or not.
That time during the spin the bottle game,
she even asked you in front of me
about your first night together.
Like I should just back off?
You’re so misleading, Kalix!
I just don't understand.
I don’t know if you guys are fuck buddies?
Are you in a relationship with her? Was she your girlfriend?
I don’t know if I should still keep my hopes up.
I don’t want to be misled, Kalix!
Luna, Amy and I are just friends.
Her question during the spin the bottle game was just a stupid little dare
that happened before.
Yes, we kissed before but it meant nothing
and I didn’t know how to answer the question
‘cause you were right in front of me and I didn’t want you to get the wrong idea.
So,
you don’t really like Amethyst?
No.
How about me?
What am I to you, Kalix?
I guess, I wasn’t clear enough with my actions.
I’m sorry.
There’s something I wanna show you, Luna.
Can you come with me?
What are we doing here, Kalix?
This is my parents' house.
And it will be mine once I graduate from Law school.
The reason it’s still empty is because
I still can’t afford to buy things for this house.
Despite that, this place has been my resting place.
I come here whenever I want to escape from everything.
I never brought any of my friends here.
Not Amy.
Not Adonis. Not Leo.
But I brought you here,
because I wanna show you every side of me.
Even the most vulnerable parts.
What I’m trying to say is–
I like you, Luna.
And I’m really sorry if I haven’t been clear from the start.
You know that I’m not really good with words
so I tried showing it through my actions.
By doing that,
I guess, I just made you even more confused.
I’m sorry.
Are you crying?
You’re crazy.
You said you weren’t good with words, jeez!
I was just asking for a yes or no.
But you made it grand by showing off this house and giving your monologue.
I wanna show you the veranda.
Wow!
This is so beautiful.
You even have a telescope!
Yes.
Does it work?
Yeah.
Can I use it?
Come on.
Here, right?
May I?
Yes.
Kalix!
I can see the moon! It’s beautiful.
The sky looks amazing.
You know what, I–
I rarely see any stars.
‘Cause, you know, Manila is full of buildings.
I would love to go here every night.
I can bring you here every night.
You know, even without the telescope,
you can still see the moon.
Luna.
It means moon.
Yes, you're right.
Now you’ll remember me everytime you look at the moon.
Like a curse.
It’s not like a curse.
More like a tattoo in my brain.
A beautiful one.
One that I’m never gonna forget.
Let’s do the boyfriend-girlfriend thing.
Okay.
Can you and Sevi just wait for me in the restaurant?
This meeting will only take thirty minutes anyway.
What’s the agenda? New project?
He said it’s gonna be a project briefing.
I guess it’s a VIP client.
To think that uncle will give the briefing to you.
Exactly!
I’m excited since it’s been a while since we got a passion project, right?
True.
I gotta go, the meeting’s about to start.
Dad! Let’s start the meeting?
Yes, we’re about to start.
Hello, Architect Valeria.
Why is Attorney Martinez here?
Am I in the right meeting?
Yes, Luna. You’re in the right meeting.
And he’s here because he needs to be here.
Why?
Before anything else, Luna,
I just want you to know that this big project
has a very high sentimental value for the client.
And by the way,
the client requested specifically for you.
I’m lost.
Can you give me the project brief?
Of course.
The rest house in Tagaytay?
That’s right, Architect Valeria.
I’m not here as your legal counsel, but as your client.
Let’s talk about the halloween break. What are your plans?
Luna, Kalix, what's your plan?
We’re going to Boracay.
- Wow! - What? Boracay?
Boracay is so beautiful.
I’ve been here a couple of times, but I don’t know why–
It’s more beautiful now.
Maybe you can finish that later?
Luna?
Where are you?
Good morning, Ke!
Hey, Ke!
Sorry, what’s wrong?
By the way, this is Miguel, my boyfriend.