(Uilhan Brewery)
(1. Malting, 2. Malt milling, 3. Mash tun, 4. Hopping)
(Kim Se Jeong)
(Highly passionate, highly sensitive)
(Lee Jong Won)
(Shin Do Hyun)
(Baek Sung Chul)
(Uilhan Brewery)
(Naro Beer)
(Brewing Love)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Scenes with child actors and animals were filmed...)
(under production guidelines along with experts.)
- What are you doing? - Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
You're not fine.
You're...
not fine.
Excuse me.
Do explain.
Sorry.
Your mood's a bit...
What about my mood?
Never mind. I apologize.
Why do I always go so far?
Thank you, sniper lady.
I'm not a sniper.
Then what are you?
Someone who sells alcohol.
Happy birthday.
Thanks to you, I got to...
Well...
I...
I should go on my way.
Bye.
Bye, sniper lady.
Hey.
(Episode 2)
The sniper lady... Didn't she say your name?
I'm pretty sure she said "Yoon Min Ju."
Did she?
That's not important.
I thought...
she looked really sad.
- Something must be wrong. - What?
I couldn't tell.
What? Are you worried about her?
What are you saying? Why would I be?
I feel whatever other people feel,
so this is an everyday thing.
You know what I'm saying, don't you?
I didn't say anything.
Why are you making such a fuss?
Where does a six-year-old learn to say that?
You usually turn a blind eye and pretend you don't notice.
You pretend not to feel anything when you do...
and don't get involved.
Why did you approach the sniper lady?
I don't know either.
When did you get so sharp?
Roundabout when I turned four?
Granny.
Why are you sleeping out here?
Did you have dinner?
I did. It's late.
Let's go to bed.
- Oh, dear. - Let's sit up.
One, two. Here we go.
What?
Is something wrong?
My branch is out of business.
Don't worry.
There will be a solution.
And I'll find it.
- Do you believe in me? - I do.
Let's go to bed.
Let's go to your bedroom. One, two.
There we go.
- Sleep well. - Go to bed.
I will. Shall I turn this off?
Yes.
I love you.
Are you all right?
You're not fine.
You're...
not fine.
He spoke as if he knew.
Get a grip, Chae Yong Ju.
Who cares how you feel?
My gosh.
Should I see a doctor?
No. Let's handle the urgent stuff first.
(Jisang Liquor)
- Are we really out of business? - What happens now?
I just joined the team.
What do I do?
Let me go inside.
Yong Ju. He's the Director of Marketing at the head office.
Hello.
He has an offer for you.
(Branch Manager Nam Yong Cheol)
Join our Marketing Team.
I can't.
What? You refuse?
You don't want to keep this branch open?
Is there a way to do that?
(Naro Beer)
Win over...
brewery master Yoon Min Ju.
And create a new product.
Impress the chairman and this place will come right back to life.
Everyone says you're the best at finding people.
We'll provide everything you need.
What do you say? Can you do it?
What is he saying?
What?
I'll do it.
I swear to get Yoon Min Ju.
(Brewing Love)
(I give my life to be Jisang's best!)
Ms. Chae.
You won't visit the wholesalers and store owners?
They'll be upset to hear you went to Seoul...
without saying goodbye.
I won't be able to leave if I say goodbye.
It's best to keep farewells short.
You punk.
Chairman.
Hello, everyone.
So you're really leaving?
You heard already?
Look after yourself.
You must.
I will.
Eat well and on time.
You're too thin.
Who, me? I'm not.
If you're in any trouble,
call me.
I'll be right there.
Yes, sir.
Goodbye.
Bye.
It's my first day.
What's most important on the first day?
The team dinner.
What do we eat?
Meat!
Darn, I'm hungry.
What's all this?
Why would you go through all this trouble?
Take a seat.
It's your first day at a new job. Don't forget your breakfast.
Don't let them intimidate you.
It's not like this is my first job ever.
You burned them all.
What if you get robbed with your eyes wide open?
You may have been born and raised in Seoul,
but your base was in a provincial city...
as well as your place of work.
Grandma, would I let anyone live after robbing me?
I'd either pluck the thief's arm or leg.
You and your choice of words.
I'll be late.
At least finish your meal.
You practically drank the rice down.
Don't be intimidated.
I'm Mad Dog Yong Ju.
As if that's something to be proud of.
A new caregiver will come by starting today.
Eat the meal she serves on time.
- Got it? - Fine.
If your head hurts when you're alone,
call for an ambulance right away.
It'll be faster to call paramedics than me.
- Got it? - Just get going.
You know you have to open your phone and press one.
Why you...
All right. I'll get going. I love you!
(Jisang Liquor)
Yong Ju.
Look at you, Mr. Kang.
You look different now that you're in Seoul.
Don't I look neat?
Why didn't you stay back in Busan?
You know the hardships ahead.
Of course I should be here too.
We're a 2-for-1 deal.
I go where you go.
Thanks, Beom. Let's go.
Being called by my name took me by surprise.
(Jisang Liquor)
Sweet!
This is the new zero-sugar edition.
Please tell us what you think.
Are these all for free?
(Jisang Liquor)
(Sparkling liquor, Beer)
How can drinking beer be a job?
What are you staring at?
Hello, sir.
It was a long commute, wasn't it?
Follow me.
From what I hear,
we hit a roadblock...
because Yoon Min Ju won't talk to us.
He turns down meetings once he hears it's us.
You'll need to figure out a way to get through to him.
Yes, sir. We'll come up with a strategy.
Unbelievable.
The Planning Team went to see him today as well.
Do so yourselves by the end of this week.
Report to me once you have a date and time.
Yes, sir. We'll go to him right away.
- What? - Right now?
- Right now? - Yes, right now.
At this very moment.
- One, two. - What the...
One, two.
This is your village chief.
This afternoon,
I propose we gather to discuss...
the One and Only Hop Beer Festival...
which is our village's largest event.
Come if you can.
It's always the same people who plan the event,
so be present at the meeting if you're not drowning in work.
Can't one get some sleep around here?
Since when has anyone been serious about planning it?
Is there something else at play?
Something's fishy.
Darn, that hurts.
(Village Chief)
It can't be helped if you're too busy,
but there are some people who choose not to participate...
despite having a lot of time to spare.
I won't name names.
I doubt he's talking about me.
I'm not talking about the young man who brews beer.
All right.
Enjoy your lunch, and I'll see you later.
Why... Why me?
- Being around a lot of people... - All right, then.
drains my energy.
That will be all.
Ah Reum.
If Yoon Min Ju doesn't meet us today, we'll quit.
My thought exactly.
There's so much rejection we can take.
We should at least try today...
and give up if we can't succeed.
(It's a match!)
(Lee Sang Jin, 31)
Hold on. You're still going on weekly blind dates.
Do you still mean it?
Will you quit your job after marrying?
Yes, and that'll happen in one year.
You're a true J personality. You have everything mapped out.
(Lee Sang Jin, 31)
You can retire early if you want to,
so why keep at this job?
To get a higher grade.
Being on the Planning Team of a major company...
will grant me a better grade with matchmaking services.
I must maintain a high grade to marry a man of that level.
Why are you this desperate to marry?
I don't get it at all.
My life has been planned up to my marriage,
and I must proceed.
The fact that you're still going on blind dates...
means you haven't found the one.
Maybe you have too high standards.
Very, to be exact.
But I'll never compromise.
Just see what perfect man I eventually marry.
Boss, check me out.
Aren't I strong?
I have push carts for that.
Seriously.
You're the merciless type.
Just so you know, compliments get me dancing.
That reminds me.
I heard Jisang Liquor came by while I was absent.
I guess I forgot to tell you.
The business proposal is on the shelf.
It seemed decent.
I'm not interested.
If they come by in my absence again, turn them down.
Sure.
When will you talk casually to me?
Aren't you older?
Did we ever agree to talk casually?
Aren't we best friends?
Then why did you introduce me to your family?
- My family? - Photo.
(Me?)
Meow.
I'm off to the town hall.
Only if you say it casually.
He's a savage at ignoring people.
Nice. I absolutely love it.
(Uilhan Brewery)
Finally, I get to meet you. You must be CEO Yoon.
I'm Bang Ah Reum of Jisang Liquor's Planning Team.
I've been trying to reach you by call or text.
Do you perhaps recall?
You should talk to me.
My boss...
isn't a fan of interacting with other people...
and tends to draw a line.
Move.
You've been calling nonstop,
so I guess we should talk.
Shall we sit over there?
(Uilhan Brewery)
That's odd.
Goodness. He'll soon turn them down.
Hang in there, Ms. Beautiful Bang.
Chae Yong Ju said she'd be here too.
Where is she and why isn't she here yet?
Hello.
I'm Chae Yong Ju of Jisang Liquor. We talked on the phone.
Goodness.
Hello.
- My gosh. - Goodness.
This really wasn't necessary.
It's nothing much.
We wanted to thank you for putting this together for us.
Goodness.
As if this will keep me alive for that much longer.
Anyway, did CEO Yoon suddenly drop dead?
- Just a second. - Go ahead.
The call cannot be connected.
- Transferring to voicemail. - Is he brewing that phone of his?
He is always hard to reach.
That's why I contact him by broadcasting messages...
even though we live in a world of smart devices.
We can wait. It's fine.
Go ahead.
By the way, I don't know what deal you're trying to make with him,
but he'll be tough to persuade.
Meanwhile, he'll mercilessly shoot your proposal down.
(Jisang Liquor)
Won't we at least get to meet him today?
I'll make it happen.
Mr. Yoon, name your terms...
and we'll meet as many as possible.
My terms?
Yes, lay them out for us.
I would like to brew my beer within the boundaries of my brewery.
That means it won't be possible to mass-produce my beer...
in a way major liquor corps would...
and sell them all across the country.
Would that be okay?
That's...
I'm afraid...
I apologize for offending you.
Gosh, no.
You saw wrong. I wasn't offended at all.
Your boss probably forced you here,
but now that I'll decline any offer.
I have business to attend to and must get going.
Have a safe trip back.
I hope you feel better on the road.
It's not like that.
Take care, Mr. Yoon.
Take care.
Did it seem that obvious?
No. You were smiling the entire time.
I'm excellent at hiding my expressions,
so that's something.
Unbelievable.
Him?
Being a master brewer...
makes him think he can do whatever he wants.
Darn.
Seriously.
Why won't he leave my sight?
(Fate)
What?
Why is there a car from Jisang Liquor here?
We will brew another beer that plays to your strengths.
I need to get Yoon Min Ju on board today.
Yoon Min Ju...
- Pink bear? - The sniper?
You said my name that day as well.
Did I?
Are you CEO Yoon Min Ju?
Yes.
This is definitely more comfortable. Nice.
Did you just get here?
Why come so early and not swing by tomorrow?
He sees himself as the man of the hour.
They're from the major liquor corp Jisang Liquor.
They begged me to let them see you,
and you know I can't turn people down.
I yield to power and authority even more.
I'll leave you to it, then.
Sir, we have more to talk about.
Do you work at Jisang Liquor?
Yes.
That's why you said my name.
You're CEO Yoon Min Ju, the brewer of Naro Beer.
I guess you can say fate brought us together.
Why don't we sit down and talk?
No.
I have nothing more to say to Jisang Liquor.
I already turned down your colleague's offer.
Then...
We work at the same company,
but our proposals are completely different.
If you can read this...
Mr. Yoon?
Forget it.
Mr. Yoon.
Please...
I know you're busy,
so how about you spare me five minutes?
What's so desperate this time around?
You must've talked to the Planning Team,
- but I'm from the Marketing Team... - Look.
The name is Chae Yong Ju.
Ms. Chae Yong Ju,
why are you going to such an extent?
Of course I should.
I can do and be good with anything...
if that means you'll talk to me.
Why do you keep saying you're all right?
We're here to suggest we brew...
a different beer that isn't Naro Beer.
Without hurting the brand...
you established with the village people,
I will have your brewery and our company...
benefit from each other.
When I first tasted your beer,
I noticed how delicate and clean the flavors were.
- So... - I said you weren't okay.
Back then and even now, you are not okay.
Are you upset?
As if.
I said this to your colleagues,
but I will never do business with Jisang Liquor.
You can hear my proposal first and then decline.
I'm desperately asking you.
Would that be too much to ask?
Yes.
(New Beer Joint Project Proposal)
Being able to see that desperation...
makes it even harder.
See a doctor.
Thank you.
How did you know?
What?
What the...
Yong Ju.
What?
The village chief was easily persuaded.
Did CEO Yoon leave?
Why did I put those slippers on her?
Why did I overreact?
These aren't my feelings.
These aren't my feelings. Don't be confused.
Focus on yourself, Yoon Min Ju.
- Mr. Yoon, are you okay? - Goodness.
Darn, that startled me.
I'm all right, but your face is too close.
Oh, right.
Why do I lose control whenever I'm with her?
This should be the last time I see her.
- Are you all right? - Yes, I'm fine.
I appreciate your concern.
I'm just glad you're okay.
Then, as of this moment,
I'll block you.
You'll do what?
What was that?
What... But...
Mr. Yoon?
What the...
He rejected you big time.
But all I did was show concern.
He'll block me?
That was him challenging me, wasn't it?
Cheers.
I feel like we get along.
Same here. You should be the boss instead.
Goodness.
I'm loved by ladies all across the country.
I have a lovable personality.
Don't I know it.
Our boss at the brewery...
is too fussy.
I'm wasting my breath talking about it.
Cleanse it.
Boss, come and have snacks with us!
Don't.
What on earth?
He must be experiencing a storm of emotions again.
Tell me about it. He's been fine for a while,
so I wonder what happened.
So much for talking smack about him.
You must've bonded seeing how you took his side and not mine.
What? When did I do that?
Our relationship is strictly business.
Exactly. Our relationship is only based on our paychecks.
- Now, drink up. - Right.
These aren't my emotions.
Focus only on me.
To be honest, I'm confused.
I don't know if the agony is mine...
or someone else's.
She was the one in distress,
but it's now eating away at me.
So,
are the feelings mine or someone else's?
Yoon Min Ju locked himself up in his house.
What did you do to make him that way?
When he goes into that space,
it's hard to tell when he'll get out.
He's like a bear that crawled into a cave.
Even the threat of a fire won't get him to leave.
Hold on.
What's that smoke?
- Is something burning? - What?
Is it really a fire?
Toast, get him out of there.
But I don't know how to get to the second floor.
There aren't any stairs inside the house.
I know that, but still.
Please calm down. I'll check on him.
Is there a way? Please help him.
Nothing should happen to our boss.
Chan Hwi, you carry that around, right?
Don't tell me you'll...
What was that?
Are you all right, Mr. Yoon?
What... How are you here?
They were scented candles! What a relief.
Mr. Yoon,
I apologize for any inconvenience I caused.
What? Who apologizes while hanging from a rope?
Will you accept my apology?
I will, so get back down.
It's dangerous, so get down already.
Since you accepted my apology,
please accept this as well.
What?
I'm unblocking your block.
Unblock me!
Goodness me. That's like a scene from a movie.
- She's not your average girl. - My gosh.
She sure is impressive.
Just this one thing.
I'll only say what I can promise you.
I will never...
do wrong by this place or your beer.
Instead, let's brew a new kind of beer.
Together. You and us.
No, I won't do that.
I saw that you were okay, so I'll get going for now.
Don't ever come back here. Okay?
Please call me if you want to talk.
I'll await your call.
No, this can't be.
Those aren't the eyes of someone who'll await my call.
I saw a lunatic in her.
I met the wrong woman for sure.
This can't be.
Excuse me.
Hold up.
Just let her leave for today.
She may seem all right,
but something is clearly bothering her.
This is huge, I give you that.
She was able to drag him out of his cave.
Even the demigod would be impressed.
- Shall we get going? - What?
- But... - Chan Hwi,
can you clean this up and also what's on the roof?
But...
Hold on a second.
Do not let her in if she ever comes back.
I don't want to see her again. Got it?
- Maybe. - Maybe.
But...
Are you leaving already? You should've sat down with him.
An ordinary method won't work. I need to change my strategy.
As expected from you.
Yong Ju. After we join hands with Yoon Min Ju,
let's head straight to Busan.
Of course. We've got many lives to save.
- You're crazy cool. - Goodness.
Let's stop by the supermarket on our way.
You should eat something.
Shall we do that?
(A fly)
Do you not have iced Americano?
Do you think we do?
It doesn't seem like it.
Right? In this day and age,
it's absurd that a supermarket doesn't have that America-something.
The owner of this place...
was born without a single wit.
I thought you were the owner.
The owner's name is Kim.
He's nothing close to a smart person.
If I were the owner,
this place would've already beat all supermarkets, even in Seoul.
Let's see.
A French modern-style display on this side...
will wow the customers...
and make them...
pinch their cheeks to make sure it isn't a dream.
(A fly)
What?
Why do I see our company car over there?
Is it the Marketing Team?
She must be the new manager of the Marketing Team, right?
I heard she was a legend in Busan.
Little did I know she was pretty, too.
That celebrity. She looks a lot like that one celebrity.
What's this?
Why are you all smiles, or is it just my imagination?
I bet we'll get along well.
Goodness.
Are you fleeing for refuge?
I'm starving.
Gosh.
Hi.
I'm Section Chief Bang Ah Reum from the Planning Team.
Oh, I see.
You had a meeting with CEO Yoon Min Ju, right?
Can we talk for a minute?
Sure. Of course.
As you may have understood from the meeting, CEO Yoon...
doesn't want to sign a contract with us.
Clinging to him won't do us any good.
We will know that only after we try until the end.
But you see, he's rejecting Jisang Liquor as a whole.
Why don't we wrap it up here...
and persuade each of our directors to put an end to this?
This is just a battle of pride between our directors.
Let's not get caught in the crossfire.
Even if we do, it won't hurt me at all.
I've got a high skeletal muscle mass.
Stop. I'm sorry.
Does this mean the Planning Team is giving up?
We're not giving up. I'm proposing we act rationally...
and think of an alternative plan to save time.
But I haven't done anything to think of an alternative plan.
I will secure Yoon Min Ju.
No matter what.
Well, if that's what you wish to do.
We've done everything possible.
All right. It's now our turn to do our best.
Great.
Ah Reum.
The Marketing Team's manager is the first person...
I've drifted apart with so quickly.
She's clearly a young oldie not even modern medicine can fix.
Gosh, I never want to get close to her.
What's this? Where did that bright smile of yours go?
Had I been that manager's direct junior,
I would've quit ages ago.
I have a bad feeling about her.
What's with them?
Why is everyone telling me I can't do it?
It's making me want to succeed.
Yong Ju.
Your eyes could kill.
CEO Yoon isn't easy to deal with, right?
He's a very hard guy to persuade.
Yes, you're right.
It's all thanks to you that we could meet CEO Yoon.
Gosh, don't mention it.
- I was born as a very nice man. - I see.
Take this supermarket for example.
It's not mine, but I'm taking care of it...
since the owner is out of the country.
Is that so? Then, we should get...
Since we're on the topic,
the supermarket owner Kim...
is such a selfish man.
It's that time of the year.
The busiest season in our town.
We need to harvest hops, brew beer,
and prepare for the festival.
But that jerk Kim...
had to go on an overseas trip right now.
Then, the town must be short-handed.
Don't get me started. If only I had ten arms, you know?
All right.
Why don't I work here starting tomorrow?
What?
That would help me out loads.
It certainly would.
Girl, stop it.
This is great. Really.
Okay.
(Jisang Liquor)
- Mr. Kang. - Yes?
Did Ms. Chae really go alone?
- Yes. - My goodness.
Anyone can tell there's no chance of succeeding.
Isn't she going too far?
Come on. Don't worry.
Ms. Chae never takes back her words.
I'm sure she already has the town wrapped around her little finger.
She's brilliant.
The ace of the Busan branch.
Chae Yong Ju is different.
She's super cool.
Please, Chief.
Just this once. Please.
What? Come on, Chief.
- Go away. - How come?
Just once!
Really.
Yesterday, you told me to come at any cost.
And here I am.
I guess you didn't hear the news.
What news?
The news that this town is off limits to Chae Yong Ju.
Sorry?
I read a text message that...
Chae Yong Ju from Jisang Liquor will work here starting today.
Who agreed to it?
- It wasn't me. - Who was it?
Come clean and ask for mercy.
You know you can't fool me, right?
Chief?
You see, as the village chief,
I suffer from this disease where I lose myself...
when I spot youngsters who can help us out.
An extra pair of hands is always good.
Don't you agree?
Stop smiling, and agree to it.
- I'm sorry. - How can you...
No. I will never let Ms. Chae Yong Ju...
into my boundary.
She's prohibited, okay?
Stop her.
One way or another.
All right. Put your faith in us.
We're experts in that area.
We're experts.
That's the story behind it.
Like I have a choice.
CEO Yoon is this town's cash cow.
Yoon Min Ju is like an iron wall.
But today, I will surely clear all of these hurdles...
and stand before Yoon Min Ju.
Just you wait.
What is she mumbling?
Take this!
What?
You can't set another foot in here.
Chae Yong Ju.
(Supermarket)
(Jisang Liquor's legendary Lady in Black, Chae Yong Ju)
(The charismatic 17th Village Chief of Baegok-ri, Lee Yi Jang)
(Chae Yong Ju versus Lee Yi Jang)
Stage One. Start.
I become extremely small in front of money and power.
I'm sorry.
Just leave, okay?
I didn't expect the chief to take such an action.
What is the most sure-fire way to pass the chief?
(Stop Chae Yong Ju)
Chief.
What?
What does she want?
You see...
I brought these just in case. I swear.
- How dare you... - Vitamins, omega-3, calcium,
magnesium, lutein, iron, maca, folic acid,
and such, but...
You are such a sincere person.
I can't play possum when you're this desperate.
I'm not a cold-hearted man.
Okay.
I'm 2km away from meeting Yoon Min Ju.
(In Search for CEO Yoon Min Ju)
CEO Yoon?
I've never been proper.
I'm so easy to please.
Chae Yong Ju.
That Chae Yong Ju...
You won't get through them.
What's with them?
Are they...
my next opponent?
- Hey! - Turn the car around...
right now!
They're quite strong.
What?
(Jisang Liquor's legendary Lady in Black, Chae Yong Ju)
(Uilhan Brewery's duumvirate, Sook and Young)
(Sook and Young Sisters versus Chae Yong Ju)
Stage Two. Start.
It's not like we enjoy doing this,
but we don't have a choice.
The CEO goes mad...
whenever he spots you.
If we don't stop you, his nagging...
will come back to us.
It's like a boomerang.
So while we're still being nice...
Please leave.
Back to your home.
You must go back home.
There's only one way to conquer these ladies.
What I always say to my granny when the odds are against me.
That one phrase that makes their world crumble down.
My stomach...
Good gracious.
It's so empty.
What?
Have you not eaten anything? But it's the middle of the day!
Eating a proper meal is all that matters in life, you know?
Why bother with food?
Only when you starve to death...
will you realize...
ignoring your hunger was the worst decision of your life.
Is it not working?
Gosh, my stomach is growling.
- Follow us at once. - Follow us at once.
I'm 500m away from meeting Yoon Min Ju.
(In Search for CEO Yoon Min Ju)
Yes?
It's me.
It's our loss, CEO Yoon.
We're sorry.
We'll pay today off by working twice as hard.
- Here. Dig in. - Thank you.
How she digs in is right up my alley.
She's definitely a kind girl.
You can tell she's a good daughter.
I'm not too sure about that.
My parents passed away when I was little.
- What? - What?
My granny had it hard,
raising me all alone.
Is that why you joined the special task force?
To earn money as soon as possible?
Yes. I sought to become a professional soldier...
right after graduating high school.
See that? I told you, didn't I?
She's certainly kind-hearted.
Are you crying?
Why would you cry...
so early in the morning?
Who says I'm crying?
Nothing in this world makes me cry, you know?
But why is Chae Yong Ju...
making you cry?
I'm okay. Eat loads.
You must eat everything.
Where did Chae Yong Ju go?
I see...
What?
Ma'am. Why are you up there? It's dangerous.
Ma'am!
Come down, ma'am!
You don't need to work twice as hard!
Get down now!
Goodness. Come down now. It's dangerous.
What if you get hurt?
Slowly. One step at a time.
That's it. One step at a time.
I banned you from going up there, didn't I?
Why did you go up there all of a sudden?
Who are you saying that to?
Is it to us?
Of course. Who else...
What?
Wait.
What? Who is she?
Standing right before Yoon Min Ju...
It's me.
(Brewing Love)
Ms. Beautiful Bang.
You really came.
Don't you work at CEO Yoon's brewery?
Who are you?
Boss. Hire Chae Yong Ju as a part-time worker.
She used to be in the special task force.
Ms. Chae. I want you to leave now.
CEO Yoon.
You messed with something you shouldn't have.
I get the job done, too. Chae Yong Ju.
I wonder who will hold...
- that guy's hand. - That guy's hand.