You are happy, aren't you?
Your eyes are closed, so how can you know that?
Your happiness is so strong I can almost feel it.
What a good girl you are.
The same as you,
who are good at everything.
Since when do you talk like this?
Like what?
This isn't strange.
It feels strange because you have such a naughty mind.
But it really isn't strange, you know?
It's normal for people who are about to get married.
Really?
You naughty girl.
I have something for you.
Hm?
Actually, I meant to give it to you last night.
But I just couldn't find the right moment.
Turn around, I'll put it on for you.
Do you like it?
Of course, I do.
Thank you.
Will I really get to wake up to the sight of you every morning?
I'm so excited.
Since I met you,
everything feels exciting.
So, do you like it?
Yes, I do.
Morning.
How's it going?
Have you found any clues?
As before, ma'am,
I only found people who looked alike.
When I asked them,
the details didn't match yours.
Then keep looking.
I believe they're still alive.
But ma'am...
It's been a long time.
You shouldn't get your hopes up.
I'm not giving up hope.
Keep doing your job.
I hope to see them again
while I'm still alive.
I'll try my best, ma'am.
Thank you.
Wow...
It's just a pre-wedding shoot. Do you have to look this beautiful?
It's the bride's glow.
Did you just realize how beautiful your girlfriend is?
Perfect timing. Okay, come on!
Keep going. Pose! Three, two...
That's good. Three, two...
Good.
Three, two...
Still can't decide?
I can't make up my mind.
They're all beautiful.
How can I pick the right one for my artwork?
Just pick the one you like.
I trust your taste.
Okay.
Then I'll pick the one where we both look beautiful,
for fairness.
I look beautiful in all of them.
Hmm...
Not gonna argue with that.
This one is cute.
You look so happy.
Of course, I do.
We're really getting married.
And our life as a couple is different from everyone else's.
It was quite a rough patch to get through.
We also have my mom to deal with.
It's like we're in a movie.
Well...
I think our life as a couple is even more dramatic than a movie plot.
But your mother plays the villain.
Hey!
But it's true.
Anyway, it's a happy ending
because the main characters got married.
After this, we'll be happy with nothing standing in our way.
Right?
Right?!
Right. That's right.
Beautiful, right?
What are you doing?
Don't you want a gift before the big day?
Why are you wearing a sexy dress?
Hey!
I'm trying to be sexy.
Why are you laughing?
I'm sorry. Can you do it again?
No, I'm not gonna.
You don't have to wear a sexy dress.
You've already won my heart.
What about you?
What were you thinking about?
Afraid of something?
No, I'm not.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
The only thing I'm afraid of...
What's that?
I'm afraid that one day you won't love me anymore.
Then you don't have to worry about it
because I'll never ever leave you.
Really?
Of course!
I'm so happy
that we're going to live together.
Me too.
Am I sexy?
Please don't try.
Hello!
Hello, ladies and gentlemen
who have gathered here to celebrate the wedding of Arisa and Lalin.
Brides, please show yourself.
Coming up, we have a special moment
for the two brides to say their vows
before the guests, family, and friends.
Lalin,
your name means the moon,
shining in the night
or when darkness consumes.
Before I met you,
my life...
was once engulfed in darkness.
But ever since we crossed paths,
there was never a glimpse of darkness again.
I promise
I will treasure this light
for as long as I shall live.
I love you, Lalin.
I want to thank you, Arisa.
I've been thankful since the day we first met.
You've changed my views on so many things and...
made me understand myself a lot more.
I wish to be with you for so long,
for eternity,
because every second I share with you
has made me so happy.
I love you, too.
You can now exchange rings.
Kiss! Kiss!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Alright, it's now the much-awaited moment,
the most romantic time of all.
Please loudly cheer for both the brides
for their first dance!
What a nice facade.
No matter what, I still don't trust that woman.
Keep an eye on her.
I will try, ma'am.
Hey!
Hey, hey!
Step back!
Are you alright? Put that down first.
Did you get splashed by the oil?
I'm okay.
You're acting like I'm a child.
So where is the maid? Why are you doing this yourself?
I asked her to do something else.
I want to show off my cooking.
I want a cute moment where I make a meal for my girlfriend to bring to work.
Dear...
You don't have to pamper me all that much.
You have my whole heart, so what else could you possibly need?
No one's a master at everything.
Jeez, it's just cooking.
Easy peasy.
The taste is beside the point, right?
Are you gonna eat it or not?
Of course, I am.
- Right, - Hm?
I've found the destination for our honeymoon.
I wanna go to Paris.
City of Love.
It just seems so romantic.
I've always wanted to go.
How about we wear matching outfits
and take some photos in front of the Eiffel Tower?
Sounds cute, doesn't it? What do you say?
Anything is great.
Whatever you like, I'll let you have it your way.
Then...
I'll catch up on work quickly.
How about we take that trip next month?
Sounds great.
But I'm not gonna let you cook anymore.
What? Why? I want you to eat my food.
How about I eat something else first?
What do you say? Hm?
Oh, give me just a second.
[Ms. Ruwajee]
Hello.
See you.
What is going on?
Why did you call everyone for a meeting?
I have no clue.
All I heard is it's important.
My apologies for such short notice about the meeting.
It's all good.
It's only once in a blue moon that you visit the company.
Should we get into it?
It's nothing major.
It's merely about the shareholders.
I trust that everyone knows
how I barely meddle with the company.
For the past 20 years, I've only been receiving dividends.
As of today,
I don't need them anymore.
I would like to transfer them to the person I trust most.
This share transfer
is in accordance with the company's policy
and has been approved by all the parties concerned.
My 29% share in this company...
I would like to pass it on
to Arisa.
[Share Transfer Agreement]
All my shares...
will be given to you.
Consider this a wedding gift
and a payback for when you gave me money to gamble.
Are you sure, Auntie,
that you'd give them to me?
I trust you with them.
Do whatever you want with them, be my guest.
I'm only asking you to take care of my niece.
Thank you.
Take good care of each other.
Thank you very much for your trust, Ms. Ruwajee.
Since the transfer has been completed,
I would like to move forward to the next session.
What session?
The review on the company's management structure,
including the CEO position.
I was never made aware of that.
What are you talking about?
It's the future of the company.
I have been rightfully granted more shares in accordance with the company's policy,
and the board of directors is well aware of it.
What are you doing, Arisa?
I ask that the board of directors
vote for or against
the dismissal of Ms. Weiling from her position as CEO.
This is proof of false accounting
committed by Ms. Weiling,
which caused the company to fall into the negative.
Hey!
Can you explain what's going on?
Why are you doing this?
You don't need to know.
Knowing your mother deserves this is enough.
Then tell me why you're doing this.
Why?
For your satisfaction?
Or what? You want to get richer?
Do you need more money or something?
You know how much my mom loves this company.
Because your mother loves it,
I have to do this.
I see.
Was all of this your plan?
You made me fall in love with you just to deceive me.
You said you wanted a future with me.
But in the end, that future is only yours. Am I right?
Tell me.
You're only with me because of my mom's company, right?
Right?!
Tell me.
Lalin...
It's...
This is between your mother and me.
It has nothing to do with you.
How can it not concern me?
I'm just a pawn in your game!
I have feelings too, you know.
But all you care about is winning.
One day, you'll understand why I did this.
I don't want to understand anything anymore.
You have no right to destroy my life like this.
Lalin...
Mom...
I'm so sorry.
I didn't think she would dare do this to you.
It's okay, baby.
Don't blame yourself.
How can I not blame myself, Mom?
I was stupid to fall for her.
It's not your fault at all.
Arisa is smart, though.
She knows all of my weaknesses,
from when she stole the Petra Project
to when she sabotaged me
during the loan application,
forcing me to share the allocation with her.
She knows everything about our company.
She intended to hurt me.
She didn't just hurt me;
she also hurt my daughter.
Why did she do all this?
It's not just about the business.
Arisa doesn't need any money.
I don't know either.
Or...
Did you ever have any problems with her in the past?
Have you ever done anything to her?
I didn't know her before.
I had someone look into her background.
There's nothing on her.
If I knew what I had done to her,
I could at least make it up to her.
But I have no idea.
Leave it to me.
I also want to know what Arisa wants.
She's no longer the person I used to know.
Hello.
Sorry to bother you,
but I need your help.
I won't say yes yet.
I'd like to hear your proposal first.
I can give you whatever you want.
I just want you to help me look into Arisa.
Why me?
I know you're a talented reporter.
And now you're looking into my mother, aren't you?
It doesn't matter, though.
I want your help
to find out who Arisa is.
I've also heard you know Ms. Aiy.
That might be one of your clues.
You want me to look into the personal life
of your new spouse?
Yes.
It's funny, isn't it?
That woman came into my life to hurt my mom.
I just want to help her.
I'm sorry to say this,
but your mother isn't really a good person either.
This kind of business...
must have left blood on her hands.
No way.
I know my mom well.
She's never killed anyone.
Before this happened,
what did you know about Arisa?
Arisa rarely told me about her family.
But I know that her parents died in an accident
around 20 years ago.
What are their names?
Thinnakorn and Saitharn.
Hello.
Where is it?
Okay, I'm going now.
Hey.
Where are you going? We're not done talking yet.
I have to go cover the news.
Oh, you should come with me too.
Why?
Your mother is in serious trouble right now.
Hey, wait for me!
You may have seen his face.
Kengkad,
a protester who used to demonstrate outside your building.
I've heard his name before.
But we don't know each other.
He is now in a coma at the hospital after the accident.
The witness testified that on the day of the accident,
your assistant
attempted to bribe him, but he refused.
So, the circumstances of the case
suggest that you
may have prior knowledge of the situation.
I want you to give a truthful statement
because your information can be verified.
As for the bribe,
my lawyers will explain that.
But I can assure you that I didn't do it.
I have never thought of killing anyone,
and I would never do anything underhanded.
Why hasn't she come down yet?
It's been an hour.
- Is that her? - That's her?
- Is that her? Yes, it's her! - Hey! Hey!
Hurry!
Let us interview you for a moment.
Could you explain everything to us?
Is it true that you offered money to the protester?
Was the money you offered related to the recent accident?
Yes, please answer the question.
Is this the same as what happened to Chet,
the protester who died 20 years ago?
- That's right. - Is there any connection?
- Won't you say anything? - Could you show us proof?
We are meeting today
- because I want to talk about… - Get to the point already?
Can I order something first?
I haven't eaten anything yet.
I'll have the Australian sirloin.
Medium rare, please.
Also, spaghetti with dried chilli,
extra spicy.
And a glass of full-bodied red wine, please.
Oh!
Here, Ms. Weiling.
She may not be in the mood to eat.
Honestly,
what do you want?
You're even blaming me for killing people.
Isn't that too much? Huh?
So, you came into Lalin's life…
do you even love her?
Or is everything you've done
just to hurt me?
So you think you're the only one who's been hurt?
Don't you think
you must have hurt someone for things to turn out this badly for you?
I'm not like you,
someone who sacrifices other people's lives to get what they want!
What are you talking about?!
What have I done to you?
Just be straight with me.
If I knew what I did, I could at least make up for it somehow.
Was your subconscious mind broken for a long time or something?
So you've forgotten the bad things you've done.
I guess I need to remind you.
You'll soon realize what you've done.
What you are facing right now
is what you must pay for.
How is it going? Have you been lonely?
It must be lonely always being here in the stall, huh?
I'll take you for a walk today.
But after this...
I won't be visiting as often.
Don't miss me.
Mom.
Why are you still awake? What are you up to?
Just looking through old photos.
I was so young.
I looked so goofy, Mom.
You were adorable.
This was the first time I traveled overseas, wasn't it?
Yes, in Italy.
Speaking of which, I kinda miss Dad.
Who is this person?
She was my best friend in the entire world.
But I haven't seen her in such a long time.
I have no idea how she's been.
I really want to meet her one more time.
What's her name?
She's Saitharn.
Saitharn...
[Mrs. Saitharn Navakul]
Why would you want to meet her again?
Hasn't she already passed away?
What did you find out?
A body was found, identified as Thinnakorn Navakul,
a world-class programmer
in a vacation home. ['Saitharn' might be fatally burned to ashes]
Only his body was found on the scene.
His wife, 'Saitharn Navakul,'
was presumed to be burned to ashes.
But Mom insisted that Auntie Saitharn was still alive.
This is the photo of Mom and Auntie Saitharn
when they were friends.
This news was kept in the archive.
Not a lot of people pay attention to it anymore.
Your mom and Arisa's mom were the closest of friends,
but Saitharn's death...
wasn't real?
Does Arisa even know
that her own mom is still alive?
If Saitharn is genuinely still alive,
we need to find her
before Arisa can get to your mom.
Exactly.
She is the one who knows all of this.
I'll leave you to it.
Are you sure she's still alive?
I am.
No matter what, the quicker we find her, the better.
But this case is 20 years old.
Hello there,
Ms. Keetraphat.
Is there anything you want to tell me, Kee?
I'm asking you, "Is there anything you want to tell me?"
Is there anything you want to tell me?!
Nothing.
In the end,
you're still refusing to tell me the truth, huh?
But it's fine.
I already know everything.
Your plan to destroy my mom is already a success, isn't it?
Congrats.
That would include hurting me in the process.
It must be another gain, right?
I understand how excruciating it must have been.
But I get to be angry, don't I?
You used me
as a bridge to ruin everything in my life!
Do whatever you please.
I hope you're happy getting your revenge.
Oh,
there's one more thing you should know.
Are you completely sure that your mom has really died?
Hello,
I am Arisa Kulnavee,
representing W Empire.
I would like to inform the press
and the public
that the company is not involved
in causing severe injury to the protester
in the past accident.
Is this going to have an internal impact on the company?
I am getting there.
As a result of an internal investigation,
we have found concealment of information
which affects the company's image and credibility.
Therefore, all the board members
decided that Ms. Weiling
be dismissed from her position as the president of the company,
effective immediately.
There is evidence
that connects to someone from her inner circle.
Right now, a charge for attempted murder is being filed under legal proceedings,
which might trace back to the death
of Mr. Thinnakorn Navakul
and Mrs. Saitharn Navakul,
20 years ago.
Should the truth be revealed in line with the evidence,
she will immediately be charged
with murder.
That information is false.
I am still alive.
Mom...
How did you leave me stuck with vengeance?
How could you to that to me?
How ?
I'm ready for the truth.
Weiling and I have been friends since university.
I've been waiting for an explanation for 20 years.
It would mean nothing if I apologized now.
Why haven't you told me that Mom's still alive?
Why would you do this?
Weiling and Saitharn were having an affair!
I'm begging you
to please get out of my life.
You're amazing for getting through everything, Arisa.
But there's one more thing
that I have to get through.