Hey, Nedumaran.
- Leo?
Yes.
- Hey, how are you?
I am doing great. How are you?
- I am fine, as usual.
Wonderful! It's been a long time
since we met. - Yes.
Where did Chika go?
Chika?
I don't know
who you're talking about.
Chika, Nedumaran.
You were friends, right?
Did you forget?
- Hey.
I don't remember anyone like that.
How would I forget then?
You really don't remember Chika?
Hey, I don't know.
- Chidambaram, Nedumaran.
Did you forget him?
The TV remote is not working.
That's why I asked you to come.
Check it.
- Okay, sir.
Chef, did you finish
the ice washing?
Then, for Riya..
Why do you look sad, Chef?
Oh, what is this?
A test for the chef?
You are not going to go anyway.
Then, why are you looking at it?
Chef?
What are you waiting for?
Inform them right away
that you are not coming.
Okay, Chef.
I came to see if the food is ready.
Is it ready?
Follow up with Grace.
Do only what you like, singer Aura.
Riya, stop.
I said stop..
Why are you behaving like this?
Please don't ask me anything.
Just leave me alone.
I don't understand.
Everyone will obviously know
you are pregnant. Then what?
Yes, Deepak, but I have to decide
where and when to say it.
You have to decide it?
What do you mean by 'you'?
Excuse me, we are pregnant.
Don't you understand that?
That is what I am saying, Deepak.
We. If you say 'we', you should
have asked me before deciding.
Riya, it's not a big deal for you
to react like this, okay?
Of course, Deepak.
Whatever you do is never
wrong, isn't it?
I can't do this.
Look here.
I am already under work pressure.
Don't irritate me. Just shut up.
What? Shut up?
Why don't you shut up?
Mind your words, Riya.
What do you think
of yourself, Deepak?
If I repeat what you just said,
you ask me to mind my words?
What the hell?
- Look here, Riya.
Don't act. Before my alter ego
gets triggered, just shut up.
Or else, I will do
something uncontrollable.
Oh, you are threatening me now?
It's not right for you to speak
this way, knowing my anger.
Rajan, ask him
to get out of my resort.
Riya, one minute, please.
Sir..
- What the fuck?
Sir. Just a minute.
- Wait.
Who the hell are you?
Go away.
He is the manager of this resort.
Rajan, throw him out.
Riya, calm down.
We are talking, right?
Sir.
- Hey, who are you first?
Just mind your business.
Get him away right now!
- You're going overboard.
Deepak, it's not just you.
I would have done the same
if it was someone else.
You told me to mind my business,
right? This is my business.
Now just get out.
Tell me, Mom.
- Vetri, are you busy? - Yes.
What is the matter?
That is..
Selvi said she was going
to play, right? - Yes.
Do you need money for that?
- No, Vetri.
You know about our village, right?
When Selvi plays,
she would wear trousers
and shorts and play without a care.
After seeing all that,
I don't know how our
villagers will talk. I feel bad.
Our reputation in the village
is already bad.
I don't have the strength
to bear their words.
Mom, what is this? Why are
you thinking so much for her?
We know about my daughter.
But, others will talk
about her by her dress.
How can they judge
a girl just by her clothes?
What are you saying?
Let them talk whatever they want.
Selvi will play, that's it.
Hey, not for that.
What I am saying is.. - Mom, look.
If we keep thinking about others,
we will lose our peace.
We don't live for others.
Our life, our peace. That's enough.
Whatever.
I don't think this is right.
It's because of you
that I'm letting her play.
I can't handle your stubbornness.
Selvi has to play. Don't think
about anything else, that's it.
Okay, you carry on. I will hang up.
- Okay, Mom.
Sir.. Sorry, sir.
I was on the phone and didn't
notice you. Sorry, Sir. - It's okay.
But, what you said is right.
What did I say, Sir?
If we take a decision
thinking about others,
you said that it is wrong.
You're right.
Did you hear that?
That's right, Sir.
Correct. But, to understand this..
I don't understand why
it took so long for me.
I don't know if I can speak as much
as you can understand, sir, but..
That's all I can understand, Sir.
Sir, no need.
- Come, get it. - Sir.
I am not giving it for free.
- No, Sir..
I am giving it
for your work Take it.
Thank you, Sir.
Hey, the cream hasn't boiled yet.
Why are you pouring it so soon?
- Hey.
I don't know what'll happen if they
find out I'm doing this for you.
And yet you fault me.
Shut up and keep quiet.
Okay, don't get angry.
There is chocolate, right?
Melt it and put it inside.
Why should I melt it?
If you put it in, it will melt
- Hey, fool.
Hey, I found
a new recipe and told you.
Why are you messing it up?
I am the chef today, I will cook
the way I want to. Just shut up.
You shouldn't speak.
You should keep quiet.
I'm helping you
and you're going overboard.
You're advising the chef.
- Look there.
What?
- Look behind you.
Why are you here today?
Oh, no..
Aishu, I don't know anything.
He asked me for help.
Superb.
Get lost,
or I'll report you myself.
Why are you talking like this?
Come closer.
Just a minute.
- Aishu.
I don't know anything.
Please come.
Aishu, I don't know anything. Don't
tell this to Nedumaran. - Please.
What?
You know Mr. Joji, right?
He asked me to make
a special dish for his lover.
Don't snitch on me.
I also tried to make it.
But, you will create problems
if I come inside.
That's why I thought of this idea.
I can't do all that.
First, get out of here.
Don't say like. He is a poor guy.
- Poor guy?
There's no one there for him.
He just met the woman
whom he loved back in college.
He has been alone for so many days.
Now, his life is filled
with happiness.
That's why I am trying
to do something for him.
It's okay if I don't do
it with my own hands.
I don't mind if someone
else does it on my behalf.
What?
What is there to think about?
He is our Joji.
Listen to me, don't do it.
If you get caught, it's over.
Look, if he does it,
it'll definitely be a mess.
Oh, no, he's pointing at me.
If you don't mind,
will you do it for me?
- Oh.
Were you plotting this for me?
- No.
Not plotting.
It's just a help.
If you do it for me,
you will feel blessed.
Okay, I will do it.
Don't do it so reluctantly.
Then, it won't taste good.
When you do it,
do it with love.
I will do it with love,
like you asked.
Tell me.
- Hey, nerd.
Come out.
- Go, sir.
Dump this, bring it.
I don't know what he said.
- Just loaf around.
Lighter.
Chef, haven't you started
the preparation? - No.
I'm making a dessert, Chef.
Do it fast. Time's running out.
Where is the lighter?
- Order, sir.
What dish is this?
This is the flavour of a dish
that is not on our menu.
That's right, Chef, yes.
This is a new dish.
I wanted to ask you
and add it to the menu. - Oh.
Oh, okay.
Wow!
Extraordinary.
It just makes
the taste buds come alive.
Quite a surprise.
Extraordinary, huh.
What is the name
of this dish, Chef?
I haven't named it yet, Chef.
- Oh.
Can I?
- Sure, Chef.
You put it in the serving cup.
Maybe you can sprinkle some
chocolate powder
and you can name it
as 'Dark Choco Kheer'.
How is it?
- Nice, Chef. - Thank you.
You did great. Keep it up.
Aishu, we would've been
doomed if we'd been caught.
Oh, God!
What did he name it?
- 'Dark Choco Kheer.'
'Dark Choco Kheer.'
It's good.
- Get lost from here.
Okay, you bring it. Bye.
Sir, we made it
despite many challenges.
Please tell us how it is.
My feedback is not important.
Let Padma come and say it.
Don't I know how
Vetri's cooking is?
Sir, I didn't cook this time.
A great chef has cooked this.
- Who is that great chef?
This guy.
- Hey.
This chef. Chef Aishu.
Then, you don't have to say it.
It will definitely be good.
Hi, ma'am.
Sir, you carry on. We will
be back. Thank you, ma'am.
Thank you.
What is this?
Try it. You will like it.
- You also eat.
Wow! It's delicious.
I asked them to prepare it
specially for you.
It's very tasty.
It's really good, Joji. Thank you.
My pleasure.
Padma.
Even back in our college days,
you used to follow the same
dressing style, right? - Oh.
Do you remember all that?
They say that you forget
everything when you grow old.
Who has grown old?
I am still a youth.
Forever young.
Eat.
- Padma.
Can I ask you something?
Why don't we
go on a date tomorrow?
What?
Padma, I just asked.
- What did you just ask?
Don't you know what to ask, Joji?
You got scared?
You will tell the truth only if
you are scared, right? - Then?
Why wouldn't I be scared?
Don't I know about you?
Oh, in a short while, I felt
as if I saw the old Padma.
Even I feel like seeing him.
- The old Joji?
Yes.
I am 60 years old. I am old Joji.
I'm not new.
Oh, no, Joji.
I have to go now, okay?
I will wait for you tomorrow
morning. Don't forget. - Okay, bye.
Sir, what is the result?
Will Joji ever fail the exam?
But, you got scared that it will
fail for a second there, right?
Okay, leave it.
She got used to scaring me
and I got used to getting scared.
Sir, what is this?
You could have told her
what you feel now, right?
Like you said,
even if I had spoken up then..
even if all this
had happened before..
even if I had spoken
in front of her,
my life would have changed.
Time waits for no one.
If you don't speak up
where you should speak,
it will become
a longing eventually.
You should never let that happen.
Hey, why is he drinking like this?
He advises us when we drink a lot.
After all, a manager
asked me to get out.
He thinks he is the owner.
For those thoughts,
she is the reason.
She is the one.
In my life, no one has
ever told me to get out.
But, today, right to my face..
Shit.
Hey, Deepak, leave it.
I never thought you'd
drink like that and blabber.
Yes..
He made me lament.
In front of my wife,
he insulted me.
I just..
It sounds crazy.
I have never felt.. I have
never been ashamed like this.
Leave it, don't feel bad.
He will regret what he did.
He won't regret it.
But, I will make him regret it.
He thinks I am an ordinary person.
His name is..
Rajan..
You have touched the wrong person.
I will show you what
I am capable of. Just wait.
Just wait.
Hey..
- Hey, what is this?
Hey, Deepak.
Dad.
- Come in, dear.
- Tell me, dear.
Tell me, Aishu.
It's nothing. Go and eat, Dad.
No, dear.
I think I will skip it today.
I don't want dinner today.
Why? What happened, Dad?
I don't want it..
I will just skip it today.
Dad, I want to tell you something.
Actually, I wanted to tell you
something. Sorry for interrupting.
Come and sit.
You know..
Today, you cooked very well.
I think this is the first time I am
saying this to you. Am I right?
You have given me
a lot of confidence today.
The dish that you cooked..
It was more than I expected.
It was just
out of the world. It was awesome.
It was awesome.
I am telling you honestly.
Do you know one thing?
Even when I won the Master Chef
award, I never felt so happy.
You are the reason I am
so, so happy today. Yes.
My dear Aishu.
You are ready
for the Master Chef competition.
Yes.
Your sister betrayed me.
She disappointed me.
Since you are with me,
I don't have to worry about
your sister or your future.
I don't know.
I thought many times
that I've raised you strictly.
I told you not to do this and that.
But, you gave me the answer.
I feared I'd be humiliated
in front of everyone.
But, you cooked a dish and made me
so proud in front of everyone.
I am so proud of you.
Thank you.
You wanted
to tell me something, right?
Nothing, Dad.
- Are you sure?
Okay, dear, I will finish
another drink and sleep.
I will sleep happily today.
With my heart full.
Yes.
Time to sleep.
Good night, dear.
Great night, Dad.