I guess I realized it too late, didn't I?
No.
Even if you had realized it sooner,
my answer would've been the same.
It has to be him.
So that means I just have to wait until I finish
the race, and then you'll agree to be my boyfriend.
He's in.
He won!
Thit!
- Arthit!
- I can't lose you. I really can't lose you.
I've had someone look into it.
It was that side's doing.
They were probably scared
of losing a lot of money.
Should I handle it?
No need for you to step in.
I won't let them get away with this.
Good thing Arthit's tough as hell.
After all that, it's nothing too serious.
He'll wake up soon and come
collect that promise from Daotok.
It's fine.
North.
What if he doesn't wake up, North?
Don't think like that.
P'Arthit's tough as nails.
He said.
I should wait for him to win,
and then he'd ask me to be his boyfriend.
And I'm waiting right here.
Calm down.
Why?
I've never seen you cry.
You're gonna make me cry too.
North.
P'Thit's been waiting
forever for you to accept him.
With that determination,
he's not dying that easily.
But if something does happen,
I'll find you someone better.
Ouch.
I just don't want you to stress out.
Damn it, North.
- Hey! Shit! P'Arthit's awake!
- North.
P'Thit.
P'Jo, Uncle Direk.
Uh, doctor!
Wait, I'll go get them.
I missed you.
Thit, you idiot. You dumb buffalo.
Why don't you take care of yourself.
I'm awake now, Direk.
No comforting words? No “there, there”?
Come here and I'll kick you instead.
You almost gave your father a heart attack.
I'm awake now. Calm down.
Guess there's nothing to worry about then.
What a shame.
Hey, North. Am I not your brother? Huh?
Jo.
Shit.
Guess I can't go on ward duty then.
Damn, that sucks.
- Then have Fah submit my leave for me.
- Fine.
If there's nothing else, we'll head out.
Looks like you've got
something to talk about.
Jo, my friend. You're a real one.
Ow.
Jo, you asshole.
Uncle.
Goodbye, Uncle.
See you.
What's with him acting all cute?
Hey.
Aren't you going home?
Can't I stay and witness this?
Oh please.
Direk, he won't say
anything because you're here.
Mm.
Fine, I'll go.
I'll come back tomorrow for your check-up.
What check-up? No need.
I'm going home tomorrow.
Go home my ass. You have
to stay two or three more nights.
Direk, you know I hate
staying in the hospital.
Just lie down and stop complaining.
The doctor needs to run a few more tests.
- Got it?
- Forget about it, I'm fine.
Please tay here a bit longer.
Okay.
You're so obedient like a puppy.
But with me, you're stubborn as hell.
Tch.
Well then,
I'll leave him in your care, Daotok.
I need to handle something.
And behave yourself.
It hurts.
- Here.
- Drink some water.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Come here.
Let's talk.
What's wrong?
Why won't you say anything?
Are you mad?
Hmm?
I couldn't do anything at all.
Maybe it's because I've never
been in a situation like this before.
But I was scared.
I was really scared.
I'm not someone who cries easily.
But I still cried.
I've never felt this weak before.
And it's all because of you.
You came out of nowhere,
and walked into my life.
You came to like me,
to care about me,
to look after me,
and then made me worry
about you like I was going crazy.
I'm sorry.
I didn't say that so you'd apologize.
Then what do you want me to do?
Take responsibility.
Responsibility for what?
Be...
Be what?
Don't tease me.
You haven't even asked yet.
I can be anything.
Whatever you want me to be,
I can be all of it.
I mean it.
Go on, ask me.
Anything at all?
Anything.
Be the blue-haired kid next door?
I will.
Be a low-battery robot?
Be someone who stays by my side,
and never leaves,
no matter what happens?
I will.
Be the one who loves me the most?
Then...
Be my boyfriend.
I will.
Let me be that person.
Please.
Arthit.
Hmm?
Why don't you call me P'?
Hey.
Don't tell me
you don't respect me anymore.
I don't call my boyfriend “P'.”
Shit.
We should get the
hell out of this hospital.
Staying here is pointless now.
Wanna leave right now?
Go to sleep.
Then sleep with me.
No.
This is a patient's bed.
So what?
Be a good boy.
Get plenty of rest,
so you'll recover quickly.
Mm.
Goodnight kiss.
I love you more than
anything in this world.
I love you too, Arthit.
You're the best.
You asshole.
I'm trying to sleep.
You wanna die a second time or what?
This idiot.
Wake up.
Why are you sleeping here?
Shit, a ghost scared me last night.
Really?
Yeah.
It was terrifying.
So I came to sleep with you here.
But you're not afraid of ghosts.
Oh?
Good morning, my boyfriend.
Hey, Hill!
Wait— Ow, damn it, Hill!
- Yeah.
- Ouch, you jerk.
You'll be fine.
Thanks, maew.
For taking care of K'John.
No problem at all.
Is he asleep or dead?
Rest in peace, my friend.
Shit, North, help me out!
I am helping.
Get in, get in!
- Yeah.
- Stunned! Stunned!
Come on, push it in!
Jo, you asshole—that's my get-well gift!
- So you can't even split this with me or what?
- I can.
But you have to feed me too.
Hurry up.
Ouch.
That's enough.
Can I talk to you for a second?
You're already dead.
You can't be hogging the bed like this.
The people lying here
were sick before too.
Why create more bad karma?
I'll make merit for you.
But you have to promise
not to haunt anyone again.
Hey.
Hmm?
Are you going to drive?
Yeah.
Then the patient should just sit still.
Want to go somewhere?
Mm.
I want to go back to my room.
Do you know
how long I've been waiting for this moment?
I also want to see how
prepared you really are.
Just relax.
No need to tense up.
I love you so much.
How are you?
Why are you avoiding me?
Was last night okay?
If I say it wasn't okay?
I'll practice more.
It was good.
Really good, you know?
The best in my life.
And it'll stay this good
for the rest of our lives.
Sweet talker.
Of course I'm sweet.
Want a taste?
Emma, look.
Our son's boyfriend
draws just as well as you.
I'm so proud.
Drawing this beautifully—I
guess you deserve a reward.
- Ouch.
- Don't try to be slick.
So now that you've got a boyfriend,
you're not into anyone else?
Of course, Direk.
If I'm doing anyone, it's my boyfriend.
Ouch.
That hurts.
What's up, Fah?
I've been discharged, but I still hurt.
Can I extend my leave?
My wound can't be seen
from the outside, Fah.
But honestly, I'm in really
bad shape, you get me?
Yeah.
If he doesn't like it, I don't know
why he'd put himself through that.
I've told him so many
times, he just won't listen.
Even before the medical exam.
I said "If you don't like
something, don't force it."
"You're only hurting yourself."
But he said he wants to study medicine.
Because of his mom, right?
Yeah.
He promised Emma when she was sick
that he'd become a doctor to treat her.
But I don't see why that's necessary.
Emma herself probably wouldn't
want him enduring something he hates.
That's true.
If it were you saying it,
maybe he'd listen.
Yeah, help me take leave.
I'll give it a try.
The professor will
probably dismiss us late.
No need to pick me up.
I'll go back with North.
Tell that North I'll slash his tires.
I'm serious. Don't come pick me up.
Or I'll be mad.
Alright.
Good job.
How much for the cigarettes?
A hundred each.
Put it on my tab. The cash is in my room.
Did you write it yourself?
Yeah.
Actually,
I started it a while ago.
But I just finished it.
The song is really good.
You're so talented.
You think so?
You're not just flattering me, right?
Why would I? It really is good.
Mm.
Can I see it?
Sure.
Honestly,
I thought I was just writing
it for fun like the other times.
But when I thought of your face,
I suddenly wanted to take it seriously.
So this song is...
Written for you.
Thank you.
I'm really happy.
You've taken another
step toward your dream.
Then I deserve a kiss
on the cheek as a reward.
That has nothing to do with it.
Just a little.
Are you going to release
it for others to listen?
I don't know.
If I really do it,
I'll need to arrange it better.
And improve the music.
Then record it in a studio.
Mm.
I want Arthit to release it.
I don't want to keep it to myself.
Mm.
Then once I finish it,
I'll let you listen it first.
Okay?
I'll wait.
Mm.
You're quite a spendthrift.
If I earn money, I've got to spend it.
Why save it?
And if one day your savings run out,
what will you do?
That just means I'm not rich enough yet.
Look at my best friend Jo.
He's so rich that his savings
are just the money he hasn't spent.
You're unbelievable, Arthit.
I really love it when you say my name.
Arthit.
Hmm?
Oh.
So, you told your family about us, right?
I did.
What did they say?
Papa and Dad were a little shocked.
Grandma invited us over for dinner.
So, shall we go?
Won't Arthit feel uncomfortable?
Hmm?
Me?
Uncomfortable?
Mm.
Just watch me win your family over.
You'll see.
Then I'll take you there.
Hey.
How did your Papa and Dad meet?
Papa was Dad's love at first sight.
They met at a café in London.
Love at first sight?
Mm.
But.
I guess ours wasn't love at first sight.
It took me quite a while
to start liking you.
I can't even imagine what it'd be like
if you hadn't moved next door.
We would've met some other way anyway.
Hmm?
Why?
I went to see a fortune teller.
Seriously?
Mm.
We're soulmates.
Mm...
So that means
no matter what happens,
we're meant to be together, right?
Mm.
Is that from the fortune teller too?
No, that's from my heart.
Damn.
Keep your eyes on the road.
Drive carefully.
I just want to get home quickly.
Let's go.
Papa, Dad.
Come here. I missed you.
- We missed you. Welcome home.
- I missed you too.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
We haven't seen each other for a bit
why have you put on so much weight, K'John?
That's the one who's been feeding him.
Seems like he's feeding my kid too?
Your cheeks are so chubby!
Ok, let's go inside. Granny's waiting.
Let's go inside.
Let's go.
Excuse me for a moment.
Oh?
Where's my grandson?
Khun Phuangthong.
How are you, my grandson?
I'm so happy to see you.
I've missed you so much, Khun Phuangthong.
I've missed you too.
Oh.
Ah.
Come sit down.
Yes, ma'am.
So handsome.
Both son and grandson.
You really know how to find a
son-in-law and a grandson-in-law I like.
I'll go help Papa in the kitchen first.
Alright, alright.
Go ahead and talk.
Okay.
What's your name?
My name is Arthit.
Hmm, that's a lovely name.
And what's your name?
Phuangthong.
Hmm, that's a lovely name.
This young man…
Not bad at all.
Here, let me help.
It's okay.
Grandma seems to like him.
They seem to get along well.
Seems like it.
Aren't Papa and Dad going to work today?
No.
We knew you were coming.
I took leave in advance.
Oh.
Papa.
Are you okay with this?
I am.
I respect your decision.
But.
I don't know him well enough yet.
So let me keep an eye on him first.
Sure.
My grandson…
He's been a quiet
child since he was little.
Back in kindergarten, the teacher
wrote that he wasn't cheerful.
Not very sociable.
Mm.
They even called in his guardian,
worried there might be family problems.
Even now, he doesn't talk much.
Back then, whenever I asked him something…
He'd just reply...
Mm.
Mm-hmm.
Honestly, we could barely have
a proper conversation, Grandma.
Ma'am.
No need to be formal.
Just speak the way you normally do.
- Like how I usually talk…
- Mm.
Can you handle that?
I can.
Just don't speak English like Gavin.
I can't understand a word.
At first, when Phai
was introduced to me, I was so stressed.
- Mm.
- It's not that I didn't like him.
But he kept saying things I didn't
understand. What if he was badmouthing me?
- Oh.
- Even now,
It's still so hard to talk to him.
All I can say is “Hey, hey, come on.”
So how did you end up liking my grandson?
I'm not sure.
After spending some time together,
I just started liking Dao for being Dao.
I can't really explain it.
I see.
What about at university?
Does he have friends?
He does.
They seem pretty close.
They're all nice guys.
Although…
Some of them can be a bit cheeky.
Why? Were you worried
Dao wouldn't have friends?
Of course I was.
I don't know why, but…
Daotok...
He always seems to attract bad people.
Oh.
But hearing this,
I feel relieved.
With you taking care of him,
I'm not worried anymore.
I won't say I'm a good person, but
when it comes to taking care of Daotok.
I promise I'll do my very best.
I promise.
The room's a bit small.
Can you sleep here?
Small?
I've slept in tighter spaces than this.
Hey.
Are you being clingy with me?
We haven't hugged today yet.
What's gotten into you, huh?
Well.
I kinda want a hug.
Dad's here.
Wanna go play soccer?
Sure.
Let's go.
Go. Move you legs.
Okay, okay, spread out!
Nice one!
Okay.
Goal!
Not bad.
No wonder you're the captain
of the Med School football team.
You're good too.
But you are not on my level yet.
Damn, I really like this guy.
But there's no way I'm
losing in front of Phai.
Me too.
I can't lose in front of Dao.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
The food is really good tonight.
- Yeah.
- I'm so full.
This is really good whiskey.
Uh...
Can I join?
What's up? Can't sleep?
Uh.
I just...
Oh, never mind. Make yourself at home.
Oh.
So...
You...
You can just call me like Daotok.
Oh.
Yes, Papa.
Hey, no need to be so formal.
Okay.
Oh, thank you.
Cheers.
Hey, I don't doubt you and Daotok.
I'm just a little worried.
He's my only son.
I want him to meet
someone who truly loves him.
And that person is you.
Thank you so much.
I haven't seen him this
happy in a long time.
No need to thank me.
As long as Dao is happy,
I'm damn happy too.
Phai, that's enough.
Dylan.
Hmm?
If you make my son cry,
I'll kill you.
You got it?
Yes.
Gawin.
You have to deal with him
if he hurts Dao.
I got it.
Kid.
Hmm?
If you ever hurt my son even a little,
I won't let you off.
If I ever hurt Dao,
you can kill me.
That's a promise.
On my life.
Cheers.
You smell like alcohol.
I don't.
- Why are you arguing with me?
- What's that?
Is it that funny?
It kind of is.
But it's cute.
You're the only one
who says I'm cute.
Well, you're cute only with me.
Mm.
Don't worry. Papa will
take good care of K'John.
Or should I take K'John
to San Fran with me?
No way.
I'll keep K'John here so you two
will come back to visit us often.
Exactly.
Dad.
- Take care of yourself, son.
- Thank you. See you.
Grandma.
Please take good care of yourself.
You too.
- Young man, take good care of my grandson.
- Of course, Grandma.
I'll take the best care of him.
Don't worry.
We're heading out now. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
- Drive safe.
- Yes.
- Have a safe trip.
Hey.
Is this your completed track?
Mm.
How is it?
It's nice.
It's really nice.
Hey!
But I haven't named the song yet.
Help me think of one.
I like the part...
That one.
On My Shoulder.
Hey!
Alright, I'll use that.
You can't just go with my idea.
- Athit made it.
- Hey.
I made it for you.
Thank you.
So...
If you like it,
I'll post it then.
Make sure you tell all
your friends to share it.
Holy shit, this is crazy.
No way, I'm gonna be famous.
Fah. Jo. Hill.
Holy shit!
It's over a hundred thousand already!
P' Thit is insane.
Can I see?
Here, look.
Hey, but Dao looks
really cute in the video.
P' Athit is pretty talented too.
He compliments himself like that every day.
Seriously, he leaves no room
for anyone else to praise him.
But honestly, the song is really good.
Honestly, at first glance,
P' Athit does look kinda cool.
- But don't get to know the real him.
- Why?
Because he's an asshole.
You jerk.
Hey, have your boyfriends replied yet?
Not yet.
P' Jo hasn't either.
Having boyfriends who
are friends is kinda nice.
When they're busy, they disappear together.
Exactly. That's why we
hang out here so often.
True. No one's as free as us.
We're freaking awesome.
Alright then.
Let's close the book and
play a game instead. Come on.
Whoa, North, what does
that have to do with anything?
You're seriously pointless all day long.
Hey.
What are you doing? I miss you.
Arthit.
Yeah?
I just found out you make
really beautiful music.
Thank you.
Is the person in the
picture your boyfriend?
Yes.
Is he cute?
Of course he is. Are you
showing him off on purpose?
Yeah, I am.
I totally am.
Oh my, I'd better get his autograph
now before he gets even more famous.
I'm heading off.
See you.
So damn smug.
Your boyfriend isn't as cute as mine.
He's only cute for me, and that's enough.
Hey, hold on.
Have you guys shared my song yet?
Of course we did.
Well...
It's pretty good.
I don't know. I don't really listen to music.
But I heard North playing it all day.
He can probably sing along by now.
North is the cutest, seriously.
Jo.
Your boyfriend has great taste.
Hey Hill, has Ter listened to it yet?
What about you? Has Phoon listened?
He has.
Wake up.
Mm?
Mm.
You'll be late for rounds.
Arthit.
Mm?
Are you tired?
Why?
Your dad and I once talked about
wanting you to do what you truly love
and live your life happily.
Why?
Why are you being so
serious all of a sudden?
Mm.
I don't want to interfere
with your decision,
but
can I share my opinion?
Mm.
I know that Arthit…
Is someone capable.
Whatever you set your mind to,
it always turns out well.
Even something difficult
like studying medicine.
But…
You're not happy with it at all, are you?
The only thing holding you back right now is
the promise to become a doctor for your mom.
I understand.
Your mom is someone important in your life.
But if she were still here,
would she really want
you to live like this?
I'm saying this
because when I see
you doing what you love
whether it's playing music
or making songs.
I see your eyes light up.
You're really happy doing it, aren't you?
Didn't your dad once say
that if you wanted to make music,
he'd even open a music label for you?
See?
There are so many
people ready to support you.
Mm.
Actually
I've been thinking
about quitting for a while.
I don't know…
Maybe before,
I never really thought about my future.
Whatever happened, happened.
But I'm not like that anymore.
My future…
It's not just about me anymore.
So.
I'll try to live more seriously from now on.
Whatever you decide to do,
whichever path you choose,
I'll be right here.
Hill said you were on sick leave. I thought
you were dying in your room or something.
But you look totally fine.
You're not even sick.
Why'd you take leave then?
Where's North?
Morning class.
You go first.
You know, right,
that I already have a job.
But I studied medicine because
Jean wanted me to.
Though she probably didn't
expect much from me anyway.
Damn, Jo, look.
I've got goosebumps, man.
We're thinking the exact same thing.
You too?
Yeah.
Damn.
Now that we're at this point,
I'm starting to feel like this isn't it.
And this is such a big turning point.
I really need to think it through.
But overthinking isn't really my thing.
So…
Why are you still studying here?
I made a promise to my mom
when I was a kid.
But thinking about it now, Jo,
I don't think she'd want me
to force myself like this.
She'd probably rather see me happy.
So what now?
Should we just quit?
What about Fah and Hill?
Are we just leaving them?
But if we quit, they
might actually be happier.
They won't have to work for us anymore.
They'll be free.
You've got a point.
But I bet they'd still feel a little sad.
I'm free now!
Wait, you quit already?
Huh?
Seriously?
Yeah.
Jo and I just submitted our
resignation a moment ago.
So you guys have really decided, huh?
Mm.
Okay.
Then good luck with the path you've chosen.
Damn, why do you sound so bitter?
You're gonna be lonely without me, huh?
How did you know?
So now Hill and I are
gonna have it way too easy?
Exactly. We can finally
get rid of freeloaders.
Hey!
We did all the work for you
attended classes for you, took notes
for you, took exams on your behalf even.
Damn!
Can you at least pretend to look sad?
Don't look like you've just
been set free or something.
We really do feel that way.
Hey, Thit.
Go home.
What the hell? Why are you kicking me out?
You're annoying.
Hill, turn around and look at this.
- I can do it one-handed, you know.
- I don't want to see.
Jo.
You up for it?
You and me. One-on-one.
Nah.
I'll even give you a one-hand handicap.
Jo, don't be stupid and go along with him.
I already have a headache as it is.
Pathetic.
- Bring it, Thit. No need for the one-hand thing.
- Then come on.
Come on.
I'm ready. Let's go.
Your playlist's pretty good.
You like this artist?
I love him.
But I heard he already has a boyfriend.
And he's very much in love.
Then try not to love him.
Hi, Mom. I brought you someone.
This is my boyfriend.
Daotok.
You might be shocked like Direk.
I can see your face now.
You always said
to choose what I love.
So, I did.
I'm happy now.
Just…
Wish you were here.
I miss you.
Mom.
So much.
Can I talk to your mom?
Mm.
Hello, Mom.
I came here to see you a few month ago.
He seem tough,
and stubborn, I guess.
But
he's so honest
and kind.
Especially he has a good heart.
So.
This is the reason why I love him.
No matter what's happen
from now on,
I promise.
I'll be by his side.
And don't worry about him.
And take a rest.
Direk…
Do you think mom would be proud of me?
I really want to know.
But she's not here for me to ask anymore.
If you want my answer,
from over ten years of
being Emma's husband,
I'm sure she's proud of you.
So am I.
You're proud of me?
From the day you were born until today,
there hasn't been a single
day I wasn't proud of you.
I want you to know that
you're the only thing
that's kept me alive all these years.
Damn, I'm gonna cry, Direk.
Thit.
Anything you want,
I'll get it for you.
If you want to make music,
I'll build you a studio.
If you want to be a singer,
I'll set up a label for you.
I'm telling you
there's nothing in this
world I wouldn't give you.
So this is…
A father's love.
Hey! My shirt!
What the hell, Direk?
You said you'd give me anything.
And you're stingy over one shirt?
Have I ever told you I love you?
Don't know.
But hey, you don't have to...
Direk, I love you.
- I said you don't have to—
- Dad, I love you.
- You idiot.
- Dad.
Did you tease Direk or something?
He walked off muttering to himself.
Nope.
What are you thinking about?
Just thinking.
I'm lucky I met you.
Arthit's lucky to have
met so many good people.
Yeah.
Especially Direk, who
raised me all these years.
He's been my father,
and my friend.
No matter what I am,
he's always loved me.
And those guys too.
Fah, Hill, Jo.
They may fight like that,
but they've never left my side.
They're always there to help me,
always supporting me.
Including the day I met you.
That was the luckiest thing in my life.
You fit me perfectly in every way.
As long as you're by my side,
I can do anything in this world,
no matter how hard it is.
Just hold your hand,
and I'll get through it.
I feel the same.
I feel like I can do anything,
and do it well.
I can go anywhere,
as long as you're with me.
No, it's me
who's lucky.
No, I am.
Then we're both lucky.
I'm lucky to have you.
You
are lucky to have me.
We're both lucky.
I love you.
More than anything in the world.
I love you too.