ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
Forget it. I'm not waiting any longer.
That's it if he's not coming.
Liar.
He won't help,
just the same as Sang Yan.
Liar.
Sang Zhi?
Get up.
Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
Why aren't you speaking?
No one comes so late.
When should I have come?
My class ended at 4:20 p.m.
It's way past that time.
I didn't know.
Then
I apologize to you.
Later,
I'll take the reprimand in your place.
-All right? -No need.
Let's go.
Will he show up today as well?
Hello, Jiaxu.
Are you awake?
If you're late by too much,
you shall
never find a girlfriend.
Do you…
I got here long ago.
I went to buy milk for you.
You ingrate.
You can't say stuff like that.
If I never find a girlfriend,
you will be dead meat.
Let's go.
Do your homework at the breakfast shop up ahead.
Come on.
Your essay booklet.
ESSAY BOOKLET
Start writing.
I don't think he read it.
Have you eaten breakfast?
I'll buy some breakfast.
SWEET COCOA CAKE SHOP
What is good here?
This is our newest red bean bun.
-Do you want one? -Sure.
Give me a bottle of that too.
Honey water?
Nothing for you?
Do you need anything else?
This is good too.
Yes, I'll have one of these.
-Okay. -How much is it?
Just scan the QR code.
Later,
the teacher will complain to you.
You just need to agree with him.
I'm experienced in this.
By the way, don't say anything later.
If we get caught lying,
we'll be doomed.
That sounds very scary.
Be brave.
Is this it?
It will be fine.
I can do it.
Reporting, sir.
My brother is here.
Hello, sir.
I am Sang Zhi's brother, Sang Yan.
Sang Zhi's brother?
It's obvious he is my brother
since he is so good-looking.
Why is it you who came today?
My parents--
Sorry, sir. It's like this.
My parents have to go to a work site today
for a meeting with a material supplier,
so they sent me.
Recently,
we noticed Sang Zhi hasn't been proactive
in doing her homework
when she gets home,
so I'm here to learn more about her situation.
You must help us.
Yes.
Come and sit down.
What's your name, sir?
I'm Mr. Chen.
Sang Zhi's academic results
are not the problem.
Her grades
have always been top of the class.
Her foundational knowledge
is also very excellent.
However, one still needs
the right attitude toward studying.
She cannot be arrogant.
-Yes. -Right?
In Mathematics…
He is so tall. Why are you so short?
What? Is there a problem?
All of it is linked.
If this lesson…
Your class teacher talks so much.
It's always the same speech.
The quality of study
and her mentality…
Look at him go.
Look at how obedient your brother is.
In our studies,
we must grasp
both aspects.
Sang Yan, take a seat.
I can grab a chair.
Thank you, Mr. Chen.
Sang Yan.
In truth,
I didn't want to trouble you
to come to school.
No, this is troubling you instead.
However, Sang Zhi
gives me a headache.
When I'm giving lessons,
she is drawing.
I called her up to answer questions
because I wanted her
to focus on the lesson.
Yes.
In the end,
she stood up and asked me, "Where were you?"
As if she had every right.
How will her behavior
affect other students' studies?
That actually happened, Mr. Chen?
Yes.
Sang Zhi.
Come here.
How could you talk to Mr. Chen that way?
That's wrong.
You must respect your teacher.
Let's forget about this for now.
Last time,
I called your parents here
because of Sang Zhi's issue.
Yes.
Was it your mom
or your dad who came?
-It was-- -Your mom.
-That's right. -Yes, your mom.
That's right.
I wasted a lot of your mom's time.
Yes.
In the end, time was wasted.
But nothing changed.
Sang Yan.
When you get home,
you must tell your mom
about our conversation
without leaving anything out.
And your dad!
Tell your dad
so he can work on Sang Zhi's mentality.
Of course.
Sang Zhi is a very smart child.
Her grades
are outstanding.
No. What is so smart about her?
She is top of her class
because you taught her well.
All of us know it.
Mr. Chen, you are an excellent teacher.
I've heard a lot about you.
Sang Zhi has caused you a lot of trouble.
Hit and scold her as necessary.
No, I can't hit her.
It's fine. If you are strict,
we will be relieved.
Yes.
The kid is smart.
We want what is best for her.
-Yes. -Right?
If she studies well,
I'm sure she can advance directly
to the high school.
I also believe Sang Zhi
will have a bright future
with you teaching her, Mr. Chen.
Sure.
This conversation
has been very successful.
Go home.
Sure.
Apologize to Mr. Chen.
Mr. Chen, goodbye.
Apologize.
I'm sorry.
Write it well.
There's cake when you're done.
ISAAC ASIMOV: THE END OF ETERNITY
Focus on your homework.
Drink the milk first.
It's better when it's warm.
What's wrong?
You act as if I'll take it from you.
Girl.
Are you angry at me because of my joke?
You haven't said anything.
I have to do my homework.
Fine. Do it.
Jiaxu.
Are you from Nanwu?
No.
I'm from Yihe.
Yihe?
Then
will you return to Yihe
during summer break?
No.
Why not?
Why do you care about that?
-Well-- -Do your homework.
Okay.
CHAPTER TWO, CLOSER
WHAT MADE ME MEET SOMEONE LIKE YOU
XURI MIDDLE-HIGH SCHOOL
I'm going in.
Wait.
What is this?
I stole a peek at your essay,
so I wrote a new one as compensation.
You…
You read my essay?
I wrote it for fun.
A STRAY DOG
When I saw this scene,
I stopped in my tracks.
My mood turned as foul as the weather.
When I saw the dog's face,
I became even more upset.
I couldn't help but go over and talk to it.
When I saw it,
I was reminded of my brother
because its face looks
as if it was made from the same mold as my brother.
It could even be my brother's son.
Sleep early.
-Bye. -What?
Last night…
HELPING MY BROTHER MOVE
"Helping my brother move."
Sang Zhi, what is this?
It's nothing.
Nothing? Is it a love letter?
No, it's yesterday's homework.
Homework?
It really is homework.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Sang Zhi.
Let's go.
One, two, three, four.
Enough, Fu Zhengchu. That's enough.
What a coincidence.
A coincidence, Fu Zhengchu?
You dance every day.
Aren't you embarrassed?
I worked hard to get into this school
so I can run into you anywhere.
Both of you.
Sang Zhi.
Did I not dance well enough today?
I told you!
One, two, three, four.
Two, two, three, four. Rhythm.
Two, two, three, four.
Three, four. Rhythm.
I heard there's an important day next week.
Do you want to know what day it is?
I don't.
It is
my birthday.
Sang Zhi!
My birthday is next week! You must come!
Your birthday is next week?
I will think of a way
to ask Sang Zhi to come.
Really?
Leave it to me.
-Then I-- -You come too, Yin Zhenru.
Order anything you want.
Sure.
Sangsang, guess what?
Just now, Fu Zhengchu…
Aren't you allergic to milk?
Why are you drinking it?
-I'm not drinking it. -Good morning.
-Good morning. -Then why did you buy it?
Let's begin our lesson.
All rise.
-Good morning, sir. -Good morning, sir.
Sit down.
Everyone, open your textbook to page 17.
SANG YAN IS A PIG
"Helping my brother move.
Today, I helped my brother move into his dorm.
My brother has so many things.
I really don't know
why a guy like him
has so many useless things.
Dot, dot, dot.
Thankfully, I was there to help him."
It's so childish,
as if an elementary school child wrote it.
"Luckily,
the silver lining is
that I saw my brother's roommate whom I had not seen
in years.
Although he called me a thief
upon seeing me,
I know
he was only joking with me."
Busted, thief.
"Seeing that
he has helped me before
and wants
to help me again,
I won't hold any grudges this time.
From now on,
I won't call him old either."
I will still do that.
"Also, the fox plushie he gave me
is not ugly at all.
However,
I still want
a brother like him.
As for my brother,
he can go anywhere he wants.
If anyone wants him,
just take my brother away.
P.S.
That boy told me
that he was also very happy
to see Sang Zhi again."
VERY HAPPY TO SEE SANG ZHI AGAIN
PASTE
SEARCHING
MESSAGE: I AM SANG ZHI
SET CONTACT NAME: DUAN JIAXU
DUAN XX
SAVING
I AM SANG ZHI
Zhizhi.
Zhizhi, have some grapes.
What are you doing? Drawing?
You…
You can't drink milk.
I'm not drinking it.
Why do you have it then?
Well…
I think the bottle looks nice.
I want to draw it.
You can't take one with milk.
I'll pour out the milk.
I won't drink it.
Honey, you're here.
Dear, you're back.
She…
She had a bottle of milk in her room.
I don't know where she got it.
Zhizhi.
Zhizhi, this weekend, your dad and I
are going to a friend's wedding.
-Do you want to come with us? -No.
Then I'll tell Sang Yan to stay with you.
No way.
I don't want to be with Sang Yan.
I'll be worried if you are home alone.
I just don't want that.
Zhizhi, what is it that I always say?
"Listen to your mom.
Don't make your mom worry."
I'll deal with your brother.
Don't worry. I won't let him bully you.
Otherwise, I'll cut off his allowance.
He won't listen to you.
I'll talk to him then.
Okay.
There's no problem with me around.
Enough drawing. Come down for dinner.
ISAAC ASIMOV: THE END OF ETERNITY
PURE MILK
SEPTEMBER 17TH, THURSDAY
THAT BOY TOLD ME
HE WAS HAPPY TO SEE SANG ZHI AGAIN.
Little demon!
Why didn't you close the door?
Mom told me to eat with you.
Little demon!
Is she in my room?
Where is she?
Why didn't you answer me?
Who are you trying to scare?
Why should I answer?
Bring it here.
Give it to me.
I'm having a hot pot later. Are you coming?
No.
What do you want to eat?
Take a guess.
Little demon.
When I was your age,
I had to cook for myself
and for you
when Mom and Dad weren't home.
That was different.
How so?
Because you didn't have a brother back then,
but I do.
Cut it out.
Give it to me.
Hello.
You're not in the dorm?
Sure.
I'll pick you up at your workplace.
Half an hour.
Don't worry. I won't forget about you.
Bye.
Sang Yan.
Who are you eating with?
Why do you care?
I even have to beg you to eat with me.
I'm going without you. Bye.
Hello, Mom.
Save it.
Hello, Dad.
You're overdoing it.
I was wrong!
That's right!
Right?
You should've just done that
instead of being naughty.
I'm telling you.
If you behave, I'll let you eat anything.
Let's go.
I'm going to freshen up.
Two minutes.
Three minutes.
Fine, 30 minutes. Go on.
Help me grab my phone.
It's inside the fort.
You're still making forts at your age?
Let me see how it is.
Little demon, why are you so quiet?
Sang Zhi.
Are you happy to see me?
Me too.
Cut the nonsense.
What are we eating?
Aren't we eating hot pot at the mall?
Is it too expensive for you now?
Do you think I'll complain about the cost?
You always do that.
When did I do that?
Turns out the roommate he's picking up
is Qian Fei.
Precious Duan Dog!
-Wake up! -Duan Jiaxu!
Hurry up! Sang Yan is treating us!
Didn't you say ten minutes?
There was traffic.
-Look at the time. -Aren't you hungry? Hurry up.
Why are you so sleepy?
He's lying to me again.
You're so sleepy.
Are you sacrificing your life for money?
Hurry up. I'm starving to death.
He's working so hard,
yet I'm always troubling him.
No, I should've lost weight.
Have you ever lost weight?
No, I weighed myself. I did lose weight.
Why haven't you greeted me since I got in the car?
Hey, you.
You what?
Just you.
"You are handsome."
No, you're not.
Am I not?
Then why did you blush
when you saw me?
You're shameless!
You are always like this.
Sang Yan.
Do you remember the physical test when I ran 1,000 m?
I was out of breath when I completed it.
Then this guy came over and said,
"Why did you blush when you saw me?"
I almost fell in love with him.
He says that even to dogs,
not just humans.
Sang Zhi, ignore him.
He is not a good guy.
He is not a good guy indeed.
Why are you sowing discord?
Did I?
Sang Zhi, did I sow discord?
I don't think he is a good guy either.
I'm not a good guy?
Fine.
I'm not a good guy.
Don't you know that?
At least he knows that he's a bad dog.
No good guy comes on so strong.
All right. You guys get off first.
I'm going to park the car.
Sure. I'm starving.
Can I wait for a while?
What for?
Just for a while. I'll stay with you.
No, I can't stop here.
I'll stay with you.
Are you going to pay the fine?
-No, I want to-- -Are you coming?
Take her.
Let's go.
Hurry up. I really can't stop here.
You are really annoying.
I really can't stop here!
What's wrong? Are you not feeling well?
A little.
I want to find a restroom first.
Do you have a stomachache?
Qian Fei, it's almost our turn.
-Go on ahead. -Sure.
I'll find a restroom with you.
No need. I can go on my own.
I'll go with you.
Wait.
Did you bring a napkin?
It's fine.
Wait for me inside. I'll buy it for you.
Go ahead.
Does this mean
he saw it?
DON'T PLACE ITEMS UNDER THE SHUTTER
Did you order pig brains?
Tick it all.
-Do you eat it? -I do.
Chen Junwen wouldn't eat it last time.
Hello.
We've ordered. Why aren't you here yet?
Your sister…
What's wrong with my sister?
It's that time of month for your sister.
What should I do?
Why are you asking me?
Buddy, do me a favor.
Help me buy it.
Me? Buddy, is she your sister or mine?
It's not necessarily a brother's job.
I've never done it over the years.
Enough nonsense.
I'm at the supermarket right now.
Come down immediately.
Fine. Buy it with me.
This one…
Okay, go.
"Nude S.
It feels like nothing at all--"
Lower your voice!
Then I'll just get the overnight one.
Sure.
This says 42.
-Are there different sizes? -No idea.
-It's 42. -Is 42 longer than 35?
Just buy the pocket pack.
Let's go.
Wait.
What is it?
Get a skirt too.
Is it on her skirt too?
Yes.
Okay, this one then.
Wait.
She is wearing a dark-colored skirt.
This is better.
Sure.
They're all the same. Let's go.
It's so embarrassing.
He saw it.
Hello, is Sang Zhi inside?
Yes.
Someone outside asked me to give this to you.
Thank you.
It's fine.
This happens to all girls. Get changed.
Thank you, miss.
How am I going to face him later?
What's wrong?
It's embarrassing.
Who said so?
It's just embarrassing.
Let's go. Time to eat.
Come on.
Why are you angry? You're not a child.
Sang Yan.
Over here.
Why are you so late?
I was afraid to dig in before you got here.
She went to play claw machines
and wouldn't come back.
You didn't win anything?
No. She even cried.
You even cried?
I'll help you after dinner.
It's not hard to get a prize.
Just use the claw and spin it around.
Forget it.
You'll get it when I show you later.
I'll order a few more dishes.
Sang Zhi, order something.
Tick a few dishes. It's my treat.
-Thank you. -No problem.
What do you usually order?
What is nice here?
Order this.
Shrimp paste?
Forget it. I ordered it already.
-Do you want it or not? -No, but it's auspicious.
Who eats sliced silkie chicken for hot pot?
Order something expensive.
Eat chicken for hot pot
and also in video games.
CHAOSHAN BEEF BALLS
Know your own limits.
I don't need to remind you.
Eating one is fine.
If something happens, I won't take care of you.
What's wrong with what she ordered?
I'm paying, not you.
Shut up.
She is allergic to beef and lamb.
Then let's not eat it
in case you get a reaction.
Give it to me.
Waiter.
Here. Help me place this order.
-Here. -Thank you.
-Drink some warm water. -Thank you.
Here.
Drink some beer.
I'm driving. I can't drink.
No one is drinking.
How can we have a hot pot without alcohol?
Don't you see this?
Iced tea with a hot pot is the best combination. Understand?
Yes, sure.
I'm telling you.
I'm not drinking. I'm driving.
You've said it 100 times.
I'm sick of hearing it.
Fine. Just drink your tea.
Let me tell you something.
That day when you weren't in the dorm,
I played solo.
My stupid teammate was so useless.
Do you know how badly they played?
-I couldn't stand it. -Wait.
-What were you doing? -Let me eat first.
What?
The three of us were in a ranked match.
Then I got a call.
You even scolded me.
-The day we almost won? -Yes, that day.
Excuse me.
Can you help me bring this into the women's restroom?
There's a girl inside who might need this.
-Sure. -Her name is Sang Zhi.
-Okay. -Thank you.
-Thank you. -No problem.
Wait for your sister here.
I'm going to find Qian Fei.
Nonsense.
Wait for her with me.
My sister is your sister.
Are you an idiot?
After what happened,
your sister will feel awkward
if she sees me when she comes out.
You're right.
You had better think of an excuse as well.
If Qian Fei asks,
she won't know what to say.
Just say she played with the claw machine
after using the restroom.
Sure.
Your gum.
Keep it for me.