(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
Who's trying to intimidate who here?
And who exactly runs this household?
I'm all ears.
You misheard me.
What brings you
to my quarters at this hour?
Don't you brew medicine
for Madam every day?
I've come to learn how.
There we go.
Master!
She...
She is being completely unreasonable!
Look what she's done to me!
It's just brewing medicine.
No need to make a fuss.
Just brew another batch.
That's not right.
She clearly can't brew medicine,
yet Nanny Zhou lied right to our faces,
saying she does it
for Madam every day.
Even when I caught her red-handed,
she still denied it
and forced Concubine Song to brew it.
Then,
the medicine spilled,
and Concubine Song
nearly caught fire herself.
Nanny,
you're making trouble for no reason.
Are you that bored of peace?
Deliberately sowing discord
between Madam and Lady Song?
I...
I'm innocent!
What I meant was,
she supervises the brewing every night,
she doesn't do it herself!
It was just
a slip of the tongue!
That's right.
Madam,
you know
what kind of person I am.
Jinzhao just came back,
she doesn't know
all the ins and outs here.
How would I not know?
This isn't my first time here.
I came once nine years ago.
Nine years ago?
You came here nine years ago?
You didn't know?
The day after my birthday that year,
I came
to the capital alone,
just to see you and Master.
But when I reached the gate,
I saw Master with Concubine Song.
Not only did he refuse to let me in,
he ordered Nanny Zhou to chase me away.
Master,
- how could you...
- No, no!
That was all a misunderstanding!
I didn't
recognize her at all,
I thought
she was some street urchin!
I never told Nanny Zhou
to chase you away!
Tell me,
what did you do that day?
I
didn't do anything!
Didn't do anything?
She pushed me, hit me,
even pinched me!
I ran far away,
and she still chased after me!
I...
Master...
This is outrageous!
You insolent servant!
How dare you overstep your place!
Guards!
Take Nanny Zhou out
and give her ten strokes of the cane!
Only ten strokes?
My neck was swollen from her pinching!
Twenty strokes!
No! Master!
I'm innocent, Master!
Drag her out now!
- I'm innocent!
- Move!
Master!
Please!
I'm innocent!
Master!
Nanny Zhou!
It's getting late.
Get some rest.
Jinzhao.
You're unwell,
you should head back and rest too.
I heard from Mrs. Liu
that Concubine Song's favor
made Nanny Zhou untouchable.
She's never even been scolded,
let alone beaten.
Who would've thought
Master would
actually have her flogged this time.
He's trying to wash his hands of this.
Beating Nanny Zhou
is his way of shutting me up.
He knows full well that
if he wants me
to play along in public,
to prove he never abandoned his daughter,
he has to let me
let out this nine years
of resentment.
But I remember it clear as day.
Nanny Zhou
was nothing but a lapdog.
The one who banned me from the manor
was him, Gu Dezhao.
Jinzhao is truly ruthless.
It's been years,
and she still holds that grudge.
Please,
this is too filthy.
Let Liu Xiang do it.
It's okay.
You raised me from birth,
so was she.
You even diapered and cleaned her,
you never found her dirty back then.
What's wrong with dressing your wounds?
Go ahead.
Be gentle then.
I'm already being as gentle as I can.
You know it hurts now?
If it hurts so much, stop lying
and egging my mother on.
Save yourself from more trouble.
What's wrong with the way you're talking?
It's the truth.
I only lied
for your mother's own good.
For my mother's good?
When Jinzhao
came to the capital alone that year,
a six-year-old child
who'd done nothing to you,
you hurt her so badly.
Was that for my mother's good too?
Be gentler!
Are you trying to get revenge for her
or something?
Fine, fine.
Lan,
do you think
I was born heartless?
Everything I did,
I did for you.
For me?
You've been pampered since childhood.
That's only because
Jinzhao didn't live here.
If she comes back,
everything
will change.
Don't you forget,
Jinzhao
is the legitimate daughter,
and you're...
I'm a concubine's daughter.
Nanny Zhou,
why are you bringing this up?
My sweet girl,
don't blame me for speaking plainly.
There are things in this world
that you have to fight for proactively.
If you wait
until someone comes for you,
it'll be too late.
Jinzhao
is cunning
and ruthless.
We all need to
watch our backs around her from now on.
Nie Fengming!
Lord Chen,
to what do I owe the pleasure?
Why did you do this?
Why?
Because I can't stand you
self-righteous Confucian purists!
Your land equalization policy,
your new tax laws,
all of it is nonsense!
You're just trying to take us down
and expand your own power!
I'll never let you get away with it!
You're a mere Cloud Cavalry Captain,
what right do you have to go against
so many high ministers?
You're a mantis trying to stop a chariot,
utterly foolish.
I know exactly what I'm doing,
I don't need you lecturing me.
You should
worry about
yourself right now.
After this stunt I pulled,
your new tax laws
will never be implemented,
will they?
I'm afraid you'll be disappointed.
His Majesty has issued an imperial edict,
officially launching
the land equalization policy.
What did you say?
His Majesty has issued an imperial edict,
officially launching
the land equalization policy.
You...
What did you say?
Say it again!
I said,
you'll be disappointed.
His Majesty approved land equalization,
with Tongzhou as the first pilot site.
We'll explore paths, assess conditions,
and set a precedent for future rollout.
Good.
Fine!
Chen Yanyun,
you won.
But
the merchants in Tongzhou
are all backed by us hereditary nobles.
I don't think your pilot program
will go as smoothly as you hope.
Well, I have you to thank for that.
Thanks to what you did,
not a single minister
in the court opposed it.
Everything in Tongzhou
is
proceeding in an orderly
and smooth manner.
Well,
congratulations.
I'll be watching from the afterlife,
to see if our Great Yan
can thrive and prosper under your watch,
Chen Yanyun.
Jiuheng,
your new tax policy
is absolutely brilliant.
Let me
join you in this.
You're a Cloud Cavalry Captain,
why meddle in this mess?
So what?
Our ancestors fought and founded
this empire.
I want this dynasty to thrive
more than any of you scholars.
If every minister in the court
thought like you,
the state of the dynasty
wouldn't have fallen this far.
What if
I take the lead in speaking up
for the new tax policy?
Would that help?
If you were a prince or a duke,
that might do some good.
What,
you think my title is too low?
I can round up others to join me!
A whole list of nobles,
from dukes down to barons.
Enough.
You don't have to do a thing.
This path is far too dangerous.
I have nothing to lose,
but you have a wife and daughter.
The safety of the realm
is the responsibility of every man.
If this new tax policy
can help our Great Yan dynasty recover,
I'd gladly
lay down my life for it.
By His Majesty's verbal edict:
Nie Fengming has committed high treason,
uttered reckless slander,
and insulted the Late Emperor.
He is sentenced to death by caning,
to be executed this very day.
That reckless stunt
by Nie Fengming
completely derailed
Prince Glorian's
entire scheme.
It's clear the momentum
is now on
Master Xuan's side.
This momentum
was bought with Nie Fengming's life.
We must not waste his sacrifice.
Once land equalization succeeds,
we will honor his memory at his grave.
Jiuheng?
You look pale.
If you're unwell,
go back and rest.
No one's worked harder than you lately.
Mentor,
I feel no hardship.
I believe
we must not
grow complacent
now that we've made an opening.
Instead, we should seize
His Majesty's full backing to plan
and act early,
clearing the way
for all that follows.
That is the best course of action.
Speak. What's on your mind?
Yes.
With the
military nobles backed down,
the biggest obstacle to our new policy
is Grand Secretary Fan.
We cannot
shake his foundation yet,
but we can first chop off
one of his arms
to weaken his influence.
Who?
Junior Vice Minister of Revenue,
Lin Xianzhong,
Lin Xianzhong.
Congratulations, Lord Lin.
This way.
Please.
Congratulations.
Let me make this clear first,
all gifts must be taken back.
The review is underway.
Let's not land each other in hot water.
We know your rules.
We all
came empty-handed today.
Good, please.
Zonghai.
Lord Lin.
You made it.
Uncle,
why did you drag me
to this birthday banquet?
- Greetings, Young Lord.
- It's dead boring.
The land equalization in Tongzhou
has sparked massive outrage.
Several people have already died.
The leader, Mrs. Ji, has had her house
set on fire multiple times.
Now she tests
every meal
with a silver needle before eating.
No one knows
if she'll survive another day.
Keep your voice down.
Miss,
the Old Madam
is in grave danger.
I knew the land equalization was risky,
but I thought
Mr. Chen
would protect our family
no matter what.
I never imagined
it would come to this.
Lord Chen, this way please.
Very well.
Mr. Chen?
Miss,
why is he here?
Listen,
go keep watch up front.
If anyone asks,
say I've gone to powder my nose.
Are you going to find him?
We finally crossed paths today.
I can't let this chance slip.
Even if it's just for Grandmother,
I have to beg him.
I'm going.
[Where on earth is she going?]
I had no idea
I'd intrude on your wife's birthday.
My apologies for the intrusion.
I think
you didn't intrude by accident.
You picked today
on purpose.
Let's cut to the chase.
Speak your
mind plainly.
Very well.
To be frank,
I've come today
to ask
a great favor of you.
What favor?
I'm asking you
to step down voluntarily,
and yield your post
as Junior Vice Minister of Revenue.
What did you say?
Don't get agitated just yet.
The Criminal Investigation Bureau
arrested a man from Zhejiang
named Su Yuanhang.
He confessed that
he acquired over 30,000 mu
of prime paddy fields in Yuyao
on your orders,
for less than
two thousand taels of silver.
Oh,
and he also said
you sent men to Datong
to dig up dirt on Grand Secretary Fan's
family back home.
I couldn't believe it
at first.
Everyone in court knows
how close you are
to Grand Secretary Fan.
Why would you
spy on him behind his back?
He...
he's lying.
You're lying.
I've never
met this man in my life.
I see.
My lord,
the Lady is asking where you've gone.
The feast is about to begin.
You may
go to the banquet first.
We can talk more later.
Send someone
to check if Su Yuanhang
has really been arrested.
Understood.
Wait.
Go yourself.
Be careful on the way.
[I never thought Chen Yanyun]
[could be so ruthless and underhanded.]
Miss Gu,
Mr. Chen has asked for you.
Me?
Yes.
Speak.
Why have you been following me?
I saw you were coming to the Lin Manor,
so I followed.
Is
everything alright with you?
The Ji family works for me.
Don't beat around the bush with me.
You saw right through me.
I heard there's been trouble
with the land equalization.
I came to ask
how my grandmother is doing.
There have been a few setbacks,
but nothing we didn't expect.
Your grandmother
has a dedicated guard detail.
You don't need to worry.
That's a relief.
Well,
Sir,
I also wanted to ask...
how much longer
will the land equalization take?
Grandmother is old.
I fear she can't keep this up.
These are not questions for you to ask.
Land equalization is state policy,
not child's play.
I know my place.
I won't speak of it again.
In that case,
I'd rather return to Tongzhou,
to stay by Grandmother's side.
It would put my mind at ease.
You want to go back?
Yes.
What are you afraid of?
I beg your forgiveness.
Your grandmother volunteered
to lead the land equalization.
Words are not enough.
She must take the risks
and make
the sacrifices.
For me,
the Tongzhou pilot
is more than just a trial.
It is the first step
of the new tax policy.
It
will succeed.
must succeed.
I entrusted this critical mission
to your grandmother.
She must show her resolve,
prove she is willing
to burn her boats.
Only then
can I fully trust her.
Do you
agree?
Yes.
I understand.
I am that resolve.
Your grandmother often says,
trim your sails to the wind,
cut your coat to fit your cloth.
No one knows better
than her
which way the wind is blowing.
Yes,
land equalization is dangerous.
Gravely dangerous.
But you must understand,
since time immemorial,
land equalization has never been
achieved without bloodshed.
The blood of our opponents,
and the blood of our own.
But Chen Yanyun
will never be the first to bleed.
Greetings, Young Lord.
Greetings.
Quite the imposing authority you have.
Everyone is paying birthday respects,
yet here you are,
hiding away in the backyard.
I do not care for crowds.
You don't even
believe that yourself, do you?
Did you come here to see him?
Don't you know
a weasel doesn't sneak into the henhouse
for nothing?
You jest, my lord.
I never jest
with men like you.
Everyone in court knows Lin Xianzhong
is Fan Chuan's right-hand man,
and you are Fu Hailian's star pupil.
Fan Chuan and Fu Hailian
are sworn enemies.
Yet here you are,
not joining the feast,
but lingering deep in the backyard.
If this isn't
a weasel in the henhouse,
what is it?
Young Lord,
Mr. Chen,
you two carry on.
I've been out too long.
I should head back.
I'm leaving too.
My lord,
Young Lord Ye
came specifically looking for Miss Gu.
It seems
the two of them have grown quite close.
Gu Jinzhao.
What do you want?
Why did you go looking for him?
It's none of your business.
I'm warning you.
You'd better stay away from him.
What do you mean?
I know you hate your father,
but you still bear the Gu family name.
Do you know the entire Gu family
is in Fan Chuan's faction?
I didn't before.
I do now.
That's why I need to get back quickly.
You...
Cheers.
- Cheers.
- Drink.
Master,
the young lady wishes to leave early.
Help yourselves, everyone.
The feast is barely halfway through.
How can you want to leave?
Where's your manner?
Stand aside.
Master,
Madam has sudden heart palpitations.
Madam is calling for you to return.
How could this happen?
Lord Lin,
my wife has fallen suddenly ill.
I cannot stay,
I must take my leave.
Of course.
Your wife's health comes first.
Go.
Very well.
How did she suddenly have heart pains?
Should I
- come with you?
- Dezhao,
you stay here.
I'll take him back first
to check on her.
Let's go.
You hurry back to see her.
Miss Gu.
Miss Gu,
- you look
- Mentor,
- absolutely stunning today.
- to be frank,
if my
mother-in-law hadn't stopped me,
I would have brought
the child back long ago.
I don't mind you all laughing.
I'm just a man
who cares
deeply for his children.
Miss Gu,
- your father is so good to you.
- Eat.
[How dare he say that.]
[No,]
[I have to think of something.]
Yes,
though I live
in Tongzhou most days,
my father
comes to visit me often.
He and his concubine
even made the trip specially
for my coming-of-age ceremony
in Tongzhou.
My wife is in poor health
and cannot stand traveling.
The household affairs have long been
managed by one of my concubines,
so I
brought her along
to the ceremony in Tongzhou.
Indeed.
My concubine is from a prestigious clan,
well-educated and refined.
She is the daughter of the former
Chief of the Court of Imperial Sacrifices.
Really?
Could it be Song Shiqi,
who retired from office
five years ago?
To think he would
marry his daughter
to Lord Gu as a concubine.
Truly remarkable.
One dared to marry into it,
the other dared to take her.
You never
spoke of this before.
My wife
is from a merchant family,
so my mother arranged for me
to take Lady Song as a concubine.
I knew it was improper,
so
I never spoke of it publicly.
Even so, a concubine
has no right to run the household.
You are quite right.
My mother also said,
if my wife's health
does not improve,
we should move back
to the family's ancestral estate,
so the brothers
can look out for each other.
But
moving is no small matter.
We need to renovate the house,
make new furniture.
How can I afford that
on my meager official salary?
Everyone says the capital is wealthy,
but I never believed it until now.
It's truly opened my eyes.
For example,
Lady Song drinks a bowl of
bird's nest soup
every single day.
Even though my grandmother's family
is wealthy in Tongzhou,
we would never spend so frivolously.
Shut your mouth.
I...
I must take my leave.
Let's go.
Sir,
just as you expected.
Lin Xianzhong did send someone
to meet Su Yuanhang.
We've now
caught him red-handed.
What's happening up front?
Gu Deyuan was the first to leave,
with Gu Dezhao right on his heels.
Good.
Lest he be implicated
and drag the Ji family down with him.
He's finally learned some sense.
Did Gu Deyuan tip him off?
No,
it was Miss Gu.
She deliberately
undermined Lord Gu at the banquet.
Every word he said,
she shot him down,
embarrassing him so badly
in front of everyone
that he had no choice but to leave.
Interesting.
She killed two birds with one stone.
Two birds with one stone?
She publicly
humiliated Gu Dezhao,
and kept him out of trouble.
What else would you call it?
But,
it harms her as much as it harms him.
Is everything ready outside?
All set.
Good.
Let's go take a look.
Understood.
Master!
Bad news.
A lot of the guests are leaving.
Let them go.
Have you
made your decision?
About what?
You fabricated this whole thing
to frame me!
Frame you?
Has your steward
returned yet?
He went...
Did you
have him followed?
Thanks to him,
the Criminal Investigation Bureau
caught Su Yuanhang
without breaking a sweat.
Or rather,
thanks
to you.
Lord... Lord Chen,
please spare Su Yuanhang.
I will
submit my resignation at once,
I will yield the post
to... to...
Fu Hailian.
I'm afraid
that won't work.
Resignation needs a solid reason.
What's more,
if His Majesty
asks you to stay,
it will only cause more trouble.
What exactly do you want from me?
What...
You've amassed quite a fortune
during your years in office.
Pleading guilty to corruption and
dereliction of duty is no injustice.
It's better than hiding undeclared land,
and a hundred times better than
secretly betraying and spying
on Grand Secretary Fan.
Don't you agree?
Chen Yanyun,
you're slaving away for Fu Hailian.
Have you ever thought about
what will happen to you in the end?
I haven't gotten around to that.
But
thank you for the warning.
Good day.
Miss!
Lin Xianzhong
has been arrested.
What?
I heard from the servants up front
that he was seized
right at the banquet, on charges of
corruption and dereliction of duty.
Everyone on Revenue Street
is talking about it right now.
It's Chen Yanyun.
It has to be.
He moves
so fast.
I entrusted
this critical mission
to your grandmother.
She must show her resolve,
prove she is willing
to burn her boats.
Only then
can I fully trust her.
Do you
agree?
Qingpu,
I think
he's got his eye on us too.
Why?
I can't be sure yet.
Something about this doesn't add up.
Here,
go grind my ink.
I need to write a letter to Grandmother.
[There must be something else going on]
[around the time of my ceremony.]
Sir, you're back.
What are you doing here?
The letter Miss Gu
wrote to Old Madam Ji
was intercepted by our men
and brought here first.
Miss Gu?
Well?
Is there anything interesting in it?
She writes that
she met me once
while in the capital,
and found me unpredictable,
my words holding hidden meaning.
She also asks Madam Ji
if anything happened
involving me around the time
of her ceremony.
So it seems Miss Gu
knows nothing about
what happened with Prince Ruichang's son
that night.
Not necessarily.
She might
have guessed
we have people watching her,
and wrote this letter on purpose
as a smokescreen.
Is that possible?
For all her cleverness,
Miss Gu couldn't be that sharp.
It might be because
I deliberately rattled her
at the Lin Manor that day.
Why?
Since time immemorial,
land equalization has never been
achieved without bloodshed.
The blood of our opponents,
and the blood of our own.
If Mr. Chen never sees the letter,
so be it.
But if he does,
he'll know
I'm declaring
my loyalty to him.
But if Miss Gu
wrote this letter on purpose...
Then she's declaring her loyalty to me.
Telling me
she knows nothing,
and even if she did,
she wouldn't breathe a word of it.
She is
really something.
Alright,
seal the letter
back up exactly as it was,
and send it on to the Ji family.
Understood.
Should our men
keep following her?
Yes.
I want to see
just how far she's willing to go.
Oh,
and there's a name
missing from the archive files.
I need to ask you about him.
Who?
Liu Siyu.
The director of Ministry of Revenue?
Yes.
What,
the Chief Councilor wants to promote him
to replace Lin Xianzhong
as Junior Vice Minister of Revenue?
Most likely.
Master,
Lord Lin is finished.
You're his protégé.
Will you be implicated?
No.
After I left the Lin Manor,
he publicly
distanced himself.
Some mentor he is,
so heartless.
Then it seems
Jinzhao really
saved you this time.
She just
got lucky, that's all.
Speaking of Jinzhao,
tomorrow you go find a matchmaker.
I've found
a marriage for her.
Marriage?
Which family?
Liu Siyu,
the bureau director
of the Zhejiang Division.
His eldest son is eighteen,
the same age as Jinzhao.
I've thought it through.
The new
Junior Vice Minister of Revenue
will be one of Fu Hailian's men.
Liu Siyu is the only one
in the entire Ministry
who's Fu Hailian's protégé.
He's about to leap
from a mere bureau director
to a senior ministerial post.
But the Mistress is still here.
Why should I be the one
arranging Jinzhao's marriage?