Do you want to go get tteokbokki?
Okay.
CHAPTER 12: YOU GUYS WANT TO GO OUT
INTO THE REAL WORLD, RIGHT?
Oh, hello, sir.
-Eui-ju! Are you still here?
-Yes.
I'm going to drop by the library.
Is something bothering you?
I think
my homeroom teacher has it in for me.
Why?
Ever since that misunderstanding
about the filming,
he's been acting like he hates me.
No way.
It's true.
First, he embarrassed me in front
of everyone by asking me my math score.
Then he made me write an apology
because I said I hated math.
And now he's giving me demerits
for a ridiculous reason.
He wouldn't do that for no reason.
Goodbye.
See you tomorrow.
Hey, Yoon!
I thought you wanted
to take Discrete Math together.
No, no, no.
This ending is lame.
Tae-ha can't let Si-on just walk away.
The math…
I mean,
Ju Si-on.
You deserve a beating.
It's going to hurt.
Blame it on the personality
of the person you're based on.
Good.
HIS EYES BLAZE WITH OBSESSION…
Hey, Ju Si-on!
TAE-HA PUNCHES SI-ON
-Let's go.
-You're bleeding.
-I'm fine.
-Hang on a second.
One punch just isn't enough. Do it again.
Sorry?
-Again?
-One more?
Just a moment!
There we go.
That hits the spot.
That's better!
This is really great.
How can I keep it to myself?
Shall I just upload it?
Right?
You guys want to go out
into the real world, right?
If I'm this excited,
you guys must be even more so.
-Do it!
Shall I just upload it?
Nobody's going to find out.
SUBMIT A NEW PROJECT
-We're going out into the real world!
WE WERE FRIENDS
CHAPTER 13: ARE HIS GLASSES
REALLY THAT BIG A DEAL?
EPISODE 4
Is it that bad?
I'll be okay.
Why would someone take glasses
they can't even use?
That's it!
Up in a tree.
You said you threw them.
If they're not on the ground,
they must be in a tree.
I thought of that,
so I looked on the way home.
They weren't there.
So where have they gotten to?
Did a pigeon take them to build its nest?
Yes!
They do say that magpies and such
like shiny things.
Apparently, sometimes they take them
to decorate their nests.
Just get some new ones.
The problem is it's not that
straightforward to make new ones.
Are you done?
He's hardly eaten anything.
They're in a nest.
What's wrong with him?
I think he's really sick.
I think I need to take a sick day.
Okay, I'll let them know at school.
Get some rest.
Laid low by a pair of glasses.
MURIM GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
Mr. Ga is feeling unwell,
so I'll be taking homeroom today.
Let's start with roll call.
-Kim Ga-yeong.
-Here!
Kim Dan-ji.
-Kim Yeong-jae.
Here.
-Oh A-rin.
-Here.
I hope our teacher changes.
-Choi Yu-mi.
-It'd be amazing if it was Dong-ju.
-Right?
-Yeah.
-Jeon Ji-min.
-Here.
He looked fine yesterday.
Maybe he bunked off
to hang out with his girlfriend.
That would be amazing.
He's being punished
for being mean to Eui-ju.
Giving my girl demerits for no reason.
-Right?
-Yeah.
Cute.
-Jenny, do you ever diet?
-Why?
Hello, Mr. Ga. Are you okay?
Oh, no! Please take good care of yourself.
Don't worry about us.
I'll make sure to tell the others
in homeroom.
Okay. Get some rest.
I explained
the concept of Rolle's Theorem.
If we insert one here…
And if we insert five here…
Great work.
-Thank you.
We're done.
I'm so sleepy.
Guys, can I have your attention?
Is Mr. Ga not coming to school
tomorrow either?
Applications for after-school programs
are due by tomorrow so don't forget.
That's all.
-Did she just ignore me?
-Yeah.
I'm off to art academy.
Bye.
Is he really sick?
It's none of my business.
MISSING GLASSES
At this rate, he'll have
to take a leave of absence.
What did the doctor say?
He has to keep resting.
If he overdoes it,
he risks damaging his other eye.
Oh, hello.
Is that your application form?
What's up with Mr. Ga's glasses?
The thing is…
MISSING GLASSES
Are his glasses really that big a deal?
They're special glasses.
He was trying to soldier on,
but in the end…
It's going to take a long time
to make new ones.
I'm quite worried.
Oh! No!
Hey!
Ga-yun!
-Stop!
-What is it?
Let me borrow your bike for a bit.
-My bike?
-I'll give it back later. Quickly!
-Sure.
-Quick!
Thank you.
Move out the way.
Hey!
Come on!
Wait!
No!
Come on!
Wait!
Stop!
Hey! Please!
Hey!
Please!
How far are you going?
Please stop!
Mister!
What the hell are you doing?
It's dangerous!
I'm sorry.
But…
You've got to help me.
My teacher's going to die without them.
What are you talking about?
The thing is…
I threw my teacher's glasses in the trash.
But without them, he's going to die.
Can you help me out?
Please. They're in there.
Please…
MUNICIPAL DUMP
Are you sure they're in here?
Yes, I threw them out yesterday.
Why would you do that?
I know.
And why look for them again?
I'm really sorry.
I'll be as quick as I can.
Mister.
I'm really grateful.
I'll search.
I'll be really quick
and clear it all up again.
Oh, look.
I've found them.
Is that them?
These are the ones.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
CHAPTER 14: YOU BREAKING MY GLASSES CAUSED
TEN MILLION WON'S WORTH OF DAMAGE
Where did you find them?
They were on the bench with poop on it.
They were already broken.
4073.
That's the last four digits
of your phone number.
One of my students has the same number.
YEO EUI-JU
What's your name?
Why is that important?
Just give me the money.
I have to go to PC room.
Name.
Yeo Eui-do.
Call your sister.
Why?
Just do it.
Hi, what is it?
There's someone who wants to talk to you.
Yeo Eui-ju.
You stole your teacher's glasses?
You're nuts.
Now she's here, you can go.
And talk to her nicely.
Sir.
So what happened was…
I clearly asked
if you'd stepped on my glasses.
You could have said something when we were
all looking, or again in the parking lot.
But you looked me right in the eye
and said it wasn't you.
I…
I was scared…
I'd get in trouble for breaking them.
But…
You gave me four demerits because of Ji-a.
I don't think I did anything wrong.
It seemed so unfair.
And I feel like you hate me.
I was wrong.
I didn't know they were special glasses.
If I knew your eyes were so bad,
I'd have given them back to you
straightaway.
I shouldn't have done what I did.
I'm truly sorry.
So.
It was clearly your fault
and you've admitted it.
All that's left is compensation.
Compensation?
You breaking my glasses caused
ten million won's worth of damage.
Ten million won?
What kind of glasses cost ten million won?
I can't take money from a student.
So you'll have to find another way
to repay me.
Okay.
I will.
However I can. Whatever it takes.
I'll give you one chance.
Thank you, sir.
I'll do anything.
After-school math.
Sorry?
I'm going to give you the chance
to rediscover your passion for math
and improve your grades.
What's the point?
Sir, that class is only for smart kids.
The ones who are top of the class.
Before class,
set the temperature to 23 degrees,
put the handouts on the desks,
and collect any homework.
After class, clean up,
put everything away, and lock the door.
I really can't.
Wednesday at five.
Wednesday at five?
Sir, I'm supposed to do after-school PE
at that time.
I really can't do Wednesday at five.
Don't forget.
Ten million won.
I really can't.
What am I going to do?
What?
My reward.
I didn't get it because of you.
Hey!
What money do I have?
I already spent my allowance.
-Mom!
-Wait!
Okay.
This is all I have.
You should learn to budget.
Why of all people did it have to be him
to get dirt on me?
So annoying!
Hang on.
It's clearly your fault
and you've admitted it.
All that's left is compensation.
Don't forget. Ten million won.
He does come up with
a lot of really great dialogue.
I bet mine's been buried way down again.
WEB NOVEL RANKING
Number one?
Hang on a second.
1. WE WERE FRIENDS
VIEWS: 130K
WE WERE FRIENDS
What the heck?
How many favorites?
One, ten,
hundred…
FAVORITES 15,320
15,320?
What's going on?
Is this definitely mine?
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 1
I'm from the future.
This novel is going to be huge.
Please let Yoon and Si-on end up together.
Tae-ha's in true love.
Really looking forward to their story.
What the heck?
That hurt!
Then…
is this real?
It's real?
The tension is thick right from the off.
-You could cut it with a knife.
-Tae-ha, you had me at red bean bread.
Yoon is so much more complicated
than math.
This line alone
tells the outlook of this story.
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 2
WHAT? AM I TOO CLOSE?
YOON SHOOK…
Dan-ji found Mr. Noh's Instagram.
I found photos of him
from back in college.
Amazing!
Can you try looking for Dong-ju's?
How much are you going to pay me?
Get lost.
Why is Eui-ju so quiet?
Is she actually studying?
YOON SHOOK HIS HEAD BUT…
You're late.
I'm tired.
We need to talk.
I have nothing to say.
If I say we talk, we talk, got it?
-I said I have nothing…
-Shut up!
Let go of me!
Sorry.
I told you to let go of me.
Are you okay?
It was clearly your fault
and you've admitted it.
All that's left is compensation.
Compensation?
Ten million won.
What?
You splitting my lip caused
ten million won's worth of damage.
What do you mean ten million won?
Heard of a little thing
called "scarcity value"?
The rarer something is,
the more valuable it becomes.
Because people want it even more.
Just like my lips,
which I don't just allow anyone to have.
You're poor, so instead of money, you'll
have to find another way to repay me.
Wednesday at five.
Come to my place.
Don't be even one second late.
That ten million won.
Pay me back properly.
You're not treating her like that
on purpose, are you?
Why are you being so strict with just her?
Blink twice if you're here under duress.
I can't accept her
only getting four points in math.
You keep making me think bad thoughts.
Yeo Eui-ju.
I didn't realize
you were such a lost cause.
I'm very disappointed.
Is Tae-ha gonna be waiting
outside your house again?
I don't know. Stop messing around.
What's so funny?
Is it R-rated?
It's not like BL, is it?
Now that's a proper cliffhanger.
There's no way
you can skip the next episode.
Subtitle: Paul Carver