[pop music playing]
DYNAMITE KISS
EPISODE 12
Look at it. I'm fine.
- What are we going to do about your wrist?
- Excuse me.
I'm sorry. [crying]
It's okay. No one got hurt.
Why are you crying?
I'm sorry.
[crying continues] I'm sorry.
Oh, my.
[So-yeong] After the divorce,
my ex-husband stopped paying
for child support.
I needed a proper job,
so I applied to Natural BeBe.
For the Mother TF Team?
[So-yeong] Yes.
I was an assistant manager
at another baby product company,
so I had high hopes,
but my application didn't pass.
I was devastated.
I felt utterly useless.
[stammering] That's not true.
I think I took out my anger about my life
on Natural BeBe.
I posted malicious comments
on online mom communities
and called customer service
to curse out the representatives
and make issues out of nothing.
I'll gladly accept
any punishment you see fit.
I'll also post on the online communities
and come clean about what I did
and explain that it was all fabricated.
I'm really sorry.
Gosh, I'm hungry.
What should we eat for dinner?
Sushi? Or pasta?
Fried chicken?
I'm fine. I'm not really hungry.
[inhales sharply] Oh.
You don't seem to be in a good mood.
Da-rim.
Everything worked out.
It's done.
Okay?
I probably took
Ms. Lee So-yeong's spot, right?
If I didn't lie to get hired,
she would've been on the team.
You're reading too much into it.
Even if it wasn't her,
I'm sure
someone more qualified
would've gotten my spot.
And that someone
could've been in a more urgent
and desperate situation than me.
It makes me question
the choices I've made.
- Well done, everyone.
- [cheering]
- Good job, everyone!
- We're done.
- It's over now, Da-rim.
- Team dinner tonight?
How about a refreshing beer?
- That sounds so nice.
- Well done.
What should we eat?
- Grilled intestines.
- Ms. Go Da-rim.
How's your injury?
It's healing.
Is that so?
CERTIFICATE OF MARRIAGE STATUS
NAME: GO DA-RIM
STATUS: UNMARRIED
[Ji-hye] Is this real?
Yeah.
That woman
- was never married.
- What?
CERTIFICATE OF MARRIAGE
KIM SEON-U, DIVORCED
GO DA-RIM, UNMARRIED
Are you saying she lied to get a job?
You shouldn't be angry at her.
- You should actually be thankful.
- Why would I?
She created an opportunity.
An opportunity
to completely crush Gong Ji-hyeok.
CERTIFICATE OF MARRIAGE STATUS
You must have been so upset.
The company should've taken
better preventive measures.
[stammers] It's okay, ma'am.
[Ji-hyeok] The company is wholly
at fault for this.
Speaking of which,
let me formally request that we establish
clear guidelines for protecting CS staff
and implement mental-health support.
[Ji-hye] That's a good idea.
We'll work on that.
- Oh my. Thank you, ma'am.
- Thank you.
[chuckles]
Also,
we'd like for you
to do a press interview, Ms. Go.
Is that okay with you?
- Pardon?
- You need to clear your name.
I think it would be even better
if you do it with Mr. Kim Seon-u
as a couple.
You could even talk about
working together.
[Nan-suk] A press interview?
Does it mean she's going to be on TV?
- You'll be famous nationwide.
- You have to do it, no matter what.
Then I'll schedule one
as soon as possible.
[Ji-hyeok] That might be difficult.
[sighs]
Ms. Lee So-yeong will inevitably come up
during the interview.
If the issue is highlighted again,
she'll come under fire.
She already confessed and apologized.
Do we have any reason
to push her to the brink?
I agree with him.
I think it would be best not to do it.
Is that so?
All right then.
But let's at least post an announcement
on the company bulletin board.
To highlight your exceptional service.
You'd be okay with that much, right?
Yes.
You were right.
Ji-hyeok knows Go Da-rim is single.
[Tae-yeong] Well done.
Just keep praising him
and stroking his ego.
The higher he rises…
the more painful it'll be when he falls.
Ms. Go, we saw the announcement
on the company bulletin board.
Congratulations on being
Employee of the Month.
Did you get that injury
while saving the baby?
- You're so cool.
- Gosh, I'm flattered.
I didn't do anything special.
Ms. Go, our Employee of the Month,
always had a strong moral compass
and acted with sincerity.
[Nan-suk] Of course.
Ms. Go, our Employee of the Month,
is known for her unwavering
sense of responsibility.
That's right.
Enjoy your lunch.
- Thank you. You too.
- You too.
[jeering]
[Go-eun] You're the Employee
of the Month's team leader.
How does it feel?
[Ji-hyeok] Well…
- It feels nice.
- [Nan-suk exclaims]
- [Jin-hui chuckles]
- [Go-eun] I see.
You know, Da-rim loves beef.
Come on now, Go-eun.
You don't need to say that out loud.
There's no way Mr. Gong would just ignore
such a momentous occasion.
After all, Ms. Go,
our Employee of the Month,
brought such prestige to our team.
[Nan-suk] Of course. If he's
at all grateful, he can't just ignore it.
For sure.
You all should know better now.
Mr. Gong would never.
[all] There's no way.
It's time for a proper team dinner.
- Beef.
- [Go-eun gasps]
It'll be my treat.
[cheering]
[chanting] Gong Ji-hyeok!
[Gyeong-min] I'll search
for a restaurant immediately.
Korean beef.
- Korean beef?
- Yes, please.
[Gyeong-min] Might as well go all out.
- That sounds so nice.
- We might as well if we can.
Let's step out for coffee.
- It'll be my treat.
- Oh, my gosh.
That's the Employee of the Month's
assistant manager for you.
- I can tell you're a learned man.
- Come on, Da-rim.
Sorry, I think I'll pass.
I don't feel too great.
You guys go ahead.
[Go-eun] She barely ate her food.
What's going on?
She's turning down free coffee?
This is totally your style, right?
But you always wear stuff like this.
[gasps] What a pretty color.
You said you had a kid
who goes to daycare, right?
- Yes.
- [gasps] Great.
Can you suggest an outfit for me?
Something suitable
for a talent show at a daycare.
Pardon? Where?
[stammers]
Gosh, that's so pretty.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
A talent show.
Show? You're going to a show?
What?
Yeah, I'm going to a friend's show.
I mean, a friend's party.
Right, so what sort of party?
What's the theme?
Uh…
The theme is
just a gathering of friends.
We'll be singing and dancing.
I guess you can call that the theme.
Ah… Okay. You should've asked me.
That's my specialty.
Let's see here.
Oh, my. [gasps]
This one's great.
Well, you see, the guests at the party
will be on the young side.
- That might be a bit too much.
- They're young?
- How young?
- Well…
They're a lot younger than I am.
Listen.
Don't be intimidated.
You need to go all out
when you're with a younger crowd.
Can you show us
a few more party dresses like this?
Yes, ma'am.
[sighs]
- Goodbye, Jun.
- Bye, Jun!
Bye.
[teacher] Jun,
your dad should be here soon.
We'll wait with you.
[Seon-u] Jun!
Hello.
[both] Hello.
My goodness, did you wait long?
I'm sorry.
I had to pick up the guitar from a friend.
- It's fine.
- Let's go home.
Give me your bag.
[sighs]
Why the long face?
What happened?
Did seeing your friends rehearse
make you nervous?
- No.
- Don't worry about a thing.
I'm an excellent guitarist.
[both laugh]
I'm sure all your friends
will end up being jealous of you.
Let's go and practice.
- Should we?
- Yeah.
Let's go!
NEW SPRING WOODS KINDERGARTEN
Be careful.
All right, all right.
I'll come visit
- when Da-rim has some free time.
- [door opens]
Don't even get me started.
- That company can't run without Da-rim.
- [door closes]
She's so busy.
All right, take care.
Bye.
- [line clicks]
- I'm home.
Da-rim.
Come here.
I was just on the phone
with your aunt Myeong-ja,
and she insists we come by to visit.
You know,
for the fresh country air and stuff.
That sounds nice.
[sighs]
It's been a while since I last saw her.
We saw her often when Dad was alive.
We used to have
marsh snail-catching contests.
That's right.
You and your dad always won.
You wouldn't stop even
in the freezing cold. Who could beat that?
- Did I?
- [both chuckle]
You really take after your dad.
He'd be so proud of you.
You're hardworking, tenacious,
and honest, just like him.
Oh, it's time for dinner.
LIVE WITH HONESTY
Dad.
Sorry.
LIVE WITH HONESTY
MOTHER TF TEAM CANDIDATE
ASSESSMENT
YANG HUI-SUK, LEE GO-EUN,
GO DA-RIM
EVALUATOR: MA JONG-GU
[no audible dialogue]
GO DA-RIM
I HEREBY SUBMIT MY RESIGNATION
DUE TO PERSONAL REASONS
[keys click]
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
I'm on board too. [chuckles]
I think we can trust him
with the development of the new product.
There won't be much
internal pushback either.
He handled the recent
mom-community incident well,
so our public opinion is good too.
Look at how she's backing you up.
I expect you to show proper results.
Enough to silence any board opposition
about you becoming vice president.
Then I'd like to make a request.
- What is it?
- If this project is a success,
please renew the contracts
of all my team members
as full-time employees.
[Chang-ho] Why do you keep insisting on
helping those women?
We still have some time
before their internships end, right?
Yes, we do.
But having his team members
become full-time employees
when he gets promoted
might be better overall.
[Chang-ho] Right.
To complement
the inauguration ceremony, huh?
All right, go ahead.
[Ji-hye] Yes, sir.
Ji-hyeok.
You can do this, right?
Of course, I can.
I trust my team members
more than I trust myself.
That's why I'm so grateful for you.
- What?
- You hired them yourself.
They're all so talented in their own ways.
You really have a good eye for people.
Ah… [chuckles]
- Don't mention it.
- Keep it up.
Developing new products
is a core business of our company.
Can we take on such an important task?
Why not?
- We've done pretty well for ourselves.
- He's right.
There were always
a few obstacles in the way,
but we've always produced good results.
I believe we can do this.
Right, Da-rim?
I'm not sure
if this is the right time
for me to say this,
but I have to tell you--
[Ji-hyeok] Before that,
there's one more important announcement.
- An important announcement?
- What is it?
What's more important than this?
If this project succeeds,
I've gotten the approval
to make all of you full-time employees.
- Really?
- Full-time employees?
- Oh, my. I can't believe this.
- Full-time employees!
We have Go Da-rim,
the Employee of the Month,
so of course we'll succeed.
Let's do our best, Da-rim.
Everyone, let's all become
full-time employees!
Let's do it!
I can't believe this!
- I'm going to work really hard.
- Where do we begin?
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
[Da-rim] Mr. Gong.
I don't think I can continue working here.
I'm sorry.
I won't take this.
I appreciate the concern,
but I've made up my mind.
With my mom out of the hospital,
a couple of part-time jobs
should be enough to make
the interest payments and what I owe you.
It's not about money.
All applicants with notable
academic backgrounds,
experience, and qualifications
were cut
during the application screening stage.
They even chose the ones
with the lowest interview scores.
Me included.
- Why did they do that?
- From the start,
they weren't looking
to make a proper team.
[sighs]
So everyone was right.
A loser team just for show.
That was true at first.
If I'm being honest,
that's what I thought as well.
Right.
When everyone had given up on this team,
there was one person
who didn't.
Do you know who that is?
It's you, Da-rim.
Are you just going to let people
look down on you?
Without even putting up a fight?
This report
is the result of us running around
and putting our heads together.
For them, this job and this report
are their livelihoods and lifelines.
JANG JIN-HUI, LEE GO-EUN,
GO DA-RIM, BAE NAN-SUK
Da-rim,
you basically made our team.
You didn't steal
someone else's spot.
You led this team to where it is now
and saved it from fading away.
Ms. Bae Nan-suk.
Ms. Jang Jin-hui.
Ms. Lee Go-eun.
Help them become full-time employees here.
You can resign after that.
All right?
Okay.
Until then,
I'll do my absolute best.
[grunts] What did I just see?
What's wrong with my eyes?
Am I overworked?
[screams, gasping]
What's wrong with them?
Why are they hugging?
No, this can't be true.
Oh, my goodness.
This can't be happening.
Why are they hugging? Why?
- I'm serious!
- Are you sure you're not mistaken?
I'm not. I saw it with my own two eyes.
With Mr. Gong?
- There's no way.
- I know what I saw.
- They were hugging.
- Then what about Mr. Kim?
- How could she bring him here?
- Spread out!
[Jin-hui coughing]
[Da-rim] Do you have a cold?
Do you want something warm to drink?
No, it's fine.
We were just talking about work.
Oh, right.
Mr. Gong suggested
we all attend the baby fair
to brainstorm ideas
for the new product.
Oh, I see. It sounds like
Mr. Gong made sure to only tell you that.
You two seem to have
a lot of conversations.
- What?
- [Jin-hui] It just seems like
you and Mr. Gong
have become exceptionally close recently.
Does it? I haven't noticed any changes.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Mr. Gong asked if we'd all be down
to go for a team dinner tonight.
Will Mr. Kim be there as well?
No, it's going to be just us.
That's so cold. Mr. Kim didn't even
hesitate to participate in the campaign
for you and our team.
How could you not invite him?
Forget it.
I won't be joining.
I can't either. I have plans.
I'm going to spend some quality time
with my husband.
[teacher] Next up is a performance
by the Moon Class,
"Heart, Heart, Mwah."
- Please give us a round of applause!
♪ Heart, heart, mwah, mwah ♪
♪ I love you so much, Mommy and Daddy ♪
♪ I really love you, I really love you ♪
♪ I don't know why I love you so ♪
♪ Heart, heart, mwah, mwah ♪
♪ I love you so much, Mommy and Daddy ♪
♪ Even when I see you over and over ♪
♪ And every day ♪
♪ Heart, mwah ♪
♪ Even when I see you over and over ♪
Hey, Jun! Jun!
You're so cute. Oh, my gosh!
Good job, Jun!
You're the best! You're adorable!
- Let's look over here.
- There, there.
- [Seon-u] Let's look over here.
- Just one.
[ululating]
Ji-ho.
Ji-ho, can you look this way?
- Over here. Let's look here.
- There, there.
Next, we'll welcome Kim Jun and his father
to the stage for their performance
of "Island Baby."
Can we please have Jun's father
come to the stage?
[murmuring]
Mr. Kim?
I guess he's not here yet.
- The next performers are ready, right?
- Yes.
Jun, let's have the next team go first,
and then you can go after that, okay?
Wait! I can do it. That's okay, right?
Who are you?
I'm…
- Jun's best friend.
- [crowd laughs]
You got this.
Let's do it.
♪ When Mom goes
To the shade of the island ♪
♪ To pick oysters ♪
♪ The baby stays behind alone ♪
♪ And keeps watch over the house ♪
♪ The sea sings ♪
♪ A lullaby ♪
♪ The baby rests their head on their arm ♪
♪ And falls asleep ♪
Hello.
- Jun.
- Dad!
My goodness.
Be careful, you're going to hurt yourself.
Dad, why were you late today?
Sorry.
I'm really sorry about today.
But still, I saw you sing up there.
You were incredible.
I would've been in big trouble
if it weren't for the pretty lady.
Thank you.
How did you know about this?
Jun invited me.
Jun and I decided to become best friends.
Bang!
THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME, DAD
[kettle whistles]
[water pours]
It's hot.
Thank you.
You have such a lovely home.
[sighs]
Thank you
for standing in for me today
at Jun's performance.
I think Jun had a lot of fun,
thanks to you.
Right? Jun and I were in perfect sync.
But…
please don't do this again.
Sorry?
You and I
will have no reason
to see each other after this exhibition.
But Jun is still a kid.
He won't understand
why he can't see you anymore,
and he could get hurt.
Then we can just continue
to see each other.
I already told you.
I like you and Jun.
I have no interest in you as a woman.
So,
please don't give false hope to Jun.
Please.
[elevator dings]
My apologies.
Seriously?
Wait.
Sorry, Tae-yeong.
I have an urgent meeting.
You haven't changed a bit.
Your apologies are never sincere.
You were always like that
when you snatched up the companies
I was in talks with first.
You knew how much I had invested
in those deals valued at billions,
trillions even.
But you just acted and apologized
like you bumped into me on the streets
or something.
"Sorry, Tae-yeong."
I'm glad that came across well.
You're right. I wasn't really sorry.
Even if it weren't for me,
you could never have closed those deals.
[scoffs] Yeah?
People can instinctively tell
the difference between someone
who will help them grow
or devour them.
And you see,
you make it too obvious.
You have the look of a beast
standing over its prey.
Yeah, that's it.
- Watch it.
- Just one more thing before I do.
When it comes to elevators,
it's exit first
and enter after.
That's basic etiquette.
You should at least have basic manners.
Okay.
See you.
Hi.
What are you doing here again?
Back to interrogate me?
Why so cold? We're on the same team now.
What? Same team?
What's with the face?
It's nothing.
- How's it going?
- Well, I did as you said
and let Ji-hyeok handle
the new product development.
But what if it's successful?
Wouldn't that be bad for us?
Wait, was that Mr. Yu's idea?
We need to make sure that doesn't happen.
I thought you said we're on the same team.
Why did you tell her to do such a thing?
Stay out of his way and support him.
- Pardon?
- What?
This is our chance. Our chance
to use that Go Da-rim card properly.
And don't worry.
Even if they produce something amazing,
it'll never see the light of day.
Uh, instead of overthinking it
and obsessing over newness,
I thought we could find an older product
and give it an update.
We could each take one--
Who cares about our opinions? [chuckling]
We'll follow your lead on everything.
- What?
- You're the idea person of our team.
- That's right. You are.
- [both chuckling]
Absolutely.
What are you talking about?
We always do everything together.
- First, we should divide the categories--
- [Jin-hui] You should tell her.
- [Go-eun] But you're the oldest.
- [Nan-suk] Be quiet.
- You saw it.
- You saw it, so you speak up.
[Nan-suk shushes]
- [Jin-hui] No, you tell her.
- I don't even know if it's true.
- Listen. [chuckles]
- [Jin-hui] Hmm?
There's something…
[somber music playing]
…I want to tell you.
[inhales shakily]
I had a second to reflect
after my mom got discharged.
That's when I finally realized
that I did something unforgivable.
I'm deceiving those who trust me.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Stop that. It's fine. It's totally fine.
- Sit down.
- [Da-rim sobbing]
Gosh. You should've told us sooner
if you were going through all that.
It's not like we wouldn't have understood.
[chuckling] I misunderstood you
for no reason.
See? I told you
Da-rim wouldn't do something like that.
When the world has you standing
at the edge of a cliff,
you have to do whatever you can
to survive. [breathing shakily]
How could we not understand that?
- That's right.
- [Go-eun] If it weren't for you,
we would've been discarded like leftovers
and kicked to the curb.
So don't cry.
[all chuckling, sobbing]
You're all crying.
- I'm only crying because you are.
- [sobbing continues]
But still, it doesn't change
the fact that I lied to get this job.
I'm going to leave after this project.
I already handed in my resignation.
Oh. Oh, no.
I want to see
my Jin-hui,
Nan-suk,
and Go-eun
become full-time employees.
I'll consider this my last chance
to repay your kindness
and do my absolute best.
So…
let's do our best
until the very end, okay?
- [Jin-hui] Da-rim.
- [Go-eun] I can't believe you.
[all sobbing]
[Da-rim] I'm sorry.
[music fades]
Mr. Gong, we need to talk.
- About what?
- You'll see when we get there.
- Where are we going? Hold on.
- [Go-eun] A restaurant.
I made a reservation at the most
expensive place near the office.
Let's go.
Great. Let's go.
Let go of me. Wait. Let me go. Let go!
Please let me go.
I said let go!
[exclaims]
[comical music playing]
[all] Cheers.
[gentle music playing]
[Jin-hui] Oh, I was so shocked
when I saw you two
hugging each other. [giggles]
I was really torn
about what to do about you two.
- [sighs]
- [chuckles]
Uh, Mr. Kang,
you're drinking more than usual.
How could I not?
Ji-hyeok betrayed me. [clicks tongue]
Hey, I didn't betray you.
I'm so disappointed in you.
You should've at least told me.
So you're saying
you had that banging dynamite kiss
with Ms. Go, right?
- "A banging dynamite kiss"?
[comical, sensual music playing]
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Mr. Kang.
Are you drunk?
[Nan-suk] Hold on a second.
Didn't you tell us you two met
for the first time in Jeju?
And you shared an explosive,
dynamite kiss from the start?
- [gasps]
- [Go-eun] Can you elaborate?
What exactly is a dynamite kiss?
How is it different from a regular kiss?
No, that's not… [chuckles]
- Well…
- [Da-rim] Yes?
- You explain it. I can't.
- [gasps]
- So you see…
- [Jin-hui] Oh, my goodness.
- It's like…
- Yeah?
[intriguing, comical music playing]
- I don't know what to say.
- [all groaning]
She can't say. She doesn't know.
- Seriously? You two are so annoying.
- [Nan-suk] Ooh!
I don't care if it's an office affair
or romance.
Let's just get rid of both of them.
I feel so empty inside, Nan-suk.
Eat as much as you want tonight.
It's on me.
Hey! Can we get more meat here?
A large, please!
- Let's go hard tonight!
- [all cheering]
Congratulations.
[Jin-hui] Here's to your relationship.
- How nice.
- [Gyeong-min] Is it good?
[music fades]
[Ji-hyeok] That must have been
really tough for you to do.
It was really brave of you to tell them.
I mean it.
I was really worried,
but they were all so understanding.
I feel bad about it…
and thankful at the same time.
- [groans]
- Hmm?
Stop crying.
Okay?
["Say You Love Me" playing]
It's okay.
I'm proud of you.
It's hot. Be careful.
Thank you.
[song continues]
I should apologize to you as well.
Why?
For everything from when we met
until now.
You went through a lot emotionally
and suffered because of me.
That's true. You're right about that.
It makes me very angry.
It does.
But all of it
is forgivable by the fact that…
you're single.
I think you're a really lucky person.
[chuckles]
- Thank you.
- [chuckles]
[sighs] What's wrong with me?
Stop running away now.
I won't ever let you go.
[dramatic, romantic music playing]
[music fades]
[whispering] So handsome.
- I know.
- [gasps]
What?
Why are you pretending to be asleep?
[grunts] Because I'm happy.
[grunts]
[gentle, romantic music playing]
[sighs]
[Da-rim sighs]
Are we not going to get up?
We need to eat breakfast.
No, thanks.
We need to wash our faces
and brush our teeth.
[groans] I don't want to. [grunts]
[sighs]
- Okay then. Let's just not do it.
- [sighs]
You want to spend the whole day in bed?
Yeah.
And do what?
You know, just this and that.
This and that?
Mm-hmm.
This and that…
- Yeah.
- Okay.
[Da-rim squeals, giggles] Hold on. Wait.
I guess Da-rim is sleeping in
because it's the weekend.
No. She didn't come home last night.
She was drinking with a friend.
Uh, m-maybe…
[chuckles]
…she has a boyfriend.
[sighs] I wish.
She needs to start dating,
but she's not interested
because she's so ambitious
about her career.
Gosh. Ji-hyeok
is also so dedicated to his work.
It's always work, come home,
work, come home for him.
I don't think
he's ever held a woman's hand before.
Gosh. It's concerning, to say the least.
They say kids nowadays just don't date.
Gosh. We should all be concerned.
By the way…
what kind of man does Da-rim like?
I wonder what she'd think
of someone like Ji-hyeok.
No, that can't happen.
Oh. W-Why not?
He's too handsome.
[scoffs] He's not handsome at all.
He's so average-looking.
Gosh. Just walk through any street
and look around.
All guys look like him.
[tense, comical music playing]
- Can you tell me where that street is?
- What?
I want to go and see.
[chuckles]
Anyhow, it won't work.
They come from different worlds.
It's best to marry someone
with a similar background.
Eat up. The soup's getting cold.
This is delicious.
[sighs] Sure.
[groans, yawns]
She sure can drink like a fish.
Oh, I guess she gets that from me too.
Wake up. We're shopping
for your newlywed home today.
I don't care. I'm not going anywhere.
You go.
Why would I go alone? [grunts]
- ♪ The sea sings ♪
What's this?
[curious, comical music playing]
So tell me.
Why were you
at Mr. Kim's kid's talent show?
Why did you go and sing?
Why else? I like him. That's why.
I told you I liked someone.
[stammers] You crazy brat! You crazy brat!
How could you be so immature?
- Why him, out of all people?
- Ow!
- Have you lost your mind?
- What's wrong with him?
Pull yourself together!
Do you think marrying someone like Dad
is being mature?
Then I'm just going to be immature.
I refuse to live like you!
[scoffs, exclaims]
[inhales sharply, sighs]
JUN BABY STUDIO
[gasping, chuckles]
He's just some nameless photographer
and a single dad.
How dare he covet my daughter?
[scoffs, gasps] I let him hold
an exhibition in my art gallery,
and this is how he repays me?
That ungrateful…
[groans] Damn it. [hisses]
I'll get straight to the point. Ha-yeong…
[groans]
Are you okay?
[groans, winces]
[muttering] That damn brat.
- Mr. Kim Seon-u.
- Just a second.
Can I see your wrist for a moment?
Excuse me.
Let's see.
[slow, sensual music playing]
It's a little cold.
Oh, you don't have to.
I also hurt my wrists a lot
because I spend all day
playing with children.
These pain relief patches are the best.
I'll put on one more.
It doesn't hurt, does it?
[romantic, comical music playing]
It should heal in no time.
[chuckles]
Didn't you have something to say?
[stammers]
And this?
I didn't know what to get you. [chuckling]
I couldn't show up empty-handed, could I?
Thank you for this.
[Ji-hyeok sucks teeth, stammers]
[cheerful music playing]
Grapefruits.
- Good.
- Okay, we'll get this.
What's your favorite pasta?
I'll make whatever you want.
You know how to cook pasta, Mr. Gong?
Of course, I do.
[chuckles]
Wait.
We're on a date. Can you stop
calling me Mr. Gong? [chuckles]
Uh, sorry, Mr. Gong.
[gasps] Uh…
Then what should I call you?
Ji-hyeok.
That's fine too, but…
Ba… [chuckles]
Baby? Like "baby boy"?
No, not that. [chuckles]
Babe. [stammers, sighs]
Whatever, just forget it. [chuckles]
Babe, let's go!
["Special Day" playing]
- [squeals, chuckling]
- [chuckling]
Let's go, babe!
Come on, babe!
[both chuckle]
[camera shutters]
- Ooh.
- [Ji-hyeok] Ta-da!
[Da-rim] This looks amazing!
- Me?
- [camera shutters]
[gasps]
Mmm.
Hmm?
[chuckles]
[song continues]
- Hmm?
- [grunts]
- Mmm.
- [whispers indistinctly]
Two.
- [exclaims]
- [exclaims, chuckles]
[both chuckle]
- [speaks indistinctly]
- Mmm.
- Hold on. You have something here.
- Mmm?
Huh?
No, not there.
[song continues]
[song ends]
[tea pouring]
[groans]
[sighs]
[tense, comical music playing]
Do you think marrying someone like Dad
is being mature?
Then I'm just going to be immature.
I refuse to live like you!
Water.
What?
What are you doing? Pour me some water.
[scoffs]
- [exclaims]
- [shouts] Are you serious?
You can't even pour a cup of water?
I hurt my wrist.
- You have another one!
- That's true.
I forgot I had two arms.
Goddamn it.
This is the short list of products
we're looking to update.
Is the development team
working on any of them already?
- Uh, we have nothing planned for them.
- [Da-rim] Mmm.
But the fact that we don't
means that those products already have
high customer satisfaction ratings.
An unnecessary update
could end up backfiring.
That's right. I know it's a challenge,
but I suggest you try
to come up with something
that's not already in our product line.
Then you'd also be pioneering
a new market for us.
- Mm-hmm.
- [Go-eun] Hmm.
- That's true.
- If I could offer a tip,
I'd say start recording everything
on your phone.
Record everything?
You don't know when an idea will strike.
Recording it the second you think of it
will be helpful.
Trial and error will be inevitable,
so if you record every step,
you'll be able to review
where it went wrong.
Oh, that makes sense.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
["Don't Give It Up" playing]
Um, it looks uncomfortable.
So I think… [coughs]
So I think it needs to be updated. Mmm.
Mmm. That's a must.
[speaks indistinctly]
The size… [sucks teeth]
- I think diaper bags might be good.
- Diaper bags…
- Look at this fabric.
- Diapers?
- That would be…
- Take a look at this one.
- This one too.
This one too.
This one's…
I'm not sure how it should be tied.
The way you tie it?
[chuckles]
[speaks indistinctly]
[chuckles, speaks indistinctly]
[Gyeong-min] Let me do it.
- [Da-rim speaks indistinctly]
- This one? Or this one?
I think that one.
[song fades]
COMPLICATED &amp; DIFFICULT KNOT
UNCOMFORTABLE FOR BABY
NO POCKETS
HIP CARRIER CAUSES STRAIN
DIFFICULT TO USE
DUE TO HOW IT'S TIED
[tender music playing]
Look. Next.
- Ta-da!
- That color is so nice.
- Yeah.
- It is.
- This is nice.
- [gasps]
- Pretty.
- Good for a tone-on-tone look.
But I still think
the fabric is most important.
[Da-rim] This isn't right.
How can I…
What's that?
[applauding]
Mr. Gong!
Seriously.
WITH BABY
- Ta-da!
- [all cheering]
- [Gyeong-min] Okay!
- This is excellent!
- We did it!
- [Gyeong-min] We did it!
- Baby carrier.
[all chanting] Baby carrier. Baby carrier.
- We did it.
- Baby carrier.
[all chanting] Baby carrier. Baby carrier.
[Gyeong-min] Baby carrier.
[Da-rim] To account
for sweating in the summer,
we can use some sort of mesh fabric.
How about making it with mesh fabric
and making it detachable?
Two options for summer and winter.
[Ji-hyeok] You haven't texted me all day.
Here you are
just recording yourself again.
Are you going home, Mr. Gong?
No one's around.
[gasps]
- [chuckles]
Are you leaving already, babe?
I'll miss you so much through the night.
[chuckles]
[Da-rim chuckles, groans]
[gentle, romantic music playing]
We can go home together.
To my place.
- [chuckles]
I can wait for you.
I really want to go with you,
but I still have a lot of work to do.
The prototype is coming out soon,
and we need
to add final touches where needed.
You should go home.
I can't concentrate.
[gasps] Oh, wait.
I left files in the meeting room.
Go first, okay?
See you tomorrow!
[exclaims]
[sighs]
I'm going home first.
I'm really leaving.
I don't know why hearing
you tell me to go home makes me so sad.
[sighs]
Can't you stop me and make me stay?
I just want to
chat and laugh with you every day.
It's finally here.
- [cheering]
- Hurry! Open it!
- I can't look.
- I'll open it for you.
- I can't.
- Ooh. Oh, my gosh, it's so pretty.
- It's so pretty.
- My goodness. I can't believe this.
- It looks so luxurious.
[Nan-suk] Oh, my.
[Da-rim] It's finally here.
Natural BeBe's first baby carrier.
[Nan-suk, Jin-hui exclaim]
[Nan-suk] That's right,
it's the baby carrier we created.
This is exactly how I felt
when I gave birth to my first son.
My goodness.
[both exclaim]
[Jin-hui] You know the feeling, right?
This will be out on the market
next week, right?
I'm not dreaming, am I?
[squealing]
Now, now.
You all worked really hard.
I'm sure we'll see positive results.
- [squealing]
- [Gyeong-min] Mr. Gong!
[panting] Mr. Gong!
You all need to look at this.
- This came out so nicely.
- Look at it.
[Da-rim] This is
the same as our prototype.
We never placed an order for this color.
This is a new product
that MomsJoy released this morning.
- What?
- That can't be.
Why would our product
be released by another company?
[Jin-hui] Yeah,
there must be some sort of mistake.
- Mr. Kang, you must be mistaken.
- [Gyeong-min] No.
- Wait, hold on.
- What?
[Go-eun] "MomsJoy is releasing
a new baby carrier.
It utilizes a body-hugging design
that notably reduces shoulder
and lower-back strain.
It's made with cutting-edge materials
to make it lighter than a towel…"
[Gyeong-min sighs, exclaims]
It's the exact same materials
and features.
- That can't be.
- [Jin-hui] Are you being serious?
- [Go-eun] Let me see.
- Are you serious?
[exclaims] They're so similar. [stammers]
Who's Go Da-rim, huh?
Oh, Chairman Gong…
I'm Go Da-rim.
Ah. You're Go Da-rim?
[Nan-suk screaming] Oh, my!
["Face to Face" playing]
DYNAMITE KISS
[gentle, romantic music playing]
[Chang-ho] So you knew she lied
to get hired and let it slide?
[Ji-hyeok] Yes.
But framing her for being a spy
when she didn't do anything?
That's enough.
[Da-rim] He knew I lied
and still covered for me,
and now he's in a tight spot.
[Chang-ho] You're just going to give up
on being promoted to vice president
and our joint venture with Taeyu C&amp;T?
All because of a woman like her?
Think wisely!
[Da-rim] I was the one who leaked
the new product to a competitor.
[Ji-hyeok] Why do you insist
on suffering alone?
- Just trust me and--
- [Da-rim] I'm suffering because of you.
Let's break up.
Let's each go back to where we belong.
This is me at rock bottom.
Subtitle translation by: Justin S. Kim