I just don’t want him getting
dragged into your family’s mess.
So please, as a mother,
I’m begging you,
stop the engagement.
As long as we’re together,
we can get through
anything, okay?
It’s only now that
I’ve felt what it’s like
to be treated like family.
Sam!
Goodbye.
I’ll see you later.
Hello? Naomi?
Ma’am, she’s gone.
Naomi, how can I live now?
Let’s just take a selfie.
Cy, please.
Let’s end this.
Maui, you’re just tired.
I was using you.
Haze?
Sam’s almost finished with
her hair and makeup.
Really?
She liked the look
you proposed
and decided to do it.
Great. Okay. Let's start!
She’s ready!
This supermodel
from the Philippines
is making waves worldwide.
She's been in the industry for four years.
And what four years can do.
Samantha Vera has fronted
magazine covers,
ruled international runways,
and is the face of
many global campaigns.
A true force
in the fashion scene.
With every step,
Samantha Vera rewrites the
narrative of the Filipina beauty
and proves that a Filipina
can own the world stage.
This is the new Sam.
The Sam who’s going to
live life on her own terms.
No fear. No holding back.
Nothing and no one will stop me.
Not even my past.
Okay.
Her throat isn't
swollen anymore,
but is Avi still coughing?
Not really, Doc.
Doc, they’re looking
for you in the ward.
Sorry, I didn’t know
you had a patient.
No, wait,
I’ll introduce you to her.
This is Samantha Vera, the model.
Do you recognize her?
Shit. The past is right in front of me.
And this is
Doctor Clyden Ramirez.
He’s a pediatric resident.
And this cute little girl
over here is Avrielle.
Av… Avrielle?
We know each other already, Doc.
Hi, Maui.
Hi, Cy.
So, how do you guys
know each other?
Common friends?
She was my fiancée.
Wait, wait. I have to take this.
Yes?
Okay. I’ll be right there.
Cly, can you cover for me
and take care of Avi?
Maui, I’m so sorry but
I’m needed in the ward.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Okay, Doc. I’ve got this.
Thank you.
How the hell did I end up in
the same room as him?
Excuse me.
Okay, what do we have here?
Avi has a sore throat
and was under
medication for five days.
It’s just a follow-up
check-up today.
Hi, Avi. I’m Doc Clyden.
I’ll check your throat first, okay?
Okay.
Okay, say aah.
Does it hurt?
How about when you cough,
does it still hurt?
Not anymore.
Okay.
Doc, am I okay now?
Yes, your throat’s not
swollen anymore.
That’s because
I’ve been a good girl.
I drank the syrup
Dr. Lana gave me,
even though it tastes eewy.
Eewy…
You don’t like the taste?
No.
If they want kids
like me to get well,
they better make it
taste like candy.
I see.
I'd better talk to those
people who make medicines.
Or you should eat mommy’s
soup and vegetables.
They’re delicious.
I see.
Your mom’s a great cook.
But I miss ice cream.
Can I eat ice cream now?
Yes. Yes, you can.
But just in moderation, okay?
He’s still good
at talking to children.
Being a pediatrician really suits him.
What does moderation mean?
Moderation means
just a little at a time.
Then can I eat it with
marshmallow toppings?
How about nuts?
He looks mature now,
and very confident and reliable.
I’m happy to see him like this.
Okay.
So, her throat’s okay now.
No need for more medication.
Just make sure she goes easy
on sweets and cold stuff.
Stick to warm water for now,
just in case the
inflammation comes back.
Or worse,
she might get tonsillitis.
Got it. Thanks, Cy.
I mean, Dr. Ramirez.
She takes after you.
Let’s go, Avi.
We’ll go ahead, Doc.
Thank you.
Say thank you to Doc.
- Thank you.
- Bye, Avi!
- Say bye.
- Bye!
Let’s go.
The rumors are
getting out of hand.
This should be easy to debunk
since it’s not even true.
We can always get a statement
from Avi’s parents, right?
No. I can’t drag Yanna
and Avi into this,
especially since Hiro
still doesn’t know about Avi.
It will die down.
Why don’t we create a new rumor?
Let’s say
a non-showbiz boyfriend?
But I don’t have
a non-showbiz boyfriend,
and I don’t even
have time for one.
Well, if you don’t have time
for a romantic relationship,
then maybe an old fling?
Maybe your ex-boyfriend?
Ma’am, remember the
last time you got drunk?
You said your last ex
was the best boyfriend
you’ve ever had?
Perfect. I like that idea.
Who is this boyfriend, anyway?
Try reconnecting with that ex,
whoever he is.
The way I broke up with him?
There’s no way we’ll reconnect.
He might still be mad at me.
Maui, wait.
Let’s talk, please.
Let me go.
Stop with the
boyfriend rumors, please.
Just let the issue with Avi be.
Again, it will die down eventually.
Okay. If you say so.
Let’s talk about your projects.
Francine.
So, upcoming bookings so far—
Photoshoots,
The Lab Cosmetics, Muse Magazine,
and Denim Haus.
Now for fashion shows,
we have Noa Atelier
and Maison Lorent.
Okay. Got it.
By the way, your parents’
lawyers sent a message.
They want you
to visit Camp Crame.
Your mom wants to see you.
Ever since they got jailed,
I haven’t visited my parents.
Not even once.
And I don’t think I will.
I can’t. I’m busy.
I don’t have time to visit.
But that’s true— because
you have a tight schedule.
Here’s your schedule.
Are you good?
Yeah. Okay, bring it on.
You have your
gym training every day.
Ten more minutes, Sam!
You can do it!
On Wednesday,
you have a photoshoot.
Friday, contract signing.
Thank you.
We are thrilled
to have you as our
new brand ambassador, Sam.
Thank you for having me.
I’m so excited to work
with you guys,
and you know what,
I can eat Botejyu every day.
Wow.
Also on Friday night,
you have a runway
rehearsal and Saturday—
you have a fashion show.
Samantha Vera
wows in fashion show,
as Modern Maria Clara.
Thank you.
Sam, the psychology students
from San Gabriel College
are double-checking
if you’re still coming
as their guest speaker.
It’s tomorrow,
unless you want to take a break.
No, I’m going there.
It’s important, I should be there.
Mental health isn’t a weakness.
It takes real courage
to talk about it.
Sometimes we think
we can handle everything—
but we’re only human.
You need to check in on
the people you care about,
even if it’s just
a simple message like,
“How are you?”
Sometimes we assume
they don’t want to be bothered
or that they’re okay.
But the truth is,
you never really know what
someone’s quietly carrying.
There are smiles
hiding sadness underneath.
Your small act of care,
just a simple,
“I’m here if you need me”.
That might just save a life.
So,
let’s all normalize
asking for help.
Let’s all normalize checking in.
You’re not weak
just because you’re tired.
We all need to pause,
reflect,
and heal together.
I hope you’re proud of me, Naomi.
I miss you.
Sam, are you busy tomorrow?
Can I leave Avi with you?
I have a sudden flight.
But I’ll pick her up
in the evening.
Of course! No problem.
But I’m going
to the gym tomorrow.
Is it okay if Avi comes along?
Sure! But oh man,
Avi will change her mind again.
The other day, she said she
wants to be a weightlifter.
Then, just recently,
she said she wants
to be a pretty office woman
because you took her
to your meeting.
Nine, eight, seven. Then other side.
Baby, be careful.
Jump.
- Slowly.
- Go, Auntie!
Chest out.
Yes.
Come on, Sam. You can do it!
Go, Auntie! Go!
Avi, be careful.
Okay.
One more set, Sam.
I’m dying, Rich.
Come on, Sam.
I’m so tired!
Don’t you have
a bikini photoshoot, Sam?
So, suck it up.
Come on.
Go, Auntie! Go!
Careful, Avi!
- Auntie… Auntie!
- Oh my god.
Baby! Avi!
Rich, I need to take her
to the hospital.
There's one nearby,
Ramirez Medical.
It’s okay, baby.
Let’s go to the hospital.
Is Dr. Lana on duty today?
She’s Avi’s doctor.
Dr. Lana’s off duty right now,
but one of our pediatricians
is already on the way.
Baby, stop crying.
It’s okay, it’s okay.
He’s here.
- Don’t worry.
- What happened?
I think she hit her face
flat on the floor at the gym.
Why would you bring
your kid to the gym?
Blood. There’s blood.
Let me see.
Can I see?
Okay. No more.
It’s not bleeding anymore.
Am I going to be okay?
Of course,
you’re going to be okay.
You’re a strong girl, right?
Okay. Let me take this.
Hold it.
The ice pack, please.
Okay, lean forward to me.
Okay.
It’s okay. It’s okay, Avi.
All right. Lean back,
lie down. Slowly.
Okay, good girl. It’s okay.
It’s okay.
Let’s get her an X-ray
just to make sure there
are no fractures or anything.
I’ll have the nurse assist you.
Okay.
Don’t worry baby.
You’re gonna be okay.
- Stop crying now, okay?
- It’s okay.
There’s no more bleeding. It’s okay.
It’s okay, it’s okay.
It’s okay.
Just a quick search.
It’s harmless.
I’m just curious.
Charles Ramirez to
Lead Ramirez Medical,
Unveils Expansion Plans
for Modern Healthcare.
Charles? Really?
I wonder what happened.
Ramirez Son, leads vaccine
efforts in rural areas.
Vaccines help protect children
from serious diseases.
We can get them for free
at barangay health centers,
government hospitals,
and some private clinics
accredited by the DOH.
Doc, thank you so much
for this program.
You’re welcome, Cap.
But this wasn’t all just my effort.
A lot of volunteers from
Ramirez Medical helped out,
and we also received
a lot of donations.
But you’re really the one
who started this program,
so thank you so much.
Ramirez Medical brings
free medical service
to hundreds of children.
Hello.
That doctor is so hot,
I’d definitely get a shot from him.
Okay, good.
Is it hard to be a doctor?
I want to cure my mom.
She’s always sick.
You can definitely be a doctor,
but you have to stay healthy.
So you have to take
all the medicine
and vitamins I give you, okay?
- Yes, sir!
- Okay.
Me too, Doc. Can I have some?
I want to be a model
when I grow up.
How lame.
You just have a crush on me.
A model and a doctor?
That’s a great dream to have.
See? I told you being a model is cool.
Clyden Ramirez is more
than just Medical Royalty.
He’s still the same old
Clyden I knew years ago.
The same principled guy
with a heart
to help those in need.
Why am I getting annoyed?
I’m just tired.
That’s right. I need rest.
Avi, be a good girl. Okay?
Don’t stress your Auntie.
When I get back,
we’re going to pack our
things for Japan, okay?
Are you excited?
I’m super excited, Mommy!
How about you? Are you excited?
Of course!
But honestly,
I’m a bit nervous too.
Don’t worry too much.
Just enjoy your first
international trip with Avi.
Besides, I’ll be there too.
I’ll make sure the three
of us have a great time.
Okay. Thanks, Sam.
All right, our flight
is coming up soon.
Okay, bye.
Avi, say bye-bye to your mommy.
Bye, mommy!
Are you buying me a souvenir?
I’m going to Thailand, baby.
We're just going to buy a lot
of souvenirs in Japan, okay?
Yeah, I’ll see you.
- Okay?
- Miss Samantha Vera?
OMG! Can we take
a photo with you?
Yeah. Sure.
Thank you.
Your daughter is so cute.
Dog!
Baby! Avi!
You look familiar.
- Hail.
- Hail?
Oh my god, is that you?
Great. We bumped into each other again.
Sorry, she just got excited
about the dogs.
I didn’t even realize this was Hail.
It’s okay.
But it looks like he recognized you.
He got excited when he saw you.
New dog?
Yeah. Solar.
Summer’s daughter.
Puppy!
Summer has a baby.
How is she?
She...
passed away.
I’m sorry to hear that.
Sam—
Yes?
Wait.
- Wanna pet the dogs?
- Yes!
- Hello? What happened?
- This is Hail.
Okay, I’ll be right there.
I need to go.
Okay. See you around?
I hope we won’t see each other often.
Excuse me, what?
Does he hate me that much?
Because that means Avi’s unhealthy.
So, please take good care of her.
Come, let’s go.
- Hail, Solar.
- Okay. Say bye-bye to the dogs!
Bye!
Sir, how’s she doing?
She’s doing okay.
She’s been feeling weak lately.
Okay. I’ll just go check on her.
Hi, Anya!
Doc, look!
I want to dance like this.
When will I be able to go out?
I want to see my friends already.
I miss them.
You know, Nurse May told me
that you’re not
taking your medicine.
I’m waiting for you.
I don’t want to take it
unless you give it to me.
You’re being picky.
You have to take your medicine,
you can’t be stubborn about it.
Am I going to get better?
Because on the internet,
it says you don’t get
better at stage four.
Hey…
Not everything you see on
the internet is true.
Okay?
Okay, Doc Clyden.
I’ll trust you more than the internet.
Because you’re the best
doctor in the world!
All right, now take your meds.
Anya, here you go.
Oh, that’s my mommy’s magazine.
Do you think she’s pretty?
She looks like my doll.
Yeah.
She does look like a doll.
Thanks for coming along
at the last minute, Sam.
Of course.
I know it’s hard to travel
with a 4-year-old.
- Avi!
- Avi, your mommy.
You stay with Auntie Sam
for now, okay?
We’ll see each other later.
Okay, Mommy.
All right, let’s talk later.
My phone’s drained.
See you soon!
Bye, Mommy!
I love you, Mommy!
Bye, Avi! I love you, too!
See you!
Look, Avi. That’s mommy.
She’s super busy, see?
Hi, Mommy! You’re so pretty.
You’re so cute, my baby.
Okay Avi, go to the lavatory.
Okay…
Girl, are you okay?
Sam, I have a problem.
I don’t know what to do.
What is it?
Hiro’s the pilot.
There was a last-minute change.
We’re also staying in the same
hotel with the flight crew.
What if we bump into Hiro?
Maybe I should just change
hotels, just to be safe?
We can do that. But really, Yanna.
What if you just
tell Hiro about Avi?
I think that’s the easier option.
Maybe this is the right timing
you’ve been waiting for.
- Avi would love that.
- Hey!
- Jeez.
- I'll buy these for her,
what else?
That’s too much candy.
No, It's okay.
I want chocolate.
That might be too much.
No, it’s fine.
I like your hair clip.
Thank you!
My daddy gave it to me.
Are you a pilot?
Yes…
My daddy is a pilot, too.
Avi, let’s go to our hotel.
Let’s put the other clip.
Wow! You look so pretty.
Thank you!
I’ll go out for a while.
Are we going to ride
the carousel now?
Let’s see.
Hi, my love.
Daddy, look at my outfit.
You look so pretty, my love.
Are you excited?
I’m excited to explore
Japan with you.
Wow! Let’s go?
- Bye, Auntie!
- Bye, have fun.
Bye. Thank you.
Hey, Raylee. I’m already
at Boteyju Shibuya.
Are you on your way?
We’re heading back to the hotel
from the amusement park!
Want to join us for dinner?
Let’s meet in Shinjuku!
I’ll pass for now.
I’m meeting Raylee here in
Shibuya. But enjoy, you guys!
It’s so nice to
see you all together!
We’ll catch up when
we get back to the hotel.
But seriously, Sam, this might
be the happiest day of my life.
Also, I’m sorry!
It should be you, me,
and Avi’s bonding time,
but Hiro butted in.
Don’t worry about me.
Just enjoy this trip. Enjoy your dinner!
Well, this is bittersweet.
I’m happy they’re finally a family.
But I kinda feel sad because
I know I don’t need to
take care of Avi anymore.
I’m solo again.
Hey, Sam, sorry!
I can’t make it to our dinner.
I had to head back
to the Philippines.
My niece got into an accident.
Oh no. I hope she’s okay!
Let’s just meet up in Manila instead.
Take care, Raylee!
Thank you.
Please enjoy your food.
Yes, thank you.
Can I join you?
Haze!
Sure, go ahead.
I never thought I’d see you here.
Same with you, Sam.
Small world.
Your date didn’t show up?
I was supposed to meet a friend.
What about you?
You got stood up too?
Unfortunately, yes—
by the businessman
I was about to meet.
But well,
I’m glad you’re alone too.
Mind if we have dinner together?
Well, you’re already
sitting there,
what else can I do?
You know what?
Hiro’s here, by the way.
Yeah, I know.
I’m sure he’s having
a lot of fun right now.
You’re still a heavy drinker,
Samantha Vera.
But, I don’t get drunk easily.
You seem a little tipsy to me.
I’m not.
All right,
if you say so.
Haze,
have you ever fallen in love?
That’s so out of nowhere
but sure, I’ll answer it.
Of course, I have.
You?
Of course.
I fell madly and deeply
in love with this person.
He’s an amazing guy, you know?
We even lived together
and promised to
marry each other, but—
I just left him.
When we saw each other again,
everything just changed.
What changed?
The way he looks at me
and talks to me.
He’s kind of cold
and grumpy now.
It hurts, you know?
Maybe,
I’m just expecting
something more.
Well,
you left him.
You can’t just expect him to
treat you the same way.
Love fades, Sam.
Why are you smiling?
You’re happy while
I’m miserable? Huh?
Huh?
Told you, you’re drunk.
I’m not drunk.
Where’s your hotel, Sam?
My… My wha—
Are you okay?
I thought you didn’t
get drunk easily?
What the fuck is this?
Haze, don’t you have a girlfriend?
No, I don’t.
Why? Are you applying?
Are you sure you’re okay?
Yeah. I’m okay.
Cheers?
Samantha Vera spotted having
a date with a guy in Japan?
OMG! Is that Sam’s baby daddy?
Even from the back,
he looks yummy!
Sam’s love life is so messy!
Why doesn’t she just
announce it already?
Thank god, Haze’s
face isn’t showing!
Are you back in Manila?
Are you free to meet today?
Thanks for meeting me here.
This is just the nearest place
to Ramirez Medical.
My niece is confined there,
and I’m the only one
watching over her.
Are you okay? Are you hiding
from something?
I fucking knew it.
Of course, I’ll see him here.
One large strawberry
milkshake, please.
Anything else, ma’am?
Make it two.
- Okay, two please.
- Okay.
- Let’s wait for our drinks.
- Yeah.
Do you have a headache?
How’s residency going?
I’m doing okay.
I’m actually learning a lot.
Well, kids are not
the easiest patients, but
I love taking care of them.
Looks like it.
Actually, I heard you’re the
favorite of the patients
in the pedia ward.
Yeah. It’s true!
Wait, so remind me,
why did you decide to go into pedia?
I really thought you
were going for surgery.
Yeah, I did. But
I realized it would take too long.
And I want to get married
before fellowship starts.
Marry? Who?
With Eva?
Looks like
they got closer, huh?
They even drink
shakes together now.
What’s with the long face?
You okay?
Not really. I just received
a message from my assistant and,
I need to head to
our agency right now.
No problem, I need to get back
to my niece anyway.
Oh, wait, do you want me
to drop you off at the hospital?
I brought a car.
No need, no need.
You’ll have to go around.
I mean, the hospital’s just
walking distance from here.
and I need to
get my steps in. So—
- Sure?
- Yeah, I’m totally sure.
Okay, I need to go.
- Take care.
- Yeah. You too.
I’ll see you soon.
Guys, look here.
Look at the camera.
- Let’s do an unboxing.
- What’s that?
Hey! It’s Samantha Vera.
- You’re right!
- Yeah!
Isn’t she trending right now?
- Right
- Right!
Hey, Sam!
Are you with your
boyfriend in Japan?
I have nothing to say.
- Can I have a picture?
- Please!
I’m sorry.
- Your baby is so cute.
- Come on.
I saw your picture
with her at the park.
Is he the father of your child?
- It’s just for our content.
- For engagement, come on.
Please?
What’s your
boyfriend’s name, Sam?
Just a picture, Sam.
- Come on.
- Sam.
- I have to go, I’m sorry.
- Just one.
Just one, just one.
- Let’s just take a photo.
- Come on.
- Just a video, okay?
- Just a photo.
- Just for our content.
- Just a video.
Just for engagement
with the fans, okay?
- Take a video.
- Hurry up. Here.
- All right.
- Come on.
Let her go.
- Who are you?
We just want to take a photo with her.
We just wanted to take a picture.
Just one picture.
Come on, just one photo.
Sir, this is Samantha Vera—
We just want to take a picture.
That’s not allowed here.
Just one photo.
I said that’s enough.
So stingy!
Thank you for saving me earlier.
I think I can take it from here.
I’ll go ahead.
Sam, you need to rest.
I’m feeling even worse
because of the heat.
The topic about the guy
you were with in Japan
is seriously heating up.
He’s Fly Asia’s CEO.
Did you bring a companion?
To watch you?
It’s just me.
My card holder is missing.
Sorry to bother you but—
Have you seen a card holder?
Sam?