( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(Lee Na Young)
(Jung Eun Chae)
(Lee Chung Ah)
(Honour)
(Supported by the Culture Ministry and Korea's Creative Content Agency)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
What's your real reason for approaching me?
It was you, wasn't it?
You're the one who tried to kill my husband 20 years ago.
It was a mistake.
I should have finished him off back then.
Well, that's an interesting way to confess.
If Park Je Yeol had died back then,
you wouldn't be going through this either.
You filed a sexual assault report, didn't you?
Ten months before your child's birth.
Shut it.
But the report was withdrawn, and Park Je Yeol got what he wanted.
Right.
You should have just killed him back then.
You don't know anything.
You don't know what he's like, or what I go through to survive.
You think I haven't tried anything all this time?
I did. I tried everything I could,
but I failed.
I'll get you out of there.
I said I'd help you. That was our deal, wasn't it?
- If a lawyer was all it took... - Here.
This is your key out of your fiery pit.
(Episode 6)
Don't get up. Stay right there.
Wait.
- Honey. - Yes?
I'm not an invalid, you know.
Right.
I was just worried the smell would make you feel sick.
So, should we order something?
Sure. Order whatever you're craving.
Here you go.
Let me see.
Honey, by the way, how's that new case you're on going?
You know, the reinvestigation.
- Hyun Jin. - Yes?
It's nothing. Let me clear this away.
Just rest until the food arrives.
- I'm seriously ordering everything. - Go ahead, order it all.
Everyone does it like this.
- No, it's definitely him. - No, it's not. Look closer.
Mom, Dad's driving me crazy.
No matter how many times I tell him, he can't tell Minje and Keiju apart!
- Is that the one with orange hair? - Gosh, you're seriously hopeless.
Did you have dinner?
She already ate with me. You're late.
Yes. Work ran late.
Just plug it into Park Je Yeol's phone.
And you can make him disappear from your life for good.
Mom.
- Yes? - I said I want some fruit.
What's with you? Did you run into someone?
It's nothing. Wait, I'll get you a mango.
- Dad, this is the last time. - Okay, I got it.
- I'll explain again. Watch. - Okay.
Hey, Shin Jae.
How did it go?
I said what I had to say.
As long as Hong Yeon Hui does her part,
we can be the ones to take down Park Je Yeol.
Proof that the Connect app exists. On top of that,
if we have proof of Park Je Yeol's involvement,
we can blow this whole thing wide open.
You'll add the abuse charge and not give him any room to breathe?
Only if Ms. Hong Yeon Hui agrees to it.
You think Attorney Kwon will just sit back and let this happen?
Don't worry. I won't let him hold us back.
Did you eat dinner?
Just grabbed a bite on my way in. Are you calling about work?
No. I just called because I wanted to hear your voice.
What's gotten into you?
I'm happy we're going to be aunts,
but I was worried you might be lonely at night.
Get some sleep.
I've been thinking.
I think it's best if I just go to work.
If you're at the office, you'll keep running into Attorney Kwon.
And he might recognise you.
It didn't seem like he recognised me last time.
And I enjoyed it. Working at your office, I mean.
It may not be a big deal to others, but it was a first for me.
Working in an office.
If that's what you want, Min Seo, let's do that.
Min Seo, wait a second.
Here, I saw this and thought of you.
(Chocolate milk)
What are you doing up? Aren't you sleeping?
I was just about to.
- You look tired. Go to bed. - Okay.
- Sang A. - Yes?
Never mind. Good night.
(That livestream just now...)
(You saw it? So cute.)
(So...)
(how was your day?)
(I want to die.)
(Senior Prosecutor Park Je Yeol)
(Senior Prosecutor's Office, Senior Prosecutor Park Je Yeol)
Any breakthroughs after just one day?
Take this case back.
That's disappointing.
Aren't you waving the white flag a bit too soon?
I'm already overloaded with my current cases.
Or is it because you're scared?
Scared this might be Pandora's box.
Do you think Hyun Jin was the one who did that to you?
I gave you the case so you could find that out.
You were the one who sent me the newspaper article too, right?
Why did you drag me into this in the first place?
Do you want to catch the culprit, or do you want to hurt Hyun Jin?
What if it's both?
This was your doing, wasn't it?
Listen to me very carefully.
If anything like this ever happens to Hyun Jin again,
I really won't let it slide.
Detective Gu Seon Kyu.
You do realise, don't you?
That you just covered up an attempted murder.
You're not the only detective in the world, are you?
I wonder.
When it's proven that I was right,
what you'll do then.
If that happens,
I'll give up my badge myself.
This is amazing!
I can't. It's so beautiful.
It's adorable.
I didn't know if it would be a boy or girl, so I chose yellow.
I wanted to be first to get a gift for my future niece or nephew.
Thank you.
I bet Seon Kyu is thrilled, right?
Actually, we're both still in a bit of a daze.
Maybe it'll start to feel real after our hospital appointment.
Hope it goes well. See that Seon Kyu treats you to something delicious.
I will. But this is seriously so cute.
Where are the paper cups?
The cups...
Here you go.
Thank you.
I don't think I've seen you around here before.
- I just started recently. - Is that right?
Keep up the good work.
I was the one who hired Han Min Seo.
How can you fire her without any reason?
Her resume has only one line on it. High school dropout.
Do we need to screen for education for a simple part-time job?
Is there a reason we shouldn't?
Or what? Is there some other reason I can't?
I'm in charge here now. An employee with her bad history.
I've never kept someone like that on my staff.
Is that so? This is a first for me too.
Working for a man who solicits prostitutes.
(Haeil Law Firm)
Are you heading home? I'll give you a ride.
Let her. She wants to.
Yes, ma'am.
Read this on the way.
It's a sex trafficking scandal involving high-profile figures.
And there are minors among the exploited victims.
There's circumstantial evidence linking it to at least two murders.
Now you're playing detective?
So?
What's your point? Are you asking for a bigger budget?
Attorney Kwon is involved. As a client.
What are you going to do?
Who else knows about this case?
Right now, only the three of us know.
Then bury it.
That's an order.
If what you say is true, more clients might be involved,
and if this gets to the authorities, our stance is clear.
We will stand by our clients.
So Attorney Kwon won't have to worry, will he?
This won't pose any risk at all.
As expected, your scales of justice have never...
tipped in favour of those without money and power.
That's my definition of justice. The winning side.
Still, I was hoping...
that you'd get rid of Attorney Kwon.
That you'd side with what's right, not what's powerful.
Just like the vain hopes you always have for me.
It's all so futile and pointless.
I'm done.
My kind of justice has no place at Haeil, Mom.
I'm getting out here.
This is Kang Shin Jae.
We need to meet today.
You can hear that, right? That's the baby's heartbeat.
It looks like you're about eight weeks along.
Eight weeks?
But I had my period during that time.
That's a common mistake for first-time mothers.
It was most likely implantation bleeding.
Excuse me, Doctor.
Heroin?
Yes. At eight weeks, she was already pregnant.
- Will the baby be okay? - I can't be sure it had no effect.
To be frank,
in a normal case, the risk would be so high...
that I would've advised you to consider your options.
But the baby is growing well for its gestational age.
Let's just keep a close watch for now.
I'll be sure to keep a close eye on it.
This baby really is a miracle.
- A miracle? - The hysterosalpingogram was fine,
but your test results, sir,
showed under 1 percent normal morphology.
Your sperm count and motility were also extremely low.
What does that mean?
Statistically, with these numbers, natural conception is impossible.
I was going to recommend IVF, but thankfully...
Wait a second.
Did you just say natural conception was impossible?
But then how...
That's just from a statistical standpoint.
It's rare, but miracles like this do happen.
You had a nice chat with my wife?
To think I wouldn't know whatever you're planning...
is just so arrogant.
Then again, some things never change.
That's your charm, isn't it, Yoon Ra Young?
It makes it all the more thrilling...
when I finally get to break you.
I'm so glad you got your memory back.
If you never remembered, I would've felt so wronged.
Don't you want to know? Who made this app,
and who else was involved.
Go public with it.
Tell them you tried to kill someone.
And for 20 years, you kept silent pretending to be a man of justice.
Confess to the world you're ready to pay for your sins.
Beg before me.
Then I'll tell you.
About Connect.
Everything you want to know.
If you can't, then stop. Right now.
Who knows?
Maybe I'll even forgive you.
Really?
But what a shame.
Because there's no way I'll ever forgive you.
The one who hasn't fully paid for their sins...
is you.
Sorry, I have to get back inside.
- Okay. - See you later.
This is driving me crazy.
This is absolutely insane.
Hello, this is Hwang Hyun Jin.
Isn't this Lee Jun Hyeok's phone?
Excuse me?
- Who? - Lee Jun Hyeok.
That's what it says here.
What does that...
A laptop?
(Computers and Laptops)
But how did you get my number?
If you can't reach me, please call this number instead.
I'll give you the files.
I've changed my mind. Be at my place by 8pm.
(Victim Testimonies, Research, Evidence, Tips)
(Tips)
It's ransomware.
This isn't like a regular virus. Without the key, it's unrecoverable.
Is there no way to fix it? These files are really important,
and this is all I have left.
Please, do everything you can.
Yes, I'll see what I can do.
(Lee Jun Hyeok)
- Did you recover the files? - I couldn't recover everything.
I salvaged some of your files from a restore point.
That's why I called.
It's Yoon Ra Young.
I'm at the park outside your place. Can you come out for a minute?
Park Je Yeol found out that we met.
- Excuse me. - Mom's taking a shower.
Then the message...
Did you send it?
- I'm a friend of your mom's. - I know who you are.
I saw you on TV.
Do you want to help my mom?
Yes.
Then don't contact her again.
And don't come here either.
- Wait, just let me explain... - Are you ready to be responsible?
How? How far are you willing to go?
("Aspiring IT Majors Triple")
("And Behind It All Was Baek Tae Joo of The Prime")
Sorry, the meeting ran a little late.
Want to go out? We still can.
I doubt we could find a better view than this anywhere else.
In that case, how about a drink here?
- Wine? Or whiskey? - Let's go with whiskey.
So what's on the agenda for today? An honest conversation.
Maybe the start of a friendship. I'd like that.
My mother put a noose around my neck,
but I'm going to use it as a lifeline.
That's honest.
I like it.
What kind of lifeline can I be for you, then?
I'm not going to inherit Haeil.
- Are you okay with that? - With pleasure. As you wish.
I want to make LnJ independent.
I want it to be a non-profit foundation.
And I'm guessing I won't have a say in the foundation's direction?
That's the point.
I've laid all my cards on the table.
Now it's your turn.
What do you want?
I want you to stay true to your path as an attorney.
As impressively as you do now.
If you do, Haeil's age will soon come to an end in this country.
Haeil is a legacy code that should've been removed long ago.
No matter how much I try to build a new system,
as long as this corrupt code exists, it will just keep causing conflicts.
And you know the evils of Haeil better than I do.
So what is it you really want to do?
I want to overhaul the system. Wipe out all the malicious code,
install a new, transparent, and fair OS,
and apply an algorithm that gives everyone the same rules.
That's the kind of new system I want to create.
Why?
Attorney, why do you defend victims instead of perpetrators?
- Because it's the right thing to do - So do I.
Because I believe this is the right thing to do.
It's funny, isn't it?
When people want more money or more power,
no one asks them why.
But why do we need a reason to make the world a better place?
You and I want the same thing, don't we?
That's why you've kept refusing to inherit Haeil.
It seems we're ultimately headed to the same destination.
From the very beginning,
did you expect things to turn out this way?
I did think we were a lot alike.
All right.
It looks like we're in the same boat now.
Here's to a smooth engagement.
Goodness. What's gotten into you? I thought you never drank.
- You made it. - Hey.
- Could I get a glass too? - Sure.
So, is this to celebrate becoming a dad?
Yes. It's pure bliss, right?
It was.
Now, it's a nightmare.
Look at you. Did you fight with your wife?
That's how they are when pregnant. They get all sensitive.
- Here, buy your wife a tasty treat. - No, come on. It's fine.
- No, just take it. - Come on, man. You can't afford it.
You idiot. Who said this was for you?
This is for my future niece or nephew.
Thanks.
This guy...
So what'd they say at the hospital?
Everything's okay, right?
Yes.
Gosh. It's Team Leader Jang. Hold on.
(Team Leader Jang)
Yes. Got it. Okay, bye.
Seung Jin.
- Yes? - So what did the team leader say?
What else? The usual nagging, on and on.
We're out of booze. Ma'am, another soju, please.
Okay.
You haven't touched the food. What gives?
How delicious.
Han Min Seo!
I know you're in there! Come out! Han Min Seo!
Darn it, open the door!
Excuse me.
What's with all the racket?
What's it to you? Am I banging on your door?
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
That's a warm welcome.
Who do you think you are, just barging in?
Nice place.
- Why are you here? - You kept calling and texting.
You were the one making a scene, weren't you?
- What's in here? - Where do you think you're going?
Unbelievable.
This is practically a showroom, isn't it?
So pretty.
The attorney is arriving any minute. Get out.
What's this?
What's so valuable in here that she had to hide it like this?
Give it to me.
You seem to have the wrong idea.
You think living the high life erases who you are?
Don't make me laugh.
What are you looking at?
Have you forgotten I took you in when you had nowhere to go?
What do you think you're doing?
What business is it of yours?
We're just having a private conversation.
A conversation? Is this how you talk to people?
Get out of my house! Right now!
We're not finished talking yet.
Why? Wasn't selling her out to stay out of jail enough?
Fine. I sold her out to Connect. So what?
Who fed and clothed her when she ran away and had nothing?
What's so wrong with getting paid for it?
Nothing in life is free. Is that too much to ask?
You were my mom.
But you were still...
my mom.
You're crazy.
That little family role-play thing...
Did you really think that was real?
See? This is what I'm talking about.
She can't even tell the difference between a game and reality.
You should be careful too, lady.
Once you take her in out of pity, she'll never leave.
- Get out of here right now! - All right. I'm leaving.
If you pay me more?
Since you're meddling with Connect, I'm too scared to even work.
- So you must take responsibility. - Lee Seon Hwa!
What's this?
- Are you kidding me? - It's for your cab fare.
Come to my office tomorrow.
And if I do?
How much are you going to give me?
We can discuss a reduced sentence when this all goes down.
You're smart enough to get the picture, right?
What you need right now isn't money. It's an attorney.
Or would you rather I call the cops on you?
You won't get a suspended sentence this time.
I'm so sorry.
She barged in so suddenly, I couldn't stop her.
I know it's not your fault, Min Seo. I'll take care of this.
Yes.
- Hi! How have you been? - Oh, my goodness. Hi, Seung Jin.
Gosh! Seon Kyu, we're home.
Shoes off. All right!
Hey, no, you stay put. You shouldn't be straining yourself.
Gosh.
- Just how much did he drink? - Sorry?
Let's see. He drank enough for five years.
Cut him some slack for tonight. He's just excited to be a dad.
Could I get a glass of water?
Sure.
(Lee Jun Hyeok)
Gosh, nice place.
Thanks.
That's much better.
Thank you so much for bringing him all the way home, Seung Jin.
It was nothing.
Hey, listen.
You really need to be careful now.
- I'm sorry? - Look, I know you're tough,
but you need to look after yourself and think about the baby.
Right?
Gosh.
Just me being nosy.
Just worried.
I'll get going.
- Thank you again. - Right. Get some rest.
- Get home safe. - Sure.
- Time to go. Bye. - Good night.
Honey.
Let's get you to bed.
Mom, what are you doing?
You're still awake?
Sang A.
Mom,
don't do anything.
Do you want to help my mom?
Then don't contact her again. And don't come here either.
Attorney Yoon?
I can't sleep, so I was wondering if I could sleep here?
Why did you just let her do that?
She was in the wrong, not you.
But she was my mom.
It was the first time for me.
It may have just been a game between us,
but at least when I called her "Mom," she'd smile and answer me.
Even when she hit me and cursed me out,
she would turn right around and call me her daughter again.
But I guess I was the only one who was happy...
even if it was just a game.
Did you ever have a child?
No, never.
You're still up?
How long have you been sitting there like that?
I'm sorry.
You know what this is, right?
Does this belong to the victim?
We'll have to run some tests.
- I have something to tell you. - Stop it.
I'm not going to ask,
and I'm not going to listen.
I don't want to know what happened,
or what you're planning to do.
Don't say a single word.
I'll figure this out and make my own decision.
I have the right to ask for that much...
don't I?
Honey.
I think we need some space for now.
I'll stay at the office for the time being.
Take care of yourself.
(Seoul Mujin District Prosecutors' Office)
(Jo Yoo Jeong's Testimony and Interview)
It was after I was investigated by the prosecution for theft.
Someone approached me.
He said it was an easy job.
He promised I'd make money and also avoid punishment.
He installed that app on my phone.
The Connect In app.
Who was he?
I don't know his name.
But I found out later.
He was a cop.
Look at her face.
She says she was sexually assaulted. By a celebrity.
Where and how did you meet him?
Yoo Jeong.
Do you get it now?
There's no escaping Connect.
It's not just Park Je Yeol. The police are involved too.
And I'm sure that's not all.
So what's higher up the chain?
If only they'd recovered all the files...
The recovery failed, except for a few audio files...
and another one of Jun Hyeok's articles.
Still, we have proof Park Je Yeol and the police are involved.
It'll also help us prove why Reporter Lee was murdered.
Lee Seon Hwa agreed to come in.
- Lee Seon Hwa? - Park Je Yeol's Connect In deals.
We need to get her testimony on that.
Hello.
(Woo Seok, Shin Hankuk Daily)
We didn't receive a request, and I have a prior engagement today.
If this is for an interview, please call to make an appointment.
You might regret that.
Are you sure? We'll run it without your comment.
The attorney is in a meeting right now...
It's just that I got a very interesting tip.
Attempted murder of a male student at Hankuk University College of Law.
What's going on? Am I supposed to leave?
Go wait in that room.
- Let's talk inside. - Hyun Jin.
It's Lee Seon Hwa.
This way, please.
What is this place?
What is this, a secret hideout or something?
Have a seat anywhere.
What's this about? What do you want from me?
You know Prosecutor Park Je Yeol, right?
Maybe I do, maybe I don't.
You're the one who gave Min Seo to Connect through Park Je Yeol.
What did Park Je Yeol demand from you?
Did the police come to you too?
What is this, an interrogation?
If you don't tell me the truth, you'll be the one in trouble.
I've been thinking,
Whatever happens later, right now, I need to put food on the table.
You're not doing this to help me, are you?
The information you want from me. How much is it worth to you?
- Excuse me? - I require payment upfront.
How much are you offering?
Just wait here for a second.
What is it that you want to know?
Here's the kind of headline I have in mind.
Lawyers at a firm known for championing the underdog...
exposed as attempted murderers from their college days.
Now, what if those lawyers were the heir to Haeil,
a controversial celebrity lawyer, and the wife of a police detective?
Don't you think that'd get a ton of clicks?
So let me guess. Your source is Prosecutor Park Je Yeol.
I can't reveal my sources. That's Journalism 101.
You do realise we're lawyers, right?
We won't stand for this kind of baseless slander.
Go ahead. Write your article.
But...
if you're a real reporter, wouldn't you be curious?
Assuming your source is correct,
what could drive three young women to attack a male student?
What could have possibly happened?
I bet Prosecutor Park Je Yeol didn't include that part in his tip.
So you're saying there was a crucial motive?
I'll give you the full exclusive. But on one condition.
I need time.
How long?
Until another story breaks first.
A reporter's death framed as a sexual assault.
And behind it, a digital sex ring with police and prosecutor ties.
So? Are you interested?
Don't tell me you're talking about the reporter Lee Jun Hyeok case.
I have evidence the authorities never even got their hands on.
Don't you want to break it? As an exclusive?
Is this solid?
Hold all your stories until we're ready.
That's my condition.
Are you sure about this? Laying it all out like that?
We need to buy time until Hyun Jin is stable.
Besides, I was planning to strike first anyway.
Right.
You might be right. Targeting the media first is best.
And we have no idea how entangled the authorities are with Connect.
Feeling sick again?
Gosh, this is killing me.
Who was here?
A reporter. We'll tell you everything later.
What about Lee Seon Hwa? Wasn't she here?
The laptop...
Jun Hyeok's laptop is gone.
Ye Ji, have you seen Lee Seon Hwa?
She left a little while ago. She said she'd come back later.
- The number called is unavailable. - Any luck?
Please leave a message at the tone...
She's not picking up.
(Mad Dog Detective)
What? What do you want me to get you?
The laptop.
The LnJ lawyers have it right now.
What are you paying?
Thirty grand?
Deal.
(Mad Dog Detective)
Mission accomplished.
Funny thing. That laptop's price just went up.
Thirty grand isn't going to cut it.
- Fifty grand. - Fine. Just stay put.
Darn it.
Go get it. I don't care how.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Prosecutor Park. Right, it's Chief Park now.
This is the Prosecutor General. You know, right?
It's an honour to meet you, sir.
Come on, have a seat. Sit down.
I arranged this because I was eager to finally meet you, Chief Park.
I must say, your profile is quite impressive.
A law school graduate.
Your training institute scores, your performance reviews...
are nothing to write home about. And going back for generations,
there's not a single notable name. A classic rags-to-riches story.
A guy who should have stayed local and quietly finished his career...
suddenly gets on the fast track to Seoul.
Then you're running reds, speeding, and cutting people off.
That's not how it works. You can't just floor the gas pedal.
Chief Park!
How exactly do you know the Minister?
I suppose he sees me as a useful workhorse.
And I'm grateful for it.
Allow me to pour you a drink.
I will do my utmost.
Prosecutor General, shall we start the night for real? What do you say?
(LnJ attorney)
So this is how she stabs me in the back.
First, Ra Young, I need you to ask Han Min Seo about Lee Seon Hwa.
Anywhere she went, anything you can find.
I'll track Do Jun and Lee Seon Hwa's movements.
- Hey, where are you? - Almost there. Five grand, right?
Yes, that's right.
The number called is unavailable. Leave a message at the tone.
Excuse me.
(Han Min Seo)
Green hoodie?
Min Seo, I'm here.
Min Seo?
Yes, Attorney.
Can you come out for a second? I have a few questions for you.
- Min Seo. - I'll be right out.
(Honour)
But inside, she was hiding ulterior motives.
Who are you, really?
Watch out.
It's a shame our promise wasn't properly kept.
Find them. By any means necessary.
Why are you going to such lengths to hide this?
There's someone on the inside. In the police force.
Yoon Ra Young told me to clone your phone.
What do you want me to do?
The victim is here right now.
Park Je Yeol killed her. Now do you see why we need that USB?