♪ I drift across the boundless skies ♪
♪ Through deserts where no one goes ♪
♪ Seeking myself ♪
♪ The self I long to find ♪
♪ Lost in a maze of lies ♪
♪ I break into your sea of clouds ♪
♪ It traps me ♪
♪ It redeems me ♪
♪ Which hue of the sky is your love? ♪
♪ Or is it the burning flame ♪
♪ Found only in storms? ♪
♪ You are the mark engraved upon my heart ♪
♪ From then on all my
memories tremble for you ♪
♪ What I cannot forget
is that fleeting gaze ♪
♪ What I cannot escape
is passion born in chaos ♪
♪ How I long to hold you again ♪
♪ Our love, high among the clouds ♪
♪ Is sealed with that kiss ♪
[Love in The Clouds]
[Adapted from Bai Lu Cheng
Shuang's "Love in The Clouds"]
Look at those slender and fair fingers.
That's why she plays well.
How lovely.
Do you know anything about music?
Not at all, but I can see
how beautiful she plays.
Just look at her.
Those delicate hands of hers.
That's truly brilliant.
Well, she's just stolen a glance at me.
You're certainly a skilled qin player.
Immortal Lin has sent us an invitation,
and he'd like to watch you play.
He's the key to my power grab.
You should know what to do, no?
Qibai.
I...
Are you refusing to share my burden?
Naturally, I'll help you with that.
I'm glad to hear that.
Go ahead, then.
Did you know?
Xinliu died trying to save you.
Please grant me death.
What's the use of taking your life?
Xinliu is gone.
Would killing you bring her back to life?
Xun Ming.
Bear this in mind.
This wretched life of
yours doesn't belong to you.
It belongs to Xinliu
and the Mu clan!
For the rest of your
life, all you need to do
is turn netherbeasts into an army.
Otherwise, Xinliu's death would be in vain!
[Episode 10]
[Luosheng Forest, Hanxing Mountain]
♪ Maybe I'm just your firefly ♪
♪ That's why I'm so fragile ♪
♪ In this world, there's too much ♪
♪ Cause and effect of
love and hate surging ♪
♪ Would you be willing to stay for me? ♪
♪ If your world ♪
♪ Was once an endless wasteland ♪
♪ I'd tear myself apart ♪
♪ To fill the wounds inside you ♪
♪ Even if this life is like a shooting star ♪
♪ Brief only for the sake of meeting you ♪
♪ In this fleeting life ♪
♪ I'll still be your light ♪
What a beautiful day.
It is.
The auspicious hour is approaching.
Since we've made this spot the venue,
Xun Ming will come, no?
He will.
He knows this wedding is for him.
Foxes are curious in nature.
Even at the cost of his life,
he will want to know
what trap we've got him.
We shall play it by ear.
Open his Illusory Realm
and Zhang Tai will be saved.
Why does that sound like a crowd?
- Immortal Ji!
That's great!
Congratulations, Immortal Ji!
- Congratulations!
Congratulations!
Immortal Ji!
Congratulations! Congratulations!
Congratulations, Immortal Ji!
Immortal Ji!
It's your big day!
It's your wedding day!
Immortal Ji.
That was unfair of you.
How could you keep your wedding from us?
Exactly.
Your wedding day has been a quiet one.
I only see a few tables here.
And look at this fox hole-like decoration.
Luckily, we found out about this soon.
That's why we managed
to make it here in no time
and liven things up for you.
How did you all figure it out?
Don't worry about it.
Come on!
Congratulations!
Immortal Ji!
Both of you are getting married?
At first, I didn't believe it.
Now I can see that it's true.
You even lied to us
and promised to spend
the rest of your life with us.
In the end, you're marrying Ming Yi.
- Indeed.
- I know, right?
It's fine if you're marrying her.
Yet you should've
informed us of this wedding.
That's right.
Exactly.
Why didn't you tell us about it?
That's it.
Anyway, we wish you a
lifetime of happiness together.
Here are your gifts.
- This is from me.
- And this is from me.
Thank you.
Why did you keep this from me, Immortal Ji?
Why are you here?
Ming Yi, why are you suddenly
having this wedding with Immortal Ji?
Have you figured out a
way to save Zhang Tai?
You've always been close to Zhang Tai.
I bet you won't stand
by and do nothing, right?
Or.
This is part of your plan?
Rest assured, I've planned it all out.
Well...
How did you find out about our wedding?
Hold on, everyone.
I've indeed made a mistake
by not telling you all about it.
But I have a question.
How did you find out
about my wedding with Ming Yi?
Well, I informed them of it.
Immortal Meng?
Immortal Ji, Fairy Ming Yi.
Seriously, that wasn't fair of you.
No matter how hasty your wedding has been,
you should've sent
each of us an invitation.
Indeed!
Good thing I've got my sources.
I visited everyone here
and told them about it.
If not,
your wedding would be a quiet one.
But how did you find out about it?
Of course I learned that from Lord Hanfeng.
Here's my wedding gift for you.
I thought
I couldn't keep
such good news from others.
Thus, I shared it with everyone at once.
Right, Yan Xiao?
Immortal Meng.
We appreciate your thoughtfulness.
However, due to how
urgent things have been,
we decided not to have a grand wedding.
We never thought
I can see that.
There are only a few banquet tables here.
I understand that you'd
like to keep a low profile.
Yet a wedding
is no small matter.
- Wait here.
- Yes, it should not be taken lightly.
I'll get you more tables.
Never mind.
Don't stand on ceremony.
I'm serious.
I was born into a family of wine immortals,
so I'm very good at this.
Just wait here.
Princess Tianji has arrived.
Tianji is here?
Greetings, Your Highness.
Both of you, come with me.
Leave these to me.
If it hadn't been for
Immortal Meng's heads-up,
I wouldn't have known
about the warrior of Jixing
Abyss getting married today.
I don't think
I need your permission to get married.
Father is bedridden.
Naturally, nobody takes me seriously.
But don't you forget this.
If I could make you who you are,
I can make you fall from grace too.
Many
covet the legendary Golden Millet Dream.
However,
since you're the one who turned
the Jixing Abyss into an Upper Realm,
they wouldn't dare to make a move.
If I were to tell the Outer Realm
that you've been cast
out of the Jixing Abyss,
do you think
the other five realms would denounce you?
Give it a try, then.
Well,
I guess I've figured it out.
Your Highness.
You don't love Lord Ji at all.
You just need him.
With His Majesty being bedridden,
no one in the palace cares about you.
However,
a marriage alliance is not the
best option for forming an alliance.
Profits are.
Lord Ji.
As a warrior,
you've certainly had your slice of cake.
And it's true that you have your backer
here in the Jixing Abyss.
Since we've gotten what we wanted,
and we need one another,
why don't we all take a step back?
How wise of you, darling.
This wedding
must go on.
Since we're on the same boat,
Your Highness,
why don't you name your condition?
Don't make things awkward between us.
Since you insist on marrying Fairy Ming Yi,
I'm fine with that.
You can have a wedding as you like.
Yet here's my decree.
The warrior, Ji Bozai,
must not form a heart imprint with another,
nor share his divine consciousness.
That is to make sure
the next Qingyun Tournament
proceeds smoothly.
Your Highness, here's the thing.
- The heart imprint...
- Sure.
We'll each make some concessions.
Say thank you to Princess Tianji.
Well... Thank you...
Deal.
Xiuyun.
Present the gift to Immortal Ji.
May you have a wonderful wedding.
I'm not joining it.
Are you happy now?
Officail Website : kissasian.be
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Let's go.
Come on, check these out.
Fairy.
Take a look at these outfits.
They come in all kinds of models.
Have a look at this.
It really suits you perfectly.
I'm sure Ming Yi will love it.
You must be the new Chief of Judgment Hall,
Immortal Situ.
Are these the presents
for Immortal Ji and his wife?
Immortal Ji and his wife?
Didn't you know?
Today, Immortal Ji is marrying
the fairy he found at Moonlit Blossoms.
Having seen all these
purchases you've made,
I thought you'd like to buy more.
Are you telling the truth?
Where is their wedding?
I guess it's true.
I learned that from someone.
The wedding
is in the Luosheng Forest.
Immortal Situ.
You're not buying it?
Now that everyone's found out about it,
how do we put an end to it?
Of course
we shall make the most out of it.
Darling.
Here comes the auspicious hour.
Look at that.
What a lovely flower!
You're right.
This is such a unique wedding aisle.
As expected of Immortal Ji.
This wedding is unlike those I've seen.
No doubt it is.
How beautiful!
It's my first time
hearing this processional.
Indeed.
Check that out.
So lovely.
They're a match made in heaven.
How grand this has been.
A beauty in such a gorgeous setting.
I envy him.
And that nice aroma.
Indeed.
Look.
Their encounter has been a fated one.
May the newlyweds forever find one another.
In the face of endless change, their
feelings for each other remain unshaken.
May the newlyweds live
in harmony and happiness.
- Great!
- Nice!
They make a perfect match.
- That's great!
- Amazing!
Congratulations!
Have a lifetime of happiness together.
May you love each other
till the end of your days.
Thank you for your presence here.
This place means a lot
to me and Ming Yi.
However, it's a rural area
lacking hospitality.
Why don't we make a move to
Moonlit Blossoms for the banquet?
Moonlit Blossoms?
Sure!
This looks fine to me.
I haven't had enough fun here.
Congratulations on your wedding, Ji.
We shall make our way
to Moonlit Blossoms now.
I haven't had a drink.
Immortal Ji, are you paying
for what we're having at Moonlit Blossoms?
It's far from here.
How do we travel there?
- Indeed.
- You're right.
Since it'll be a long journey,
of course we don't
expect you to walk there.
We'll see to that.
Follow me.
- Come, let's go.
- Let's go.
- Here.
Come on.
Let's join the rest.
Together.
Come on.
Why isn't he responding to all this?
Could it be his most cherished memories
have nothing to do with
his wedding with Xinliu?
Today is the best time.
We have to save Zhang Tai no matter what.
We can't let them get away with it.
Let's go.
Hold on.
I didn't expect your presence
here, General Xun Ming.
Why don't you join me and Ming Yi
for a boat ride there?
You sure know how to amuse yourself.
You chose this spot
to have your wedding according
to the Yousu Fox Tribe's rites.
And now you're trying to make me stay.
I bet you're after something.
Do you even hear yourself?
I'm just inviting you
to join me for our wedding banquet.
Don't read too much into it.
Is that so?
It's a shame
that all of your efforts
will go down the drain.
There was the wedding aisle.
As words of blessing were recited,
both the qin and flute were played.
It was all a fox banquet.
You managed to enter my fox hole
to figure out Zhang Tai's whereabouts
because I allowed it.
Of course Zhang Tai would tell you
how we had our wedding.
Immortal Ji, did you think
my most treasured memories
have anything to do with my wedding?
Did you truly think
you'd enter my Illusory Realm so easily?
Are you saying you made
us think so on purpose?
Go ahead if that's what you want.
I'm not going to stop you.
But you must bear this in mind.
Remain steadfast.
(Watch on www.kisskh.ws to support Admin)
Don't you worry.
I'm too good for that.
I learned from the Mistress
of Moonlit Blossoms
that Ji Bozai ever asked her
about the way to get rid
of the Yousu Fox Tribe.
Thus, I intentionally
let Ji Bozai and Ming Yi
enter the Dengxian Cave and meet Zhang Tai.
I wanted to make them believe
that my most precious memories
are related to my wedding with Xinliu.
Unfortunately, they failed to find out
that the Yousu Fox Tribe is best
at killing someone
by tricking them into one's Illusory Realm.
When Ji Bozai
insists on entering my Illusory Realm,
I'll seize the chance to deceive
him into revealing the whereabouts
of Golden Millet Dream.
Then I will kill him.
It's time for you
to enter my labyrinthine Illusory Realm.
Ji Bozai.
Ji Bozai!
Where are you, Ji Bozai?
Zhang Tai!
Are you there, Zhang Tai?
Where exactly are you?
Answer me!
Ming Yi.
Master.
Great! You're still alive!
Come, I'll get you out of here.
Ji Bozai.
You're doing all this
to avenge me, aren't you?
As long as you're still alive.
Come, Master.
Let's tend to your wounds.
How will you avenge me?
I...
Avenging me
doesn't matter
as much as all this.
Tell me.
Have you kept the Golden Millet Dream
somewhere safe?
Tell me.
Where is it now?
Ji Bozai!
Where exactly are you, Ji Bozai?
Where are you?
That rogue with his same old trick.
Bozai.
Tell me.
Where is the Golden Millet Dream?
Did you know?
I ended up in this state
because of you.
Yet Master
I've promised you
not to reveal the Golden Millet Dream.
It's all because of you.
It's all because of you!
I died from saving you!
Hand the Golden Millet Dream over to me!
I...
Hand it over to me!
Master...
Master.
I'm sorry, Master.
I'm sorry...
You're not my master.
And you shouldn't have pretended to be her.
Since you don't like
me to pretend to be her,
how about this same old face?
Tell me.
Where is the Golden Millet Dream?
Show yourself
or I'll annihilate every
single clone of yours!
Both you and I will be trapped here.
You can't kill me even if I show myself.
If you can't find my original form,
there's nothing you can do about me.
Because you will never be able
to tell truth from fiction.
Perhaps everything is nothing but fake.
Nothing has been real.
Stop struggling, Ji Bozai.
You're not getting out of here!
Hand the Golden Millet Dream over to me!
Stop struggling, Ji Bozai.
You're not getting out of here!
It's fake. Everything is fake!
What do I do? I...
Are you all right, Ji Bozai?
Hand the Golden Millet Dream over to me.
Hand the Golden Millet Dream over to me!
Ji Bozai!
This is bad.
If this goes on, he'll be
trapped by his inner demon.
He got drunk
and kept saying,
"Whether you have true
feelings for me or not,
you're the only one I love."
Whether you have true
feelings for me or not,
you're the only one I love.
You managed to figure out
my most precious memories.
Since you're eager to know what happened,
you shall experience
everything I've been through.
This tune
was supposed to sound
as carefree as flying birds.
Yet your piece
was nothing but sorrowful.
Mister.
You could read the emotions in my piece?
You need not be sad.
A broken qin string
can be fixed.
And the bluebird
will fly again.
General.
Whether you have true
feelings for me or not,
you're the only one I love.
General.
I'm back.
Why have you had injuries lately?
And they appear strange.
What have you been up to?
Xinliu.
You no longer want to
be part of the Mu clan,
don't you?
I'm marrying you
to give you your most desired freedom.
General.
Here's the prescription I
got from the Jixing Palace.
It helps heal the wounds
inflicted by the miasma.
Thank you for that.
What's happened to your hand?
I... I accidentally cut it.
Tell me.
What have you done?
Did you bleed yourself
to come out with a cure for me?
I did that of my own accord, General.
As long as it helps General.
General!
- General!
- Xinliu.
I've told you a thousand times.
Don't ever hurt yourself
to save my life again.
For my sake,
take a sip of it.
General.
Just a sip will do.
I can't live without you.
General.
It's the netherbeasts.
I'm going to lose it.
Go.
- Go!
- No!
General!
I won't let them hurt you.
No...
Xinliu...
It's all my fault.
I brought this upon you.
You did all this to save my life.
Xinliu...
Whether you have true
feelings for me or not,
you're
the only one I love.
[Tomb of Beloved Wife Xinliu]
To our surprise,
despite the fact that he's helped
Mu Qibai raise netherbeasts,
he's had such a tragedy as well.
That should be his real Illusory Realm.
It's said that the Yousu
Fox Tribe is powerful enough
to blur the line between truth and illusion.
Looks like
this is Xun Ming's real hideout.
What was that...
It was me.
I haven't finished my sentence.
Didn't you
see that?
I did.
Poor Xinliu.
She was unfortunate enough
to have such an older cousin
and a lover like Xun Ming.
Ji Bozai!
You're something else.
You actually managed to find me here.
However, do you think
you can defeat me?
In my most cherished memories,
you found my original form.
Yet in my Illusory Realm,
your spiritual power will be weakened.
This is the Illusory
Realm I created for her.
And you can't escape it!
Xun Ming.
Look what I have here.
In those most treasured memories of yours,
Xinliu couldn't stop talking
about how much she loves you.
But I have a question.
In your memories,
why was she always
in the Dengxian Cave?
She had no freedom.
Why did I feel
that Xinliu wasn't happy at all?
She even wounded
her own hand.
Are you hiding something from us?
That's not it...
Shut your mouth!
Xun Ming.
Why are you reluctant
to answer my question?
Xinliu wasn't happy at all!
Yes.
She was once used by Mu Qibai.
She was sick of socializing
and playing a good host.
Therefore.
I married her.
I agreed to raise netherbeasts
in exchange for Xinliu's freedom.
I'd do anything for her.
[Beloved Wife, Xinliu]
Anything.
I simply can't take it anymore.
What did you say?
If you had been sincere
in buying back Xinliu's freedom,
why did you even marry her?
You should've let her go.
Instead, you kept her in the Dengxian Cave.
Is this what you call freedom, huh?
That was because I...
Xun Ming.
Those days she spent with you
had been nothing but suffering.
I'm afraid you've been living in a lie
by assuming that yours is true love.
Officail Website : kissasian.be
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
No...
That's not it.
It's you.
It's you!
Why must you doubt Xinliu's love for you?
Ji Bozai.
Ji Bozai?
♪ When the drifting clouds ♪
♪ Flow toward me ♪
♪ They drench my very soul ♪
♪ Until it turns weak ♪
♪ I deceive myself into
thinking that to love once ♪
♪ Is enough ♪
♪ Even if no true vow has ever been given ♪
♪ From the stars, how long must
my tears travel to reach your heart? ♪
♪ The tenderness you give me
is but love's poisonous wine ♪
♪ I drink down all of my sorrow ♪
♪ To trade for your freedom ♪
♪ Once I've tasted love, I
long to be lost in its wine ♪
♪ After long struggles in the
abyss, I ask the heavens ♪
♪ Even if my armor shatters
for you, what does it matter? ♪
♪ Fate is never wrong ♪
♪ Even the sun must one day fall ♪
♪ Against the world's absurdity,
I fight with all my might ♪
♪ From the stars, how long must
my tears travel to reach your heart? ♪
♪ The tenderness you give me
is but love's poisonous wine ♪
♪ I drink down all of my sorrow ♪
♪ To trade for your freedom ♪
♪ Once I've tasted love, I
long to be lost in its wine ♪