I think this might be
the start of our busy era.
We promised to have our regular
date every Sunday, right?
I know you’re a Ramirez.
But lives are on the line here.
It’s our date night.
Do you still want to go?
Should we skip? 'Cause I’m sleepy.
Isn’t Clyden gonna look for you?
Don’t you guys
have a celebration today?
How’s your therapy lately?
Are you taking your meds?
What more do you want from me?
Is it true?
The accusations against you?
You benefited
from my money, too!
It’s not good to act out
on your emotions, Maui.
You don’t know a thing about
what I’m going through right now,
so don’t act
all high and mighty!
Auntie—
I’ll make this short.
Cy has a brighter
future ahead of him.
I just don’t want him
getting dragged
into your family’s mess.
Some goodbyes hurt
more than others.
Because you don’t want to let go,
but you know that you have to
even if you want
to keep holding on.
These past few weeks,
I’ve had to say
some of the hardest
and most painful
goodbyes of my life.
So please, as a mother,
I’m begging you,
stop the engagement.
He only agreed
with everything because
he didn’t want you
to end up with Charles.
Huh?
Yeah, because when
they were younger,
Charles used to beat him up.
And maybe he was scared that
the same thing
might happen to you.
You know,
Cy has the softest heart
among my children
despite his tough attitude.
He might be acting based
on his emotions right now.
He loves you so much
that he might even
end up helping your father.
Even though your father is
the person he hates the most.
Auntie, I understand
what you’re saying—
but please, give me some time.
Everything’s just too much
for me right now.
So I hope you can
understand me too.
Of course. I’ll let you
think about it.
I have to go.
I’m so sorry I have to
drag you with all of this.
I just want the best for my son,
and I know you want
the same for him.
I understand.
How long will we let
these corrupt politicians
- run and destroy our country?
- How can we still trust
- a family with issues like this?
- Senator Vera doesn’t
- deserve to be in power.
- The Vera family
will never change.
Look at their kids,
they’re the next generation
of thieves and corrupt officials!
Sam Vera is my schoolmate.
She’s a party girl.
What a shame if it turns out
she was using taxpayer money
to fund her lifestyle!
This family has
so many issues!
Is it true that Senator Vera
has a child out of wedlock?
Word is, the kid’s living
in their mansion,
but they’re being
quiet about it.
They belong in jail,
not in the Senate!
Auntie Jaida is right.
I have to protect him.
I’ll never forgive myself
if he gets dragged
into my family’s issues.
I...
I have to let him go.
Hi, love.
Hi.
Can we talk?
I can’t.
I need to rest.
There were a lot
of patients earlier.
I love you.
This hurts more than
I ever thought it would.
But I have to do this.
Even if I don’t want to.
Even if it breaks me.
This is for your own sake.
For your future.
A future where
I’m no longer with you.
Hello, Sam. I hope
I’m not disturbing you,
but Naomi is still
missing her sessions.
I’m worried about her.
I heard about what happened
to your family.
Thank you
for informing me, Doc.
I’ll check on her.
I think this is
the illegitimate child.
She was spotted in
the same neighborhood
as the Vera residence.
OMG, I know her!
She goes to my school!
They say her mom died
from drowning.
I don’t even know if
it was really an accident
or something more.
What a super
scandalous family!
Cy?
Are you awake?
Naomi, are you there?
Leave me alone, Sam.
Just go away!
No, I’m not leaving.
I told you, didn’t I?
Open the door.
Let’s talk, please.
I don’t want to!
Stop pitying me,
I’m not some charity case!
What did Mom
tell you this time, huh?
Naomi, I’m your sister, and
I want to take care of you.
I’ve never treated you
as a charity case.
Naomi, I love you, okay?
You don’t deserve
to be caught up in this.
You’re still young, and
I want you to be happy.
So please,
don’t push me away.
Let’s fight for each other.
Naomi.
Naomi?
Naomi, open the door!
I’m worried about you!
Naomi!
Naomi, please.
Please open the door—
Naomi.
Please, just leave, Sam.
No. I told you that
I will be with you
throughout your healing process.
I’m not leaving.
You don’t understand.
You don’t understand because
no one is talking shit about you
for just being the daughter
of your father.
Every time I’m at school,
people keep staring at me.
And you’re no different, Sam.
You’re looking at me
with the same eyes.
Naomi—
And don’t even try to sound
like you understand.
My face is all over
the internet.
They even brought up
my mom’s death.
Why is this happening to me?
Why should I suffer?
I never asked to be born.
I didn’t ask for
all of this. So, why?
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry, Naomi.
You don’t deserve any of this.
I deserve this.
My mom died because of me.
I deserve everything.
No, you don’t. Naomi…
It hurts. Why does
it always hurt?
I always feel sorry for living.
Why do I have to suffer when
all I want is to be happy?
I shouldn’t have left my room.
I should’ve stayed in my place.
I shouldn’t have hoped
things would get better.
Naomi—
I’m right here, Naomi.
Lean on me.
I wish I had never been born.
I wish my mom
had lived instead of me.
My father hid me like a monster.
You denied me
in front of your friends.
I felt so ashamed.
Why did I have
to live like this?
Why didn’t I just die
if this is the kind of life
she was going to leave me with?
I tried everything.
I tried pleasing your parents.
I followed and did
everything they wanted.
I even took Political Science,
even though that
wasn’t really what I wanted.
I made friends, and yet
they betrayed me.
Nothing good
ever happens in my life,
your mom was right—
I bring misfortune
to everyone’s life.
I could never be happy.
It feels like a sin to be happy.
Am I just not allowed
to be happy, Sam?
Naomi, stop. Please.
Do you remember
what you told me?
You’re worth more than
what they say.
Don’t listen to her.
You are worth
more than what she said.
So, just focus on doing
things for yourself, okay?
Don’t believe what my mom says.
Don’t believe what people say.
They don’t know anything
about your life, Naomi.
So let’s fight back.
We can do this without them.
Just the two of us,
we’ve got this.
Stop.
Stop making me hope again.
Things never get better
as long as I’m alive.
Everyone around me will suffer.
Please, Naomi.
Please don’t push me away.
Didn’t I tell you?
No matter what happens,
I will always be here for you.
And I’m not suffering
because of you.
No one is suffering
Hope.
Yes.
Yes, hope.
There is hope, Naomi.
Sam,
be free.
Naomi, come with me.
I’ll take care of everything
you need. Trust me.
I will do some things
so we can get through this
without anyone’s help.
I’m sorry.
Why? Why are you saying sorry?
Don’t you want to come with me?
Naomi, I won’t leave
here until you do.
So, please. Just trust me.
Come here.
How’s your sleep?
I’m okay. I’ve been
sleeping fine, Sam.
That’s good.
Wow, you broke them perfectly.
I practiced a lot.
I’m excited to eat.
Let’s make a lot
so the dogs can eat too.
Of course, we’re all
eating together, okay?
It feels so good
to be back here.
I feel so happy
you’re back here.
Just feel at home, okay?
You’ll always have
a home here, always.
Thank you, Sam.
By the way, where’s Cy?
I haven’t seen him around.
He’s busy.
He has a lot
on his plate right now.
How about you?
How have you been?
I haven’t asked you yet…
I know we’re both affected
by the news about our dad.
Thank you for asking,
but I’m okay, Naomi.
Whatever happens,
I’ll make it through.
We’ll make it through.
As long as we’re together,
we can get through
anything, okay?
Thank you, really.
For letting me stay here.
For everything you’ve done.
It’s only now that I’ve felt
what it’s like to be
treated like family.
I wish I had known this sooner.
I wish I had let you
into my life earlier.
You’ll always have
a family with me.
You don’t ever have
to worry about that.
You’re the best sister
in the world.
Jeez…
Well, I am your only sister.
Now that we’re living together,
we can do this more often
in the future, right?
By the way,
can you please help me
with my hair
and makeup tomorrow?
It’s because
I have a photoshoot.
Of course!
It’s an honor to do
your hair and makeup.
Okay.
What happened?
I didn’t mean to.
Can I see?
Wait, let me help you.
Just hold it like that.
Put some pressure.
You okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
It’s okay. Accidents happen.
All right,
I’ll take care of this.
No, that’s okay.
I can still do it myself.
- Sure?
- Yeah. I just—
Okay.
Be careful.
Yeah.
If you need help,
I’m right here.
Okay.
Let me see.
Let me see your makeup.
You look good.
Nice. I love it.
You’re so good.
New details emerge in
Senator Vera’s plunder case,
including offshore
accounts tied to him.
Meanwhile, rumors of
an illegitimate child
add to the growing controversies
surrounding his family.
I’m going to Mom this afternoon.
Okay. Do you need
money to go there?
No, I’m good.
Don’t worry about me.
I’m so proud of you, Sam.
This is just
the beginning for you.
You’re going to be
a big star soon.
You too.
You’re already
a star in my eyes.
Everything I have now
is because of you.
Everything I do,
you’re part of it.
I even got the confidence
to be a model
with your help.
And when I become
a bigger model soon,
I’ll get you as my makeup
artist and photographer.
I wish.
You're going to be a great model
even without me as your
photographer and makeup artist.
It’s just a matter of time.
You’re becoming more confident
working with
other photographers now.
And if I’m not there with you,
just imagine I’m the one
taking your pictures
when you feel shy.
Okay, I will.
And if I’m not in the audience
and you’re nervous,
just imagine I’m there
yelling and cheering for you.
I’ll always be your
number one fan, Sam.
Thank you.
Okay, I won’t be
able to finish this.
I have to go.
Bye, Naomi.
Bye.
Sam!
Goodbye.
I’ll see you later.
Cy…
What happened to you?
Did you have a fight
with someone?
Wait, let’s get
that treated.
- Hold on.
- Don’t bother.
It’s not a big deal.
It’s just a fight
between brothers.
I need to rest now.
Cy—
Can we talk now, please?
Sam, listen to me.
No matter what happens,
I’ll stay with you, okay?
I am marrying you.
Why are you still
fighting for us?
Because, I love you.
I love you, Sam.
No matter what,
no matter when.
I’m not giving up
on you just like that.
Okay?
Her dad’s corrupt.
I know, right?
I even saw it on the news.
Do you think she’s the same?
Well, what do you expect?
The fruit doesn’t fall
far from the tree.
Oh come on, girl,
let’s not be so judgmental.
Sam’s nice, but her sister?
Nevermind.
Okay, guys, let’s take
a five-minute break.
Hey, how are you?
Let me know when
you’re home. Love you!
Why hasn’t she
replied to me yet?
Don’t worry, Sam.
She’s fine.
But it’s already late,
maybe she’s home by now?
Did something happen?
- Hello?
- Naomi, where are you?
Hello?
I’ll...
I’ll stay at my friend’s house,
since it’s already late.
Don’t worry about me.
Are you sure you're okay?
You know, I can pick you up.
Hello? Naomi?
Are you still there?
Yes. I’m okay, Sam.
I just want to hang out
with my friends for now.
We’re just stargazing.
The stars are so beautiful.
The stars are so bright.
But they feel so far away.
It’s like they’re shining,
but you can never
really reach nor touch them.
I need to go, Sam. Bye.
Okay. Enjoy your time there.
I love you, Sam.
I love you too, Naomi.
Okay, guys, let’s resume.
Thank you, Sam.
Thank you.
- Thank you, Sam.
Hello? Naomi?
Ma’am,
she’s gone.
Last night, she slept here.
But when I was going to
ask her what she wanted to eat,
she was already unconscious.
What do you mean?
Ma’am...
No way.
I called an ambulance,
but it was too late, Ma’am.
They said Naomi wasn’t breathing
anymore when they got here.
I wanna go there.
Where?
To the moon.
Or just beside it.
I wanna be one of the stars.
Do you think
there’s pain there, Sam?
I’m not sure,
but I hope there’s none.
Thank you for making me happy,
even for a short period of time.
Sam!
Goodbye.
Naomi.
There’s so many of you!
But not one of you noticed!
None of you
were doing your jobs!
None of you even noticed
that the girl’s gone!
Naomi’s gone!
Get out of my sight, all of you!
- I’m sorry.
- We’re sorry, ma’am.
Damn it!
No one wanted this to happen.
Shit!
Shit, Naomi.
Naomi…
I’m sorry.
Oh my god, I’m sorry.
Sam—
Naomi.
Naomi, how can I live now?
How can I live without you now?
I’m sorry.
I can’t believe
this is happening, Yanna.
I hope this is just a dream.
I wish I could just wake up
from this nightmare.
Please, Yanna.
Yanna…
I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
I’m sorry.
You can get some rest now.
You’ve been the one
handling almost everything.
It’s the least
I can do for Naomi.
‘Cause she suffered a lot.
I’m here if you need me, okay?
I would look good in this.
This one?
Yeah. Go try a different pose.
Let’s just take a selfie.
Hi.
How do I start this?
If you’re watching this,
I’m probably—
Nevermind.
Hi, Sam.
I miss you.
Of course, this video
is for you, dummy.
I’m here to ask if you have
already improved your walk.
Just kidding.
I don’t know how it would
sound less painful for you.
If ever you’re crying right now,
stop it or you won’t
be able to focus
on what I’m about to say.
So, okay…
Sam,
I’m sorry I pushed you away
a lot of times
when all you wanted
was to save me.
So, please stop acting
like you care about me.
I really care about you, Naomi.
I never really wanted
to push you away or hurt you.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Thank you.
But I was afraid
that being with me would be
more painful for you.
The death of my mom
still lives inside me.
The guilt from it.
I have been living my life
with nothing but pain.
I was in the darkness
for a really long time.
A lot of times,
I compared myself to you.
Actually, I envied you.
Naomi, if you want more makeup,
you can ask me for some.
I don’t need you
to buy me makeup, okay?
Now, leave.
I wanted to have
everything you had.
I have always thought
that you’re so lucky
because you have everything.
That’s why I was mad at you.
I was such a lonely kid.
I had been suffering for
so many years now until—
until that day.
Naomi? Naomi?
Help!
- Naomi?
You were so persistent
that I had to let you in.
And you know what?
You made me so happy.
You made me explore
so many things.
You helped me heal.
You never left my side.
You were there for me
when no one else was.
You became my mother-figure—
and I couldn’t thank you
enough for that.
You were my hope.
You were my only hope.
If you’re still blaming
yourself for what happened,
please know that you did enough.
You were more than enough
at some point,
I felt like I wanted
to get through it.
You made me stronger,
but there were still times
when I would break down
no matter how happy I was.
It wasn’t because of you.
Do not blame yourself.
Do not live like me.
That feeling is the feeling
I had to bear for so many years.
Sam, I already told you this,
but you will become
a great model someday.
Please, live for
yourself this time.
Choose yourself,
because I know
you’re completely drained.
Do the things you want
and be happy.
Genuinely happy.
I’m saying this now,
and I will never get tired
of repeating this up there,
in the sky.
I am so proud of you.
I am now a star, and
I will shine bright for you.
Look up when you miss me,
and I will look down
when I miss you.
I love you, Sam.
Hi, what’s your name?
Naomi.
I’m Sam, do you want to borrow?
Here, you can play with her.
Do you like her?
My mom gave her to me,
that’s why I always
bring her around.
She’s a model.
She’s so pretty, right?
You’re so pretty, too!
Are you a model?
I’m not. But someday,
I will be one.
Let’s play.
You asked me if
I think there’s pain there.
I hope not.
I hope there is none.
And here, too.
I could only
wish that you didn’t leave.
I love you, my brightest star.
I’m sorry, I wasn’t there.
I’m sorry you had
to go through this alone.
It’s okay.
It was my choice
not to tell you.
How did you know though?
Your mom called.
She told me to check on you.
You weren’t answering her calls.
Cy, can we talk now?
We can’t.
No. Let’s talk now.
Stop avoiding it.
We both know
where we’ll end up—
Married, Maureen.
That’s where we’ll end up.
Cy, please.
Let’s end this.
Please.
Maui, you’re just tired.
We can talk about this
some other time.
- Clyden!
- Sam! Fuck!
I will never leave you.
If you don’t want me
anymore, I don’t care!
Even if you push me away
or try to make me leave—
I’ll stick with you
because that’s
what I promised you.
So, please,
stop telling me to end this.
It’s not going to happen.
I was using you.
My mom told me to stay with you
‘cause we needed
your family to save me.
I had to hold on to you
to secure my future.
But now, I realized that
I want to secure my own
future without your help.
I want to live for myself now.
Use me, then.
What?
Use me. I don’t care, Sam.
Use me. Just don’t
leave me, please?
How can I use you
when your father already took
the inheritance away from you?
I don’t have a secure
future with you anymore.
I don’t want you anymore.
You’re nothing without
your family’s money.
What?
I’m nothing?
Without my family?
Yes.
So, just go back
to where you belong.
I will now do things by myself.
I don’t want to be
with you anymore.
Maui, that’s not true.
Sam, please tell me
you don’t mean that, right?
Love, you don’t mean that—
Cy, wake up!
I meant everything I said.
What else do I need to say?
What reason do you
want me to come up with
just for you to let me go?
That I never loved you?
That’s a lie.
I know that’s a lie.
You loved me!
That’s a lie, Maui. Come on.
You’re so desperate.
Look at yourself.
Why do you keep
forcing yourself on me?
How many times
do I have to tell you?
I don’t like you anymore.
I don’t want you anymore.
And if you can’t accept that,
then it’s not my fault anymore.
Maui, wait.
Maui, let’s talk first.
Maui.
- Stop.
- Love, please.
- Clyden, stop.
- Love.
- Let me go.
- No.
Let me go!
I was using you.
I don’t want you anymore.
You’re nothing without
your family’s money.
Are you really going to leave?
Will this make you happy, Sam?
Okay.
All I want is
for you to be happy.
So, be happy.
If you’re really
going to leave me,
do it without crying.
Or else I would take you back
into my arms again.
I’m sorry.
Can you sleep beside me
for one last time?
Please?
Sam?
Can you keep the ring for me?
Hey, answer me.
I will.
You said you love me…
Maui you said...
Sam, I don’t want
to watch you leave.
Be happy.
I’ll become someone
you can be proud of.
See you around, Love.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
pray for us sinners now and at
the hour of our death. Amen.
Lord, please forgive me—
for whatever pain
I may have caused this child.
I didn’t want
any of this to happen.
I didn’t want a life lost.
I was only trying to teach her
respect and discipline
in a way I thought
would be good for her—
and for our family.
God, may her soul rest in peace.
Naomi…
Let’s go.
Sam.
Sweetheart, thank you
for coming. I miss—
Thank you for all the things
you’ve done for me.
Starting today,
I’ll do everything by myself.
I won’t follow you anymore.
I won’t follow the things
you want anymore.
What are you saying, Maureen?
I’m saying that I’m not
one of your possessions.
I’m Samantha Vera—
and I will create a name
out there for myself.
Maui—
Haze?
Do I know you?
I give up. I can’t remember.
Samantha Vera.
Yeah. Hiro’s friend.
Yeah, and we’ve met before, too.
I guess you don’t
really remember.
But that’s okay. See you around?
See you around.
Maybe someday, I’ll make your
head turn again with my walk.
Take care of
yourself, Doc.
Is she still coughing?
Not really, Doc.
Doc, they’re looking
for you in the ward.
We know each
other already, Doc.
She was my fiancée.
Upcoming bookings so far—
Photoshoots, Muse magazine,
Denim Haus, and fashion shows—
we have Noa Atelier
and Maison Lorent.
Go, Auntie! Go!
Auntie… Auntie!
Oh my god!
Rich, I need to take
her to the hospital.
There's one nearby,
Ramirez Medical.
May I join you?
Are you okay?
Haze, don’t you
have a girlfriend?