Hello, Mom?
Woo-jin and Mr. Moon got hurt,
so we're at the ER.
Are they badly hurt?
Woo-jin has a knife wound
on his left hand,
and Mr. Moon has a gash on his forehead.
My goodness…
It's all my fault.
It's all because of me.
Oh, Gun-woo…
This is not on you.
These things happen.
MIN GANG-YONG
Unexpected things come up.
SIR, GUN-WOO NEEDS HELP
But the most painful moments,
when you're at rock bottom,
can become a turning point for the better.
If I'd just done what they said,
no one would've gotten hurt.
That's all I can think about.
No one wants you getting involved
in that shady deal.
That's why everyone's helping you.
I'd rather get hurt myself, Mom.
Gun-woo.
What would you have done
if Woo-jin said he'd do that?
You would've stopped him no matter what.
See?
That's how everyone else feels now.
So,
let's get through this.
Bad things will pass
if we just hang in there.
Good things will come.
Okay.
Son.
Stay strong.
Okay.
This will sting.
Yes, it stings. Hang in there.
I'll numb the area now.
Wait.
-Doctor.
-Yes?
Please make it nice and pretty
so it doesn't scar.
Understood, sir.
-Just a quick sting.
-Wait!
-Almost done.
-Ouch!
All done.
Sir, how's the pain?
Ma'am, back in the day,
I was stabbed in the stomach twice,
but I made a full recovery.
Oh…
Are you in a gang?
Not at all.
I'm a boxer, ma'am.
I'm not a gangster or anything like that.
-So…
-I see.
Anyway,
it's been a while since I stepped down
from the ring as a pro.
But with this hand injury,
my fighting days are over.
Well…
Sir, you shouldn't fight.
I must fight.
You shouldn't fight with this hand.
Ma'am, I'm Hong Woo-jin.
If I can't fight,
I'll become a nobody.
I'm a boxer.
I'm the invincible Marine Southpaw.
Then you must fight.
Fight.
You can do it, okay?
I have to fight.
Sir, are you okay?
Oh, this is nothing.
The doctor stitched me up nice and pretty,
so I won't need plastic surgery.
This is really delicate work.
If you botch it, you have to rip it out
and start from scratch.
-That's a no.
-Right.
My looks are all I've got.
Hold on. Doctor!
Well, goodness.
If you ever need some fast cash,
please contact me anytime.
Oh.
Please.
Take care.
God.
Damn, my head…
You got injured because of me.
I'm very sorry.
Gun-woo.
My God, have you been crying?
Oh.
Look at you.
You have an iron fist…
but a heart of cotton candy.
I'm sorry.
Promise me one thing.
Here. Harden your heart
like cast iron as well.
That way, your people stay safe.
Yes, sir.
-Gun-woo.
-Yes.
Hey, Woo-jin.
-Oh.
-Damn.
You haven't had your hand stitched up yet?
They told me to wait an hour.
The wound is so deep
that they're calling in a specialist.
Good to know.
Listen carefully.
Consider skipping the anesthesia.
-Stitches without anesthesia?
-Hey!
I've got six injections on my dome.
It hurt so much that I teared up,
but I only got four stitches.
Forget the interest.
I didn't even get my principal back.
GANG-YONG
Sir, I'd need those shots…
You don't. I'm telling you.
But, sir…
Okay, fine.
Do you want a squeeze toy just in case?
Hello, Gang-yong.
Hey, champion. Where are you now?
Well…
I'm on my way to Min-beom's company.
I don't know what's going on,
but I've got you.
Don't worry, okay?
We can get through this together.
You got that?
Yes, Gang-yong.
BLOODHOUNDS 2
Goodness, are you okay?
Yes, thank you so much.
We haven't met…
He's a senior marine to Woo-jin and me.
He helped us take out Kim Myeong-gil.
I'm Moon Gwang-mu.
I've heard so much about you.
I'm Hong Min-beom.
What an honor.
I'm Min Gang-yong,
team leader at Seoul Metro Police.
Yes, sir.
-Sir, this is Tae-yeong--
-Of course I know.
I helped move her IKEA desk last year.
You remember me, right?
Of course.
Only Woo-jin was there back then.
I see.
Let's sit and talk.
-Okay.
-Sure.
If you don't mind me asking,
what line of work are you in?
Well, I run a small…
I'm running a small loan company.
I'm basically a small business owner.
I know how you feel.
But as for me,
I learned the trade under Mr. Choi.
I wouldn't do things
that go against my conscience.
-It's Gwang-mu, right?
-Yes.
I appreciate you helping Gun-woo,
but I'm a cop.
If I see you breaking the law,
I have to do my job.
You understand, right?
I sure do.
Who's handling the break-in at your place?
A detective at Incheon Station.
Give me his number.
If this ever happens again,
call me the first thing, okay?
So I can sort it out faster.
Will do.
LEE WOO-JEONG
CLASS 39
Excuse me. This is urgent.
Sure.
Hey, Woo-jeong.
Sir, you arrested Kang In-beom
in 2021, right?
Yes, why?
So, Gun-woo.
I've been looking into safe places
where your mom can stay comfortably.
Unfortunately,
my hotel is still under construction.
My friend runs the Marriott
in Times Square.
I'll have a room
and a security team ready.
Don't worry. I'll take good care of her.
Is it okay to accept all this?
Remember what you said last time
when we almost gave up?
We'll help you.
It's not over until it's over.
You didn't give up.
That's how we're alive.
This is nothing.
I haven't even begun to pay you back.
Anyway, your mother must be very shocked.
Let's protect her.
Yes.
Gun-woo.
This afternoon,
Kang In-beom escaped.
-What?
-The police are looking into it.
They are trying to track him down.
But this seems bigger than I thought.
-I told you to bring her.
-I'm sorry.
Hey, you fucker.
I burn 300 million won a year
on your salary, you son of a bitch!
I'm sorry, sir.
Should I send your daughter
to an orphanage?
I'm sorry.
Do it right.
Yes, sir.
Fucking dumbass.
Kang In-beom.
Must be nice to be out.
So,
made up your mind?
Work with me.
Then you're set for life.
Kang In-beom has a vendetta against us.
Someone that driven is easy to manipulate.
That's why they broke him out--
The bastards want to leash a wild dog
to turn him into a bloodhound.
Here's what worries me.
In this country,
you don't just break out of prison.
From what I heard,
the plan was pretty meticulous.
They're using a pro.
What if Kim Myeong-gil escapes too?
Min-beom.
Kim Myeong-gil is locked up on an island
20 km off the west coast.
No one can break that bastard out.
Don't worry.
I told them to ramp up the surveillance
on Kim Myeong-gil and his crew.
Don't you worry about a thing.
Sir, I just remembered something.
What is it?
Back in the Cyber Investigation Division,
I shut down a site on the dark web.
They specialized in contract killings,
but they also handled prison breaks.
These people operate out of the dark web.
And we never caught the site admin.
If you don't have any other plans,
should I look for the gangsters
who attacked us?
You'll look for what?
The gangsters who fought Woo-jin and me.
Why?
I'm trying to be helpful.
I know people too.
Look.
I'm going to handle this by the book.
Mr. Min.
Not everything I do is illegal.
I'll be the judge of that.
Yeah, so just sit tight for now.
Gang-yong.
It's late.
Let's get Gun-woo's mom
to the hotel first.
Sure, let's do that.
For fuck's sake.
Give me the damn money, you prick!
You're asking the wrong person.
Fucking hell.
Hey, man,
I heard those fuckers were pro boxers.
Fuck, you should've told me that!
Hey.
Calm down, will you?
Calm down, my ass.
Whatever.
Do you see this?
I need stitches for this gash
so it doesn't scar.
So hand over the money.
Let's talk outside, just us.
Quit fucking playing
and cough it up, asshole.
Fuck!
Get off me, you fucker!
I'm sorry!
I'm very sorry, sir!
Please stop.
Bite it.
Please don't do this.
Bite it, you fucker!
Man-bae.
Man-bae!
Deal with this prick on your dime.
Got it?
-Yes, sir.
-Send the guys in.
Yes, sir.
Ms. Yoon, here's our Security Team 3.
This is the lead and deputy lead.
Oh, hello.
I'm Joo Ji-uk. I'll keep you safe.
I'm Ryu Gyeong-nam.
So sorry to bother you at this hour.
Your trip here must have been tiring.
We've secured the safest room.
It's late. Get some rest.
Thank you, Min-beom.
Thank you so much.
-Get some rest.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Ms. Yoon and Ms. Kang, right this way.
And Mr. Kim, your room is this way.
Thank you.
If you need anything, please let us know.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
-Gun-woo.
-Woo-jin.
How's your hand?
Luckily, the skin on my palms is so thick
that my nerves and tendons
weren't injured.
I should've gotten there sooner.
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
No need to be sorry.
I didn't get stabbed in the gut
like last time.
It's just a gash on my palm.
How can you say that?
Don't worry. All I need is a quick bite.
I'm hungry. Let's get room service.
Sir, are you okay?
It's nothing serious.
-I followed up on our call.
-Yes.
A bunch of guys born in 1999
formed this Nine-Nine Gang.
Apparently, the gang members
all drove matching British Grenadiers.
Yeah, that off-roader.
It's gotta be those bastards.
The bastards must have a base camp.
Yes, in Yongsan.
Oh my, you found it already
without me even asking.
I thought you might need it.
I love your go-getter attitude.
What do you think I need now?
-Coffee?
-Get moving.
DU-YEONG
I'm in a fucking foul mood.
What's your move?
What?
I'll find Kim Gun-woo first.
How?
How?!
Iil Group's son.
The fucker is Gun-woo's friend.
Bring him here.
Kang In-beom is a wanted man.
It could work against us.
I'll mobilize the bloodhounds myself.
Fuck, you want more money?
Use your own goddamn cash.
Yes, sir.
And you?
They contacted us
after seeing Adik's last payout.
They want a meeting.
I think they'll buy it this time.
Listen up, everyone.
To expand the operation,
we really need Gun-woo.
Get me that bastard at all costs. Got it?
You got that?
Yes, sir.
Are we all set?
Consider it done.
Yes, hello.
Tomorrow at 11:00, Detective Choi
is meeting the lead investigator.
He'll hand over the forensic evidence.
What evidence?
Money first.
I'll wire it right away.
TRANSFER, LEE MAN-BAE
20,000,000 WON
We're in.
What is this?
It's you, Gun-woo.
I think this was AI-generated.
He has much sharper eyes.
You've never taken a photo
with bloody fists, right?
Never.
Isn't this a violation of privacy?
It is, but the site itself is illegal.
Everything on the dark web is illegal.
Give me one second.
What does it say?
"IKFC37 is a challenge tournament."
"It will be held in Seoul this March."
"The new WBC super middleweight champion,
Kim Gun-woo the Scarface, will join
the tournament as the first contender."
Scarface?
Those bastards.
They even created his ring name.
What's a challenge tournament?
The winner advances
to face the next challenger.
If you win,
you'll keep fighting.
Let me look up the previous matches.
What? Do you know him?
He was Gun-woo's opponent
in the title match.
Wait. Please pause.
THREAT DETECTED
-What is this?
-What's wrong?
Someone is planting a virus.
FILE SYSTEM ERROR
Why isn't it working?
You should never turn on this computer.
If you do,
it'll connect us straight to those
who attacked us.
I'm so sorry.
Once we get our prize money,
we'll get you a high-end laptop.
Thanks for the offer.
Get ready.
Can I help you?
I'm here to see Kim Gun-woo.
-Oh.
-Wow.
This is basically a hotel staycation.
This is why you gotta make it big. See?
-It totally changes your life.
-Please.
-Please have a seat.
-Sure.
Sir.
You know the boxer who fought Gun-woo?
-Yes, Adik.
-Yes.
We saw some of the IKFC fight
before the laptop was hit.
Adik was in it.
The guys who hit our place snatched him
and forced him to fight.
And
he disappeared.
He disappeared?
Those bastards.
They will stop at nothing
to get Gun-woo to fight.
We all have to protect Gun-woo.
Got it?
Yes.
What are you two going to do now?
I'm meeting Gang-yong
and Detective Choi at 11:00.
Okay.
I was going to rest.
Rest? When I'm running like crazy
after busting my dome?
I guess I should run too?
But, sir,
Woo-jin shouldn't use his hand yet.
-Gun-woo.
-Yes?
Then what about me?
I can't even pick it up.
It feels numb.
I'll run with you, sir.
But where are you going?
Spotted.
Are you tired of living?
You know how much fucking cash you owe me?
You're supposed to call me first!
Son of a bitch. Are you shitting me?
After all that cash I sank into you?
You fucking prick!
Fucking dickhead.
It's just a gym.
This is supposed to be
the Nine-Nine Gang's hideout.
Are you… sure?
Okay, then.
Let's play it cool.
I'm here for some proper training…
Fuck, catch that bastard!
Sir, no!
-Catch him already!
-Get off!
-Hurry, Sun-bo!
Just get off!
-Get in there! Grab them!
-Get lost!
-Sir!
-The bastards are getting away!
-Hurry! Get them!
-Turn!
-The other way! Hurry!
-Catch them!
-You fucking bastard!
I'm at the nail salon in Daedong Mall.
There's a situation here.
Stop!
Wait! Don't do it!
Wait. Let's not do this, okay?
Like real men,
we can talk.
Let's talk it out, okay?
Yes?
Yes.
Fuck you!
-That little punk.
-Fuck you, son of a bitch!
-Son of a bitch!
-Fuck off, bastard!
The bastards just said, "Fuck off."
Damn it.
Fuck this. Let's split up!
Hey!
Wait!
Hey, take out this bastard!
Son of a bitch!
You fucking bastard!
Die, you fucking bastard!
You!
Sir!
Damn it!
Get off!
You son of a bitch!
Fuck!
Damn it.
-Yes!
-You bastard!
-You fucking…
Die, you fucker!
-Freeze!
-Hey, give it up!
Don't move!
Hold it right there!
-You crazy bastard, what?
-Split up!
-Break it up!
-Crazy bastards!
-Settle down!
-Go ahead!
Shoot me, you fucking bastards!
If you move, I'll shoot!
Don't move!
-Cuff them all.
-Line up.
-I think that's him.
-Him?
What was that?
What happened?
Gun-woo!
Catch that bastard! The one in the hoodie!
Detective Choi!
Damn it!
Detective Choi, stay with me.
Detective Choi!
Damn it!
Stop!
Whoop!
GANG-YONG
I'M SORRY, GUN-WOO
I COULDN'T SAVE DETECTIVE CHOI GYEONG-WON
WOO-JIN
-Yes, Woo-jin.
-Gun-woo.
-Yeah.
-Can you talk to Gang-yong?
Will you two meet us here?
Mr. Min!
-Can I help you?
-Hello, Officer.
I'm Min Gang-yong, Lead Investigator
for the Special Investigation Division.
Sir!
Where is the chief?
Over there, sir.
Could we have a moment?
-Yes. This way, please.
-Thank you.
How is your hand?
-Well, it's just…
-Let me see.
-It's nothing.
-Hey.
I'm fine, okay?
No need to worry.
-Sergeant Lee.
-Yes, sir.
The lead investigator
and I talked things through.
You can uncuff those three.
-Yes, sir.
-What's he saying?
-Fucking bullshit!
-Settle down!
Over there, be quiet! Sit down!
It's not fair! They started it,
but we're the ones locked up!
Sit down.
Sit down? Fuck you!
You are the police! This is not fair!
What?
Why?
I took over this case.
Do you know what that means?
If you keep acting up,
I'll expose you
and call for victims to come forward.
Shut up and listen.
If your face gets out there,
your siblings and relatives,
not to mention your parents,
and I hope you don't,
but if you do have a girlfriend,
will get a lot of calls.
Then their business, work, and daily lives
will be completely upended.
Should I do that?
No, sir.
What's your name?
It's Gu Dong-yeok.
Dong-yeok, I'll be watching you.
Yes, sir.
Thank you so much, sir.
I know how busy you are.
But strictly speaking,
it was self-defense.
I told you to sit tight!
I wanted to help--
So did you?
We found the guys who attacked us.
The police would've caught them.
But it's better
to work together like this.
Can we have a word?
If they make a wrong move
and we get exposed,
all my plans will go out the window.
I'm sorry.
What I did was wrong. I mean that.
But can't you let me pitch in?
I mean,
I'm an uneducated loan shark.
You are not thrilled. I get that.
But not all loan sharks are bad people.
President Choi mentored me.
And he was a truly remarkable man.
Ask these boys.
I try every day to live up to his example.
Besides, they are bad guys.
Can't we play a bit dirty to nail them?
Gwang-mu.
Look.
I'm not afraid of getting my hands dirty.
Getting it done is my top priority.
To get it done,
dirty or clean doesn't matter to me.
But the problem is
that you don't listen to me.
That messes up all my plans!
I apologize.
I'll follow your instructions.
But please…
let me help.
I'm here because of these boys.
Like you, I'd like to do my fair share.
Let me act like a proper senior
to these boys.
Later tonight,
grill Gu Dong-yeok
and find out who's behind the attack.
Yes, sir.
-I'll do as you say.
-Oh…
Okay.
What are you doing? Get in.
-Okay.
-Me too.
Hello.
-Which room?
-Please go to room seven.
What are you doing after work?
Let's get a drink.
Room seven, please.
What a pig.
Hello.
-Hello.
Moa.
-How is business?
-Good, thanks to you.
-What happened to your face?
-It's nothing.
Well, Moa.
I'll deduct double today's sales
from your interest.
Please pull down the shutters.
Which room is that meathead in?
He's in room seven.
Lucky number seven.
Come in.
Relax, sir.
Arms up.
Thank you.
What the hell?
What the hell, you bastards?
-Fuck.
-What else? It's a massage.
You'd better think twice
before fighting back.
It wouldn't be the first time
a neck snapped
while getting a very firm massage.
You get the picture?
Fuck you, you fucking bastard.
That's no way to talk to an adult,
you punk.
Hey, I'm a professional.
I didn't want to be, but here I am.
Why?
Because I'm too good.
Dong-yeok, you little punk.
Let's do a routine checkup.
Traps.
Bad.
Lats. Underwhelming.
Spinal erectors. Terrible.
But the worst of all is…
What the…
What the hell?
Your sphincter, you bastard.
This spot is sensitive,
so the pain is two or three times worse.
Look at this. It won't go in, you bastard.
No, stop!
Now, I'll be asking you some questions.
Answer me truthfully,
or you'll spend the next month in diapers.
Question.
Who ordered the hit?
My boss did.
Who's your boss?
It's Du-seong. Fuck, you're in deep shit.
Where could he be now?
I don't know.
You don't?
-I really don't.
-Well, then.
I promise you a life of no constipation.
Well, I'm going in. Let's get in there!
It's halfway in!
Hey, relax.
You're shitting yourself, you bastard!
-Oh my, what do we do?
-I'm telling you the truth!
Fuck.
Fuck…
I really don't know.
The bastard is telling the truth.
Then do you know who Adik is?
I do. I saw him fighting a few days ago.
Where?
I saw Adik and a long-haired dude
fighting at a closed subway station.
I was standing there.
A long-haired dude? Who?
I don't know.
You don't?
I really don't know. Wait!
I can't think with my head pinned down.
-Sun-bo, he says the pressure is too much.
-Okay.
Go ahead.
I took a photo with my phone.
It's not exactly a photo of him.
But I took a picture
of the watch he was wearing.
It was a fucking pricey one,
so I took a photo to flex it on Instagram.
I praise you for your little selfie game.
Snap and post a photo
of this place too, okay?
Okay.
Fuck…
Wait, guys. I mean, excuse me!
Damn it, fucking uncuff me before you go!
MOON GWANG-MU
What am I supposed to do with this?
Woo-jeong.
Yes, sir.
-Come. Take a look.
-Sure.
You're a watch expert, yes?
Yes, I've done my homework.
Good. Look at this. Could this be a lead?
Let me see.
I'll look into that.
-I'll see what I can find.
-Thanks.
Doors closing.
Hye-seon, ice cream!
Hye-seon!
Mr. Cho Won-yeong.
Right now--
Please don't do this.
Let him finish. Got it?
Okay.
You heard him.
-So don't interrupt me and listen.
-Okay.
Right now,
he's rubbing numbing cream
onto your sister's hand.
Do you see the man next to her?
You see the person next to her?
He's a doctor.
Yes.
Answer my questions promptly,
and you two will be just fine.
Okay.
So…
Got it?
Where is Kim Gun-woo?
I… don't know.
Wait! Don't hurt her! I'll tell you!
Wait! I'll tell you!
I'll tell you!
At the Marriott Hotel in Yeongdeungpo.
The Marriott! In Times Square, the hotel.
At the Marriott. What's the room number?
The room number?
Room 1602.
-Room 1602.
-Yes.
Isn't Min Gang-yong
Min Gang-yong and
Hong Min-beom's relative?
Hong Min-beom are related, aren't they?
I'm just wondering.
Do you know
What's Hong Min-beom doing
tomorrow evening?
What's Min-beom doing tomorrow night?
BLOODHOUNDS
SEOUL
LOOKING FOR SOMEONE TO WORK
TOMORROW EVENING
And the drug for tomorrow?
One drop will do.
Can I mix it with alcohol?
Mix it with alcohol?
Used with alcohol?
Hmm. That makes me curious
how strong it would be.
Fuck, I'm really curious what'll happen.
It shouldn't kill him.
I don't want this to kill anyone.
It won't kill.
He won't die.
PSYCHO69
I'LL DO IT
We're not open yet.
I'm sorry. We're not ready yet.
Ma'am, we're not open yet.
You can't come in.
You can't be here.
What did you just…
In three hours, the effects will wear off.
It'll wear off in two to three hours.
When does Hong Min-beom get here?
Eight o'clock.
And drinks?
And for drinks?
Tell me his drink.
What's his usual?
You want a drink, Won-yeong?
Do you want a drink, Won-yeong?
I'm only having one tonight.
Seriously, I'm only having one.
I'll wait and drive you home.
-I'll just wait and take you home, sir.
-Hmm. Next time then.
Okay, maybe next time.
Good evening.
Hello.
Where's Dong-u?
Where is Dong-u?
He's usually here.
He's not feeling well,
so I'm covering for him.
Oh, he's feeling sick tonight
so I'm here instead.
Please have a seat.
You're President Hong Min-beom, right?
Have a seat. You're Hong Min-beom, right?
I am.
Here's the Bowmore 27 you reserved.
Thank you.
Subtitle translation by: Jooyea Lee