I'm just so pissed off.
Fukami.
Let's go grab a drink later.
We could even finish
what we started last night.
Oh.
No thanks. I'm heading out.
A perfect guy like me...
getting pumped and dumped
by a total loser? Unbelievable.
- Sorry to bother you, Kaji-san.
- Yeah?
Can I ask you about the project schedule?
Ah...
Well...
The tech team would
probably know more about that.
The head of tech...
Oh, that's Fukami-san, right?
- I don't really know him.
- It's fine, don't worry.
I'll go talk to him.
Just you wait, Fukami.
Perfect timing.
Fukami, got a sec?
Eh...
Playing hard to get to grab my attention?
Not like I'm short on options.
I don't have time for
guys with an attitude.
See?
I'll find someone else in no time.
"Unexpectedly Naughty Fukami"
He's not even my type.
Huh?
What's wrong?
(Episode 2)
What is wrong with me?
This guy, that guy...
none of them are as hot as him.
Damn it.
Not here...
I'm getting turned on
just thinking about it.
- Alright, let's go.
- Let's go.
Oh, Kaji-san.
Are you sure you won't join us for a drink?
Ah—sorry, not today.
- Good work today.
- See ya.
That Fukami...
Don't think this is over.
I'm going to make your body crave me.
I heard a computer's down.
Did you put in the request?
Yeah, the one with the mark on it.
But I'm just about to head out.
Got it. I'll take care of it.
- Thanks.
- Fukami!
Yui, let's go.
We're heading out now.
Good work.
See you later.
- Good night.
Hey, we're the only
ones left on this floor.
Huh?
When it comes to sex...
how do you even bring it up?
Before...
I never had to actually ask.
What should I say?
Do you want to...
try it again with me?
No.
That makes it sound like...
I'm the one obsessed with him.
Isn't there another way to say it?
A better line...
I guess I could let you be my fuck buddy.
Wait, that's not right.
What are you doing all of a sudden?
You've been watching me
this whole time, haven't you?
We only did it once.
You're making me uncomfortable.
Idiot.
Stop, someone might come in.
You know it too, don't you?
We're incredibly compatible.
Maybe it was just luck.
If you can satisfy me a second time...
then prove it.
Mr. Top Salesman.
Wait.
I'm all sweaty.
I want to shower first.
I want to do it right here, right now.
You do too, don't you?
Since we're already like this.
No, I told you to wait.
Don't look at me like "why?"
It's embarrassing.
Being all frantic like some porn scene.
If we're going to do it...
can't we just be normal about it?
Normal?
Up until now...
it's just been about scratching an itch.
But this...
It's throwing off my rhythm.
What do you mean by...
"being normal"?
Don't ask.
Just... slower.
Like, with kissing and stuff.
It's just a gentle kiss...
but my head is spinning.
Like...
touching each other's bodies.
I don't get it.
Just his fingers on my skin...
is driving me crazy.
Fukami.
I want to go inside.
No.
Not yet.
Wait a bit longer.
Can I now?
Wow...
It feels so good...
my mind is going blank.
I knew it...
this is amazing.
This guy...
is incredible.
Why did you sleep with me?
What kind of question is that?
Because you...
don't seem like the type
to do one-night stands.
For a gay guy like me...
you have to take the chance when it comes.
Or you'll never get one.
I'm not good-looking like you.
That's not true.
He's dangerously oblivious.
I've tried dating apps.
But I just couldn't do it.
Just looking at looks...
or stats.
It feels so soulless.
If that's the case...
I'd rather be with someone I actually know.
Soulless...
I never thought about it that way.
Isn't looking at the surface enough?
I mean, "true feelings"...
are pretty fragile anyway.
I don't really need them.
Besides...
you're surprisingly attentive.
Like how you keep your nails trimmed.
I think it's actually quite thoughtful.
It's not like that.
I just...
I just want a hookup, not a relationship!
Fine.
I'm down.
To be your fuck buddy.
Honestly...
I can't with you.
Since...
- you're offering.
- But I have one condition.
A condition?
You...
You absolutely cannot fall in love with me.
If you can do that, then we're on.
I just want to keep things casual.
No strings attached.
Easy.
If anything...
you're the one who shouldn't fall for me.
Idiot.
Are you in grade school?
This cocky loser...
Who would ever fall for you?
Moron.
Listen up.
Fukami.
By the time you're...
totally addicted to my body...
you'll be the one crying.
Kaji-san, that's a bit harsh.
- Yeah, it's the liar's fault.
- No...
Sorry, my bad.
Oops.
What were we talking about?
Kaji-san is right. When
you fall for a married man...
the one who ends up crying...
is me.
- Can I sue him for emotional distress?
- Give me a break.
You only get hurt because you get attached.
It's better you found out he's married now.
It saves you some heartache.
I finally got a boyfriend...
and I really liked him.
Just forget about him.
And move on to the next one.
You...
aren't you being a bit insensitive?
You can't just turn off
your feelings like that.
Crap.
I said the wrong thing.
True.
I know it's better to forget...
but it's not that easy.
Exactly.
Sorry.
I'm heading straight home
after my client meeting.
Ah.
Lunch is on me at the next meeting.
Cheer up.
So annoying.
All this talk about love and feelings...
is such a bore.
Sex...
doesn't require being in love.
Why bother with the
hassle of a relationship?
It's a total waste of time.
Fukami?
A bridal shop?
That guy...
is into women too?
No, no way!
No way, no way!
But...
what if he's already married?
He's married.
Can I sue him for emotional distress?
Would I be the one paying the settlement?
(Preview)
You...
what do you want?
Here's my contact info.
Message me if you need anything.
Wait... what are you doing?
I want to see your place.
Isn't there something you want me to do?
My name.
I want to hear you say my name.