When was it exactly
that I started being unable
to take my eyes off him?
"Feel What You Feel"
(Episode 2: Let's be best friends, okay?)
Senior!
You're here too?
Let's go.
Hello, judges.
I'm Li Ming, a freshman
from the Law School.
I'll be singing "Courage" by Fish Leong
for everyone.
We all need courage
to face the rumors.
Finding the courage
to hold you tight...
our love is worth it.
Okay, that's enough.
Wait, Professor!
It's just... what I had for dinner
was a bit too salty.
I don't usually sound like this.
Professor,
could I have one more chance?
That won't be necessary.
Thanks for coming.
You're done?
How'd it go?
Me?
I just read a poem
and blew them away.
You should've seen it...
the judge held my hand and said,
"Yu Lei,
we've been waiting so long for you!"
Passing was a piece of cake.
By the way,
what were you laughing at?
Oh, just the students
auditioning today.
They're awful.
There was this one guy who was even worse.
He looked like a gorilla
and sang "Courage."
I have no idea who gave him the courage
to sing that badly.
And then there was this
guy who looked like a poodle.
He tried to breakdance,
but as soon as he got on stage,
he just fell flat on his face.
That was a floor move!
You clearly don't know anything.
Floor move? More like mopping the floor.
You...
Li Ming, Ouyang Han,
both of you just drop it.
What?
You know each other?
Li Ming,
this is my friend Ouyang Han.
Ouyang Han,
this is my friend
Li Ming.
We're all on the same side here.
Just consider this a
rough start to a friendship.
Who'd want to be friends with him?
Next!
Instrument Group, Number 6.
Chen Ke from the Law
School, please get ready.
[TN: Scoring rubric]
Now this is real music.
Chen Ke is the man.
I guess even a gorilla can
appreciate the finer things.
It's called art.
Like a poodle would know.
Yu Lei, how do you stand his
bad breath every single day?
You're the one with bad breath!
No, you!
You!
I didn't realize Chen
Ke actually had talent.
I totally underestimated him.
But why does that piece sound so familiar?
Have I heard it somewhere before?
The list is out!
Look, Li Fei-hang and Chen Ke are on it.
Wait, why is my roommate on there?
How did he make the cut?
I can't believe I'm not on the list.
These judges
have no taste.
Yu Lei,
you're right here.
Under the hosts.
Well, I guess they
aren't that blind after all.
Look,
Chen Ke.
No surprise there.
I mean,
he is actually good.
But still,
even if he's some piano prodigy,
he's still not going to outshine
a handsome host
like me.
What's that supposed to mean?
Yu Lei?
Were you looking for me?
No, I was just passing by.
I'm not...
bothering you, am I?
Not at all.
By the way,
is your foot all healed up?
It's been fine for a while.
Anyway,
that piece you were
playing was really nice.
What's it called?
This?
It's Beethoven's
"Moonlight Sonata," the first movement.
Why? Do you like it?
I can lend you the tape sometime.
Oh, no, I couldn't...
I'd feel bad.
Well, actually,
how about I just make a copy
and give it right back?
It's fine. It's hard to
find a kindred spirit.
Besides,
I've had this tape forever.
You can have it.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
So,
why were you asking about this piece?
I don't know.
I just feel like I've heard
it somewhere before.
It's familiar,
but I can't place it.
It feels like it has some kind of
special meaning to me.
Really?
It has a special meaning to me, too.
Grandma?
Where is that sound coming from?
It's coming from inside here.
Oh, I know!
There must be
a little person living inside.
And when I press this,
they start singing.
You're so smart.
Here, press this button.
That was my grandmother.
The "Moonlight Sonata"
was her favorite piece.
She's the one who taught me
my very first song on the piano.
Oh, and
she was a graduate of Ming De University, too.
Really?
So she's an alumna!
So, where is she now?
Actually...
she passed away.
But I think
if I can perform her favorite piece
on the stage here at Ming De University,
maybe it'll make up for the fact
that she never got the chance
to perform here herself.
Anyway,
that was my grandma.
The "Moonlight Sonata."
I got it on tape.
It's okay.
Wait, what?
I can't believe you actually
talked to Chen Ke for that long.
I thought you two were enemies.
We are.
But he helped me out before.
If I don't find a way
to return the favor,
I'll feel too guilty to
keep competing with him.
Whatever.
Let's just call it a temporary truce.
Well, it's not like he's
competing with you.
Yu Lei!
Yu Lei! There you are.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Here's the updated program
for the gala.
There have been a lot of changes,
so we'll need to rewrite the intros.
Chen Ke's performance was cut.
Fine, let's do that.
Okay.
Sis?
You're the one who invited Chen Ke
to the gala.
Why would you suddenly cut his performance?
You have to give him an explanation.
I did invite him,
but cutting the act wasn't my decision.
We originally had
two piano pieces
and my violin solo.
The administration felt there
were too many instrumentals,
so they decided to cut one.
But why'd they have to cut Chen Ke's?
Why not someone else's?
Why do you think?
It's totally rigged!
Sis,
you're the Student Union President.
Can't you do something about this?
Look, the administration
already made the call.
But at least
your hosting gig is safe.
The higher-ups really like you.
Since when did you start
caring so much about this?
We're in the same class, that's all.
Anyway, I've gotta go.
See ya.
Okay.
Oh, I thought you guys weren't back yet.
Perfect.
Were you looking for me?
Here, like I promised.
Here.
This is the recording my grandmother made.
No,
I can't take this. It's
too precious to you.
It's fine.
I just made a copy for you.
Here.
Thank you...
Director, please reconsider.
That student really...
he's been practicing for so long.
Look, Yu Lei,
this is the third time
you've come to see me.
I'll say it again:
this isn't about personal preference.
It's about the big picture.
The big picture.
Does "the big picture" always have to come
at someone else's expense?
Look,
we have to keep the
show within the time limit.
If you want
to add a segment,
we have to cut one.
So,
who do you suggest we cut instead?
I...
Let me think.
I could step down as host.
If there's one less host,
would that save enough time?
Let me think about it.
Oh, good, you're here.
Here's the latest program.
Apparently, they changed it again.
They're unbelievable.
Changing the script every day...
I didn't even get to watch
"Happy Camp" this weekend.
Yu Lei,
why are you so happy?
Isn't all this rewriting exhausting?
Wait, why did it change
from a solo to a duet?
The production team felt
the gala needed
more variety.
That's why they decided
to have us perform together.
Don't read too much into it.
No,
actually, I'm just happy
I still get to perform.
It's just...
I rarely play with others.
I hope I don't mess up the performance.
It'll be fine.
We'll just practice a few times.
I've prepared Chopin's
"Nocturne Op. 9 No. 2."
Are you familiar with it? If not,
we can pick something else.
I think I can manage.
Great.
Then let's try playing
it together now.
- Okay.
- Let's see how it feels.
So,
why do you think Zhang Han
is perforMing De with a freshman?
Yu Lei,
are they really close?
How should I know?
Well, I heard
Chen Ke is a total heartthrob.
And playing Chopin's "Nocturne" together?
There's definitely something
going on between them.
Don't you think?
Think what?
Don't be dense.
Look at Zhang Han...
she's beautiful
and a great violinist.
And Chen Ke?
He's handsome
and amazing on the piano.
They're a match made in heaven.
When you play music like that together,
things are bound to happen.
No way.
Why not?
It's totally impossible.
There's an age gap!
Look at Nicholas Tse and Faye Wong...
they're ten years apart.
And they're still going strong.
It's so romantic.
I'm so jealous. I wish I had
someone to hold hands with...
And what are you two talking about?
Don't get ahead of yourself.
We're just talking about celebrity gossip.
Oh, I see.
Well, shall we?
And what do you think
it has to do with you?
Come on.
Good.
Oh, hello, Professor Meng.
Was our practicing too loud?
Did we disturb you?
No, not at all.
It sounded so beautiful
that I just found myself
following the music subconciously.
Sorry about that.
We'll keep it down next time.
Don't worry about it.
A scholar like me
shouldn't stay cooped up
in a study all day anyway.
I need to know what's
going on in the world.
Besides,
what the two of you are
making is music, not noise.
By the way,
someone gave me these pastries,
but I can't eat them
because of my blood sugar.
So, I'm giving them to you two, as thanks
to both of you for the wonderful music.
Here.
Thank you, Professor Meng.
You're very welcome.
Sis!
Lei-lei...?
Come here.
Sis,
your violin solo
is usually a school tradition, isn't it?
Why'd you change it to a duet with Chen Ke?
I had to make a small compromise
to keep everyone happy.
Besides, didn't you go to
the administration yourself?
You were even willing to give up hosting
just to save Chen Ke's act.
Isn't everyone happy this way?
That's only because he helped me out.
I had to do something
to return the favor.
But that doesn't mean
you should have to lose out.
Where is he, anyway?
Why isn't he practicing with you?
Is he throwing a fit?
You're overthinking things.
I'm not losing out at all.
We've been practicing all afternoon;
he just had to step out for a bit.
Well, at least he's being professional.
Actually,
I've had a bit of a surprise myself.
I didn't expect
us to have such great chemistry
the first time we played together.
So you two
are really in sync, huh?
He's also very dedicated
and works hard on his own.
You know,
you could really learn
a thing or two from him.
Wait,
Sis, that's not fair.
Why do you always find a way to
praise him while putting me down?
I'm dedicated too!
Besides, what's so great about
being wound up like that all the time?
You need to strike a balance
between work and play.
You have a point.
Actually, the school is
showing a movie tonight.
I bought two tickets
and was planning to invite Chen Ke.
I thought it would help him relax.
What?
You're taking him to a movie?
That's basically a date!
Sis,
don't tell me you're trying
to be like Faye Wong.
You're not actually into
younger guys, are you?
This is crazy.
- That's too much.
- Yu Lei!
Aren't you supposed to be
a modern college student?
It's just a movie.
That doesn't mean we're dating.
What's wrong with a senior
looking out for a junior?
Everything is wrong with it!
President!
The committee has some urgent business.
They want to meet with
our department tonight.
Tonight?
Yeah.
I...
Sis, Sis!
How about I go to the movie instead?
The tickets are already bought,
it'd be a waste not to use them.
Fine.
I guess I'll let you have them.
Lucky you.
Great!
Thanks, Sis.
(Student's Club)
Why isn't senior here yet?
Hey, Bo Ya.
Waiting for your Ziqi?
[Reference to the classic story of musicians
and "best friends" Bo Ya and Zhong Ziqi]
What are you talking about?
You know, "High Mountains
and Flowing Water."
Bo Ya and Ziqi.
Aren't you and my sister
like kindred spirits?
If you're Bo Ya,
then she must be your Ziqi.
Musically speaking,
I think we do have a certain connection.
But as for anything else...
I wouldn't go as far
as calling us soulmates.
What about me?
Do I qualify as your Ziqi?
You're unbelievable.
Anyway,
I'll stop teasing.
My sister had something
come up at the last minute,
so she gave me her ticket.
Come on, let's watch the movie.
Chen Ke,
you always act so serious.
I can't believe
you actually cried during the movie.
Look at your red nose!
You were sobbing too.
I heard you.
I wasn't nearly as bad as you.
You were
twitching
like a little squirrel.
Get the hell out of here.
If I'm a squirrel,
then what are you?
A devious old fox?
Me?
How am I an old fox?
During that scene in the car,
I didn't even know what was going on yet,
but you were already laughing.
You've got a dirty mind.
And you say you're not an old fox?
You're a pretty good-looking guy.
Have you really never had a girlfriend?
I don't buy that you're this innocent.
It's not anything like that.
I've only ever had one girlfriend.
We didn't even kiss.
The most we did was hold hands.
Love?
I don't think it was really love.
It was probably just curiosity
about the opposite sex.
Alright, level with me.
Is there a girl you like right now?
Right now?
Not at the moment.
Well,
what's your type, then?
I think...
we'd need to have common interests.
A genuine, mutual
attraction from the heart.
So...
what do you think of my sister?
Why are you asking me that?
Didn't you say the other day
that whoever lost the game
wouldn't talk to her?
I was just joking then.
I'm just using her as an example.
So all that time
you were targeting me,
it was because you were
worried about me and your sister?
Don't worry.
It's not like that.
She's amazing,
but I just
don't feel that way about her.
What way?
I remember a writer once said:
"To me, love
isn't just about physical intimacy
or sharing a meal.
It's an undying desire...
a heroic dream in a weary life."
I've always loved that quote.
I think that's what love should be.
Something sacred.
That's the "feeling"
I'm talking about.
I think
that's true for everyone,
throughout history.
It's like they say:
"They talk of a match
made in gold and jade,
but I only dream of the old
alliance of wood and stone."
A lot of people who read
"Dream of the Red Chamber"
think Xue Bao-chai is smart
and proper,
so she's the best match for Jia Bao-yu.
But I don't think so.
Exactly.
Bao-yu and Dai-yu are the
ones who truly belong together.
They have a real soul connection.
Some of those sequels that
force Bao-chai and Bao-yu together
completely miss the point.
Yeah.
If Cao Xueqin knew,
he'd probably want to take them all out.
He wasn't that hot-headed.
But
speaking of souls...
how do you actually see someone's soul?
Maybe it's because
souls are so hard to see
so people have always
lamented how rare true love is.
When someone has something
on their mind, they frown.
Just like you're doing right now.
I think seeing that frown...
is like seeing into someone's soul.
You're right.
I think that's it.
And I believe
that beautiful souls are
naturally drawn to each other.
They just keep getting closer.
It's like that poem:
"You're from Yunnan, Yuanmou,
I'm from Beijing, Zhoukou.
We reach out our furry hands...
and it's love
that makes us walk upright like a pole."
Chen Ke,
I hope everything goes well.
Wait, no.
I mean... I hope the
performance is a huge success.
It will be.
September 2000. Sunny.
Every day is busy and fulfilling.
New people, new experiences...
my schedule is packed.
As the performance draws closer,
I'm getting more and more excited.
Not just to fulfill my grandmother's wish,
but also to live up to
everyone's expectations.
Like the senior...
Professor Meng...
and
Yu Lei.
Get out of my way.
You're so childish.
Chen Ke,
you're up next.
Good luck!
Chen Ke, it's time for you to go on.
"You ask me how deep my love is..."
"I love you as much as—"
Meng-yu, stop singing!
Have a drink first. Here we go.
We'll have plenty of time for that later.
Come on.
Let's all have a drink together.
Cheers! Come on.
Everyone!
Cheers!
Bottoms up!
Chen Ke,
you did a great job at the gala.
Senior, I'm the one who
should be thanking you.
Sis!
Why are you only praising Chen Ke?
You didn't even mention my contribution.
Oh, right. Chen Ke, you
probably didn't know this,
but the administration
almost cut your piano piece.
It was all thanks to our Lei-lei.
He fought so hard for you.
That's the only reason
we got to perform together.
If you're going to thank anyone, thank him.
Well, thank you both, then.
Easy there.
Wow, look at him go.
Nice! Take it easy.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Sis, I can handle this.
You're being way too sincere.
You're such a good kid.
Yu Lei,
I want to thank you
on behalf of my grandmother, too.
Don't mention it.
Director!
We all worked hard, too.
Why are you only paying attention to them?
One at a time, Meng-yu.
You were great, too.
Tell you what...
National Day is coming up.
Let's all go on a trip together.
Anyone who's free can come,
and you can bring friends.
Sounds good!
Long live the senior!
Come on, everyone!
Let's go!
Trip time!
Cheers!
(Ming [De] University celebrates
the National Day holiday)
Wow, he's so handsome!
Look.
Isn't he handsome?
Here, you can have this one.
This one's really cool, too.
No way!
Which one do you like best?
Why are you being like that?
You're so stingy.
Look at this one.
Stingy?
I think you're the one with the nerve
to just tag along.
I have no idea why you even came.
Hey, I helped set up the stage
for the school, okay?
Why shouldn't I be allowed to come?
Besides,
there are plenty of pretty girls here.
Isn't that why you're here, too?
You're delusional.
You think everyone is
as girl-crazy as you are?
Pervert.
Yu Lei invited me.
I'm basically family.
Family?
You look more like a rat to me.
You...
Yu Lei! Hey.
Yu Lei, how are we splitting up the rooms
at the guesthouse?
Senior, why don't we share a room?
Sounds good.
Yu Lei!
Let's share a room.
Sorry,
I already told Chen Ke
I'd stay with him.
Wait, when did we agree to that?
Chen Ke keeps saying he
doesn't have feelings for my sister,
but you never know.
During this trip,
I need to keep a close eye on him.
Our bus is here. Let's go.
Let's go, let's go! Let's go, let's go!
Looks like you've been dumped.
Feeling a bit left out?
Get lost.
Fine.
I'll be generous
and let you stay in my room.
You must be dreaming.
Who knows if you snore
like crazy?
You're so ungrateful.
Just get in there.
Stop stalling.
Yu Lei!
What took you so long in the shower?
Was I that long?
It's your turn.
Why didn't you dry your hair?
There's a fan right there.
You're going to catch a cold.
It's fine. I'll just let it air dry.
You can't do that.
Yu Lei!
You guys have to let me stay here tonight,
or I'm not going to make it.
What's wrong now?
Li Ming!
He was out the second
his head hit the pillow.
And he snores!
It sounds like a thunderstorm in there.
I think I'm going deaf.
But...
this is just a single bed.
It's not big enough for two people.
I promise
I'll be good.
I won't even move.
Just let me crash here for one night.
Please, Yu Lei?
What about the sofa in the living room?
I already checked.
It's too drafty out there.
Tell you what...
you two take the room,
and I'll go sleep on the sofa.
- Okay.
- No way.
I'll go.
(Museum of Cinema)
What?
What's this?
Out for an early walk without telling me?
Look at those dark circles.
Didn't you sleep well?
Don't even get me started.
I spent all night
in the living room shivering.
I only managed to catch a
few minutes of sleep at dawn.
What about you?
You look like you didn't sleep much either.
I always have trouble sleeping
in a new environment.
Plus, Ouyang Han
wouldn't stop talking to me.
Honestly,
I really envy you sometimes.
You have so many good friends,
and they're all so full of life.
Not like me.
It's raining! Let's go.
Oh, man.
We were planning on going for a hike today.
I guess that's not happening.
Damn.
It looks like it's really
starting to come down.
Let's just run for it!
Come on!
Cheers!
This is actually really good.
Is it ready yet? Let me see.
Is it boiling?
The water isn't boiling yet.
We can't put the food in.
Not yet.
Just wait a bit.
How about
we watch a movie first?
Sure.
What do you have?
Any Hollywood blockbusters?
I heard "Mission:
Impossible 2" is really good.
Tom Cruise is so hot.
I don't have that.
But I do have this.
Why don't we watch this?
["Happy Together" dir. Wong Kar-wai, one of
the most depressing gay movies ever made]
It's got Leslie Cheung and Tony Leung.
There are a lot of stars in it.
Sounds good! Let's do it.
Put the food in!
Okay.
Wait... is this a porno?
Why are there two guys?
Leslie Cheung and Tony Leung were in this?
Did the shopkeeper give us the wrong tape?
I thought...
Hey, why don't we just watch this instead?
"King of Comedy." It'll be more fun.
Yeah, "King of Comedy" is great.
Hurry up, Yu Lei!
Come on, Yu Lei.
Cheers!
Why'd you stop eating?
I don't know.
Between the beer and the hot pot...
Look.
I feel like my stomach is about to explode.
That's ridiculous.
You don't have a stomach.
Those are abs.
Yu Lei...
do you ever feel like I'm not normal?
Everyone else is out chasing the sun,
but I...
I'm always alone in the dark.
Chen Ke,
what are you talking about?
Yu Lei,
you know...
when I was a kid,
it was just me and my grandmother.
Between practicing and competitions,
I never had time to talk
to people my own age.
I didn't even know
how to act around other kids.
After a while,
I just got used to being by myself.
So...
I've been following you
around this whole time.
Do you... do you find me annoying?
Get drunk!
Let's go.
No.
Actually, I like it.
I'm happy to tell you about myself.
I even find myself thinking...
that I wish I'd met you sooner.
Maybe then...
I wouldn't have spent my
whole life without any friends.
Chen Ke...
I'm sorry.
To be honest...
to be honest...
I used to think
you were just this cold, difficult person.
That's why I couldn't stand you.
But then I realized...
that's not who you are at all.
It's okay.
I'm used to people getting
the wrong idea about me.
I always felt like
people would come and go,
and in the end, I'd always be alone.
But when I'm with you...
I don't feel that way.
Look.
Even the rain has taken on meaning now.
Yu Lei...
can I consider you my friend?
No.
My best friend.
Is that okay?
Sure.
Pinky swear.
Chen Ke...
That night,
I couldn't take my eyes off Chen Ke's face.
I suddenly realized
how cute he actually was.
I felt this sudden urge
to be even closer to him.
It was only later that it finally clicked.
- That was the moment I started falling for him.
- Goodnight.
(Next Episode Preview)
Lately, you and Chen Ke
have been joined at the hip, haven't you?
I thought you'd completely
forgotten about me.
Do you want to try the pose I mentioned?
What pose?
Are you free on Christmas?
I...
Christmas?
I... might have some plans of my own.
Is romance the only way to be intimate?
Can't friends, brothers,
or family be close, too?
Can't we express that physically?