(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
Her name is Lalin.
My only daughter.
I understand it well that,
How does it feel...
when we failed.
- You cannot get inside, Lalin. - Move!
I'm gonna a word with Arisa.
Hey, ma'am!
Can you please quit avoiding me?
Let's talk for once.
Why do you come?
Got any more lies to use?
How can you say it like that?
Aren't you also the one who lie too?
Isn't it the right choice?
I have to protect myself from people like you.
We are both liars.
What do you want more?
I didn't want to do it.
But my mom asked me to.
One day, I'm going to tell you the truth anyway.
But how can I know that you are my mother's rivals?
Perhaps you knew it all along?
You dated me just because my mother's business?
I don't care whatever you think.
I just didn't have a chance to tell you...
that I got any other job.
But you lied about everything.
Name. Background.
Now you're standing here.
Does it have any truth left?
It's my feeling.
All my feelings are real.
Noone forced me.
What about you?
Have you got any feeling for me in these few months?
My feeling doesn't matter.
Because two of us...
will never work.
The relationship that starts with lies.
There is no good ending for that.
Every moments,
There's nothing worth to remember.
I'm an easy to forget person.
Fine.
I'll take that everything between us was never happened.
And you...
A stranger who I never ever know the real her.
Left! Left! Right! Right!
Left! Left! Right! Right! Kick! Kick!
We better take a break, miss.
We practiced for hours.
You're upset that Lyla is Lalin, your rival's daughter, aren't you?
You don't have to worry.
I broke up with her.
And I haven't take her seriously.
Miss.
Don't you really have any feelings for Weiling's daughter?
No, I don't.
The revenge for my father and mother...
is the most important thing.
Let's continue.
Yes, miss. Come on!
Left! Left! Right! Right!
That's not very easy.
You know that me and Weiling are a long time partner.
We know each other well so the workflow is very good.
But if you don't try anything new,
you still stick to the same result.
Maybe going off the old track,
it also makes the market moving.
"Trust" is not the easy thing people can gain.
It needs time.
I'd say you need more flight time in the job,
if you really want to be in this business.
Look at how Weiling counterplay...
You might got a lot of money and won the aunction.
But she came to my mother and my mother forced me to choose her.
Understood.
That you don't enough power.
So you have to follow your mother.
I'd like to give you some advice as a long time businessman.
You can use this advice to other businessman.
You can't just use your guts.
You need look inside your target's hearts.
Thank you for the business advice.
Maybe I need new techniques just to satisfy you.
I'm not a complex man.
Easy to satisfy.
You just need to hit the right spot.
- Hello, sir. - Hello.
You guys saw that girl there?
Her schedule always full.
Not enough?
I ain't cleaning your mess if you puke.
No!
I will drink it all up so I can forget everything.
Those liquors just a temporary things. When you sober, you will still remember everything.
Then I'll drink everyday so I can forget everyday.
Damn girl.
What do you want me to do then?
Do you want me to think like all these months are just my imagination?
Didn't you lie to her too?
Come on. You know that you and her is impossible.
Is it better to just focus on being heir of your mom's business?
You know what?
My knowledge about this business is on negative level.
In the meeting room, I understand nothing at all.
Can't do whatever I want and my love is just a lie!
What do I have left in my life?
Obviously me.
I still got your back, Lalin.
At least I still got a friend like you.
Everything will be alright.
Lalin.
Can we talk?
About what?
Imma drink with my friend.
Let's just talk.
Just the two of us.
What do you want, miss Arisa?
CEO of A-list company.
If there's nothing, I'll excuse myself.
My time is precious.
Drink too much? Your body's hot.
You don't have to worry about me.
I can take care of myself.
Lalin.
Can we go back like we used to?
Hold on.
Days ago, you just broke up with me.
But now you wanna make up.
Why suddenly the hot and cold?
Lalin...
People just need some time to learn about their feeling.
We both got our own reason to lie.
Today, I cannot lie to my own feeling anymore.
Everything we've been through is nice, really nice.
So nice I don't want to lose it.
Please give me a chance.
I promised I'll never make you cry again.
From now on, no more lies to each other.
Thank you.
I think you should give it a second thought.
This might be our chance to use Weiling's close ones as a weapon.
Our target got inside our lair, why let it go so easier?
Hey, What are you doing here?!
Stalking me?
What?
Drunk again?
I live here.
Ok. Ok.
Thought you were some psycho.
Those bottles.
Wanna be a living legend?
You are such an alcoholic.
Right, miss Somsak, please stop.
No more getting the fuel and park the car today?
You.
- Here. Let me help. - No need to.
I'll help myself.
Come on. I'll help.
Now you owe me nothing.
I'm not going back to help you taking out the trash.
No need to help me. I'll take care of it.
Worry about yourself.
Where can I put them down?
Anywhere that you can.
Hey.
I'll take my leave.
Wait. Where're you going?
Taking out the trash.
I just want to say thank you.
Oh, you're welcome.
See ya.
Woke up, love?
It's alright if you want to sleep more.
Nah, i'm good.
Hey, dear.
Don't let my mom concern you.
My mom cannot force me.
But she's persistence.
You're right.
That's why the way we will talk to my mom...
is going to be her daughter way.
I'll take the role of...
the little miss that whenever she needs anything, she has to get it right away.
How's that?
Like...
if she wants me to go home, do some works, she has to let me date with you.
If not?
If not, I'll go back to be Lyla.
Run away with you and never let her see me again.
Lalin.
Think about it carefully.
I don't want you to upset your mother.
She loves you very much.
Perhaps.
I have to prove myself.
That I can take care of her only daughter.
You don't have to prove anything.
It's my life and I chose my way.
I also know that I chose the right choice.
- You sure? - Yeah.
More than sure.
[Miss you already. Wanna grab dinner tonight?]
[I got a meeting but i'll rush to you when I finished.]
G' morning, boss.
Wow, you seems happy today.
Like those who got a lovey-dovey.
Boss, what lovey-dovey?
Aiy don't have time for that kind of thing?
I only got time for good news for you.
Does this mean...
You've got a lover, right?
It's not that. Come on, boss.
Good news is I found way that we can defeat your rival's company.
How?
It's Mr. Kevin.
I found his weakness.
Let's talk later.
I have to leave now.
I'll wait for your message.
Got it.
You're beautiful enough.
Thank you.
Miss Kratai, right?
Yes. Do we know each other?
You don't know me.
But I know you.
I know even your real job.
So what?
Got a job for me?
But I only accept VIP's request.
One Prosecco please.
Your bar...
is so nice. I really like the deco.
If I want to launch the bar more, how much does it cost?
A lot. No need to launch it more.
Just try to keep what you have alive first.
Come on. I just like this style.
Have you slept?
Yeah, just a lil bit.
Before you wanna open more bars, just try to rest properly.
Right.
Here's your Prosecco.
Your bar is full of customers, no?
- Lady first. - Thank you.
So you really think this through, about going back with Arisa.
What about your mother?
I'm dealing with those.
No need to worry.
I got this.
I didn't worry about anything and I always support your love life.
But I just concerned that you might got tricked.
And you got no idea about that.
What do you mean?
Take a look at this.
Here.
I was doing my things at my friend's bar and met her with that girl.
That girl is kinda hot, dressed in a sexy outfit and they talked so close. What do you think?
You're overthinking.
They're probably friends.
It could be but if not?
I don't know but I'm your friend.
She's my suspect.
Yeah. Thanks.
But I think it's nothing.
She'd told me if it's something.
We promised, no more lie to each other.
Right. It's up to you then.
I'm just the messeger.
By the way, what do you want eat? Today is on me, yeah?
- Yeah. - Right. Give me a sec.
What would you like?
Umm...
Red wine by glass, please.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Have you met this woman before?
She probably comes here every friday.
No, I haven't.
Thank you.
Here.
Good evening.
This way.
Pardon me.
This is restricted area.
This area is only for VIPs.
Good morning, Weiling.
Good morning, Kevin.
How can I retain myself from calling you, Lady Boss?
Get through my mother.
Just to force me to choose your company.
There was really no other choice left.
You really impressed me.
There's big scene coming today.
Good morning to every commitees.
This is Petra Corporation's first time in Bangkok.
With their six stars graded hotel, Cornerstone Bangkok. Cooperate with national company.
And we will know what is that company today.
Right now, I'd like to invite Mr. Kevin Lee, president of the company to kindly do the opening remarks. Please, sir.
Good morning, everybody.
Petra Corporation,
is one of the best company that lives on for generations.
That's why the way we choose our partner this time.
I have to choose the one I trusted.
The one who I felt like family.
Therefore,
I'd like to invite the official partner of Petra Corporation...
Ms. Arisa Kulnavee.
CEO of A-list company.
Uh, miss Arisa.
I think you got into the wrong restroom.
No, I don't.
I got personal matters to talk with you.
So...
you really need this project that bad.
To the level that...
you do the sacrifice?
Need it?
Yes, I really do.
But the one who do the sacrifice,
It's not me.
It's more like you have to.
You saw that girl over there?
Her schedule always full.
Do you want me to be your friend tonight?
I'm free tonight.
What do you want?
Choose my company.
And I'll delete those pictures.
How can I trust you?
That you will get rid all of them.
Rest assured.
Woman like me.
Won't use the same weapon twice.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
Becoming the part of the hotel. I wish you the best of luck.
Thank you. Good to see you again.
Absolutely.
- Bye. - Bye.
You wanna make an enemy out of me?
What enemy?
It's just a business. Nothing personal.
Ever since the aunction day and now today.
No respect for me at all, huh?
You're overthinking, miss Weiling.
I don't know what did you do to Kevin to change his mind.
But I only know that it's not clean.
Speak of which.
You sounds like someone who did something foul too.
Fine. If you want to play this game.
I'll play with you.
But I'm warning you.
All of enemies...
has no good ending.
I'll be prepared.
Do you realize what you just did?
So tired. Can you be my recharger?
What's going on?
Why didn't you tell me?
Didn't we agree about no more lies?
But there's nothing tho.
I don't know how you lived, who you having fun with.
But now we're dating.
All you can have is me.
What are talking about?
Then what's this?
Just a customer.
A customer?
Yeah.
How do you seems so close with her?
Dear.
Doing business...
got to have every way.
Just to get what we wanted.
Even with the charm of mine.
Ah, are you saying that your beauty can won your customer's heart, right?
Correct.
Understandable.
Business woman really does need tricks.
Lalin.
Thank you for understanding.
You are my only special person.
Can I really trust you?
Yes, you can.
Hold on.
There's one more thing.
What is it?
You just declared a war against my mother.
It's stressing me out. What should I do then?
About that...
Yeah.
it's complicated.
Do you have time tonight?
- I'll tell... - No, I don't.
Come on. I haven't charged my power yet.
I've missed you so bad.
Yes, ma'am.
Who is this "Arisa" girl?
Who are her parents?
Search all of her background and bring it to me.
I'm not gonna let her abuse me easily.
Got it, ma'am.
Hey.
Did you trick me to take a bath with you?
Trick?
Aren't you the one who want this?
I'm scared...
the situation will make our relationship worse.
Normally, my mom already were prosessive of me.
Now, there's you.
We're hopeless.
Even she asked us to break up.
I won't allow it.
What do you want me to do?
That's mother and here's the love one.
Come again?
Love one?
Yeah.
The love one.
Want to be only my crush?
I won't allow myself to be in a bathtub together with my crush.
Alright. Now that's refreshing.
I can now fight with your mom.
Such a teaser.
What about you?
Just like or love?
Are there only two words?
What if it's more than that?
The word that can describe my feeling.
When I was near you.
I can be myself.
Miss you when we can't see each other.
Want to kiss.
Want to hug.
Want you to be near me.
Don't wanna let you go anywhere.
Beside those two words...
do you got more?
Lalin.
I don't want you to get in trouble.
And I don't want to get on your mom's bad side.
I don't want your mom to see me as enemy.
I want to get everything right.
I really want to be in your life.
Yes.
Got it.
Later.
Mom.
Lalin.
Barely see your face these days even we're living together.
I'm sorry but I was so busy.
What's on your mind?
So... I want you to meet someone.
Who's that?
Mom.
Arisa and I are dating.
I want you to know. Don't wanna keep it from you.
Hope you understand.
Since when?
Lalin!
Answer me.
Quite a while.
You wait exterior.
But mom...
I come here just to tell y...
Can you listen?!
Lalin has to be here.
This is our matter.
What do you want, Arisa?
The reason I come here today,
I'm respecting Lalin's pride.
And I don't want to do things behind your back.
I want to do everything right.
I want to marry Lalin.
Am I cute when I was a child?
Right now, you are cuter.
Here, eat a lot.
The only reason that I allow you to get inside my house.
I just want to make sure.
That you're being sincere about my daughter.
I have nothing to hide.
Weiling already allow me to date with Lalin.
Now you just need to play the role of the lover a while.
Thank you for helping my mom.
But be careful.
Your heart...
can be your own weakness.
I won't allow my heart...
to play in this game.