(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
=Echoes of Gang City=
=Episode 17=
(Friends Fight, But They Make Up Easily)
Be careful.
Stay safe.
Boss, Lawyer Fang is moving
the wine cabinet
and the cigar cabinet.
Why don't you tear down
the load-bearing wall while you're at it?
I had someone
custom-built the wine cabinet in Europe.
Someone said
he needs me to drink with him
to fall asleep.
Every bottle I'm taking
is my collection
and my soul.
But all of these were gifts for me.
If I remember correctly,
Article 658 of the Civil Code states...
Mr. Shen.
Are you arguing law with a lawyer?
Wait.
Don't wear that robe to the meeting.
The board will laugh at you
for three months.
Mind your own business.
Our strategic cooperation with Minghui
has been fully terminated.
For the shareholders' meeting,
I've initiated a share buyback plan.
I'm negotiating with the board as well.
Mr. Shen,
I didn't fly here for 12 hours
to hear this.
Have you found out
Shen Gu's background?
His information is protected.
We haven't found anything yet.
After he appeared,
Qingniao invested in Minghui.
Don't you find that weird?
Either
Minghui has close ties with Qingniao,
or Shen Gu can tap into
their core resources.
(Report on Qingniao's Founding Entities)
I need to know
(and Organizational Structure)
who's behind Shen Gu.
(Chairman, President cum CEO)
Since he cares so much about Minghui,
we'll crush Minghui at all costs.
The board won't support that.
Raymond Group will cover
all funding gaps.
Including the eight percent equity
you've pledged.
Gu, how does it feel
to be back in Gang City?
Everyone's going as planned.
Very smooth.
Why isn't Lawyer Fang with you?
He's busy moving house.
Hey, everybody.
I'm late. I apologize.
Traffic was heavy.
I'm so sorry
for being late.
Traffic in Gang City was bad.
Since everyone's here,
let's begin.
We have to face reality.
Because you've been appearing
in the media frequently lately.
Rumors that you are
the actual controller behind Qingniao
have spread privately.
Risks such as technology transfer
and data compliance
could crash down on us at any moment.
Gu, your identity
and Qingniao's investment portfolio
will be subject to
endless over-interpretation.
The global supply chain
is interconnected.
Any shift in sentiment
affects our local partners'
confidence.
Are you done?
Everyone,
I've been aware of these risks
earlier and more clearly than you.
That's why I've kept my identity hidden.
No matter what comes next,
technical barriers or monopolies,
we'll fight fairly, by the rules.
We have the best legal team,
and we're prepared to spend
whatever it takes
to prove
what fair competition
and contract integrity mean.
My identity
stays undisclosed for now.
It's to minimize damage.
What I'm trying to say is
that this is not just a challenge,
it's also an irreplaceable advantage.
Proceed with everything
according to plan.
Good luck to all of us.
Since signing Su Mei as our ambassador,
the public sentiment index on our side
is up 127 percent.
Weekly product sales
(Reports on Sales)
have increased by 34.6 percent.
(and Public Sentiment Statistic)
Excellent news.
Anjie,
how's the termination with Junlin going?
It's smooth overall.
But the cooperation
is deeply intertwined.
It'll take time.
Our priority
is to fully cut ties with Junlin Group
to avoid future risks.
Okay.
The legal department will complete
all termination procedures
within 30 working days.
Very well.
Wanxin.
What's wrong, Mr. Changhe?
Our five core raw material suppliers
have all sent termination notices
at the same time.
Have a look.
All five at the same time?
If the supply chain breaks,
we'll suffer major losses.
Someone is targeting us.
Who else but Junlin Group
could do this?
Don't worry.
There's always a solution.
(Grandfather)
Grandfather.
Shen Gu,
Junlin Group
took away our core material suppliers.
It'll take time
to fully resolve this.
Since Wanxin took over the company,
there hasn't been a day
without trouble.
She's been stuck in her office
working all day.
I understand, Grandfather.
When Zhaoming was around,
he could always talk her through
moments like this.
Given what has happened now,
it's best if you handle this.
Don't worry, Grandfather.
I'll pick her up from Minghui later
and bring her back to see you.
Good.
I was just saying yesterday
I wanted to have dinner with you.
See you later.
Alright.
Is everything packed?
Are you
kicking me out?
It's one street away.
I won't see you off.
What are you doing?
I bought this from Sotheby's.
I'm having dinner
with Grandfather tonight.
I thought I'd let him try
the Islay flavor.
Leave the cigar cabinet here.
A reason for you to come back anytime.
Okay.
Right.
Next time you come back,
give me a heads-up first.
He might prefer Chinese bajiu.
Wanxin,
how about we shortlist
some suppliers first?
You haven't eaten anything all day.
I'm not hungry. We're short on time.
We need to make a decision quickly.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to invite Ms. Wanxin to dinner.
I'm busy. I have no appetite.
Still worrying about suppliers?
I've talked to the suppliers
we used to work with.
They terminated the contracts
under pressure from Junlin.
Even if I find new suppliers,
this might happen again.
I'm stressed out, and you're laughing.
They're pressured by Junlin
not to work with you,
but that doesn't mean
they can't work with other companies.
That makes sense.
Instead of looking for new suppliers,
I should look at
their partner companies.
Find ones that have ties with Minghui
and set up third-party contracts.
I'll call Diana right away.
Let's have dinner first.
Where are we going?
You're laughing again.
This...
This is the road back
to Grandfather's place.
He missed you.
Grandfather.
Why did you come out, Grandfather?
I heard you didn't eat all day.
I had them prepare
a few dishes you like.
Fish maw and mutsutake mushroom
chicken soup.
It's made in the traditional way.
You'll definitely like it.
You love me the most, Grandfather.
Come on, let's eat.
That's more like it.
You need to eat well
to have energy for work.
Grandfather,
you already know
what happened to the company?
Mm.
I just took over not long ago.
I wanted to prove myself quickly,
so I got a bit anxious.
When your dad first took over,
he'd secretly go to hotels
and cry by himself.
He'd call me at 3 AM
and say, "Dad,
our research project failed.
What do we do?"
I can say
that's true.
Your father
started out just like that too.
So I take after him.
Don't learn that from him.
Running a company
means you'll make wrong decisions
sometimes.
They can be fixed.
What matters is holding on
to the company spirit.
To benefit the people
and to strengthen the nation.
I'll remember that as Dad did.
Good.
Aren't you going to have a drink
with me?
You're just looking for an excuse
to drink again.
The liquor tastes good,
but you shouldn't drink too much.
One last glass.
Shen Gu brought this.
Why shouldn't I drink it?
Then just one last glass.
Alright.
Grandfather, a toast to you.
Nice.
If you like it,
I'll bring you more next time.
Sure.
You've had some liquor tonight.
Don't go back.
Stay here
and keep me company.
Alright.
I'll do as you say.
I haven't arranged
a proper home for you two yet.
Tonight, you'll stay in Wanxin's room.
Grandfather.
Changhe,
I think I'm a bit tipsy.
I'm tired.
Help me get back to rest.
Alright.
Take it slow.
Okay.
Get some rest early, Grandfather.
Enjoy the food.
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on
no distance could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled
one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending
we face?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪