Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, ETC. ARE FICTIONAL
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
WITH GUARDIANS PRESENT
ANIMALS WERE FILMED
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION AND WELFARE RULES
Elizabeth?
Elizabeth. Elizabeth.
Where did she go?
Where is it?
Not here.
MOM
ACCEPT
-At Jenny's aunt's house?
-Yes.
She'll be in Hong Kong until next month,
so she told me to take her there.
You should've told me beforehand.
I was startled.
Anyway, where is Jenny's aunt's house?
Beauté Palace.
Beauté Palace?
Hey, I should've gone with you.
Why would you come with me?
What do you mean?
I heard it's really exclusive.
I could've looked around
and said hi while I was there.
Should I head over now?
No, I'm hanging up now.
I'm leaving as soon as I drop her off.
She has no idea how I feel.
Where is it?
That's not fair. I told you my wishes.
-Don't ask.
-Then spit out the food you just ate.
Okay, then.
Tell me if I catch you.
-Who is that?
-Kim Wooju.
I swear that was Meri.
Am I seeing things?
Elizabeth, stop!
Get back in there.
Do you think he saw me?
I'm sure he didn't.
Either that, or he didn't recognize you.
But didn't you say he was in Hong Kong?
Actually, he called me to tell me
that he's back in Korea.
But I hung up because I was flustered.
Do you think he came here knowingly?
Well, then he wouldn't have just left.
You're right. He wouldn't.
But if in the worst case...
The worst case?
If he came knowing everything,
then we can only tell the truth
and team up with him.
No way.
It's unlikely
that he'll give up on this house.
That means he won't easily expose us.
And since you two
are still legally married,
Beauté won't cancel your winning.
I'd rather get caught
than team up with Wooju.
Not after what he and his family did
to me and my mom.
If he knew that I won this,
he'd gleefully threaten me with it.
It's obvious that he'll demand this house
in exchange for keeping the secret.
I can't bear to see that.
I get that you're feeling wronged,
but what about the loan?
Isn't the money you borrowed
from your mom everything she had?
The person who needs this house
more than anyone is you, not him.
So, don't get emotional
and just think rationally.
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
EPISODE 6
One, two, three, four.
The other side.
Left foot behind.
Going low. One, two, three.
Let's stretch our hips. One.
The other side. Two.
Three.
After a five-minute break,
we'll lightly stretch and start.
Okay, let's all give a round of applause.
-Let's go.
You got new trainers.
You noticed already.
I told you that my feet hurt
if I run for a long time.
Apparently, it's because
my arches collapsed.
So, I had my feet scanned
and got custom trainers.
I could fly away in these.
-I guess exercise is all about the gear.
-Yes, it is.
You should try
for a half-marathon this time, then.
I was also thinking of trying out for it.
He shows up regularly.
He is the managing director.
He's a true young-and-rich
who lives in Beauté Palace.
Apparently, he's the reason Beauté hit
legendary sales numbers
three years in a row.
Isn't he so dashing?
I guess he's good at his job.
But he's so cold and unapproachable.
He doesn't even stay for a beer afterward.
I think he's single, though.
Let him be. He seems busy.
Okay, let's get started.
If you don't feel well,
let me know straight away.
Keep your pace in check.
Also, keep your distance.
-Let's go.
-Yeah, let's go!
Ma'am!
Are you okay?
-Stop!
-Hold!
-Ma'am!
-Can you hear me?
Oh, my gosh!
Does anyone have their phone?
-Hey...
-What's wrong?
Excuse me.
Ma'am, are you okay?
Can you hear me?
Call 911 and tell them
that someone's in cardiac arrest.
Okay.
We're at Hangang River Park,
and we have a medical emergency.
We're currently at... Please hold.
Check if there's an AED
at the information center.
I'll go get it.
Stop recording and let's go.
Why? This is great.
-We'll be in trouble if we get caught.
-Give me a break.
Oh, no.
Let me take over.
Excuse me, what are you doing?
-Do you even know how?
-You should cover yourself up.
I think this one will tip over
when we pull out the drawer
from the weight of the hangwa.
Side-opening drawers would be better.
I think so, too.
It would showcase the items better.
But this part looks a little dull.
It might be nice to add
an accent to the handles.
How about fancy gold leaf detailing?
No.
Let's focus on the design,
not the materials.
A sleek linear or round design
would maintain that elegant simplicity.
I'll come up
with more designs for the handle.
Could you contact Monk Haeho, Songhee?
Okay.
We've set the packaging concept
as "jewelry box."
It symbolizes a jewelry box
containing hangwa
that's as precious
and beautiful as jewels.
If we're allowed to make it function
like an actual jewelry box afterward,
it will be made of wood rather than paper.
Wouldn't the costs spike?
Specialty paper
isn't exactly cheap, either.
I got separate quotes for paper, wood,
and mother-of-pearl options.
I think mother-of-pearl
would cater to specific preferences.
And it might seem outdated.
I also think wood would be better.
We have a few VVIPs in their 20s and 30s.
-Right.
-Let's settle with wood, then.
And we'll adjust the cost accordingly.
How's the thank-you card going?
We're planning to incorporate a verse
from Monk Haeho's poetry.
He's famous for his calligraphy.
Who is Monk Haeho? Is he famous?
Yes, he's trending these days.
He's also famous for couples counseling.
-True.
-Really?
-Did you get his approval?
-Yes, we did.
We're currently deciding
which poem to calligraph.
What happened?
-I performed CPR for about seven minutes.
-Okay.
-The patient is conscious now.
-Got it.
We'll transport the patient now.
Wait...
Passcode.
It's 0901.
Illegal filming carries
up to seven years in prison
and a 50-million-won fine.
If forensics reveals more,
you'll be charged
as a repeat offender with no leniency.
If you are a repeat offender,
even rich parents will have
a hard time getting you out.
Damn it.
He made me do it.
I did not.
Hey, you made me do it.
You threatened me if I didn't record it.
MOVE TO TRASH
I'll let you off
since it looks like your first time.
But I won't the next time.
Hey.
Come here.
Do you get good grades?
Pardon?
I do.
You'll have to be really smart
if you want to pick up the crumbs
next to your rich friend.
Okay, got it.
Beauté confirmed.
-It passed on the first try!
-Oh, yes!
Good work.
No, you did all the work.
Listen to you.
Your social skills have come a long way.
I could send you out
for sales now.
TEAM LEADER KIM WOOJU
I loved your packaging idea.
It shows you put a lot of thought into it.
I'm glad that I could be of help.
-Is it your boyfriend?
-No.
You were smiling
from ear to ear while texting.
Nonsense.
How's your wedding preparation going?
What?
Speak of the devil.
Looks like he missed you already
and came running.
Hello.
Hi.
And if Wooju contacts you again,
we'll need to find out his motives.
What brings you here?
I just wanted to see you.
Gosh, it's been a while
since I've been here.
Was it three years ago?
You got fired
and rented this place to go independent.
For the opening ritual,
we got boiled pork slices, Choco Pies,
and makgeolli from the convenience store.
Do you remember?
After the ritual and sending Songhee home,
do you remember what we did?
-We kissed--
-Where are you getting at?
Nowhere, I was just reminiscing.
Oh, what did you do on Sunday?
Why do you ask?
My friend's acquaintance lives
at Beauté Palace,
so I went there for something,
and saw someone who looked just like you.
I was just wondering if it really was you.
I was in the office the whole weekend.
I have a lot to do these days.
Right?
Of course, there's no way you'd be there.
That's what I thought.
You must've been mistaken.
That's how I am these days.
I'm seeing things now.
It might be because you're
on my mind day and night.
These days...
I think a lot about you.
Does your new girlfriend know
that you're acting like this?
I broke up with Jenny.
I understand her position.
She knew I wasn't over you.
She told me to make a choice.
And my choice...
was you, Meri.
Honestly...
I just couldn't get over you.
That's why I called
as soon as I came back to Seoul.
Since we're on the subject,
I want us to get back together.
Like you generously used to,
could you forgive my momentary mistake?
I'm sorry,
but do I have to?
You were like this every time we argued.
And I understood
and forgave you every time.
I thought that's what you do
when you love someone.
But not anymore.
It's not because of your mom,
who has always been embarrassed by me.
It's also not because of you.
It's because my mindset changed.
How can love change?
It did for me
because I was hurt too many times.
Is this because I didn't
answer your call in Hong Kong?
-Back then, I was--
-Yes, I think it started then.
I want to be with someone
who's there for me when I'm struggling.
Not someone who wants me
only when they need me.
Meri.
This conversation itself
is ridiculous.
It's already over between us.
Can you leave now? I need to work.
What?
Oh, sure.
I guess you're a bit emotional right now.
Let's talk again later.
I'VE PLANTED YOU LIKE A FLOWER IN MY HEART
CEO YOO MERI
Name?
HANGIL DELIVERY EXPRESS
MARKETING TEAM
What?
What's this?
Mr. Han.
Ms. Oh, Mr. Kim,
I think you need to see this.
-What is it?
-What?
DRUNK PASSENGER DISRUPTS FLIGHT
ASSAULTING CREW AND IN-FLIGHT DISTURBANCES
THE FAMOUS MONK HAEHO DISRUPTED A FLIGHT
Monk Haeho,
famous as a poet and life coach,
was arrested by the airport police
after causing
a drunken disturbance on a flight.
On yesterday's 7:00 p.m. flight
from Incheon International Airport
to J.FC International Airport in New York,
video footage has emerged
showing disruptive behavior
and assault on the flight crew,
sparking public outrage.
The individual in the video
has been identified as Monk Haeho,
a public figure who has been active
as a poet and life coach,
using his influence for good...
Our calligraphy is doomed.
What do we do?
Haven't we finished that already?
Are the deliveries complete?
-When are they delivering?
-Today.
Can you check
if the deliveries have begun?
That's not a big deal.
We can just take out the cards.
The issue is that the deliveries
have already begun.
I just went to check
on the marketing team.
It's like someone died in there.
Beauté is calling
to complain and everything.
If Grandma finds out,
Wooju might get fired.
It's that serious, Mom.
Calls from Beauté?
That's not good.
What are you saying?
With Wooju gone,
I can go back to the marketing team.
Hey!
That deal's happening because your dad
has connections with Beauté's CEO.
We can't mess it up.
This could blow back on your dad.
Gosh, Wooju acts so smart,
yet how can he mess up like this?
Embarrassing his uncle...
Honestly, he's useless.
-Hey, Mom.
-What?
Who will you save
if Dad and I fall in the water?
What kind of ridiculous question is that?
Are you hungry or something?
No, but I think
you'll choose your husband over your son.
You think I should save you?
We already taught you how to swim.
You were taught by the national athlete.
You should swim on your own.
On the other hand, your dad can't swim.
And he only knows me.
Even when I was getting married,
he caused a scene in front of my dad,
saying he couldn't live without me.
I married him,
thinking that it was like saving his life.
Mom, let's not distort history.
Everyone knows
that you were begging him to marry you.
Anyway, Mom, you need to depend on
and trust me, not Dad.
When you get old,
I'll be the one next to you.
Gosh, how creepy.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to bother you like this.
-What did they say?
-Well, for now,
they've put a hold on all delivery men
that they could contact.
But apparently, they can't get in touch
with a few of them.
Texts have been sent,
but it seems they aren't checking them.
It's hard to look at the phone
during deliveries.
We should go.
-Pardon?
-Now?
-Us?
-It's doable
if we split by region
and catch up with the trucks.
It's only been an hour since they left,
so we'll catch up if we leave now.
-We just remove the cards, right?
-Yes.
Sejung, give us the delivery addresses.
Okay.
Ms. Oh.
Here's yours, Mr. Kim.
How are we supposed to do this?
-Where is Ms. Yoo?
-I'm right here.
Ms. Yoo!
How could you let this happen?
I'm sorry.
This isn't Ms. Yoo's fault.
-Shall we get going then?
-Okay.
Come with me, Songhee.
Sejung, you come with me.
I'll go get ready.
Us together?
DELIVERY ADDRESS LIST
Sir!
I'm calling from Myungsoondang.
-You're out on delivery, right?
-Ask him where he is.
Where about are you?
-Yongsan?
-Tell him we're coming.
We're on our way now.
There's a mix-up in the orders, sir.
Yes.
Yes, okay.
Thank you so much!
What a relief.
He couldn't start the deliveries yet
due to the traffic.
Let's go to Yongsan Park!
Here.
I think taking the taxi would be faster.
This is the best
if we are using shortcuts.
Mr. Han, when did you start
biking to work?
Me? I do this from time to time.
-Haven't you seen me?
-You have a license, right?
Geez, my family owns a Chinese restaurant,
so I've been riding one
since middle school.
Hop on already. Come this way.
Good.
Okay.
Here we go. Hold on tight.
HANGIL DELIVERY
EXPRESS
Gosh.
-Sir.
-Sir!
Give it to me.
I'm really sorry.
This was really important.
Oh, I see.
Mr. Han, is this how you do this?
Gosh, don't make it crooked.
-They'll notice that it's been undone.
-Oh, how do you tie this?
Let me. Give it here.
You go like this.
And if you go like this...
It looks weird.
I told you.
Sejung, should we call Ms. Yoo?
Hold both ends.
And tie it once.
Create a hook with your left hand.
-No, this part has to be on the outside.
-Oh, I see.
Like this?
Yes, that's right.
Put this end through the hook
to complete the knot.
And lastly,
just tidy up this middle part
so that it's pretty.
-I did it!
-It worked!
-We did it!
-Good.
Oh, where is Mr. Kim?
I thought you went with him.
I'm waiting for the deliveryman here.
Mr. Kim went to get the package
that had already been delivered nearby.
Okay.
What?
Calm down.
Good boy.
I wasn't trying to steal this.
I'll just put it back, okay?
Hey!
Okay, sit.
Good boy.
Wait.
Such a good boy.
Sit.
Good. Now, wait.
Wait.
I'm so sorry.
His leash slipped out of my hand
while I was parking.
No, it's okay.
I'm really sorry.
-Let's go, baby.
-Bye.
He is so lucky.
I was just about to knock him over.
Why do you laugh?
Nothing. Let's go.
Anyway, where did you get that?
What do you mean, where?
It's my emergency snack.
-Do you carry around jerky?
-Yes.
I've got crispy rice snacks, gummies,
and some red ginseng.
Tell me if you get hungry.
You're like
a walking convenience store.
It looks heavy.
Do you want me to carry it for you?
-I'm fine.
-Come on. Let me.
It's really okay.
Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
It's heavy.
Those shoulders look sturdy.
You should carry it.
Here.
This is for the jerky.
We also just wrapped up. Heading home now.
Mr. Han and Sejung are
also clocking out right at the site.
Okay, I'll see you tomorrow.
Ms. Oh and Songhee said
they've completed the retrieval.
Are you heading home?
Actually, I need to go back to the office.
I have a draft to send over.
I'll drop you off.
WOOJU
It's Kim Wooju.
Pick it up.
We should find out why he's calling.
I met with him already.
Please pick up.
The call can't
be connected. Transferring to voicemail.
She's not picking up her phone again.
Oh, my gosh. You startled me.
What do you want with Meri?
Don't listen in on other people's calls.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm flying to Japan with Mom tonight.
To Beppu Onsen.
When are you coming back?
It's a three-day package trip.
-There's beef bone soup in the fridge.
-Okay.
Don't even think
about contacting Meri again.
If she finds out
that you're marrying a rich girl,
she might cause a scene at the wedding.
She's probably already fuming
because Mom and her mom had a fight.
Mom met with Meri's mom?
-When?
-What do you mean, when?
When you were in Hong Kong.
It seemed like Meri hadn't told her mom
that you guys broke off the engagement.
So, Mom went berserk there and then.
Why would you do that?
What do you mean?
It was to stop her from clinging to you.
Geez, I can't believe this!
No wonder.
That's why Meri is so mad.
If she doesn't forgive me,
it's all your and Mom's fault.
Go and be ready to apologize, okay?
Where are you going?
Aren't you going to drop us off
at the airport?
Hi, Songhee.
I can't get a hold of Meri.
Do you know where she is right now?
Oh, we had a small argument.
You know.
Just a lovers' quarrel.
She's out on business right now,
so she might be hard to reach.
There's been an incident at Myungsoondang.
It's one of our clients.
She's probably
with the team leader from there.
The office?
Yes, I think she'll head to the office
once she's done.
I see. Thank you.
I'll treat you to a meal later.
PLEASE FIND THE ATTACHED
DESIGN DRAFT YOU REQUESTED
DESIGN DRAFT B
DESIGN DRAFT A
That's a relief.
That Wooju doesn't know anything.
But you know there's still a risk, right?
Of course.
By the way,
did you mean what you said back then?
About what?
That you wouldn't team up with Wooju
even if you had to get caught.
Oh, that.
I just said it in the moment.
Right?
I did say it in the heat of the moment,
but I'm sticking with it.
You see,
I thought it through after what you said.
It's a lot of money.
What wouldn't I do for it?
But I just couldn't.
I know. I seem pathetic, don't I?
That's just me.
I'm the kind
who just goes all in, no brakes.
We'll do it together.
Come to think of it,
Wooju hasn't done anything.
You entered the raffle.
And you won the raffle.
I went to the ceremony with you.
It feels wrong for someone
who did nothing to profit from it.
We did all the work.
Mr. Kim.
Thank you so much.
I won't ever forget
what you've done for me.
I was actually really nervous
this whole time.
In case you'd say you want out.
I was really struggling,
but I couldn't tell anyone.
I'm really going to do my best,
so you hang in there, too.
We're close to the end.
Okay.
Then I'll trust you and go with it, okay?
-On the left.
-I see it.
Who's that?
Where are they going?
NO UNAUTHORIZED ENTRY
Are you a resident?
I'm not. I'm just visiting.
Visiting which house?
Well...
This is my aunt's address.
Unit 2 of Complex 3 at Beauté Palace.
Unit 2 of Complex 3.
Okay.
Thank you for dropping me off.
-Drive home safe.
-Okay.
I'll leave after I see you head in.
No, you should get going.
I'll get going after I see you go in.
I'll go in after I see you get going.
All right, then.
Yes.
Yes, I'm on my way now.
I'll look for it in the car.
Okay.
Gosh, he's standing right there,
so I can't get going.
You should leave a bit later.
Since there was a mistake
in the deliveries today,
someone might need to ask something.
Shall I?
I'll leave later, then.
Do you need any hammering or fixing done?
No, I'm okay.
The management office
sorts it out for me if I ask.
Gosh, what if they catch you living alone?
Tell me while I'm here.
There isn't anything.
What's that?
I can hang the curtains myself
since you installed the bar for me.
It's fine.
This is when a husband comes in handy.
"Husband"?
Oh, no. That's not what I meant.
I mean...
Oh, gosh. Are you okay?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
-Are you really okay?
-Yes.
Oh, no. Your clothes are all wet.
I'll do it. Don't worry about it.
It's okay.
I'll dry this while you dry your hair.
Okay, then.
I'm sure it'll dry soon.
By the way, just call me
if you ever need someone tall.
Okay.
What are you doing tomorrow?
I don't have anything tomorrow.
-Do you want...
-How about a lunch...
Let's get lunch tomorrow.
Sure.
Where did they go?
I'm sure they went this way.
That's 7794.
That guy...
What?
So, it was Meri back then.
What's with my expression?
I look so tense.
Next time we retake it,
I'll try to be more natural...
Why would we retake it?
He's out of my league.
Yoo Meri.
Kim Wooju.
What are you doing here?
And who was that man before?
The one who dropped you off.
Did you follow me?
Yes.
I went to your office
because you wouldn't pick up my calls.
But then you got in some guy's car.
And you two went into this house.
That day, you saw me, didn't you?
On the roof.
You did.
Why did you lie?
You said you worked.
I didn't want to tell you where I lived.
You live here?
You lost everything in that rental con,
so how are you...
No way. Are you...
working part-time?
You work as a housekeeper?
Yes, it's my friend's house.
But because no one lives here,
I'm currently managing it
while staying here.
A friend? Who?
None of your business.
Is this that guy's house?
It's not.
Leave.
Open this.
Then who was that guy?
Why did he drop you off
this late at night?
Are you cheating on me?
What you did is called cheating.
Who I meet is none of your business.
Meri, now I know why you're so angry.
It's because of my mom.
I'll apologize
for how my mom talked to yours.
You don't need to.
And I have nothing to do
with your family now.
I told you I'm sorry.
How many times do I have to say it?
Just accept the damn apology.
What?
Do you want me to kneel?
Stop it.
Why do I have to accept your apology?
I don't want to, so stop apologizing.
I don't need you or your apology anymore.
Move.
Let go. What are you doing?
You're acting like this
because you're guilty!
Get out. I'm going to call the police!
Go on because I'm about to lose it.
Are you crazy? What are you doing?
Yes, I'm crazy.
How could you start dating another man
only months after the breakup?
Were you always like this?
The house is that punk's, isn't it?
He's also the one
you were with on the rooftop.
Look at you.
You're flustered.
I got you, didn't I?
Got what?
Get out now.
Were you cheating on me with him?
And yet you treated me
like a cheating scumbag?
Let's see how well off
your rich boyfriend is.
What's this?
-Get out.
-What are you doing?
-Get out!
-Let me go!
I said, let go.
Let me go!
Let go!
Doctor!
I checked your CT scan.
It seems you fractured your wrist
when you tried to break the fall.
Fractured?
There's just a small crack
in your right pelvis and thigh,
not fractured.
Let's admit you and keep an eye on it.
A crack?
Doctor, tell me...
Am I going to be paralyzed
from the waist down?
It's not that bad.
For now, the guardian should assist
the patient when moving.
A fall could turn that crack
into a full fracture.
Okay, but I'm not his guardian.
Meri!
My arm hurts. Come here, hurry.
What do you want?
It hurts so much.
What do you want me to do about it?
Kiss it better.
It seems the VVIPs' response
to the founding anniversary gift
was quite good.
Beauté contacted us
to express their gratitude.
There was some trouble with the cards.
That's right.
I heard from Ms. Kim.
I heard that Wooju handled it well.
It's really thanks
to all the members of the marketing team.
Do your best to support him.
Your job is to help Wooju
lead Myungsoondang.
That's why you're in that position.
CEO KO PHILNYUN
Of course, well noted.
Hello, sir.
She's the wife of the late Mr. Ko.
I don't know
what to say to console you.
Please stay strong.
Have you been well?
Yes.
What brings you here?
To meet with the chairwoman.
Let's go. She must be waiting.
I found this while I was sorting out
my late husband's things.
This was deep inside the drawer.
It seemed important.
FINANCIAL STATEMENT
210,000 TRANSFERRED
CONSULTANT FEE
220,000 TRANSFERRED
It looks like J Consulting
is embezzling some of it.
I found it odd
and contacted our US counterpart,
and the company itself seems to have
exaggerated their performance.
J CONSULTING
CONSULTANT FEE
Yes, dear.
What made you call me at this hour?
I was just balancing the books.
I have to send it to Myungsoondang
by the end of this week.
What do you mean, clean up the accounts?
Mr. Ko's wife came to the company
to meet with the chairwoman.
Start by shredding every company document,
and proceed with the business closure.
Also, close down the restaurant.
Okay.
No harm in being cautious.
But the chairwoman
doesn't know about this, right?
Mom.
Sweetie, you're up.
Do you want to talk to Dad?
Daddy?
Daddy.
Henry, did you just wake up?
How's your cold?
You're all better now?
What a good boy.
Daddy will go back to the US soon.
Stay healthy so we can go camping again.
Be good and listen to your mom.
I can't wait
to see you, Daddy.
Me too.
Director Jang, are you busy?
No, come in.
CFO JANG HANGU
I was just waiting for you.
Thank you.
You can drop the formality
when it's just us.
Oh, okay. Uncle.
Good work on sorting the issue out
for Beauté Department Store.
I've cleared things up with them,
so don't worry.
They could've made this into a big deal.
But it seems to have gone over smoothly,
all thanks to you.
Come to me
if you ever face any trouble again.
I can help you.
Okay.
This isn't ours.
I got it from a café across the street.
It's tastier than ours.
Drink this in secret.
Thanks.
Thank you. Thank you.
Gosh, my documents...
J Consulting America COMPANY FINANCIALS
-It's fine now.
-Oh, okay.
-I'll get going then.
-Okay, thanks.
Seriously.
Meri, my leg.
Be gentle!
Thank you.
You still can't reach your mom?
No, I don't think she enabled roaming.
And my sister's phone is turned off.
What about your dad?
You know he got dismissed
from the university and started farming.
He's been lying low alone in Jeju,
but he's also not very well.
Hey, shouldn't you stay with me for a bit?
Technically, I slipped
because you turned off the lights.
Are you serious?
You're the one who trespassed.
That's a crime.
I could report you to the police.
Since when did you become so heartless?
You weren't like this before.
Yes, I was.
I've always been heartless
to people I don't like.
Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
-Meri.
-What?
Meri, here.
Being in pain is making me hungrier.
I saw a sundae soup place downstairs.
Could you pick some up for me?
You've got a lot of nerve, seriously.
I had it cleaned.
Thank you for that day.
From Yoon Jingyeong.
Where did he go?
I need to give this back to him.
Illegal filming carries
up to seven years in prison
and a 50-million-won fine.
If forensics reveals more,
you'll be charged
as a repeat offender with no leniency.
I'll let you off
since it looks like your first time.
But I won't the next time.
What is he, really?
He's such a mystery.
YOON JINGYEONG
DOCTOR OF FAMILY MEDICINE
REAL FRUIT JUICE
GUMMIES
I've been saving this, but it's my treat
since I am grateful.
Do you know?
You're the first person
to introduce me to sundae soup.
You took me to that famous place
in the Jongno underground.
I couldn't even eat such things back...
It's hot.
Looking back,
I discovered a lot of things
thanks to you.
You also showed me that you can eat
steamed sweet potatoes with their peel.
I was taught to peel everything.
It looks like I taught you
so many useful things.
So, I'm always grateful to you.
You always teach me new things.
Being in the hospital reminds me of this.
In the human body,
they say there are 30 trillion cells.
And 330 billion of them
die and regenerate daily.
The cells that let you down
a few months ago don't exist anymore.
They're all gone.
Now I'm completely made up of new cells.
I'm a new person.
So, Meri, let's forget the past
and start anew.
Okay.
I'll be cool and forgive you
for that brief fling with another guy.
It's not like I'm all that innocent.
So, let's be generous
and just call it even.
What are you trying to pull?
People don't change.
Are you done? I'm cleaning up now.
I'm not done. Hey.
I thought you were done
since you kept talking.
No, I'm sorry.
Just another bite, please.
Please?
Eat it yourself then.
Hey, Meri.
Hey, Meri!
Was the cell metaphor lame?
What are you doing tomorrow?
-Do you want...
-How about a lunch...
Let's get lunch tomorrow.
Sure.
-I'll order when my company arrives.
-Sure.
Hello.
I guess he hasn't been discharged yet.
He will tomorrow.
Your jacket. The windbreaker.
Oh, that's just my way
of saying thank you.
You seemed pretty skilled at CPR.
Did you learn from somewhere?
When I was still a student,
I worked part-time as safety staff
at an amusement park.
Anyway, thank you for that day.
Personally, too.
I saw you make them delete my photos.
Thank you.
I can't grant an extension
to the hospital stay,
but I'll keep a bottle of liquor for you
at your usual bar.
Enjoy it when you have time.
It's my token of gratitude.
It's okay.
It wasn't a big deal.
Anyone would've done the same.
So, no need.
No, I... Wait.
I haven't confessed to him,
but why does it feel like I got dumped?
That felt oddly unsettling.
Oh, right.
I'm so sorry.
I completely forgot.
Is that so?
-Did you have lunch then?
-No.
I'm currently at the hospital.
Are you sick?
No, not me. It's...
My friend got hurt.
I was busy nursing all through the night,
so I forgot to call you.
Was your friend hurt badly?
It's okay. We can eat together next time.
Don't worry about me
and focus on nursing your friend.
It's miserable
when there's no one around while sick.
Okay.
JINGYEONG
Hey, Wooju. Did you eat?
No, not yet.
You haven't? What were you doing?
-What about you?
-Me?
I most certainly...
have not eaten yet.
Do you want to eat together?
Sure, let's grab lunch together.
I'll go to you.
It'll be a break-time
by the time you get here.
Okay.
Meri.
Come closer, will you?
I wouldn't even have been able to go
to the bathroom without you.
Call in a caregiver tomorrow.
They're uncomfortable.
If I'm at unease--
You're not dying.
I'm busy. I don't have time for you.
And if you keep this up,
I'm going to report you for trespassing.
But I'm in pain.
Mr. Kim.
You...
What are you doing?
That's the friend who got hurt?
Yes.
What are you doing?
I'm a patient, so don't do anything.
Where is his room?
It's Room 601.
I told you to call me
if you need someone tall.
Let me go.
I said, let go!
Hey, Meri!
Meri!
Let me go!
Yoo Meri! Meri!
I'm sorry for not telling you
that it was Kim Wooju.
And for not showing up to lunch.
Did you get any sleep?
You said you were up all night.
I'll get some sleep now.
Then, go get some sleep.
Let's talk more
when you're feeling better.
Are you angry?
I'm not angry.
But I'm not feeling great, either.
I mean, why didn't you call me yesterday?
Or you could have told me earlier today.
I'm always asking you for a favor.
How can I ask you to come for Kim Wooju?
Do you have to nurse him?
It's not like I wanted to do it, either.
He's throwing a fit,
and we couldn't reach his family.
So, I couldn't just leave him alone.
Just leave him.
Why do you care for such a person?
After all you went through,
do you still have feelings for him?
No.
It's because...
If I just left,
he'd lose it and cause trouble.
It seemed like he'd do anything
to find that house's owner.
Also...
Even if it didn't end well with him,
he was hurt in front of me.
Wait.
Last time,
didn't you say to team up with Wooju
if push came to shove?
I did.
Right.
I said that.
So, what's with you?
Why are you so angry?
Well...
Maybe it's because I like you.
I don't like seeing you with another guy.
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
Does it bother you
that I like you?
I think I really loved Meri.
Who is Miso?
The name keeps popping up.
She's someone you liked, right?
He's the grandson
of Myungsoondang's CEO.
Can't you just end it on your end, Meri?
Why doesn't
the guy I like see me as a woman?
You got it wrong.
I like Meri.
All is well as long as
Meri is cherished.
It's not because I'm sorry.
It's because I like you.