My name is
Kim Mi-jeong.
I impersonated Sarah Kim.
I killed her to become Sarah Kim.
What did you just say?
My name is…
Kim Mi-jeong.
Did she just say she's Kim Mi-jeong?
Not Sarah Kim?
No, but she's definitely Sarah Kim.
She is.
I've been impersonating Sarah Kim
and deceiving you all this time.
It was to obtain official recognition
as Sarah Kim by an investigative agency.
I disfigured her face
and threw her in the sewer
so that she'd die as me,
and I would live as Sarah Kim.
I admit my wrongdoings
and readily accept the due punishment.
But I'm not sorry.
For that, I'm sorry.
Is it because of Boudoir?
She and the victim are indistinguishable.
She's exploiting that.
If Sarah Kim is an innocent murder victim,
the Boudoir fraud case will be closed
due to a lack of authority.
The key is to prove her identity,
not the murder.
Why are you giving up everything
just to save one thing?
Anyone linked to the case will know
that's a lie just by looking at you.
If that was your plan,
you should've come in with a smashed face!
Why? Couldn't you bear to do that?
Then why'd you do it to the victim?
Detective.
Some people are better off dead.
Sarah Kim was that kind of person.
To those who knew her
and to me too.
Nobody would want Sarah Kim alive.
You've taken action.
I only relayed news of her death.
Let me make a call.
Hello?
Why'd you call?
With Sarah Kim's death,
Nox has control of Boudoir
as the top shareholder.
That doesn't change anything.
You are Sarah Kim,
and you killed Kim Mi-jeong.
You can't prove that.
You donated a kidney in the past.
Luckily, the hospital
still had your tissue sample in storage.
By now, our detectives will have arrived
at the hospital.
I'll go.
We have one hour left now.
I win if the call comes in by then.
If not, you do.
INTERROGATION IN PROGRESS
But you know, Detective,
I confessed,
but I haven't told you everything.
I haven't told you
how I killed her and disposed of her.
I can tell you
the story you want to hear now.
So tell them to stop wasting time
and come back.
No. I already know the full story.
- Only as circumstances and speculations.
- What if they're plausible ones?
Would you like to hear them?
That day,
it snowed heavily.
That day was the celebration
of Boudoir's new collection,
but it was also the day of its downfall.
Because everyone who despised you
was at the event.
Did you start without me, Sarah?
I didn't think you'd come.
We should finish our talk.
Jeong Yeo-jin stated that she spoke to you
as the after-party began.
That was only the beginning
of what was to come.
Because misfortunes never come singly.
Choi Chae-u arrived at the Boudoir party
around 22:40.
She said she had attended the party alone,
but that wasn't true.
She had company.
Find Sarah Kim.
Yes, ma'am.
I wonder why she hid that from me.
Choi Chae-u said she wasn't aware
of your relationship with Kang Ji-hwon.
But in fact, she knew.
You had to get impatient
and make a mess of things.
I'll return your investment tomorrow,
so leave quietly.
And don't get any stupid ideas.
I can hire people too.
I just met someone interesting.
Who?
An Oxford graduate
who's a private equity manager.
Don't freak out.
They graduated in the same year
with the same major as you.
Isn't that wild?
I wasn't a diligent student,
so they probably don't know me.
No, they remember you.
They do?
Yes.
They said you stood out as special,
even among them.
I have a lot to attend to now.
Maybe next time.
It'll only take a moment.
When did you become an Oxford graduate?
When did you start?
Start what?
Conning me.
I saw everything in Sinwol-dong.
So don't be sneaky and answer me.
How much do you know?
Goddamn it!
No, that's not it.
You should be denying it!
How much do you know?
Because of you,
I was prepared to kill someone.
Because of you, I even sold my body
to a woman older than my mom.
But you… Damn it!
You use that to threaten me?
Seriously.
Why is everyone doing this to me today?
You should deny it.
Would you believe me if I did?
If I weren't a businesswoman or a whale,
you never would've looked my way.
If I hadn't been Kim Eun-jae or Sarah Kim,
would you have stolen my car keys?
So I made you this way?
Is that what you're saying?
What I'm saying is…
if you hadn't been materialistic,
would I have deceived you?
So the person who made you this way
is you.
What will make you stop?
Will you stop if I expose everything?
Can you even do that?
You're finished too
if Choi Chae-u finds out.
You'll regret it if you go now.
Then I wouldn't have even started.
Everyone thinks we're strangers.
So you don't know anything.
Chairwoman, when did you arrive?
Just now.
If I'd known,
I would've come to greet you.
By the way,
did you really think I wouldn't know?
Kang Ji-hwon told me
that you two were in cahoots,
plotting to get one over on me.
I only met him a few times
to learn more about you.
I overstepped trying to get
more favorable contract terms.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
You're the one who was betrayed, not me.
Kang Ji-hwon may be on my side now,
but you will pay
for planting a mole on me.
I want a 30% commission.
That is Samwol's final offer.
Would you give me some time
to think it over?
You have until the end of the party.
After Choi got wind of your ties
with Kang Ji-hwon,
she bulldozed the contract
for personal revenge.
She likely didn't want anyone
to find out the truth.
Admitting defeat would be more humiliating
than the damage to the department store.
What do you think?
Isn't this more convincing
than Choi Chae-u's statement?
I wouldn't know.
I see you don't remember.
Screw you!
I hope you crash and burn!
Go fuck yourself, moron! Fucking shit!
- Fuck!
- What are you doing?
Excuse me. Please wait inside.
HOPE YOU CRASH AND BURN
Please enter in an orderly fashion.
We'd appreciate it
if you could wait upstairs.
"Who would've done this?"
No matter how hard you tried,
you had no idea.
You had too many faces
going through your mind.
Hello.
And finally, you would've had to face
the one you least wanted to recall.
Desperation.
Fuck.
And then?
What happened next?
You have no way of knowing.
Only I know what went on in there.
No.
There was one more person there.
The victim, Kim Mi-jeong.
The autopsy is
the victim's final statement.
The victim had a weapon with her,
most likely a tool she was familiar with.
The victim may have planned the murder,
but you had just as much murderous intent.
You had no hesitation
as you struck her face many times.
Take a good look
at what you've done.
You then quickly made a plan
to hide the body,
one that you couldn't execute on your own.
You needed someone
to handle everything for you.
You knew from experience that Choi Chae-u…
could make things seem
like they never happened.
Your answer?
I'll sign.
I knew you would,
so I had the construction started.
I can't leave the luxury space vacant.
Move in this month.
I think I'll start today.
- Come here.
- Lift it.
Why aren't you coming?
Hurry up.
- These too, sir.
- Coming.
Are these going
to the Boudoir flagship store too?
To Samwol Department Store.
- Okay.
- And you knew.
Knew a place
where the body wouldn't be found.
Once inside Samwol,
things would've been easy.
You knew that place
like the back of your hand.
You believed
it would be the perfect crime.
But at the time,
the victim was still alive.
Hello and welcome.
We sincerely thank our customers
for visiting
Samwol Department Store today.
Following the light,
she crawled through the dirty sewer.
We lifted hundreds of the victim's prints
from the sewer walls.
It's proof that she struggled to survive
until the end.
But by the time she was discovered,
it was already too late.
You knew
that the victim was still alive
at the time.
But even so…
HYEON JAE-HYEON, VIOLENT CRIMES TEAM 1
Once the analysis results come in,
there's no going back.
You can't reduce your sentence after that.
I suggest you give up.
What's left for me to give up?
I've come too far.
How did it go?
She got to it first.
The tissue sample is gone.
But who could've…
I've won in the end.
Your reasoning was logical.
But the truth is not like that.
It's hard to take in,
and it doesn't make sense.
I know this isn't easy for you,
but what I'm about to tell you
is the truth.
Have you gone mad?
How did you know to come here?
Am I not allowed to be here?
Others may not know, but you do.
Boudoir.
I made it with my own hands.
I made all this happen.
You have no idea
what I've had to sacrifice to get here.
What the hell do you think you've done?
Stay here until the party ends.
I don't know what I'll do if you go on.
You said I reminded you
of someone you know.
You meant you, didn't you?
Looks like I'm right.
Then why the hell are you acting all holy?
What are you gonna do with that?
Are you going to kill me?
You become me,
and I become you now.
Damn.
Now you're the only one
who knows that I'm Kim Mi-jeong.
Stop talking crazy.
They have security cameras all over.
They haven't been working for a while now.
Haven't you noticed?
I sent all the factory workers
back to their countries,
and I had a hard time
making that place clean of any prints.
Hundreds of people just outside that door
know who I am.
Do any of those people truly know you?
Would anyone even look for you
if you went missing?
Try desperately as you might,
a fake is still a fake.
If you can't tell the fake from the real,
is it really fake?
Ms. Kim,
I'm not trying to be you
because I'm a fake.
It's possible because you're a fake.
What do you know about me
to run your mouth?
It wasn't my intention to kill her.
If Sarah Kim had just apologized to me…
things wouldn't have gotten
this out of hand.
"I'm sorry."
She refused to say those words
until the end.
Please help me. Someone's been…
Please help me. There's someone…
Kim Eun-jae.
Eun-jae.
You've got the wrong person.
If you can't tell the fake from the real,
is it really fake?
Sarah Kim didn't know how to stop.
That's why she died.
Damn it.
Do you truly believe
you can be Kim Mi-jeong?
I have faith in you.
You won't let me be released like this.
I confessed everything as Kim Mi-jeong.
I will retract all confessions
and deny all charges as Sarah Kim.
It's up to you now, Detective.
What's your plan?
It's not just your ass at stake here.
It's everyone else's too.
It's your call.
The suspect's confession aligns
with the entire investigation.
She has admitted to the motive
and all aspects of the murder.
Some facts were distorted,
but they weren't false.
She's the culprit, whoever she might be.
- Yeah.
- She's also not Kim Mi-jeong.
Even if we release her now,
we can verify her identity and apply--
How the hell will you verify her identity
when she has none?
Unbelievable.
Damn.
It's six o'clock.
It's up to you now, Detective.
Will you release me as an innocent person…
or lock me up as Kim Mi-jeong?
REQUEST FOR WARRANT
NAME
KIM MI-JEONG
Do you have a different hat?
Let's go.
- They're coming out!
- They're here.
- Say a few words.
- Anything to say to the victim?
How does it feel right now?
Was there any coercive investigation?
Given the meticulous planning
of the murder before the act
and the willful abandonment of the victim
in a life-threatening situation,
the defendant must face punishment
equal in severity to her crimes.
Considering these
and other sentencing factors,
the sentence is imposed as ordered.
The defendant, Kim Mi-jeong,
is sentenced to ten years in prison.
It's hot.
"Inspector Park Mu-gyeong
of the Regional Investigation Division."
"In recognition of your exemplary service
as a Korean police officer,
we present this commendation."
"Presented by Commissioner Kim Ki-chul
of the Seoul Metropolitan Police
on August 5, 2024."
Salute.
Sir.
I should call you chief now.
- I'm told you opted for patrol unit work.
- You saw that?
- I was going to tell you.
- Hey.
I'm busting my ass to stay here.
Why go there?
I just think it'll be fun.
Okay.
Go.
Yes, sir.
"Fun"?
Dogs are sensitive,
so hold firmly like this and cut gently.
2389. Visitor.
I thought you said
you had no one to visit you.
2389.
How is life here?
You came here to ask me that?
No.
I came to tell you what happened.
Sarah Kim's funeral was conducted
as a Jane Doe's.
DECEASED JANE DOE
And Boudoir
is as successful as ever.
Even without me?
Yes.
That's a relief.
How does it feel to have pulled off a con
against the world?
You got promoted for capturing me,
I was able to protect Boudoir,
and Kim Mi-jeong became Sarah Kim,
just as she wanted.
There are no victims,
so how is this a con?
So,
are you satisfied now?
The only satisfaction in this world
is the word "satisfaction."
I have one last question for you.
It's the easiest question in the world.
The answer is also simple and concise.
What is your name?
THE ART OF SARAH
Subtitle translation by: Yung Un Choi