[wind whistling]
[footfalls crunching]
[wind howling]
[man panting]
What were you doing at my house?
It’s a shame.
[laughing]
You’re such a child.
[gun cocks]
[gunshot echoes]
[ominous music]
[vehicle approaching]
[engine revving]
[door chimes]
[distant background music]
[soda machine clicking]
[distant background music continues]
[sipping]
[camera shutter clicks]
[door chimes]
[car engine revving]
[male voice] What can I do
to kind of venture this...
...the conversation about liberty,
individuality...
...the common good, community.
All these aspects...
[crickets chirping]
[car door closes]
[car chimes]
[door creaks shut]
[chair squeaks]
- [metal music]
- [plastic wrap rustles]
[keyboard clacking]
[chat dings]
- [keyboard clacks]
- [chat dings]
[keyboard clacking]
[chat dings]
[distant metal music]
[chat dinging]
[chat dings]
[jackpot sound]
[intense, dramatic music]
[intense, dramatic music intensifies]
[grunting]
[Never Fight a Man With a Perm plays]
"A heathen from Eton"
"On a bag of Michael Keaton"
"He thinks he's suave"
"You're not suave"
"'Cause you watched
get Carter..."
[knock on door]
[sleepy groan]
[door lock clicks]
[door thumps]
[distant dog barking]
[envelope seal tearing]
[safe button beeping]
[safe lock clicks]
[safe door thumps]
[distant dog barking]
[birds calling]
[distant siren blaring]
[distant dog barking]
[birds calling]
[mailbox creaks open, closes]
"I had things going on tonight"
"But I don't bother"
"Religion [indistinct]
what’s right"
"But I don't bother"
[muffled background music]
[engine rumbling]
[engine humming]
[soft keyboard clacking]
[distant metal door opens]
[looming music]
[low, unsettling music]
[low, unsettling music continues]
[footsteps approaching]
[footfalls]
[huffing smoke]
[unsettling music]
[birds calling]
[knock on door]
[bed squeaks]
[heavy footfalls]
[door opens]
- [door slams]
- [Cole grunts]
[door bangs]
[punch thrown]
[objects clattering]
[punches thrown]
[body slumps]
[Cole groans, coughs]
[blood splatters]
[heavy footfalls]
[coughing]
[panting]
[low, ominous music]
[chuckles]
[keys jingling]
Let's go for a ride.
[low, ominous music]
[car engine revving]
[tuts]
So, you're gonna
do me a favor...
...and then we'll go
our separate ways.
Tell me how you make your money.
- Don't fuck around. [smacks]
- [winces]
Fuck!
It's best to do it
Thursdays after midnight...
...because that's when
most companies...
...run payroll
so their accounts are the fullest.
[looming music]
You drive around
you look for a...
...retail shop or a nicer restaurant
with a certain kind of web code.
Usually outdated shit...
...missing patches,
hard-coded keys.
Minimal or neglected security.
[looming music]
[keyboard clacking]
[chat dings]
You jump onto
their Wi-Fi network...
...and spoof their employee
credentials.
[trackpad clicks]
[laptop beeps]
[looming music]
[trackpad clicks]
The money that I drain
gets moved around fast...
...so it's more likely to get flagged
by the bank or a payroll company.
[looming music]
[Oscar] And what about the people
you steal from?
That doesn't bother you, right?
I don't steal from people.
I steal from banks.
Which is okay?
I don't have a problem
with that, no.
Server got hacked last night...
...and all the payroll was drained,
just completely wiped out.
That's it.
[low, unsettling music]
There's this girl who comes
into the restaurant...
...every Friday night
to have dinner with her father.
Easily the most well-off
of all the regulars.
Last week she steps out
to take a call.
Casually mentions
she has 800 grand...
...in her checking account.
[train rumbling]
- [sighs]
- [car door thumps]
Look, I told you,
I don't rob people.
Okay, that's very noble of you,
but you do now.
All right?
This week... when she comes
to the restaurant,
I'm gonna mark her.
You're gonna follow her home.
You're gonna do your thing, okay?
You're gonna transfer
everything she's got...
...to exactly where I tell you.
[hearty laughter]
Hey, give me your phone, man.
[softly] Thanks.
That's me.
Hey, listen, bro.
You do anything stupid with me
you get hurt, okay?
[unsettling music]
[car door opens]
- [car door closes]
- [keys jingling]
[unsettling music intensifies]
[unsettling music stops]
[keyboard clacking]
[chat dings]
- [keyboard clacking]
- [chat dings]
[keyboard clacking]
[chat dings]
[computer beeps]
- [foot thumps]
- [screams]
[clamoring]
[crowd shouts] Hold it down!
Hold it down! [indistinct]
- [chat dings]
- [keyboard clacking]
[chat dings]
[mouse clicks]
[chat dinging]
Fuck.
[car door slams]
[mailbox clanks]
[mysterious music]
[huffing breath]
[grunts]
[keypad beeps]
- [phone trilling]
- [panting]
Hey.
I got something
I want to run by you.
- Yeah.
- [gun clicks]
I think there's
a kid we can use.
[sniffs, sighs]
[upbeat tense music]
[upbeat tense music intensifies]
[train rumbling]
[car engine revving]
[upbeat tense music continues]
[keys jingling]
[tense music]
[tense music intensifies]
[phone buzzes]
[tense music]
[car zooming]
[car revs]
[crickets chirping]
[computer chirps]
Shit.
[crickets chirping]
- [car door opens]
- [keys jingle]
[car door closes]
[crickets chirping]
[keyboard clicks]
[softly] Fuck.
[keyboard clacking]
[crickets chirping]
[keyboard clacks]
[keyboard clicks]
[door opens]
[door slams]
[footfalls]
[crickets chirping]
[keys jingling]
[car door opens, closes]
[engine revs]
[engine rumbling]
[crickets chirping]
[mysterious music]
[mysterious music intensifies]
[laptop chimes]
[running footsteps]
[mysterious music]
[engine idling, stops]
[car door opens]
[car door thumps]
Checked my account.
- It's all there?
- Yeah, yeah, it's all...
[laughs]
Bro, it's all there.
We're straight.
- Are we?
- Yeah, yeah.
Hand to God,
scout’s honor, all that shit.
Yeah. [chuckles]
All right.
Cole.
[background chatter]
Do you want to join us?
We got weed, we got booze.
We got a connect at the complex.
No. I'm good, man.
I'm not asking.
[intense, dramatic music]
[engine revs]
[upbeat club music]
[upbeat club music intensifies]
[upbeat synth music]
[music distorting]
[snaps fingers]
[muffled] Cole.
- Cole.
- [upbeat synth music]
[muffled] Cole, you good?
[upbeat synth music]
[muffled] Hey, man.
It's getting late.
I'm getting out of here.
[muffled]
Are you sure you're all right?
See you when I see you.
[dark synth music]
[building crescendo]
[music snaps out]
[gasps]
[distant dog barking]
[softly] Oh, my god.
[gulping]
[water bottle crunching]
[water bottle clatters]
[sighs]
[munching]
[gulps]
[cup thuds]
[keyboard clacking]
[keypad clacking]
[chat dings]
[distant mower humming]
[potato chips bag rustles]
[munches]
[keyboard clacks]
[mouse clicking]
[cat meows]
[Sarah] You gonna get her, Tino?
[cat grunts, shrieks]
[background music]
[mouse clicking]
[keyboard clicking]
[mouse clicks]
[chair squeaks]
[keyboard clacks]
[mouse clicking]
[intriguing music]
[mouse clicks]
[receipt rustles]
[forlorn music]
Uh, do you mind?
Sure, go ahead.
[mouse clicks]
[keyboard clacking]
[mouse clicking]
[pensive music]
[utensils clattering]
[waiter] Order 15 is up.
[pensive music]
- [soft background chatter]
- [distant phone ringing]
[crickets chirping]
[Bilson] Did you steal from me?
- [Sarah] No, I didn't steal anything.
- [Bilson] Why are you scared?
[Bilson] Okay, talk me through again
what happened today.
I... [sighs]
I got the envelope.
[Bilson] Stand up when you talk to me, please.
[Sarah] I got the envelope and
I went to the bank to deposit it...
...and the lady told me
that the account...
...had been completely emptied.
You know I care about you...
...but if you make me
take the hit for this
...and I have to cover the damage...
...then you're stealing
from my family.
Is that what you're trying to do?
Take from my wife?
Take from my son?
No, I'm not trying
to steal from your family.
You promise?
I promise.
[light slap]
Let's just say
you did take the money.
It's a lot, right?
Eight hundred K?
Yes. It's a lot of money.
[Bilson] Is it?
It maybe gets you a small house,
white picket fence...
...and sure, you'll be driving
a nice, shiny car.
But before long,
you'll be right back...
...where I found you,
which is what?
It's not where you want
to be, is it?
Sarah, you said
I could trust you.
[whispers] You can trust me.
I didn't steal your money.
- If I stole it, then why am I here?
- You said...
- Why am I here?
- ...I could trust you.
Why didn't I run then?
- [Bilson] You said I could trust you!
- [shouts] I didn't steal your money.
[shouts] But I didn't take it!
I didn't take your...
Ah!
[Bilson] Like I said, look,
Doug's outside...
...and I wasn't lying
when I said I cared about you...
...but you assumed the risk here.
I will give you a chance
to make it right.
If you don't put that money back
where it belongs...
Doug makes you disappear.
One week, Sarah.
[footsteps receding]
[door opens]
[crickets chirping]
[distant footsteps]
[car door opens, closes]
We gotta talk.
- I thought we were good, man.
- No, we got a problem.
- Good evening.
- The guy's not her father.
Money wasn't hers.
- Meet me out back.
- [door shuts]
[door opens, slams]
What are you doing here?
- Come on, man.
- What are you doing here?
- Huh?
- You knew when they were together.
If they'd come here every week,
you would’ve known it.
I don't know what the fuck
you're talking about.
She's in a lot of danger.
We need to give
the money back.
What?
We need to give
the money back...
[strains] [grunts]
We're not giving any of
that fucking money back.
He went back
to her house.
He hit her.
She's a girl
on the side, man.
She knew what it was.
- Hey, do you understand?
- Yes.
Good.
[shoves]
[keyboard clacking]
- [wife] Say bye.
- [son] Bye.
I got a long day.
I'll see you tonight. [lip smacks]
[engine humming]
[low, looming music]
[keyboard clacking]
[chat dings]
[engine humming]
[sighs]
[chat dinging]
[chat dings]
[heavy equipment clanking]
[footfalls]
[device humming]
[male voice] Let's go.
Put him in.
[device humming]
[engine humming]
[looming music]
[keyboard clacking]
[chat dings]
[chat dinging]
[mouse clicks]
- [rifle firing]
- [fire crackling]
[rifle firing]
[chat dings]
[mouse clicks]
[chair squeaks]
[low, looming music]
[box thuds]
[utensils clinks]
[low background chatter]
Thanks.
- Yeah, great. Yeah.
- Yeah.
Hi.
Um...
Can I sit?
Sure.
Have you had one
of these before?
No, I haven't.
Um, they're cool.
There's a marble inside.
In the top.
And just...
[thuds]
[fizzles]
Okay. [chuckles]
What's your name?
Cole. What's yours?
Sarah.
[distant phone ringing]
You're not from here, Cole.
- I'm not?
- Mm-mm.
You're talking to strangers.
It's a dead giveaway.
How is that a giveaway?
Most people here tend
to be from here.
I mean, they're born
into a full setup.
Aunts, uncles, cousins,
school friends, church friends.
So why talk to a stranger?
Much less hit on one.
Just a heads-up, Cole,
with the strawberry soda.
Being cute to me
might get you in trouble.
[waiter] Order 86.
That's me.
[distant phone ringing]
Hey, Cole.
Do you want
to give me your number?
[utensils clattering]
Yeah.
[sighs]
[bell dings]
[utensils clattering]
[distant laughter]
See you around, maybe?
Depends on how much
you like Chinese.
[chuckles]
Thanks.
[bell dings]
[huffing breath]
[phones clattering]
[low, uneasy music]
[slurps]
[ice cube rattles]
[low, uneasy music]
Stupid.
[keyboard clacking]
[chat dings]
[engine rumbling]
[keyboard clacking]
[chat dings]
- [keyboard clacks]
- [chat dinging]
[keyboard clacking]
[chat dings]
[car zooming]
[tense music]
- [keyboard clacking]
- [chat dings]
[keyboard clacking]
[chat dings]
[car rumbling]
You in?
[whispers] Are you in?
[tense music]
[chat dings]
Thanks, man.
- [door opens]
- [electronic humming]
[vape hissing]
[blowing smoke]
[door chimes]
[dramatic music]
[card swiping]
[keypad beeps]
[money rustling]
[vape hissing]
[dramatic music]
[dramatic music intensifies]
[keyboard clacking]
[chat dings]
[low, dramatic music]
[keyboard clacking]
[chat dings]
[dramatic music intensifies]
[plastic box clicks]
[cards swiping]
[pen scribbling]
[dramatic music continues]
[door chimes]
[low, uneasy music]
[plastic box squeaks]
[door chimes]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[plastic box squeaks]
[officer 1] You want a coffee?
Um, yeah.
Give me an iced one.
- [indistinct radio chatter]
- Gross.
[plastic box squeaks]
[low, uneasy music]
[tuts]
[dispatcher's voice]
dispatch... 1I 10-8.
[tuts]
- [strains]
- [plastic box thuds]
[sniffs]
Hey.
Evening.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[shoes squeaks]
[dramatic music]
[vape hissing]
[dramatic music continues]
Yes, I am.
[dramatic music intensifies]
[car door closes]
[dramatic music continues]
[keyboard clacking]
[dramatic music intensifies]
[chat dings]
[keyboard clacking]
[engine humming]
[vape hissing]
[puffing smoke]
[knock on car window]
[light chuckle]
[car window whirring]
Everything okay, sir?
Yeah.
[officer] Can I help you
with something?
- No. I'm good, thanks.
- [laptop clasps]
What are you doing out here?
Um...
...I work for Verizon,
and they send me to...
...places to look for,
uh, dead spots.
I've been getting a lot of reports
of dropped calls in this area, so.
I've got Verizon.
It's never given me
any problems.
Really?
You've had zero dropped calls
in the past six months
...in the past six months
from this location?
Maybe one or two.
Well, that's what a professional
might call a problem.
Now, look, I don't mind you
coming out here to check on me...
...but I really got to get back
to my job...
...so...
[radio buzzes]
Nah. Just some guy
with the phone company.
[engine humming]
[car zooming]
[birds chirping]
[pen scribbling]
[paper rustles]
[pen clicks, clatters]
[birds chirping]
[footfalls]
[mailbox squeaks]
[door opens]
Cole from Chinese?
What are you doing here?
[mailbox squeaks]
[paper rustles]
Uh...
- What is that? I don't...
- It's for you.
[paper rustles]
[whispers]
Okay, how did you, um...
Uh...
I'm... I'm not bad as a hacker.
I can, like...
I can break into things
like computers and...
...servers, bank accounts
and steal things...
...and this guy found out...
...and he knew you had money,
and...
- You did this?
- Yeah, but I...
Do you know how much danger
you've put me in?
No, he put me up to it.
- I didn't have a choice, but...
- Get off my porch right now.
- I'm gonna fix it if you just...
- You're gonna get me killed.
- if you give me another week.
- [shouts] Go!
[paper rustles]
[distant dog barking]
How are you?
[sobbing]
[birds calling]
[vape hissing]
[puffing smoke]
[crickets chirping]
[chair squeaks]
[sighs]
[objects clattering]
[keyboard clacking]
[chat dings]
[lollipop clinks]
[arrow swings]
[chat dings]
[lollipop clinks]
[mouse clicks]
[foreboding music]
[chat dings]
[unsettling music]
[lollipop clinks, clatters
[chat dings]
[keyboard clacking]
[unsettling music]
[gaming chair thuds]
[puffing smoke]
[crickets chirping]
[phone trilling]
[puffing smoke]
[phone buzzes]
Hey.
[Sarah] Wanna come over?
[crickets chirping]
Hi.
You might have saved my life.
He gave me another week.
Did he ask you
where the money came from?
I lied.
[Sarah sighs]
Can I ask you something?
Why do you stay here?
Why not just leave?
Not a question.
[light chuckle]
Do you want
to smoke some weed?
Yeah.
[crickets chirping]
- [lighter flicks]
- [weed crackles]
Good roll.
[Sarah] Hmm.
[weed crackles]
[puffing smoke]
Oh, fuck.
[coughs]
[chuckles] [coughs]
[rousing music]
[sliding door rattles]
[tuts]
So where are you from?
Um...
I...I don't normally
tell people that.
Okay, I won't... I won't push.
It's just safer
in case someone comes looking.
Do you have any family?
No.
You?
Nobody I want to talk to.
How long have you been
on your own? [sighs]
A while.
Do you like it?
It's lonely.
Hmm. Yeah.
The answer to your question
is... [sighs]
I would if I could.
You would what?
Leave.
Do you know
what I really want?
I want to hurt the people
who hurt me...
[whispers] ...and then just...
vanish.
[whispers] Me too.
So where will you go...
...next?
[soft chuckle] I don't know.
- You don't know?
- [gulps]
Do you know
when that will be?
[gulps]
No, I don’t...
I don't know that either.
[sniffles]
Do you think
you could take me?
Really?
Yeah.
Well, what I do is risky.
Eventually
I'm going to get caught...
...and thrown in jail
for a long time.
[low, pensive music]
Even getting what I did for you
last week I came this close.
I came this close
to getting caught more than once.
Well, what if you did...
...one time...
...bigger amount, same place,
all at the same time?
Big amounts don't come
without security to match.
Well, you see, Mark...
...he has three million in cash.
At his house.
[softly] The money's dirty,
so if someone steals it...
...he can't call the cops.
[softly] You could stop,
you know...
[softly] ...now if you wanted to.
And that line...
[softly] ...drawn so clearly...
[softly] You and me,
we could just...
...step right through it.
[panting]
[rousing music]
[smooching]
[dramatic music]
Can I get some fry sauce?
And um, a large diet Coke.
[dramatic music continues]
Hey, excuse me.
Hey, do you like tots?
You want some?
I got an extra tot.
You want my tots? Yeah.
- [male voice] Oh, thank you.
- You're welcome.
You can just have them.
Yeah, I got an extra.
- Thank you. [indistinct]
- Yeah.
Have a good night.
[upbeat music]
[slurps]
- [engine humming]
- [footsteps approaching]
[whispers] Stop, stop, stop.
- [engine humming, stops]
- [keys jingling]
[whispers] Sorry.
Uh, there's a man inside.
In there.
He broke in
when you were gone.
I saw him.
Um...
Okay.
Go inside.
Don't call the police.
- It's okay.
- [whispers] Okay. Be careful.
[panting]
[car window whirring]
[sliding door squeaks]
[floor creaks]
- [screams]
- [Doug grunts]
- [bat thuds]
- [Doug groans]
[gun clatters]
- [straining]
- [Doug grunts, panting]
[strains, chokes]
[gun clicks]
[smacks]
- [grunts]
- [smacks, body thumps]
[punch thrown]
[gun smack]
[panting]
[whispers] Uh, fuck!
[gun clicks]
[chat dings]
[panting]
[shuddering breath]
[chair squeaks]
[gulps]
[chat dings]
[keyboard clacking]
[menacing music]
[gun clicks]
[menacing music continues]
[body sliding]
[trunk door slams]
[engine humming]
[engine revs, idling]
[menacing music continues]
[car door slams]
[trunk door opens]
- [gun clicks]
- [Doug winces]
[grunts] Motherfuck...
[panting]
[footfalls on gravel]
[body thumps, scrapes]
[panting]
What were you doing
at my house?
[gulps]
[sniffles]
[shouts] What were you doing
at my house?!
Yeah, I expect honest answers...
...pointing guns at people.
What about your boss?
What does he know about me?
Not much.
Not yet.
[wind howling]
You could just leave...
...skip town, and none of this
will be your problem.
Yeah, what about her?
I just leave her to you?
You don't even know
who you're defending.
It's a shame. [cackles]
You're such a child.
[mocking laughter]
[gun clicks]
- [gunshot echoes]
- [phone buzzes]
[lipstick clasps]
[phone buzzes]
Hello?
[Cole] I'm in.
But I need to know if what you said
is even possible.
Are you okay?
[Cole] How soon can you meet?
[door creaks open]
Hey
If what you said is true...
...if Bilson actually has
that much money at his house...
...then we need
to find a way in.
I don't steal cash.
I don't do B&E, so...
Well, can you hack
into someone's phone?
Yeah. Sure.
Bilson's entire house
is connected to his phone.
Um, okay.
So...
Here's how we need to play it.
You need to call him.
[phone buzzes]
- Yeah?
- It's me.
Say you want
to see him again.
Tell him you have the rest
of his money...
...and you want to make
things right.
[Sarah] I was thinking
we’d start over.
I really miss you
and I want to fix things.
Can I see you, please?
What did you have in mind?
[Sarah] We can start
with something easy.
Usual place, usual time.
You have the rest of it?
Yes, I do.
Fine.
We're going to need to make
an exact copy of his phone...
...in order to break
into his house...
...so his security system
can't tell the difference...
...which means we're going to
have to get our hands on it...
...without him knowing.
And that part's really important...
...because if he feels like
it's been messed with...
...if he gets suspicious
even for a second...
...calls his service provider,
we're busted.
And we're going to
have to do all of that...
...within a really short window...
...which means we're going to have
to get someone else to help us.
[tense, dramatic music]
[banging on door]
[door creaks open]
[door creaks closed]
So what's the plan?
You're gonna...
you’re gonna break
into this dude's house? [scoffs]
Oh, man, why?
That's none of your business, is it?
Okay, I'm not helping you
or you, I'm good.
How about another 500K
to get you past the million mark?
All you'd be at worst is a doorman
that returns a lost cell phone.
It's an awful lot of pay
for next to nothing.
[menacing music]
If this goes bad and
somebody starts stabbing up...
...you and your little girlfriend
here in the restaurant...
I'm just going to
stand there and watch.
[engine rumbling]
[menacing music]
[phone buzzes]
[engine humming]
I missed you.
The rest of my money, where is it?
You said you'd have it.
[menacing music]
Account transfer info.
Just like last time.
I told you I had it.
Yeah, we'll see.
Come on, Mark.
I'm not giving back
what was stolen...
I'm covering the loss.
[engine rumbling]
[seatbelt clicks]
Hey.
You look so hot tonight.
[scoffs]
Let's talk inside.
[car door closes, opens]
[uneasy music]
Thank you.
[car door slams]
[keys jingling]
[car door opens]
[utensils clinks]
[rousing music]
[cricket chirping]
[vape hissing]
[hushed chatter]
[tense music]
[back door slams]
And for you, ma'am?
Gin and tonic, please.
[softly] Thank you.
Hi.
- [relieved sigh]
- [drink pouring]
[keyboard clacking]
[laptop chimes]
[tense music]
[vape hissing]
In my business,
people try to betray me.
But I don't let them
because if they did, I pay.
My family pays.
I care about you very much.
And that makes you a liability.
And if anything ever
happened to you...
I would be very, very sad.
Nothing is going to
happen to me.
I'm right here.
[menacing music]
[menacing music continues]
[gate beeps, rattling]
Can we please start over?
[paper rustles]
[knife clatters]
- [gulps]
- [ice cube clinks]
Oh.
[sighs]
[paper rustles]
[menacing music]
[distant chatter]
[foreboding music]
[keyboard clacking]
[automated voice] House disarmed.
Front door unlocked.
[tense rhythmic music]
[crickets chirping]
[soft footfalls]
[door opens]
[paper rustles]
Yes. Let's... start over.
Unless you're not
being honest with me.
I...
I have always been honest with you.
- Have you?
- I have.
Because the people I owe money to...
my commitment is to them.
Just like my commitment
is to my family
My commitment to you.
[foreboding music]
I would never betray you.
I wouldn't.
I can see that. Now...
[crickets chirping]
[taps on keyboard]
[laptop chimes]
- [laptop chimes]
- [chuckles]
[keypad beeps]
[safe clangs, whirs]
[door opens]
[laptop thuds]
[cabinet opens]
[drawer opens]
[rousing music]
[zipper unzips]
This will be hard
for me with you.
So hard.
It's going to take time.
But my job, as you know...
...it being what it is...
What's wrong?
[tuts] My phone.
What about it?
I don't have it.
[back door clangs]
[back door creaks]
[back door slams shut]
Maybe you left it in the car.
I didn't leave it in the car.
I had it when I...
- [hurried footsteps]
- [utensils clattering]
- You sit.
- Okay.
[male voice] Mr. Bilson.
Sorry, I believe you left
your phone outside.
[tuts] Yes. That is my phone.
Thank you.
Tell me your name again.
Oscar.
Thank you, Oscar.
I'll make sure to find you later.
[zipper zipping]
[dramatic music]
[zipper zips]
[zipper zipping]
[bag slumps]
[dramatic music intensifies]
[car trunk slams]
- [car beeps]
- [keys jingling]
[building crescendo]
[door slams]
[panting]
[sighs]
[door creaks open]
[Oscar whispers] Hey.
- Hey.
- [chuckles]
[smooches]
Almost there.
We're almost there.
Oscar, he's acting like a psycho.
I don't think he believes
a single fucking word I'm saying.
Look, Cole has the money.
I'll go take care of him.
That's it.
[whispers]
Let's just not hurt him.
Let's just get the money and go.
[soft chuckle]
[rousing music]
Oscar. Oscar.
[dramatic music]
[car approaching]
[panting] Fuck!
[dramatic music intensifies]
[bag slumps]
[dramatic music continues]
[light system whirs]
[bag slumps]
Thought I left the alarm on.
Hello?
[building crescendo]
[wife] What?
You all right?
[tense music]
[bag slumps]
[trunk thumps]
[sighs]
[foreboding music]
The center console. Open it.
[object clatters]
Really, Mark?
Yes, really.
[phone buzzes]
Answer it.
It's just a friend.
I know. You'll answer it...
...and tell your friend that
everything went as planned...
...but now you're going
to meet at a new location.
Answer it.
[phone buzzes]
- Hey.
I just want to
make sure you're okay.
I'm good.
Um, was gonna do the same.
I cleared it all out,
but, um, it got close.
His wife came home for a second.
I just wanted to make sure...
Oh, don't worry.
He's probably off
at a strip club somewhere.
We should probably meet
at a new location.
Just in case.
Okay. [hesitates]
Uh, you’re sure you're okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
All right, I'll be there soon.
[Sarah] I'll text you.
[phone rings]
Hey, it's me. New location.
I'll send you a pin.
[tense music]
[tense music intensifies]
[rousing music]
[car door slams]
[metal clangs]
[engine humming]
Fuck!
[engine revs]
[car door opens]
Lose the gun.
[gun clicks]
[gun clatters]
Out of the car.
[car door closes]
[car door slams]
Come on.
You packing?
Huh?
Toss it.
[gun clatters]
Join your friend. Come on!
[metal door opens]
[metal door slams shut]
Keep walking.
There. Stop!
[footfalls]
[machine hissing]
[heavy door thrumming]
You can have your money back.
It's not my money.
The people you stole from,
when they find out...
...they'll kill your friends,
your family.
Then they'll grind them up
and feed them to you...
...while they skin you alive!
What, do you think I didn't
do any research on you...
...before I got into this?
I have a timed delivery set...
...on the content on
your home computer...
...desktop at your work,
both of your laptops.
It's on the secret server
connected to a passcode on a timer.
It's all your information.
It's all your family...
...all your work...
...all your secrets.
All of it.
If you kill us, the timer goes off,
your information's leaked
to the public.
It goes to the police right away
and a few new sources too.
I will fucking dox you!
[gun clicks]
[softly] Mark! Mark!
[softly] It's okay. It's okay.
[foreboding music]
[gunshot]
[Sarah gasps, echoes]
[screams]
[metal clangs]
[head thuds]
[grunts]
[strains]
[Bilson choking]
[Oscar straining]
[metal clangs]
[screaming]
[strains]
[screaming in pain]
[panting]
[winces]
[body thuds]
[screaming]
[grunting, screaming]
- [blood trickles]
- [metal clangs]
- [Sarah groans, strains] - [whispers]
Sarah. Sarah, Sarah, Sarah.
- Sarah. Hey. Look at me.
- [coughs]
Okay, stay with me.
Sarah, just look at me.
Stay with me.
[weakly] Call my brother.
- [weakly] Call my brother.
- Yeah, I'm gonna bring him the money.
[weakly] Promise?
[Cole] Yeah.
[whimpers, panting]
[chat dings]
- [keyboard clacks]
- [chat dings]
[chat dings]
- [Cole panting]
[mouse clicks]
[hissing breath]
[chat dings]
[mouse clicks]
[shuddering breath]
- You gotta come with me.
- [Reka sobs]
Okay? You gotta come with me.
[weakly] I'm sorry, Cole.
[sobs] Oh.
- Oh, sorry, Cole.
- [softly] Sarah. Sarah. Sarah.
[softly] Sarah?
Sarah, Sarah, Sarah.
Fuck.
[shouts] Fuck!
[sobs]
[Oscar panting]
[metal door opens]
[menacing music]
[metal door closes]
[Oscar winces]
[shuddering breath]
[Oscar groans, winces]
Open it.
Open! [panting]
I'm sorry.
- [gunshot echoes]
- [blood splatters]
[body thuds]
[gasps, exhaling]
[metal creaking]
[shuddering breath]
[car trunk thuds]
[sniffles]
[shuddering breath]
[footsteps approaching]
[gunshot]
[panting]
Are they in love?
[Doug's voice] Listen, kid.
The only thing you could know
about a girl like that is nothing.
[Reka's voice]
Do you have any family?
[Cole's voice] No. You?
[Reka's voice]
Nobody I want to talk to.
How long have you been on your own?
- [Cole's voice] A while.
- [Reka's voice] Do you like it?
[Cole's voice] It's lonely.
She says he has three million dollars
at his house.
Is that true?
That safe. In his closet.
Could be.
You like your boss?
Boss is a piece of shit.
[exhales]
I like my roof.
[panting]
[menacing music]
Where's Bilson?
Inside.
I'll take care of him.
Pleasure doing business.
[menacing music builds]
[menacing music intensifies]
[music snaps out]
`[dramatic music]
"I want to feel it all"
"It all, it all"
"But I lose"
"Control"
"I lose"
"But I lose"
"Control"
"I lose"
[upbeat, tense music]
"I try to stay awake"
"Awake"
"But I lose"
"Control"
"I lose"
"But I lose"
"Control"
"I lose"
"But I lose"
"Control"
"I lose"
[music fades]
[soft music]
[soft music continues]
[music fades]