Miss Xu,
time to change.
I'll wait outside.
Mm
=Echoes of Gang City=
=Episode 8=
(As If Drunk, As If in a Dream)
Mr. Lover.
Tonight's charity gala
is your stage.
Shen Hao and Shen Tingyuan
have way too much free time.
Exactly.
Illegal stock manipulation.
Spreading fabricated rumors.
That's enough to keep them busy.
Your efficiency has dropped this time.
Why rush me?
I have my own pace.
Alright, Mr. Pace.
Is everything arranged?
All set.
Good.
When I see Xu Wanxin later,
hand her the drink.
Yes.
Bye. Take care.
Congratulations, my dear Miss Xu.
The charity gala ends on a perfect note.
Jewels and beauty.
Surely you're making headlines tomorrow.
That was all for show.
Really?
You acted so well
that I was almost convinced.
Maybe
Mr. Shen is a good actor.
You're not bad yourself.
Wanxin,
I need to talk to you.
She has nothing to talk about with you.
Really?
Last time we met,
you were still my fiancée.
This time, you're already
married to Shen Gu.
Don't I deserve
an explanation?
I have nothing to explain.
I just want an answer,
so I can let go.
I promise you won't bother you again.
Fine.
Let's talk somewhere else.
Don't worry.
Let's wait
a few days.
Shen Hao,
say what you need to say here.
Alright.
Wanxin,
we were engaged for eight years.
I know my dad went hard on Minghui,
but I've never done anything
that fails you.
Sir.
Even without the engagement,
we can still be friends.
Drink this,
and from now on,
it's strictly business between us.
Why are you here?
I came to look for you.
Since your husband's here,
I won't disturb the newlyweds.
You haven't finished your drink.
Where are you going?
Do you have to do this?
Wait.
Drink it.
Is something wrong with this drink?
I can't let him leave.
Don't worry.
He's not going anywhere.
Are you Mr. Shen Hao?
I am.
Who are you?
I'm Li Zhengying from
the Commercial Crime Unit.
Mr. Shen Hao, please come with us
for an investigation into
illegal stock manipulation.
It's been a while, Officer Li.
What's going on?
Officer Li,
what is this?
Is there some misunderstanding?
This is Minghui Group's charity gala.
All our guests are distinguished.
If there's anything,
we can talk in private.
Mr. Xu, I didn't mean
to disrupt the event.
But Mr. Shen Hao must come with us.
Take him.
You!
Officer Li.
- Officer Li.
- Let go.
I'll walk myself.
Thank you.
Sorry, everyone.
There was a small incident.
It's resolved now.
Let's head back in and continue.
Let's congratulate Miss Xu.
This year's donations
have hit a record high.
- Great!
Congratulations!
Thank you, everyone.
Let's move to the banquet hall
to celebrate.
Celebrate.
Alright.
No one leaves sober tonight.
That's right.
You should drink more.
You too.
No way I'm letting you off.
♪Who does the wind blow for?♪
♪Reluctant to part♪
Come back in, Wanxin.
It's dangerous.
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appear♪
Perfect.
Take it back.
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
It's strange.
I already returned it to you.
Why is it back?
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
It's exactly the same.
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
Wanxin.
You're drunk.
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way
to be fulfilled one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
Wanxin.
Sit back, alright?
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪
♪It feels like our souls are in sync♪
♪Past or future,
love goes on beyond memory♪
♪When you hold me, broken as I am♪
♪As the stars flow,
fate holds this moment still♪
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
Miss.
Careful.
I'm fine.
Leave her to me.
It's a dream.
Yes.
All a dream.
It's all a dream.
It has to be a dream.
Good morning.
Wanxin.
Why are you here?
Grandfather asked me to come.
- Last night...
After you.
You were drunk last night.
How are you feeling now?
Much better.
Did I
do anything embarrassing last night?
There's lipstick on my shirt.
Does that count?
I'll get you a new one.
Sure.
I'll be waiting.
Let's go.
Don't keep Grandfather waiting.
Grandfather.
Shen Gu is here.
Wanxin,
I'm going to a temple in Shen City
to redeem a vow.
I can also bring your dad's
memorial tablet back.
Alright.
Shen Gu.
Yes.
You come with me.
It's a good chance for you
to learn the way to the old family house.
Sure.
I'll make the arrangements.
So
you're going to Shen City with Mr. Xu?
Yeah.
If Grandfather asked me to go with him,
it means he acknowledges me
as his grandson-in-law.
The latest update says
Mr. Xu is coordinating
with Qingniao Group.
To show sincerity,
he plans to go to Shen City
and meet with you, the president.
He's taking you along to meet you.
So who are you now?
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on no distance
could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way
to be fulfilled one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending
we face?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪