( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(All characters, places,
and organizations are fictional.)
(Children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 2)
(Nua General Hospital)
(Ha Yong Joong...)
(is in the director's office.)
- When did you get here?
- What happened to Momo?
- Who told you?
- Does it matter who told me?
The bends?
She's almost recovered,
thanks to oxygen therapy.
What's her room number?
She's not seeing anyone but her mom.
She doesn't want anyone
to see her without makeup.
She's an actress, you know.
This snowman is too risqué.
(Six Months Before Momo's Accident)
Yong Joong.
Have I changed that much...
that you don't even recognize me?
I guess I haven't
crossed your mind at all.
Confirm the facts, post the headline,
then write the full article.
(Sungwoo Daily: Pop Star A
to Release New Collab with Global Artist)
Let's see...
how the article turned out.
(Sungwoo Daily)
Why isn't it here?
The article didn't run?
It's running in the weekend edition.
The weekend edition?
Act like men, you punks!
And stop picking on weaker kids.
You punk...
Some guy develops one game...
and makes 100 million dollars.
I can't even wrap my head around it.
- One hundred million dollars?
- Who?
Ha Yong Joong.
The guy who created "Lost Knights."
- That's got to be an exaggeration.
- No, it's true.
(Ha Yong Joong,
Developer of the Mega-hit "Lost Knights")
That's insane.
Move out.
- I've gone up an inch, haven't I?
- You still have a model's physique.
There's a stack of paintings in my room.
It's next to my desk.
Got it.
Is she new?
Momo's new stylist. She started last week.
This isn't a fake, is it?
Paul Kim. You've never heard of him?
I was told he's an artist
who was based in Germany.
Did you buy it directly from the artist?
("Scene within You," Paul Kim)
(Passenger Terminal One)
(Bus Stop)
Judging by your luggage,
I take it you've been living abroad.
Yes.
Whereabouts?
(Republic of Korea Passport)
Hello.
The article was very well-written.
Thank you.
Do you need help with anything?
No, I'm good. You can head home.
Hello. Didn't you get the message?
My father in the US suddenly passed away,
so our reporter, Geum Ba Ra,
went to the interview in my place.
(Ha Yong Joong,
Developer of the Mega-hit "Lost Knights")
(Geum Ba Ra, Culture Desk Reporter)
Bow!
Ready for sparring!
Sparring, begin!
(Sungwoo Daily)
(Geum Ba Ra,
Culture Desk Reporter, Sungwoo Daily)
(Sungwoo Daily)
This is Ha Yong Joong.
I was wondering if you were...
the Geum Ba Ra in the fourth grade
at Minjin Elementary 16 years ago.
Yes, that's me. Yong Joong.
Yes, I am.
Can you talk now?
I'll call you in about ten minutes.
(Geum Ba Ra)
Hello?
Look at you, all grown up.
Amazing.
Why didn't you say anything yesterday?
You totally played dumb.
We were meeting for work.
So you're saying you knew it was me?
How could I forget?
Yes.
The nerve! If I were with you now...
If I were with me now?
I'd give you a noogie.
I thought I was texting
with Kim Jeong Ah the whole time.
I figured as much.
I just can't believe it.
How could that little kid...
- I haven't changed, have I?
- Not at all.
An Hee hasn't aged a day either.
- How is he?
- He's doing well.
- Have you married?
- No.
Let's meet up and talk.
You're off work, right?
I'm about to leave now.
We have to meet tonight.
If you're busy, we can meet later.
Bring An Hee.
I don't have any other plans.
I'll try calling An Hee.
What foods do you like? I'll book a table.
Okay, just act natural,
like you're having a conversation.
Could you give me a little smile?
Great.
You're kidding, right?
About never having been to Paris.
I'm serious.
I've never even been
on an international flight.
I spent all four years of college
working part-time jobs.
Yes, great.
Okay, could you stand up for a moment?
I thought you grew up like a princess.
I was wrong about you.
Would you like to take a look?
I can delete them if you want.
If it's not going to run, why bother?
Could you send them to my phone?
I can still see the little kid
you used to be.
I can't get a hold of An Hee.
He might be working.
What does he do for work?
He can't even answer your call?
Take a guess.
I just know that he joined the UDT.
Was he able to complete the UDT
with his personality?
He did.
So, did he get a corporate job?
He's a bodyguard for some chairman.
A bodyguard?
That suits him.
It's the perfect job for him.
Order whatever you want.
The course menu here is nice, isn't it?
And the portions aren't too big.
- The tasting menu?
- Yes.
- And for wine...
- Let's save the wine...
for next time with An Hee.
- Okay.
- And how would you like your steak?
- Medium, please.
- Maybe I'll get the fish so we can share?
- How about the sea perch with caviar?
- Yes.
Let's toast with our water then.
Am I dreaming, or is this real?
It feels like the impossible has happened.
Are you leaving for Italy tomorrow?
I was supposed to leave today,
but I changed my flight to see you.
Goodness.
When did you get so tall?
Starting in sixth grade.
You were just a little kid.
Are you disappointed
I'm not that little kid anymore?
Not disappointed, it's amazing!
You were barely kindergarten-sized
with the face of a four-year-old.
I was really insecure about that.
I was insecure about everything, though.
Especially my height...
Would it be okay to ask...
something like this?
Did you end up getting adopted?
I was about to be, but it fell through.
- Why?
- It's a long story.
There was another kid
you always used to hang out with.
- Jin Ju. Kim Jin Ju.
- Right, what's she up to?
She studied fashion design
and works in the field.
Sounds like everyone's doing well.
You have a boyfriend, right?
What makes you think I do?
I was deliberately
holding back that question.
Are you seeing someone?
Why were you deliberately avoiding it?
I was worried you'd get the wrong idea
and think I was interested.
Using the interview as an excuse.
I was completely honest with my answers.
I never even had the time to date anyone.
But you have plenty of time now, right?
If someone catches my eye, why not?
Are you trying to set me up with someone?
Tell me what you're looking for.
What do you mean?
I'll start thinking about it now.
No reporters, though.
What's wrong with reporters?
You're saying that to a reporter.
You're family first, not a reporter.
So where are you living now?
In a multi-unit house in Myeongil-dong.
It's about 46m².
- By yourself?
- Yes, of course.
What about An Hee? Is he seeing anyone?
He was almost Prince Charming,
but it didn't work out.
Her family was against it?
After his UDT service,
he was a bodyguard
for a conglomerate heiress,
and the heiress he was protecting
fell for him.
A pretty princess or an ugly one?
Come on.
An Hee is picky about looks,
so she must have been pretty.
So what happened?
The heiress even decided
she wanted to marry him,
so he got fired.
Hey.
Liven up the mood a little.
You, sit down.
I'm sorry, Staff Sergeant.
I had no other choice.
When your commander is getting humiliated
in front of his men,
it'd be a dereliction of duty
to stand there and watch.
Now that you're here, have a drink.
I'm not much of a drinker, but...
Get in, Little Reporter.
- Where are we going?
- Don't ask.
We'll go to An Hee's place later.
It's 30 minutes away.
Or 10 minutes if there's no traffic.
The more I think about it,
you're really something else.
How did you manage
not to show any emotion?
Do you know what I was thinking?
"Should I try to hit on her?"
I was so happy to see you and so proud,
but on the other hand,
it's kind of a shame.
If I hadn't recognized you
and made a move,
would you have pretended not to know me
and just played along?
Of course not.
What do you mean, "of course not?"
Come on,
I know you don't really mean that.
I'm not just saying that.
You're joking.
What if I'm not joking
or just flattering you?
How should I put it?
As they say these days,
"Insanely charming."
You're sharp and articulate,
but also polite and refined.
And yet, you're completely unreadable.
That sounds more like you.
You think so?
What about hiding your emotions?
It's not on purpose.
My environment forced me to be that way.
I'm not saying you're jaded.
Thank you.
I really want to thank the skies...
for helping you grow up safe and sound.
Have you ever thought of me?
Of course I did.
Whenever I thought of An Hee.
What about you? Did you think of me?
- I did.
- Really?
That punk, An Hee.
Should I go rough him up?
He's a bodyguard.
I can hold my own in a fight.
We're an even match.
We were the top dogs together,
and we ran the Isu neighborhood.
Why'd you drop out of high school?
I was better at brawling
than I was at studying.
I didn't exactly drop out. I got expelled.
What's with the sour face?
You already knew.
Hey, kiddo.
You look even prettier when you smile.
Yong Joong.
I missed you.
So, so much.
I was desperate to see you again.
Dear deity,
did you finally answer...
my prayer?
Do you still play the double bass?
I see marriage in your future.
You're going to get married.
- When?
- Within five years.
But...
your bride will be quite young.
Very young.
How young?
She'll basically be...
young enough to be your daughter.
What more could I possibly ask for?
- Doctor Shin.
- Hey, James.
Can I get Momo's number?
- You didn't get to meet her?
- I did, but she left for a shoot.
Really?
She's a top star,
so she's incredibly busy.
Or did she just not like Doctor Shin?
- I'll text you her manager's number.
- Not her manager's.
I want Momo's number.
No way. It was hard enough
just to set up that meeting.
I'm Shin Ju Shin.
I'll take full responsibility.
Whose responsibility isn't the issue.
I'll get in deep trouble with her.
She'll have my hide.
Ha Yong Joong's car has arrived.
Didn't Yong Joong go to Italy?
I thought he did.
You should ask CEO Hyun directly.
That's the best way, I think.
Alright.
- Bye.
- Tomorrow at 11:00 a.m.
- Today...
Did the housekeeper let you in?
Your mother gave me the passcode.
She said she was at an art fair.
I feel a little awkward.
I'm not used to doing this kind of thing.
Then don't.
I don't like flowers.
Believe it or not,
some women don't like them.
Okay, then forget the flowers.
There's nothing I want.
I hate them because they wilt.
The flowers I've thrown out so far
would probably fill a few trucks.
Please see yourself out.
Your mother wouldn't give me
your phone number.
Like I said, I'm a mama's girl.
I need my mom's permission for everything.
And I'm really tired.
Then I'll just walk you to your door.
I thought all women liked flowers.
You've only dated that type, then.
Isn't he leaving?
You're just as I expected.
I figured you'd be prickly.
- That's a first.
- They probably just don't say it...
to your face.
I've never really been
that interested in women.
And I don't care.
That sounds like a line from a TV show.
But don't TV shows reflect reality?
What, you think that's a good thing?
A good thing?
Are you proud
ff not being interested in women?
I'm sick and tired of getting attention.
Well then.
Let's be more honest next time.
Emotionally.
- I'd like to get married.
- To whom? Me?
Yes.
- All of a sudden?
- Give me the time and a chance.
I'll earn it.
You think that was honest?
It wasn't at all.
- You're being impulsive.
- I've never been called that before.
Who would say that to your face?
I'll pretend you didn't mean
that I looked easy.
Quite the opposite.
Please leave.
I'll forget this ever happened,
so you don't have to regret it.
I won't ever regret this.
I never have.
You never know.
There is someone I am seeing.
But in your interview, you said otherwise.
And you're not the type to lie, are you?
I do sometimes to reporters.
Have you eaten anything?
A few bites of kimbap.
Then let me order you
something to eat before I go.
You think an actress
would eat late at night?
Aren't actors people too?
Your work just puts food on the table.
So stop that.
You don't have to starve yourself
for this job.
Says the man who got that body
by only eating chicken and vegetables.
I eat everything. I'm not a picky eater.
I thank my parents for my metabolism.
Must be nice.
At least have some fruit
before you go to bed.
You don't have any?
Want me to go buy you some?
I'm not allowed to keep any in the house.
- CEO Hyun?
- Me.
Because you're worried you'll eat it?
Yes.
That's kind of sad.
Though I'm sure you don't see it that way.
(I do feel sorry for myself.)
I do feel sorry for myself.
Even if you were divorced,
I'd still want to marry you.
Even if you were dating ten other guys,
I wouldn't care.
I'll see you again.
Why do you keep switching
to informal speech?
Give them to me.
If you're just going to throw them out.
I'm not throwing them out.
I'm not drawn to your fame or your looks.
I heard from my father that
you were CEO Hyun's daughter,
but I wasn't the least bit interested.
The 20th floor.
This can't be your place.
It's my father's.
But I thought he passed away.
At least, that's what I heard...
when you were nine.
An Hee told me.
You remember all that?
So much for trying to mess with you.
Goodness.
My goodness.
You know her?
You're just getting in?
I thought I told you
not to buy this stuff.
You found that?
I get indigestion every now and then.
Could that be your mom?
- An early morning delivery?
- But do they ring the doorbell?
Oh, right. It must be a fan.
But there's no one there.
Go and check.
Who would leave this...
You didn't order this, did you?
Did a fan leave it?
But how'd they get in?
Gosh, my bladder's about to burst.
(Greek yogurt)
(Milk wafer ice cream)
He's decent, I'll give him that.
Looks aren't everything.
So, does that apply to me too?
Why'd you give him the code
to the front gate?
He's not just some random person.
He's Professor Shin's son.
How could I not?
Moon So Young reads her scripts
just fine without glasses.
She's seven years older than you, Mom.
And she's single with no kids.
What does being single have to do
with her eyesight?
Enjoy your acting career with no regrets.
You can get married in about ten years.
- You think he'll wait for me?
- Not him, someone else.
All the good ones will be taken by then.
What about someone
five or six years younger?
After I married your father,
people thought I was 50
before I went under the knife.
Mom, honestly.
The way plastic surgery is advancing here,
maybe there won't be any old people left.
That's a real possibility.
Nothing's wrong with aging gracefully
as a glamorous actress.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
Says the woman who lived a happy life.
I was happy.
But...
If he contacts you, shut him down.
Don't give him any false hope.
Don't lead him on.
Who is it?
I'm from Noir Hospital.
I'm on an errand
for Doctor Shin Ju Shin, head of surgery.
The doors are opening.
Here.
(The passcode is the first 3 digits
of your front gate code.)
The passcode is the first 3 digits
of your front gate code.
I kept the flowers
and arranged them nicely.
I chose them carefully
while thinking of you.
My mother passed away five years ago.
She left this for me to give to the person
I fall in love with.
I wanted to express...
my sincere feelings,
and it had to be something meaningful.
No matter how hard I thought,
this was all I could think of.
With no strings attached,
I hope you'll accept it
without feeling any pressure.
I didn't admit any new patients yesterday.
But we did get two calls,
one was for orthopedics,
and the other didn't seem to be
a major trauma case.
We got a call from emergency services
in Gangnam at around 11:00 p.m.
A woman in her 30s fell in the street
and started vomiting blood.
It sounded like a viral syndrome,
so I told them to contact the ER.
Her ankle and toes were crushed.
But the ankle was the only major damage.
But the confusing part is this.
There's this mark on the frontal lobe.
I'm wondering if it could be a hemorrhage.
That's calcification.
(Calcification)
Mornings are when I'm happiest.
It's the one time
I can actually eat something.
Is it that hard for you?
You said it was hard for everyone.
When filming eating scenes,
other actors just fake it,
but I actually eat for real.
I'm completely starving!
Seriously, you aced that eating scene
in 'A Maiden's Prayer."
Is that my ring?
It's not yours.
- It was a gift.
- Who from?
Not Shin Ju Shin, right?
Was it from him?
Why did you accept it?
I told you to cut him off completely.
For goodness sake.
He's really determined, isn't he?
He's really counting his chickens
before they hatch.
But you're not going to let...
something as little as this sway you,
are you?
This isn't little.
You'll never get its worth if you sell it.
Send it back to him now.
What time is Manager Oh getting here?
What if something happens in transit?
It's not a difficult surgery,
so please try to relax.
Okay, thank you.
Momo is here to see you, Doctor.
- Any patients waiting?
- There are two left.
- Tell her to wait for a bit.
- You want Momo to wait?
- Yes.
- Okay.
(Department of Neurosurgery,
Angiography Room)
You can go in now.
(Shin Ju Shin, Neurosurgeon)
I'm sorry I don't have anything
to offer you.
I'm here to return this.
It's too much.
Have you never given someone a gift
just from the heart?
I have.
- And?
- This isn't that.
A gift from the heart shouldn't have
an ulterior motive.
Are interest and attraction
considered motives?
Your highest level of education is
a high school graduate.
That's if you don't go back
to theater and film at Korea University.
My mother was also a high school graduate.
She was in her sophomore year of college
when she married my father.
And she had me when she was 23.
She was a very affectionate
and wise woman.
When I lie down to sleep,
I'd always picture my mother's face,
but now, there's someone else
I picture too.
- I want to share my whole life with you.
- But, I don't.
- I'm asking for a chance.
- Does what I want not matter?
I'll scream.
You must've heard that
you're like an onion a lot.
Peeling back each layer
reveals something new.
That's just your fantasy.
What you see isn't everything.
I like a woman with substance.
There must be many women with substance
working here as doctors.
I'm not talking about book-smart fools
who think their degree is everything.
Someone with love...
and compassion...
in their heart.
I'm not compassionate.
But I can feel it.
I can't help what I feel.
You're always on my mind.
How do I get you out of my head?
If you know how, why don't you tell me?
Are your feelings the only ones
that matter?
And what about how the other person feels?
If you've become a top actress
by starving yourself,
isn't that enough?
Study, or do whatever else you want,
eat to your heart's content,
and pack on the pounds.
Because I'll love you
even if your whole body jiggles.
Just don't let your brain get fat.
I'll become your everything.
I can promise you. I swear it.
I'm confident I can be...
a responsible husband.
As husband and wife,
let's live an ordinary life together.
What's so complicated about love?
(Dad)
It's my dad. I have to take this.
Yes, Director.
No, I can't.
The mother of an acquaintance
is on her way to the ER.
Hello.
Oh, my.
Are you here with Professor Shin?
My father has dinner plans.
If you're not meeting anyone...
I'm not. Have a seat.
So this is how you stay in shape?
I hardly ever get to come.
My Momo just loves the ocean.
Since I have you here,
there's something I'd like to discuss.
I'd like to start dating Momo seriously.
And what did Momo say?
- She turned me down.
- Oh, my. Did she?
She said she's seeing someone,
but it feels like an excuse.
Maybe it's not an excuse.
She's so busy,
she barely has time to breathe.
Besides her staff,
she's drifted apart
from the few friends she had.
As her mother,
it breaks my heart sometimes.
She's at an age
when she should be out having fun.
And what does Professor Shin think?
I haven't told him yet.
I was hoping you could help me, CEO Hyun.
I'm all for it, especially since it's you.
I have a meeting
at the Chinese restaurant here.
But I wonder
if Professor Shin will approve.
My father always respects my decisions.
Besides, you two are close, aren't you?
That's a separate issue
from our friendship.
I'll see you around.
Yes.
(Nua General Hospital)
(You have a visitor.)
Who is it?
Yes.
Right this way.
Hey.
I didn't realize
you'd already left for the day.
I wanted to say hello to the Director,
but it's hard to get a moment with him.
What do you mean?
I'm sure he'd be glad to see you.
There's one for the Director in there too.
I just got a full-time position.
I brought a little something.
The thought is more than enough.
I'll tell him you stopped by to say hi.
Where did you end up?
Lim Company.
You mean James's company?
Yes. I just finished
my two-year internship there.
Take it back, whatever it is.
I can't return it.
Didn't you get it at a department store?
It's been over a week.
It's not much, but please accept it.
Stop licking your lips.
They say people who lick their lips
are insincere.
But that's not true for me.
And who gave you permission
to get married?
Do I need your permission to get married?
I'm 24. It's the perfect age to marry.
The "perfect age" now is 33 or 34.
How many times have you even seen him?
You two haven't even dated.
Mom, you told me you and Dad got married
just six months after you met.
You're just hitting your stride
as an actress,
and you can stay at the top
for at least another ten years.
What makes you think marriage is so great?
I'll never know if it's good or bad
until I try it.
You're young.
Have fun and play the field a bit.
Do I even have the time to have fun
and play around?
There's no one else like him.
I'll regret it if I lose him.
There are plenty of fish in the sea.
And how many of those
are actually worth it?
And what guarantee do I have...
that I'll ever find another decent guy
I'm compatible with?
- But you should see more people...
- I've made up my mind.
What about me?
If I marry, do we become strangers?
Would you rather I stay single
and grow old by your side forever?
Shin Ju Shin is 33. I'm 46.
That's only a 13-year age gap.
A son-in-law 13 years younger than me?
The very thought is unsettling.
It's humiliating.
I want to get married soon
and start a family right away.
I grew up alone, and I was so lonely.
I'm going to have 2, maybe 3 kids.
You expect me to be a grandmother
at my age?
Thank you.
Please, feel free to speak comfortably.
All in good time.
What did your father have to say?
He's happy, of course.
Not that outfit.
On a day like today,
you should've dressed up a little.
Given your father's disposition,
I don't think he'd like a daughter-in-law
who's an entertainer.
Not at all.
He was very happy and supportive.
Do you really have to steal my Momo
away from me?
I'm sorry.
Think of it as gaining a son,
not losing a daughter.
Honestly, what's the rush?
You could just date for a few years.
Momo still has a lot of endorsement deals.
They said it was not a breach of contract.
I consulted a lawyer,
and the agency thinks it could be good
for her image.
You've heard that as well, right?
How about an engagement first?
- Mr. Kim, the driver, is here.
- Okay.
Let me see your hand.
You can read palms?
It's not an exact science, but...
Momo's father passed away far too young.
What?
Staff Sergeant.
Staff...
Listen up, Geum Ba Ra.
Things like what happened today
are going to keep happening.
In two years, I'll be gone from here too.
Only you can protect yourself.
So what are you going to do?
When you're pushed around,
are you going to take the money...
and go buy some stupid snacks
and cry about it?
The crying stops today.
You're 11 years old.
You're too old to cry so easily.
From now on,
eat even if you don't want to.
Force it down with water if you have to.
That's how you'll grow.
You're an orphan. If you're weak,
middle school will make this seem easy.
It'll just be kids looking down on you
and picking on you.
You have to endure it.
You could even get abducted by bad people.
I'm going to teach you
how to protect yourself.
So are you going to learn or not?
Harder.
I can't feel a thing. Harder.
Harder!
- Darn it.
- Hey!
Hey, I said let go!
Darn it! Hey, you!
Hey!
Why, you...
Ba Ra!
Hey!
Shoot!
What?
Darn it.
- You brats!
- Darn it.
Get up.
I'm letting you off the hook this time.
Don't try anything like this again.
It won't be pretty next time.
Life's too short for this.
Why live like demons
when there are better things to do?
The way you act is evil.
You filthy orphans!
What did you say?
I didn't quite...
hear you.
You're orphans, aren't you?
We don't have anyone to protect us.
Remember, you'll be expelled
for the slightest bit of trouble.
Unless they attack you first,
don't hurt anyone.
Someday,
you're going to regret this.
You'll be the one crying, not me.
Maybe even tears of blood.
What are you, a psychic now?
How disgusting.
Who are you to lecture me
when you weren't even raised right?
I'll teach that tramp a real lesson
one of these days.
I didn't brush my teeth today.
Hey, Geum Ba Ra!
Ashes, ashes, Ba Ra falls down.
Aren't you curious about the parents
who abandoned you?
If I were you,
I'd search all the mountain temples.
Babe!
Hey, what happened to your face?
I got hit.
Who was it?
A guy?
A girl.
Hey, you piece of trash.
How dare you scar my girl's face?
Keep your eyes down...
with respect.
She needs to be taught a lesson.
- A proper one.
- Strip her.
- Do something.
- Darn it.
Take that!
Darn it.
Hey, hold her down.
What is this, a girdle?
Gosh, that's awesome.
Look at that definition.
You could do your laundry on these abs.
They might look soft,
but they're as hard as a grindstone.
You could really grind on these.
Instead of working your thighs out
at night,
have you been training your abs?
What are you doing?
- Take my girl home safely.
- Babe!
Hey, stomp her!
Darn it.
Hey, move out of the way.
Today is a turning point in your life.
I'm going to make a woman out of you.
Hey...
An Hee.
You don't have to worry about me anymore.
You can rest easy now.
I'm going to sell this house
and donate the money in your name.
And on the anniversary of your death,
don't forget...
to visit me.
I'll make your favorite...
kimchi fried rice for you.
(Present Day)
Come here.
(Doctor Shin)
Tell me...
- your name.
- What am I supposed to say?
You know how it's hard to explain
feelings and emotions.
They said Momo fainted while scuba diving,
but I haven't heard anything since.
She hasn't shown up at all.
Do you think Momo is in trouble?
Confusing, isn't it?
You'll get used to it in time.
What's so great about it?
You've never been into anyone, have you?
It was bound to happen, Momo.
Geum Ba Ra,
are you biting the hand that feeds you?
Her phone's been off,
and Jin Ju told me about the accident...
- Excuse me...
- Go ahead.
What's going on? Was it an accident?
Apparently, he's the one who called 911.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)