♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 16=
Actually,
there is something
I need your help with.
I'm glad to help.
Just say the word.
A man named Chai Anxi
currently resides in Jiyang.
Could you
get rid of him for me?
Xiuluo Boutique
is the biggest
local clothing store.
They also
sell trendy accessories.
Huaijin asked me to find this place.
He said that the guests at the banquet
will be local nobility.
So,
it's your chance
to establish
(Xiuluo Boutique)
yourselves in Jiyang.
Dress
to impress.
Here we are.
Clothes make the man.
Ask Huaijin
to buy you a nice dress.
Cheng Lisu.
Thank you, Commander.
Let's go.
What? I want a dress, too.
Stop being
the third wheel.
They're not really...
Come on.
Let's check out
the herb shop
for your book.
Are you looking for clothes, Madam?
Yeah.
Welcome
to the biggest
clothing store in Jiyang.
Please.
(Daughter of the Censor)
My apologies.
My handkerchief
dropped and disturbed you.
Honey, if you like this,
just buy it.
Sir,
you have excellent taste.
Once your wife
puts on
this lotus-pink peony dress,
she'll resemble
a fairy from paintings.
Sir.
My lady will take this dress.
Miss Yan.
I apologize for
neglecting you.
Madam, perhaps,
you could pick something else.
Sir.
- This one...
- We will take that, too.
Sir.
Are there more clothes in there?
Yes, Madam.
Those are our most exclusive pieces,
including our finest
mermaid-silk celestial gown.
Alright.
Honey.
Please wait here
while I take a look.
Sir,
I'm Yan Min'er, daughter of
Censor Yan Ling.
May I ask your name?
Madam,
this heavenly fragrance dress is simple
and elegant.
And it complements
your complexion.
It would be a nice dress to wear
to any banquet.
- Miss Yan, here.
- You
will outshine everyone else.
Alright, I'll take it.
My lady will take that one, too.
Miss,
have I offended you somehow?
Not at all.
I'm simply
shopping for clothes.
You're overthinking.
In that case,
let's go by who came first.
I've claimed this dress.
If you like it,
the shop owner
can get you another one.
Classic country mindset.
All garments here
are one-of-a-kind.
I have picked this one.
Pick something else.
Are you going to pick
whatever I choose
from now on?
Well,
it depends on how I feel.
Sir.
This, this, and these two...
My lady will take them all.
Well...
Madam, will you...
Don't worry, sir.
I wanted to say that
I picked those dresses
for this young lady.
You tricked me.
Do you have any idea who I am?
No, I don't.
But I'm sure you're from
a wealthy family.
However,
your upbringing seems lacking.
You should know
that those who rest
on their ancestors' laurels
may squander their inheritance.
You...!
What happened?
Sir,
I merely picked the same dress
as this lady.
If she truly
likes this dress,
I'll give it up.
But
she toyed with me
on purpose,
which made me feel humiliated.
I was asking my wife.
I only trust her.
Didn't you mention
a collection piece?
Bring it for my wife.
Naturally,
she deserves only
the finest garments.
Please follow me.
Sir,
I dare say that this gown
doesn't exist
anywhere else throughout Wei.
The fabric
was purchased at great cost
from an overseas merchant.
But the true marvel
lies in the detachable shawl.
Steeped in alchemical solutions,
it's impenetrable.
It looks nice
and offers
protection.
If you like it,
let Madam try it on.
How much is it?
One hundred.
Miss,
we should leave.
Master will punish you
for spending a fortune
on one dress.
Only a hundred.
As long as it pleases my wife,
it's worth it.
Does it look good?
Yeah.
Miss,
settle your bill.
It's a small business
that relies
on your generous patronage.
Pay up.
Thank you.
Sir,
I've helped
with your business.
Won't you thank me?
Thank you, Madam.
Alright.
I'll take you along next time.
That's a promise, then.
So you came alone?
Min'er.
Isn't it
Xiuluo Boutique's latest design?
So pretty.
Of course.
No one brings out its elegance
better than you, Min'er.
They'll be here.
Mr. Cui's nephew and niece-in-law
have such a lofty air.
They're so late
for the banquet.
I heard
they're from Wuzhou.
Small-town folks lack etiquette.
They've probably never been to banquets.
Who knows how they will embarrass
themselves?
Yeah.
Alright.
This is Master's
nephew Qiao Huanqing,
and our niece-in-law
Wen Yuyan.
Please be seated.
Come on.
Qiao Huanqing is so handsome
with refined grace.
But his wife
is utterly detestable.
She offended you?
Don't worry.
I'll put her in her place.
What's wrong?
Originally there was nothing.
Where could dust arise?
What a lady-killer.
Mr. Cui,
let me toast you.
Cheers.
It's nice.
Come on.
Honey.
I'd like some soup.
Would you serve me a bowl?
No wonder you're furious.
She does employ cunning tricks.
Mrs. Qiao.
You're too delicate,
relying on your husband
for every little thing.
You haven't been married yet.
So you don't get
the playful intimacy.
Or perhaps
you wish to be
neglected
by your future husband?
A woman must
demonstrate dignified conduct
to earn her husband's respect.
You're merely
relying on your looks
to play the temptress.
Mr. Qiao, you must be careful
not to be tempted by mere appearance.
I am
playing the temptress?
So she's into me,
and not you?
Maybe you made quite an impression
at Xiuluo Boutique,
making her
thoroughly captivated.
Tell you what.
Save the snide remarks.
She was obviously infuriated
because
you spent a fortune on that dress
you bought me.
I bet she's going to
look for trouble again.
This is all your fault.
Weren't you very confident?
Now you fear trouble?
Mr. Cui,
at this joyous
family reunion,
I volunteer
to play a musical piece
for celebration.
Alright.
Xiu is renowned as Jiyang's
most talented lady.
You're in for a feast
for the ears.
Bring the zither.
Exquisite playing.
Beautiful.
Wonderful.
- Marvelous.
- Good.
I hope you liked it.
Here we go.
We've heard Mrs. Qiao
is renowned in Wuzhou
for her peerless musical talents.
Fate brought us here today.
May I have
the honor of admiring your music?
You are indeed
a peerless zither artist.
I would rather not embarrass myself.
Mrs. Qiao.
I also wish to appreciate
your zither music.
If Xiu alone
can't convince you to play,
can I change your mind?
Help me out.
Didn't you learn a piece?
I also learned circus stunts.
Mrs. Qiao, what do you say?
The elders are waiting.
Indeed.
Will you help or not?
No.
Honey.
Speak properly.
So you're helping me?
Yuyan,
are you not interested
in the zither?
To be honest,
we made a vow when we
got married.
My wife's zither skills are exceptional,
but
she only plays for me.
Therefore,
she can't fulfill
your wishes today.
But you reunited
with Mr. Cui today.
Why can't you make
one exception
for all the guests here?
My promise to my wife
is unbreakable.
If you insist,
I'll play instead.
You can play the zither?
Only passably.
Our ancestors were all military men.
We've never cultivated
such a refined talent.
Attendants.
Clean the zither.
No need.
I have mine.
(Isn't it the zither I gave him?)
Beautiful.
Well...
Xiao Jue,
do you like me?
(It's hard)
(to find someone)
(more outstanding)
(and prettier than him.)
What a gentleman.
Wonderful.
Huanqing,
your music left us spellbound.
Her Highness
praised Miss Xiu
as Jiyang's finest musician.
Had she heard your performance,
she would've showered you with praise.
Indeed.
It appears that
Mr. Cui is accepting Mr. Qiao,
so we can't treat him
as a mere merchant.
So what?
He's still a merchant
without manners
who has offended you.
You're right.
We should
teach them a lesson.
Thank you.
In fact,
my zither skills
are nothing
compared to my wife's mastery.
Really?
Yuyan,
you must be
a zither master.
My husband spoils me.
He indulges my every whim
and exaggerates my skills.
At first,
I only found you handsome.
But now I feel
that you do resemble
my late elder brother.
Meanwhile,
your temperament resembles mine.
You're truly my family.
I once held you when you were
a newborn.
Then you went missing.
Your parents never let go
until they died.
If they knew
you had turned out to be outstanding,
they'd be overjoyed.
Sorry.
Why did I bring up
the sad stories?
Right?
Huanqing, Yuyan.
You're here just in time
for the Start of Spring,
which marks Jiyang's Water God Festival.
You must go out
and look around.
You'll never
want to leave after that.
Start of Spring?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It happens to be
my birthday
a few days after that.
What a coincidence.
Really?
Fate binds you
to Jiyang, as you were born
so close
to the Water God Festival.
Huanqing,
we must
celebrate her birthday
properly.
Alright.
Master.
Yuyan,
may I have a word?
Alright.
Excuse me for a second.
Those young ladies are waiting
for you in the garden.
What for?
They are
local noble ladies
who genuinely wish to hear your music.
So, they are
waiting earnestly.
Since those noble ladies
are so earnest,
I'll certainly meet them.
Alright, let's go.
A maiden departs,
a world away from kin.
- Look.
- Mrs. Qiao is here.
I hear you noble ladies
- are waiting for me.
- Mrs. Qiao.
Not exactly.
We are simply having
casual conversations.
I hope
you don't mind our intrusion.
The weather's fine.
How about
we host
a poetry exchange here?
Firstly for fun,
secondly
to admire Mrs. Qiao's literary talents.
(Is she)
(holding a grudge)
(over the dress?)
I have no desire
for poetry, chess,
or calligraphy.
Nor will I
play the zither.
Do you disdain our company?
You got me wrong.
Would you like to talk about
something
more entertaining?
I hear Miss He
is pestered
by those noble ladies.
Can't you walk faster?
What if
they tear her apart
and devour her alive?
Even against ten men,
let alone women,
she'd still prevail.
What do you know?
Mean words
hurt worse than blades.
Didn't you hear me?
Walk faster.
Hurry up.
I know
you're concerned about
my married life with my husband.
True.
We're deeply
in love.
I have
a terrible temper
and get sulky all the time.
My husband
has no choice but to appease me.
He makes noodles for me
and buys me jewelry
and clothes.
You were there
when he was picking clothes for me,
weren't you, Miss Yan?
Therefore,
what's the point
of learning the arts?
When I'm angry,
my husband
plays the zither
to cheer me up.
What you've glimpsed
is merely the tip of the iceberg.
The unseen devotion
overflows endlessly.
Such an extraordinary man,
peerless among his contemporaries,
chooses to shower affection
solely on me,
seeing no one else.
Tell me.
What can I do?
My bad.
She doesn't need us.
Let's go.
Since we're here,
let's hear
what other nonsense
she can spout.
So,
you're free to learn
all those arts.
But you should
learn those for your own pleasure.
If you want to please men,
you'd better study
the art of taming a husband.
The art of taming a husband?
Tell us
what that is about.
Yeah.
My husband and I met
during the Lantern Festival
very briefly.
We barely crossed paths.
However,
he came to propose the very next day,
vowing to marry no one but me.
He even threatened
to hang himself
if I refused.
I thought
I might as well do a good deed
and save his life.
Besides,
even the most virtuous woman
can't resist a persistent suitor.
He pestered me relentlessly,
so I had to marry him.
You know what?
The key to taming a man
boils down to
one principle.
What is it?
You may love him,
but never lose yourself.
In relationships,
men and women should be equal.
In trivial matters,
one may take the upper hand,
another the lower.
It's just like warfare.
If you constantly
prioritize him,
things may not end well.
Treat yourself well,
and love will find you naturally.
Take me,
for example.
I never try to
fawn over my husband,
but he treasures me dearly.
That's what I've achieved.
I don't understand
what she's saying,
but it sounds impressive.
Then, memorize
everything she says.
What nonsense?
Women must adhere
to the norms
and obey their husbands
once they're married.
You are spouting nonsense here.
Aren't you ashamed?
Everyone should
treat each other with equality
and respect.
Why'd I be ashamed?
Or perhaps,
you believe that
you're born inferior to men.
Women shouldn't
be confined to
inner chambers.
The world is vast.
We deserve
a broader horizon.
But...
But we don't know
where to begin.
Travel ten thousand miles,
read ten thousand books.
If it's difficult to travel,
start with reading.
We do read regularly.
But there are
many other books to read
beyond the ones
guiding you to be ladies.
For example,
we could read the books
men read.
Yeah.
Take me, for example.
I embrace all kinds
of knowledge.
I've even studied images
with my husband.
- What images?
Erotic...
Honey.
Images.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm just
having tea
with these ladies.
Sisters,
I'll take my leave.
I've never
seen someone so vulgar.
It's exhausting.
I sat upright all day.
Acting like a woman is such a challenge.
It's much worse
than a full day's training.
Acting like a woman?
As if you're not
a woman.
Whose reputation
are you trying to ruin?
Yours
or mine?
Sorry, Commander.
But I just don't get it.
Jiyang City
is governed by Her Highness.
But why are the local women
still bound by
those outdated norms?
But then again,
women have been
confined
for thousands of years.
How could they
change overnight?
How can I blame them?
Your good looks caused trouble,
and I bore the consequences.
Commander,
didn't you eat enough
at the banquet?
Someone was flustered
at the banquet
because of Ling Xiu
and barely had food.
So, these
are for me?
Thank you, Commander. You're so sweet.
You're the best person
in the world.
Let's eat together.
Dig in.
Cut the flattery.
Is your birthday
really coming soon?
According to the registry,
it's in the summer.
I just made it up.
What if
Mr. Cui gives me
a birthday gift?
It's my chance to make
a good profit.
Liar.
What is it?
Commander.
We've located Chai Anxi.
If you come along in this dress,
you may
arouse suspicion.
Alright.
Go ahead.
Hurry up.
You'll regret it
if I change my mind.
Have you seen a man
in his forties
with a limp
on his left leg?
No.
He is crucial to us.
He's served in the army.
If you spot him
one day,
inform us.
We'll reward you.
Commander.
Cuiwei Pavilion
is a jewelry shop.
A fire broke out
two hours ago.
The owner and the workers
all survived.
Only the new accountant
with immobility
died in there.
And the body?
It's inside.
Want to see it?
If I'm not mistaken,
the body
must be unrecognizable.
Indeed.
That is not
Chai Anxi.
Commander.
Are you saying
that he set the fire
and faked his death?
Makes sense.
If I were Chai Anxi,
who's wanted by the authorities,
I'd fake my death
rather than
waiting to be caught.
Security
was tightened in Jiyang City
after the fire.
Chai Anxi is injured.
He must be hiding in the city.
I'll send people
to search for him.
We must hurry.
Chu Zhao also has eyes
fixed on Chai Anxi.
We must beat him to it.
They beat us to it.
Should we go in?
No need.
Didn't you
gather enough
information?
The witness only mentioned
that someone died.
That was convenient.
Chai Anxi
is prudent and cunning.
This is merely
a smokescreen.
Let's go.
We can't be spotted
by Xiao Jue.
Watch out.
Young Master!
(Xu)
Let him go.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Weird guy.
He stalked us,
suddenly attacked,
and fled in haste.
What does he want?
Fashioning weapons from bones
is a Wutuo custom.
He's from Wutuo.
But why was he
interested in Chai Anxi?
And why
did he spare my life?
Anyway,
watch Xiao Jue's men.
When the time comes,
we'll strike first.
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪