ظآزThat dayظآز
ظآزNothing stays together foreverظآز
ظآزI've quit romanceظآز
ظآزWho hasn't failed againظآز
ظآزCrying in deathظآز
ظآزAnd in lifeظآز
ظآزEven nowظآز
ظآزWe keep learningظآز
ظآزIt's no surpriseظآز
ظآزBeing happy is so hardظآز
ظآزWeirdly, I became a role modelظآز
ظآزOn the day we met again, we said hiظآز
ظآزIt was a reminder,
a test, and a complaintظآز
ظآزWho can do anything without regretظآز
ظآزI am all rightظآز
ظآزMay you live in peaceظآز
ظآزLet the world roarظآز
ظآزSounds like a carnivalظآز
ظآزBeing alive is never dullظآز
ظآزHow wonderful to be freeظآز
ظآزI became even better without youظآز
ظآزNothing can be perfectظآز
ظآزWe bless each other in painظآز
ظآزWe nod and smileظآز
ظآزMay we both be wellظآز
= Love's Ambition=
=Episode 29=
Mr. Shen, your guest is here.
Haoming.
Mr. Qu.
Long time no see.
Come, give me a hug.
You're still the same.
Not really.
But you are more handsome.
Why didn't you tell me earlier
that you came to me?
Chen Lin could've picked you up.
The driver can also bring me here.
Alright, please have a seat.
Your office is quite spacious
and splendid.
Jinda is indeed splendid.
Have you
met my dad?
I visited your dad long ago.
He invited me
to a meeting,
but I wasn't interested,
so I came to you right away.
Glad to see you.
Dahongpao Tea from Mount Wuyi.
Haoming,
it's been years,
yet you still remember my preference.
I remember
when my dad took me
to Guangdong as a child,
you were the one who took me
to tea houses
to drink Dahongpao Tea.
How is it?
Excellent!
Haoming,
I have
devoted most of my life
to Jinda.
To be honest,
I haven't managed my family well.
And I'm still a bachelor.
I've
watched you grow up.
In my eyes,
you're like my own son.
Mr. Qu.
You are my dad's best friend.
Your dedication to Jinda
has been witnessed by all.
Without your efforts
in the Greater Bay Area,
we wouldn't have achieved that much.
As a junior,
I must learn from you.
I just did what's right.
Haoming.
This time, I came
for one purpose only.
I heard you joined the board,
so I came specially to vote for you.
All these years,
I've always supported your dad.
Now, of course,
I offer you my support.
Don't feel burdened.
Just do what you want.
Thank you, Mr. Qu.
Here. Haoming.
Let's toast.
How's it going?
We've been acquiring
stocks from Jinda's retail investors.
But we still don't
have enough stocks.
Several major shareholders
are reluctant to sell.
I'll figure it out.
If you can uncover that child's
connection to Shen Haoming,
then things
will be much easier.
Weiping and I are working on it.
I need results.
Understood, Mr. Qu.
My people have found out
that Shen Haoming
and Fang Yu did have a child
while studying abroad.
During Fang Yu's pregnancy,
Haoming stayed with her.
But after returning from abroad,
Shen Haoming
remained single.
Where was the child?
Not long after Shen Haoming's returning,
Shen Jinsong and Yu Lan
publicly announced they had given birth
to a second child overseas.
Guess who
the biological father
of this child actually is.
Maybe Shen Haochen isn't
Shen Haoming's
younger brother,
but his son, right?
If this gets exposed...
Chen Lin,
I never thought Mr. Shen's
entry into the board
would go so smoothly.
Of course.
Mr. Shen
truly deserves it.
Thanks.
Now,
all these board members
invite him to dinners.
We have to accompany him
in tonight's dinner.
Why did you sigh?
I need to drive Mr. Shen home.
Today is my girlfriend's birthday.
She has warned me
that if I don't show up,
I'll be off her list.
You have to choose
between career and love.
I am so worried.
Don't worry.
As you are in dilemma,
after tonight's dinner,
I'll drive Mr. Shen home.
But your hand is injured.
Minor injury. No problem.
Leave it to me.
Don't worry.
Seriously?
I'll arrange a driver
to send you both.
I'll go
to request leave now.
Thanks.
You help me a lot.
I'll treat you to a meal.
Mr. Shen, here.
You're home.
Here.
Thanks.
I'll help you up.
You don't need to come up.
Are you okay?
Sure.
Be careful.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Shen Haoming's child
had a paternity test in London.
(Where is the test report?)
Verification failed.
Please try again.
(Not his birthday.)
Verification failed. Please try again.
(Not his phone number.)
Failed.
(Not license plate.)
Please try again.
(Come on.)
(I've)
(failed three times.)
(Another failure triggers the alarm.)
(September 20, 2023)
Verification passed.
(Probability of paternity: 99.997%)
(Jinda Group)
Though it's pixelated,
this building
is our company, right?
(Passing Off Illegitimate Son
as Younger Brother)
He has a son out of wedlock?
His family helped cover it up?
Our company
has such a scandalous executive?
(Jinda Group Executive Shen Haoming
Passed Off Illegitimate Son as Brother)
This happened so long ago.
Why is it revealed now?
Especially when Haoming
just joined the board.
Hello.
Chairman,
shareholders want
an emergency board meeting.
Come with Mr. Shen
to the company now.
Understood.
Mom.
I know.
Liu,
where is Haochen?
Shen Haochen is in school.
Ten minutes ago,
he got there.
Turn around and bring him home.
Chen Lin.
Find someone
to remove all related news immediately.
Inform the press
this involves a minor
and I can file a lawsuit anytime.
Lin.
Yan.
Have you seen this?
What?
I'm going out.
Cancel my schedule today.
Okay.
Be careful.
(Jinda Group Executive Shen Haoming
Passed Off Illegitimate Son as Brother)
My dad saw the news
when he was driving me here.
My dad even knows his brother.
Wait.
Now it's his dad.
My mom saw it too.
It's all over the internet now.
Our class
has a celebrity.
What are you talking about?
Shen Haochen,
you've become
a celebrity now.
What do you mean?
Don't tell me you didn't know
your brother is your dad?
Don't talk nonsense!
Or I'll beat you to death!
Stop it!
Shen Haochen.
I got a call from your family.
You have one day off.
Go home with Mr. Liu.
Thank you, Miss.
Haochen, come with me.
Mr. Liu.
Give me your phone.
(Jinda Group Executive Shen Haoming
Passed Off Illegitimate Son as Brother)
Mr. Qu.
After exposure of Shen Haochen being
Shen Haoming's illegitimate son,
Jinda Group's stock price
has dropped by 5.63 percent,
losing at least
two billion market value.
The Investment Department
suggests now is the time
for a low-price acquisition.
Tell them to start.
Okay.
Mr. Qu came
from out of town today.
Thank you.
Alright.
Today, everyone is present.
Let's begin then.
On behalf of everyone,
I have a question.
Online rumors say
Haochen isn't your son,
but Haoming's illegitimate son.
Is that true
or not?
Regarding this,
since its release online,
in just three hours,
our stock price has been
continuously dropping.
This has caused Jinda Group
a huge loss.
If it's fake,
we must immediately
issue a response.
Make a statement where necessary,
and prevent
the further loss.
How could this be fake?
There is a paternity test report.
In my opinion,
it's most likely true.
I wonder
what the truth is.
Chairman.
At this critical moment,
just tell us the truth.
- Exactly.
Jinsong,
all of us have followed you
and suffered a lot
to build Jinda
from scratch.
After the company grew,
we all agreed
to let you take leadership,
because we believe
you are trustworthy
and could lead us all
to make Jinda
thrive smoothly.
When this news broke out,
we couldn't believe
our own eyes.
But the paternity test report
is solid evidence,
leaving no room for doubt.
As a long-established
construction group,
if we lack basic ethical principles,
how can we face the public?
What reputation remains?
What credibility remains?
This damages our group's
public image.
Hear me out.
My clients are pushing for answers.
Are you my dad?
We're in session.
Leave for now.
Answer me,
are you my dad?
We're in session.
Get out!
No!
- Tell me now!
- Get out!
No!
- No!
- Get out!
No!
Are you my dad?
Take him away.
Answer me,
are you my dad?
Let me go!
Answer my question!
Are you my dad?
Whose son am I really?
Let me go!
Answer me.
Are you my dad?
Who is my real dad?
I just want to know
if the online news
is true.
Are you my dad?
Tell me!
Haoming.
Mom.
I went to Haochen's school.
His teacher said
the driver picked him up.
He came to the office alone.
Don't worry. He's safe.
Okay.
I'll arrange his ride home.
If you're my dad,
why tell me you're
my brother?
Where's my mom?
Who is she really?
Why did you lie?
Do you never
want me at all?
I understand you have
questions right now.
Go home first.
We'll talk later.
Chen Lin,
drive Haochen home.
Yes, Mr. Shen.
The board wants you
to return to the meeting right away.
Besides,
many reporters
are in the lobby.
Bring my car to the underground garage.
Don't let any reporter
approach Haochen.
Got it.
Don't overthink.
Ignore the online news.
Wait for me.
The Chairman's family matters
shouldn't concern us,
but you father and son
are our core leadership.
Your every action
reflects the image,
reputation, and integrity of the group.
Jinsong,
any solutions?
Just tell us
and be honest to us.
Let us know clearly.
Don't drag this on.
Exactly.
We must
address this problem.
You've caused us pressure
while tricking customers.
Exactly.
Your silence
leaves us unable to explain anything.
You must explain to us.
Haoming.
Dad, are you feeling unwell?
The Chairman isn't well.
Let's end it for now.
Listen to me.
The Chairman isn't feeling well.
No matter what,
we shouldn't pressure him.
Anyway,
this situation can't get worse.
Let's wait and see.
Let's see how long
he can stall.
Dad. Take the medicine.
Put it there.
Chairman, Mr. Shen.
What's wrong?
Several companies
are acquiring
large quantities
of Jinda's stocks.
The main buyer is Situo Construction.
It is the one
that competed with us
for the Baraikin project.
How many stocks?
3.7 percent of stocks,
and it's increasing.
Haoming.
Initiate buybacks immediately.
This shows market
our confidence.
Shen Haochen!
Haochen!
(Secretary Chen)
Hello.
Mr. Shen,
Haochen opened the car door
during a red light and ran off.
He disappeared
before I could catch up.
Haochen.
Why are you here?
Mr. Han.
I know what happened today.
You must feel
terrible now.
Come on, I'll take you home.
No.
Do you want to know who your mom is?
Yes!
I'll take you to see her.
We're here.
Didn't you say
to see my mom?
Why bring me here?
To protect your mom's identity
from revealing.
I got it.
Now,
I'll take you in
and get some rest.
Wait for me there.
Don't run around.
I'll fetch your mom.
Okay?
Okay.
What did the police say?
They've filed a report.
They are checking surveillance footage,
and dispatching officers
to Haochen's usual spots
to search for him.
Yan has already gone
to check Haochen's usual spots.
If Yan finds him, she will tell me.
Haoming.
Don't worry.
How is Dad?
I didn't tell him
about Haochen's situation.
I let him rest upstairs for a while.
I'll tell him
when possible.
Okay.
Mom.
Haochen will definitely be fine.
Don't worry.
Many reporters
are out there.
You should stay here
for now.
Alright.
I need to go out
to look for Haochen.
Haoming.
Haochen's backpack!
(Yongxiang)
Yongxiang Building?
Officer Liu.
I just received a photo.
It's Haochen's backpack.
Location is Yongxiang Building.
Please
dispatch officers.
Thank you.
Yan.
Where are you?
Han Weiping?
Wait for the police.
Where is Haochen?
Mr. Shen.
What are you doing?
I didn't harm Haochen.
You are the ones who harmed him.
He wants to know
who his mom is.
Is he wrong?
You're the ones who kept lying to him.
Not me.
Where is Haochen?
The innermost room on the second floor.
Haochen!
Haoming!
Are you okay?
Thank you.
It's okay. We're just doing our job.
He is fine.
Please help us
with a statement later.
No problem.
Thank you.
Be careful.
I'm fine.
They're coming out!
We're on official duty.
Step back!
Haoming.
It's okay. Stay behind me.
- Mr. Shen!
Make way, please!
Shen Haochen...
No interviews.
Mr. Shen.
Is Shen Haochen
really your son?
If it's not true,
how do you explain the paternity test?
If it is true,
why didn't you
acknowledge him as your son?
Do you never want...
Haochen. Look at me!
Let me go!
Don't hold me!
It is okay now.
It seems Shen Haochen
also wants the truth.
Can you tell us the truth?
You're my son.
Mr. Shen.
You just admitted
he is your son out of wedlock.
Who is his real mom?
Where is she?
Rumors say you are getting divorced.
Is Shen Haochen the reason for it?
How's your marriage now?
It's said
Haochen's biological mom drowned.
Did you know about this earlier?
How will you face
the child?
This child is my son.
I am Shen Haochen's mom.
You've all seen it.
My son is not
feeling well.
I hope that you
have professional integrity.
Don't harass
a minor.
We are doing fine.
Don't worry.
But if you continue doing so,
we'll file a lawsuit.
Please make way.
Make way!
Haochen.
You haven't eaten
all day.
Here's your favorite spareribs,
rice balls,
and pumpkin cubes.
All your favorite food.
It smells good.
Let's eat a little,
okay?
Smell it.
Who's that thoughtful,
preparing Haochen's
favorite cola?
It's still cold.
Haochen.
Please eat
or drink something.
We're really
worried about you!
Haochen, please.
Haochen, come on.
Don't scare me.
Say something.
Let's go out.
Do anything you want.
Please say something, Haochen.
Please.
We're all worried about you!
Haochen.
Shareholders demand another meeting.
Dad is already there.
I must go.
You got this.
Don't worry. I got this.
You and Dad take care.
You're here? I get flowers for you.
What's wrong?
Did you disclose
the paternity test report?
What paternity test report?
I don't know.
Han Weiping.
Stop pretending!
Only you
kept asking about
my sister and Shen Haoming.
Yes, it was me.
Please leave.
Between us, there will be
no more contact.
(Parallel to Big Dipper)
Shen Jinsong.
(2019 Most Influential Entrepreneurs
No. 32: Shen Jinsong)
Entrepreneur.
Qu,
you have 12 percent of shares
of Jinda Group.
Right?
Now I have 16.3 percent.
You initiated buybacks
and capped the shares
Situo bought
below 5 percent.
I won by a narrow margin.
Situo
predicted Jinda's trouble.
Haoming,
there's a mole in Jinda.
Otherwise,
Situo wouldn't have
reserved massive funds
to buy shares.
And this mole
is the one who leaked
Haochen's identity.
I just never imagined
it was you.
You should've expected this.
I have been excluded
by you for so many years.
I have attended
few board meetings, right?
Just once or twice.
I was just speaking
on conference calls.
Did you forget
about me?
Holding onto such resentment,
you've had a hard time pretending.
For decades,
you've been acting
like my best buddy
in front of everyone.
We started
the business from scratch together.
But after we expanded,
you became a dictator.
We had to obey your orders.
All our founding buddies
from the early days
got exiled by you
far from Jingzhou.
Every one of them.
Think about it.
Like me,
I have worked in Guangdong for 30 years.
If I hadn't explored
the market of Hong Kong, China
and defended my territory,
you would kick me out anytime.
Enough.
You've occupied
this position for decades.
Time for someone new.
Your beard has turned white,
and you aimed at a child?
How despicable!
There's an old saying,
"always hit where it hurts."
It's a fight,
so why care about morals?
Haoming.
Han Weiping
is your lawyer, right?
He's my godson.
That bad guy!
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Help!
Call an ambulance!
(Jingzhou Yuekang Hospital)
Doctor,
how is he?
The surgery
was successful.
The patient had a ruptured aneurysm
with subarachnoid hemorrhage.
The surgery
has stabilized
his condition.
When will he wake up?
It is hard to tell.
So you should
be prepared.
Mom,
it's okay.
Let's wait patiently until Dad wakes up.
Okay?
Don't worry.
Your dad
has managed the group for years.
We've weathered
countless storms together.
He'll overcome
this hurdle too.
He definitely will.
You look exhausted.
I'll stay here.
Go home and rest. Okay?
No need.
I'm staying here.
I need to see him wake up.
Qu Mingcheng schemed against your dad.
I won't let him get away with this.
Hello.
Haoming,
how's your dad now?
He is out of surgery.
It is still uncertain.
I'll stay
with Mom at the hospital.
Help take care of Haochen.
I see.
I'll stay with Haochen.
Don't worry.
Dad will definitely recover.
Has he eaten?
No.
He stays locked in his room,
without saying a word.
He's usually
such an energetic child.
But now...
I'll go, Hui.
Haochen.
I'm coming in.
If you don't eat,
your body will collapse.
How about this?
Officail Website : kissasian.biz
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Look.
I'll leave
a pen and notebook here.
We'll talk through this.
Write down whatever
you want to eat.
Okay?
It's a beautiful day today.
And the sun isn't too strong.
Perfect for skateboarding.
Want to go out?
You don't want to go out
or speak? You don't want to talk to me?
Alright then.
I'll stay here with you.
Okay?
Good boy, Haochen.
Jinsong.
Haoming and I are both here with you.
You must wake up.
We're waiting for you.
Haoming,
I check on your dad.
Here.
Mom, let me introduce.
Yu Yiming, Dr. Yu,
the boyfriend of Xu Yan's sister.
Hello.
How is he doing?
He is conscious, with stable condition.
But he's not awake.
It is good enough.
It takes time.
He has just had surgery
and needs time to recover.
Madam.
His attending physician
is my mentor's classmate,
also the expert in neurosurgery.
I just met him
and asked him
to pay more attention.
Thank you, Yu.
No problem.
It's nothing.
We're family.
Thank you for coming.
He needs rest.
I'll take my leave.
I just want to say
if you need any help,
tell me anytime.
I can help you
with night shifts and rotations.
Thank you.
Rest assured.
I'm going back.
Where's the child?
In his room.
He doesn't eat, drink, or say a word.
I don't know what to do.
But I can just stay with him.
While caring for him,
you also take care of yourself.
Yu Yiming went to the hospital.
Okay.
Thank you and Yiming.
I've been swamped lately.
So please take care
of the company.
Rest assured.
With such a big incident,
Haoming must be concerned too.
His father and son need his care.
It's okay.
You stay here
and share his burdens.
We've got the company covered.
Gubei Town's botanical dyeing project
and our physical stores
are progressing as usual.
If you have any question,
just call me.
Got it. Don't worry.
Have water.
Hello. Lin.
Yiming.
I just met Yan.
I have
met the doctor
and told Haoming
to call us anytime
if he needs help.
I've told her too.
Yiming.
Yan has been swamped lately.
I need to take care
of Yan Studio.
Wait until this busy period ends,
I'll make it up to you.
Special times.
I understand.
Let's help share
their burdens.
But don't
overwork yourself.
Love you!
I'll hang up.
Okay.
Bye.
Thank you.
You're here.
ظآزLike fireworks that lovedظآز
ظآزRushing toward the starsظآز
ظآزUndaunted by painظآز
ظآزFearless of flamesظآز
ظآزEven if just a fleeting sparkleظآز
ظآزWe shed tearsظآز
ظآزDeep blue seas turn to foamظآز
ظآزWe regained freedomظآز
ظآزIf you remember meظآز
ظآزThen I'm pleasedظآز
ظآزI just wanna take my time tonightظآز
ظآزTo do all the things I said I'd tryظآز
ظآزI go surfing, go diving, go driving,
and go flying to a different placeظآز
ظآزI go drink, go party, and go danceظآز
ظآزEven if I'm lonelyظآز
ظآزCause I just have been hurt
too many timesظآز
ظآزI'm giving it all to get nothing backظآز
ظآزI was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even seeظآز
ظآزSee the world and how it flows.
We never let goظآز
ظآزSo I'll take my timeظآز
ظآزTo reigniteظآز
ظآزThe love I should deserveظآز
ظآزWhen the time is rightظآز
ظآزYou realizeظآز
ظآزIt will all be alrightظآز
ظآزCause I just have been hurt
too many timesظآز
ظآزI'm giving it all to get nothing backظآز
ظآزI was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even seeظآز
ظآزSee the world and how it flows.
We never let goظآز
ظآزSo I'll take my timeظآز
ظآزTo reigniteظآز
ظآزThe love I should deserveظآز
ظآزWhen the time is rightظآز
ظآزYou realizeظآز
ظآزIt will all be alrightظآز