CHAPTER 8: I'M SURE IT WAS MY GLASSES
YOU TROD ON EARLIER
EPISODE 3
Looks like he's on his way
to catch the bus.
Am I going to run into him
every time I go to school?
He's a teacher. He should leave earlier.
Get a move on.
What's he doing?
Mr. Ga!
Mr. Ga! Are you okay?
What's that?
Is that bird poop?
Gross!
Mr. Ga?
Mr. Ga!
Mr. Ga.
Sir…
I don't think he's breathing.
Mr. Ga! Wake up.
What do I do?
Mr. Ga!
Man, he is not breathing!
What do I do?
Come on, Eui-ju.
You're doing this to save a life.
Mr. Ga?
Mr. Ga.
Are you okay?
Are you…
It's me, sir. Yeo Eui-ju.
Are you okay?
What are you doing here?
What do you mean?
How can you say that to the person
who just saved your life?
Anyway, why did you pass out here?
Surely not just because
of some pigeon poop?
Pigeon droppings not only carry avian flu
and other infectious diseases,
but also contain ammonia and acids
strong enough to damage concrete.
"Just because"?
Have you lost something?
Oh, your glasses.
Shall I help you look?
Sure.
Okay.
What was that sound?
Did you just step on my glasses?
No.
No, don't be silly.
I was just…
I mean…
I just stepped on a branch, that's all.
-That was the crack of it snapping.
-What time is it?
-Sorry?
It's 7:40 a.m.
Will you call Dong-ju?
Sure.
It's locked.
Okay.
Here you are.
Is your vision that bad?
It's me.
If you go to my room, my spare glasses
are in the first drawer of my desk.
Can you bring them to me?
Yeah, I'm near the bus stop.
Okay.
Where have they gotten to?
I told you to carpool with us.
Ignoring me always leads to trouble.
What do I do?
Shall I just chuck them somewhere?
Oh, I found 500 won!
Come on!
Let's go or we'll be late.
If we haven't found them by now,
they're not here.
I'm sure someone saw them and took them.
They recognized how expensive they were.
-Don't you think?
-Yes.
-Right?
See you at school.
What's with that look?
Is she hoping for a lift?
Darn it.
Sorry, it's so cramped.
No, it's fine.
I'm just grateful for the lift.
THIS IS CRAZY!
This is crazy!
I'm in the teachers' car right now.
Mr. Jung's driving, and I'm stuck between
Mr. Noh and Mr. Yoon.
No way!
How'd that happen?
There was a whole thing.
I'll tell you later.
I'm putting my seat back.
Okay.
I knew it.
Mr. Ga knows no one but himself
and sweet Mr. Yoon doesn't say anything.
Were you up all night again?
It's because you wouldn't let him sleep.
-Don't you know he's a sleepyhead?
-I didn't do it on purpose.
He wanted another round. That's all.
It doesn't matter
how much you're enjoying it,
make sure he gets his rest.
Got it?
Unbelievable!
What can they have been doing all night?
God, forgive me.
I'll go to hell after writing this!
What's wrong?
Are you hot? Shall I put the AC on?
No.
There's no need.
MURIM GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
Who are you to ride in his car?
Cat got your tongue? Answer me!
-Say something!
-How dare you!
What's wrong with her?
Just a moment, sir.
If they see me in here,
they're going to kill me.
Hey, it's Mr. Jung!
No, this can't be happening.
No!
If the other kids find out I'm here,
I'm dead meat.
What do I do?
I need more oxygen.
I can't say that didn't hurt.
Still, he saved my life.
It's because you wouldn't let me sleep.
You know I'm a sleepyhead.
They're the one true pair.
Aren't you getting out?
Hey.
Yes?
Tell me the truth.
About what?
Whichever way I look at it,
I'm sure it was my glasses
you trod on earlier.
No, it wasn't.
If you're lying to me,
you're going to regret it.
I'm really not.
-Where's your essay?
-I'm working on it.
CHAPTER 9:
HI! I'M JENNY
-Good morning, Mr. Ga!
Come in.
-Who is it?
-A transfer?
We have an exchange student joining us
for the rest of the semester.
Hi! I'm Jenny.
I'm here on exchange from Singapore.
Nice to meet you all.
I'm really excited to be here, so
I hope we'll have a lot of fun together.
Welcome, Jenny!
She's so cute.
You can sit there.
-Hey, Jenny.
-Hello.
Hello.
Hi!
She's probably not used to Korean culture
or Korean schools,
so look after her.
-Yes, sir.
Dismissed.
-Thank you.
Jenny.
-Hi!
-Hello!
Hello!
-Hey!
-Hello!
My name is Yeo Eui-ju.
Do you speak Korean well?
Yes. Okay, maybe like…
I can't speak that much Korean.
But I'm learning.
If you help me,
I'm sure I'll soon pick it up.
My name is Go-ya.
Nice to meet you.
Jenny, why did you come to Korea?
Doesn't everybody want to come to Korea?
There's lots of yummy food.
And I wanted to visit the places
I've seen in K-dramas.
-I see.
-That's right.
That makes sense.
Then why did you come to Jeonju
and not Seoul?
I did apply to a school in Seoul.
But…
I was on the computer, and I was like…
I clicked on the wrong one.
-You…
-You clicked on the wrong…
-Oh, she clicked on the wrong one!
You selected this school by mistake.
But it's okay. This place is great, like…
Jeonju is really pretty.
-Yeah, it really is.
-It's great!
CHAPTER 10:
I'M GOING TO TUMBLE YOU AROUND
Darn it.
Is it because he switched glasses?
Why does he look sick?
Why won't this stick?
Shall I just throw them away
and feign ignorance?
I can't do that.
I have to give them back.
It seems like his spare ones
aren't the right strength.
Come on, help me out here.
Type one verbs
refers to almost all verbs
that do not end in "ru."
So, the verb "iku" will become "ikanai."
You add "a" to the "ku" form.
Type two verbs are much easier.
All you have to do is take off the "ru."
So it will become "tabenai."
As for type three verbs…
I'M TRULY SORRY
JAPANESE LANGUAGE
During my class…
You're not paying attention to me?
I cannot believe it.
How are you feeling?
Like I've been watching
the Mandelbrot set zooming out
at ultra-high speed all day.
Mandel…
I said I feel dizzy.
I see.
Come in.
I caught one of your students
doing homework you assigned
during my Japanese class.
You deal with it, Mr. Ga.
Read it.
Sorry?
Can't you just read it?
All the other teachers are here.
"Dear Euclid."
I can't hear you.
"Hello."
"I…
live in Jeonju in the year 2026,
and my name is Yeo Eui-ju,
and I am 18 years old."
"When I was in seventh grade,
I was humiliated in front of my classmates
while solving a proof problem."
"The shame of that
led me to give up on math."
"Why were you so obsessed with proofs?"
"Are things that can't be proven
totally useless?"
"If I'd been born before you, would I have
been spared from that kind of torment?"
Is this an apology or a complaint?
"Nevertheless,
I can't help but admire
the first sentence of your book,
'A point is that which has no parts.'"
"Even someone like me who gave up on math
can understand that in one go."
"Sir,
I'm truly sorry for hurting you
with my ignorance,
and for that I apologize…"
That's as far as I've got.
If you're going to write it during class,
don't bother. Two demerits.
What? You think that's unfair?
No, sir.
I think taking care of your friends
is one of the most important things
you learn at school.
Starting today, you take care of Ji-a.
From now on, if Choi Ji-a is absent, late,
or not at her desk during homeroom,
I will give her two demerit points,
and you four.
-Sorry?
-Go.
You can't do that!
Mr. Ga!
I can't.
But, sir…
Darn.
Wow, that's ridiculous.
How can you get more demerits than Ji-a?
Why does he only ever pick on you?
That's totally unfair.
Wait, surely not.
Do you think he likes you?
Or maybe you look like his ex-girlfriend?
He's picking on you
because every time he sees you,
it reminds him of being dumped.
What if it turns out
your parents and his parents
are mortal enemies?
Guys, just give it a rest.
Maybe he just doesn't like your face.
That could be it!
Hey!
Let's try something.
-Good afternoon, Mr. Ga.
Where did we get to last time?
Mr. Ga,
Eui-ju isn't feeling very well.
What's wrong with her?
I don't know, sir.
I feel dizzy and nauseous.
And, gosh, I'm feeling so weak.
Oh, no.
What am I going to do?
I can't take it.
I think I'm dying.
Yeo Eui-ju.
Yes?
Define left-hand limit
and right-hand limit.
Sorry?
If both the left-hand and right-hand limit
exist but aren't equal, does the limit
exist or not?
Sorry?
If there's a single point
separated from a graph,
what kind of discontinuity is that?
What conditions do we need to prove
that f(x) is continuous at x equals a?
Didn't we cover this last class?
Were you even listening?
If you'd revised
instead of faking being sick,
you'd be able to answer.
What are you doing here?
I thought you wanted
to take Discrete Math together.
Cut!
Ju Si-on!
Yes?
Isn't that what I told you last time?
Were you even listening?
You guys were great.
-Thank you.
Do you not get the meaning
between the lines?
Here, Yoon is talking to Tae-ha,
and you're supposed to feel
angry and jealous, but…
Yoon has already agreed
to take one of your classes with you.
You know
you're on a different level to Tae-ha.
You're supposed
to radiate an air of superiority!
Are you not capable of that?
I think I did.
How dare you answer back!
I'm the writer,
and you're just a character.
Get it?
I'm the writer, and you're just a teach…
Hang on.
You're just a character.
Why do you always go off script
and do what you want?
Every last period of my writing has soul!
So stop whining and do exactly what I say!
Yes, ma'am.
What are you fuming about?
Write the basic concepts of functions
ten times each.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Full-of-regrets Ju Si-on.
Just you wait and see.
I'm going to tumble you around.
Round and around.
CHAPTER 11:
HE NEVER LIKED ME TO BEGIN WITH
Is this a pork cutlet?
-It's a fish cutlet.
-Jenny.
Is the food okay?
-It's pretty tasty.
-It is, isn't it?
If you enjoy it too much, you'll get fat.
-Just eat up.
-Hey, Jenny.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Yes.
He's Brazilian.
Brazilian?
His name is Luiz.
So global.
How did you meet him?
At the Louvre in Paris.
He's studying photography at college.
He kept asking me to be his model.
So, that's how we started dating.
So, he's in France right now?
Yeah.
You must miss him.
He said since I left,
he's completely lost his appetite.
He said he doesn't smile much either.
Isn't that funny?
Brazilian guys are different.
How would you know?
How would I not?
Jenny, what did your boyfriend say
when he asked you to model for him?
Excuse me.
I've been searching for the perfect
golden hour light all day.
But I've ended up finding something
even more beautiful.
Let me capture this beautiful moment.
That's so romantic.
YUL EYE CLINIC
PRESCRIPTION
BUBU PHARMACY
There's seven days-worth.
Take them three times a day.
This is the anti-inflammatory
and this is for your stomach.
-Okay.
-And,
your eye medicine is a steroid,
so make sure you shake it before use.
That'll be 9,600 won.
Your eyes are really bloodshot.
Since you're wearing glasses,
I guess you didn't get LASIK.
You'd better change your glasses.
Our eyes are so important.
I'm sorry.
I was just reminded of that thing.
You know in cartoons,
when the main character
takes off their glasses,
and they're transformed
into someone really handsome.
You really should wear lenses if you can.
Bye!
A man straight out of a comic.
AFTER-SCHOOL PROGRAM APPLICATION
Get your parents' signatures
and bring it back to me.
Yes, sir.
What the heck?
Is he sick?
What did the doctor say?
It'll take at least two weeks
to get new glasses.
Two weeks?
How are you going to cope for that long?
Well done.
-Thank you.
Ji-a!
Ji-a, where are you going?
You have to wait for the final bell.
Are you off to work?
Can't you wait until the bell rings?
From now on, if you come in late
or leave early, I will get demerits.
Hey!
I asked nicely.
Can't you just do me a solid?
Do you think I want to do this?
Mr. Ga! Did you see that?
I clearly told Ji-a not to go.
But she didn't listen and just left.
Can't you just count this
as me having done it?
There's really nothing I can do.
Yeo Eui-ju.
Four demerit points.
GENERAL WASTE
Go-ya was right.
Things were screwed up from the start.
He just never liked me.
I saw you filming. Delete it.
I want you to write a letter to Euclid.
Twenty pages.
Yeo Eui-ju.
Four demerit points.
Subtitle: Paul Carver