This is a work of fiction.
Underage drinking is strongly prohibited and illegal.
Scenes involving alcohol with forceful consumption and shameful acts are not encouraged. Please view this as a comedy. Furthermore, all characters appearing in this work are of legal age.
This work is an original copyrighted material
of the Content Provider. Unauthorized reproduction
or distribution of this work in any form or manner is prohibited. Some viewers might find this work disturbing as it may contain strong language, a degree of violence or adult situations. Viewer discretion is advised. Please watch it at your own risk.
The story, names, characters and incidents portrayed
in this work are fictitious. No identification with actual
persons, organizations, religions, places and products is intended. The Content Provider, the producers and related parties shall have no liability, as to the accuracy, legality, safety or suitability for any purpose of the information provided in this work. The views and opinions expressed herein do not reflect the views and opinions of the Content Provider, or any of its affiliates, partners, subsidiaries, or Licensee.
Izu Spring Festival! Yay!
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
GRAND BLUE DREAMING
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
An expanding ocean of possibilities
Summer is our amore
We'll swear to the crystal clear sky
Summer is in our hands
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
With a cheerful heart
Don't mess with me
Keep going even if you fall
And let summer take it all
OKONOMIYAKI
I was happy...
But it looks like we have to man the stall.
Thanks for waiting.
Thanks for your hard work!
How's everything going?
All right.
It looks like we have a competitor.
Oh, it's Tinkerbell.
Tinkerbell?
It's a tennis club with lots of cute guys
and the highest ratio of girls.
-How about trash?
-Pig's blood would be better.
Stop talking about
what you want to throw at them.
Hey!
It's so hot!
You walked here?
I rode the bus part way.
How can you talk
like everything's normal?
Please put this on.
I'm okay.
No!
Why are you dressed like that?
My shirt just got drenched.
Shouldn't you wash that?
It's going to get dirty again tonight
when you guys puke.
What's going to happen tonight?
This is the devil's festival.
Why don't you go look for a T-shirt?
I'm fine with this.
That's a little too...
I guess you're right.
Come with me, Iori.
Wait, why do I have to go?
Welcome! Please have a look!
School festivals are so lively. I love them!
You seem like the type who likes festivals.
Well, yeah.
-Since we're talking about our interests...
-Yes?
What type of guys do you like?
-What do you mean? That's random!
-Well...
You know, we're both into the same stuff...
Now that you mention it...
Actually, I'm okay with both too.
Anyway, as for guys, I like Tokki.
For girls, I like Nanaka.
Nanaka?
So how about you?
What do you mean?
What type do you like?
Clear up the misunderstanding!
This is my only chance to tell her I'm not bi!
Actually...
I'm so glad I met someone like me.
Even I can't talk about this stuff
with other people.
Help me, God!
So, what's your type, Iori?
Hey, Kitahara.
What?
Why did Azusa say she wants to switch shifts
with me all of a sudden?
I wonder...
-Just go off and have fun alone with Iori!
-Okay...
It's just that...
I feel bad for doing this to you.
You bastard. What did you get me into?
It's so peaceful.
It's because the others aren't here.
It's nice to spend time like this sometimes.
It's Iori and Kohei!
You came at a good time.
What?
We were talking about going out drinking
with some other clubs we interact with.
So it's a mixer.
So cute girls will be there?
Check with them.
RUGBY CLUB
-Yeah!
-There definitely won't be any girls.
So how about it?
Want to come over to our tent?
It's going to be fun.
I'm not really interested...
How many do you want to order?
I'll buy five, tell me your Line ID.
Hey.
You look like you're having fun.
Do you want to die?
-Friends of yours?
-Yeah.
We'll come invite you again.
Throw the salt!
Be gone, demons!
-Thanks for helping us out.
-Great.
Do you want to switch shifts?
Okay.
Then let's have Chii-chan switch with Iori.
Tell me how things went with Kohei.
-What's wrong?
-Nothing.
I'll work the stall with Chisa.
You can take a break.
I've been working the whole time.
Please!
Sorry, Chisa.
Come on. Tell me why.
Well, how should I put it...
I want to avoid being left alone with Azusa.
Well, Azusa is pretty, after all.
You get nervous when you're with her, right?
Well, I guess I do get nervous...
What's with that answer?
Welcome!
-Thanks.
-One moment please.
What time is the women's beauty pageant?
It's at 4. The award ceremony is tomorrow.
Ours is tonight.
-Thanks for waiting. 600 yen, please.
-Okay.
-Thank you!
PEEK-A-BOO
Shouldn't you start getting ready?
I was just going to go like this.
You can't do that, Chii-chan.
You're cute, so we have to get
lots of people to notice you.
This is our chance.
Good luck.
Where did Kotegawa go?
To do her makeup
for the beauty pageant.
Are you having them do yours next?
Are you trying to embarrass me?
You have long hair.
You should dress up as a girl!
No! You're the one entering the joke category!
Hey! We're going to close the stall
and go watch!
IZU UNIVERSITY SPRING FESTIVAL
WOMEN'S BEAUTY PAGEANT
There's a lot of people here.
This is the main event, along with the male pageant.
We're going on stage in front of
such a huge crowd?
You'll be fine.
You'll be dressed as a guy.
You're not happy in the joke category?
I don't understand why I have to enter.
What are you talking about?
Look, Iori.
AINA YOSHIWARA
(20 YEARS OLD)
That's a lot of makeup.
The other clubs are also entering the joke category.
Aina-chan, you're so cute!
Hi!
She looks harsh.
Is she mad?
Please say your name and your club.
I'm Chisa Kotegawa from Peek-a-Boo.
I think she's nervous.
Kotegawa's so awkward.
This is bad.
At this rate, she might lose.
-What's your hobby?
-Diving.
Kohei, do you have any ideas?
You know lots about these games, right?
Well, you're right. I do know a lot...
If you want to make a quiet girl shine,
you make her smile.
Brother Kohei...
Smile?
It's hard to make Chisa smile.
If we smile, maybe she'll smile too.
Let's try that!
Chisa!
No! We made it worse!
She shouldn't make that face
in front of the crowd.
Do you have any other ideas?
How about showing them her bashful side?
Bashful?
How can we do that?
Based on what I know...
Can you introduce your club?
Chisa!
WE LOVE CHISA
She's not being bashful.
That's weird. Normally...
Why are you doing this?
She would say that.
She looks like she's looking at trash.
Our plan failed.
-There's only one thing left.
-What is it?
-Today's outfit.
-Okay. We're lifting up her skirt.
I didn't even have to say it.
How come he knew?
You have weird ideas.
How are we going to lift up her skirt?
-Look at these!
-Bouncy balls?
Are you going to throw them at her feet?
This is so embarrassing!
I get it.
It's what kids do to tease each other.
This would make Chisa really mad.
You're right.
She might kill you, Iori.
Who said I'm the one who's going to do it?
It's Chisa.
So you should do it.
Let's decide with rock, paper, scissors!
-I have a better idea.
-What is it?
Let's all throw them at the same time
so she doesn't know who did it.
That's not a bad idea, coming from you.
Then, let's go with that.
Ready! One, two...
Take this!
-Nice!
-Do it!
Nice control, Iori!
You're the only one who can do this kind of thing!
Leave it to me!
Are you okay?
Why aren't you guys throwing them?
Hurry up and let her
execute you.
You bastard! You act like you're innocent!
A ghost!
You were in the women's beauty pageant...
Cakey?
Hey, you...
What is it?
Please go out with me.
GRAND BLUE DREAMING
Go out with you? You and me?
Yeah. Got a problem with that?
Hold on! I don't even know your name.
Aina Yoshiwara, a freshman at
Oumi Women's University. Okay?
Not at all.
Congratulations, Kohei.
I hope you live happily ever after.
Where do you think you're going?
I thought you two should spend time alone.
How can you leave me alone like this?
That's so inhumane!
You left me to die just now, you loser.
Never mind.
What was that about?
So that's where you guys were.
What were you doing?
-Experiencing youth.
-What?
Cheers!
-You've got the wrong guy.
-I haven't said anything yet.
It's not what you think!
I did it to draw out your charm!
I wanted to show the audience
how cute you are!
That's enough.
You're forgiving me?
I owe you one.
Really? Thanks, Chisa!
To show my appreciation,
I'll buy you some sexy underwear.
She said she'd forgive you. What a waste.
So you looked!
You pervert!
Chisa?
Are you really mad?
SHOCHU
I'll drink it.
Thanks for the drink.
He drank two liters.
That took some guts.
Impressive, Iori!
I'm back.
You're late.
Did something happen?
Some guy was hitting on me.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
You promised earlier today, right?
I already have plans.
It's okay. You're talking about those guys, right?
Come on.
MEN'S BEAUTY PAGEANT
REGISTRATION DEADLINE: 30 MINUTES LEFT
Aren't you going to enter the men's pageant?
I'm letting the younger students
do it this year.
Did you want to see me compete?
Yes! I do!
I'll cheer for you in the front row.
Well, if you insist...
I ran away while he was registering.
Impressive, Azusa.
-Are you going to cheer for him?
-Of course not.
-That's terrible.
-I'm glad you're safe.
You're in time for our gathering.
That's right.
Gathering?
We're here, just like we promised!
RUGBY CLUB
Contain your excitement,
Iori and Kohei!
This drinking party is crazier than usual.
Oh, that's...
You guys...
You...
Cakey! Wait! Wait! Wait!
Why me? Go drink with the guys from the tennis club!
What did you say?
Why did I ask you out?
That's not what I mean...
She smells like alcohol.
It's because you're hot.
Just like the tennis club.
They're all hot. That's why I joined.
I thought I'd be happy if I found a boyfriend.
Then I'd have the perfect college life I dreamed of!
But... Tell me!
Why do I always end up like this?
-She's a drunk mess.
-All that makeup isn't helping.
I'm trying really hard, right?
-I'm trying really hard!
-Yeah.
You were trying hard.
In a bad way.
I studied how to do makeup,
and dressed up in clothes I'm not used to.
I tried so hard to fit in,
and did things I didn't want to.
Movies and shows didn't teach me that!
-Well...
-I bet.
Why does everyone make a fool out of me?
-Everyone?
-She's talking about the guys from Tinkerbell.
Well, dressed like that...
With that much makeup,
they'd think she's weird.
Everyone said I was cute at first!
Everyone was laughing!
You let it slip out.
Did I hurt you?
Even I already knew that.
At first, I didn't mind being treated as a joke.
As long as I could be friends and have fun,
I was okay with it.
-Really?
-Then isn't this what you wanted?
But at the drinking party after the pageant,
those guys told me...
"We've laughed enough.
You can go home now."
I shouldn't have tried so hard to change.
No matter what I do,
I'm always getting laughed at.
And they're the ones laughing at me.
-Cakey, You...
-What are you talking about?
There's no one who's always laughing,
or always getting laughed at.
But...
I'll show you something interesting.
IZU UNIVERSITY SPRING FESTIVAL
MEN'S BEAUTY PAGEANT
-Nice!
-Yeah!
You guys always mistake the male pageant
for a bodybuilding contest.
Look who's talking!
Up next!
I'm Kudo, the captain of the tennis club.
Nice to meet you.
Can you say a few words about your club?
You're so casual.
Because I'm talking with a guy.
Kudo, you can do it!
Captain!
You're going to win this year too!
Of course!
I'm on a different level from the others!
Next!
-A pretty boy!
-Why is he in a uniform?
Wasn't he with the naked idiots?
I'm Kohei Imamura from Peek-a-Boo.
It doesn't matter.
I'm going to win anyway.
A few words, please.
Azusa Hamaoka!
Please go out with me,
not Captain Kudo from Tinkerbell!
Imamura confessed his feelings!
He stands out.
How dare he use my name without asking?
No. Choose me instead.
Captain Kudo also confessed his feelings!
Who is she going to choose?
Whoa, it's Captain Kudo!
Sorry things turned out like this.
People are all at different levels.
I bet there's a good match out there somewhere
for you too.
A good match?
Too bad! I'm a man!
Oh, really?
I never imagined I was a good match for Captain Kudo
from Tinkerbell!
That's great, Kitahara!
You guys are on the same level
when you're dressed up like a girl!
Iori Kitahara from Peek-a-Boo
is entering the male pageant!
They did it.
Hey, hold on! I--
What should I do?
The captain confessed his feelings for me!
It hurts to lose,
but I'll step aside.
Captain, I hope you two have a long happy life together!
-Who are those guys?
-Kudo! What's going on?
No! This is--
Oh, right, captain.
We've laughed enough.
-You can go home now.
Pretty funny, right?
They did it!
Congratulations on the women's beauty pageant
and the male pageant!
Let's have a toast! A toast!
That's a washbowl.
You can't toast with that.
Hey.
I just want to--
How should I put this...
What's this?
It's what it looks like.
Do you want a bigger bucket?
That's not what I mean. I--
Drinking is better with lots of people!
Don't just stand there.
Sit down.
What? If you want to drink with me,
then you should just tell me.
That's not what we mean.
Your makeup is thick as oil.
Just drop it already!
What's this? It's too strong.
-Of course!
-You finished it?
We've been trained well!
-They're good freshmen.
-Right?
-Give them to us.
-In your dreams.
They were against it at the beginning.
I was surprised when they asked me too.
It turned out great in the end.
Especially for her.
OKONOMIYAKI
You were in the beauty pageant, right?
You're so cute!
Can I take your order?
We have a yakitori stall.
Want to hang out later?
No thanks.
Hey, we talked to her first!
Don't be so cold!
Just let the other two handle the stall.
Stop!
Do you have some business with her?
She looks unhappy.
Hey! Get lost!
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Come on.
Those guys are useless.
Hey! Get up, you guys!
It's time for the award ceremony.
Congratulations on winning!
Thanks.
The audience liked your stage performance.
-What's wrong?
-She looks mad.
Well, that makes sense.
-What?
-Why?
Well, Chii-chan entered the pageant
just for Iori and the others.
But Iori and the others
worked hard for another girl.
Chii-chan gets bothered by guys
because she entered the pageant,
but no one helped her.
That'd make anyone mad.
Now that you mention it...
I'd feel mad too.
Who do you want to share this happiness with?
Yes. Well...
I want to share it with my boyfriend,
who's passed out drunk over there.
Your boyfriend? Him?
He's a pervert!
I see. She used Iori to repel other guys.
So now they're a couple?
Come on. Those two...
What are they going to do?
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
DEEP BLUE AL FINE
KAYA MIZUKI
Here's your mic, Kitahara.
Me, too...? All right, let's do this!
-Yeah, sing your heart out.
-You guys seem to be having fun.
A fairytale whispers
In a fake world
Hiding in the complete darkness
I reach for the forbidden fruit
In my last days
Now I know the meaning of the song about hope
A broken gear will never stop again
Even if I were to lose everything
I'd still want you to know
Trapped in the sky so far away
I'm praying with ripped off wings
Because we span together
The vows of areppegio
If life sparkles only to the beat
of the resonating stars
I'll sacrifice everything
Till death do us apart
Cheers!
Thank you!
I might just be imagining things.
What? Kitahara?
Everyone's looking at me differently.
What? Is something happening to me?
Am I going to die tomorrow?
Tell me! What's going on?
NEXT EPISODE
"TOO LATE"