WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
Sir?
Hello--
It keeps disconnecting.
Wait for now.
OFFICE BUILDING B
What?
What was that?
What? What's wrong?
- I think someone's here.
- Who? No one would come here.
See? I told you.
It's connected.
I'll stop it now.
Good job.
From now on, wait on all fours like that.
Who knows?
I might even throw you a bone.
What?
What did you say, bastard?
What are you trying to do?
I really won't stand for this.
Did someone order pizza?
But why is it so heavy?
Don't regret this later.
Don't open it!
Sir?
Sir.
Sir!
Sir?
Are you okay?
You shouldn't get up.
What happened?
I brought you to Dr. Kim's hospital.
What about the others?
They're being treated in the ER.
Thankfully, no one was seriously injured.
Was it an explosion?
Yes.
The police are analyzing the footage now.
But you need to see something.
It's from the security room.
I think it's him.
At 10:49 p.m.,
Hong Hee-joo is safely at home.
What will you do?
The police don't know you're involved.
So? Should I sit back and do nothing?
He broke into my personal office
and bombed my team.
He's trying to challenge me!
But if you get involved now,
the reporters will catch wind.
Maybe this is what he wants.
A situation where I can't step forward.
But…
I have to respond.
There are plenty of ways to screw him over
without revealing myself.
EPISODE 3
The perpetrator,
who had been making threats,
set fire
to the victim's office last night.
- The fire department…
- A fire?
…put out the fire in 20 minutes.
When did I do that?
There could've been casualties,
but quick action averted disaster.
The police, fire department, and forensics
are conducting an investigation.
They'll form a dedicated team
to look into the incident.
This was Jang Seok-hyeon with HBC.
Lately,
nothing makes sense.
There can't be a Hong Hee-joo
I don't know about.
I need to find out
which one is the real one.
Right now,
you're my only lead.
So cooperate.
Are you hurt?
Some crazy man
delivered a bomb to my personal office.
- Was it the kidnapper?
- Yeah.
From now on, I'll be asking the questions.
You said you didn't know
who he was, right?
Any guesses on who it is?
You don't know?
But why…
does it seem like…
he knows you so well?
Even your private…
What do I say if he asks me
about the picture?
…and intimate stories.
Can things get more complicated from here?
What are you doing?
And what are you doing?
What does he know about me?
And what are you trying to check?
He kidnapped me,
and you got hurt because of him.
So, what are we doing right now?
So…
you don't know what I'm trying to do
or what I'm trying to see, right?
PARK DO-JAE
I apologize if you were offended.
How did it go?
I managed to get away with it.
A serial arsonist?
Yes.
In the last six months, there have been
multiple cases in the area.
The police are investigating this
as part of it.
Serial arson…
Either he's lucky or he planned this.
- It's one or the other.
- What?
He got lucky
without knowing about the serial arson,
or he intended
to ride the arsonist's coattails.
However,
it was probably intentional.
We'll investigate independently.
And there's something strange.
What is it?
The explosion happened during the call.
Do you think there's an accomplice?
That seems possible.
Yes, it's more than possible.
The fact that he knows so much about me
suggests that he's very close.
The police are requesting
the threat recording. What shall I do?
It must not be leaked.
What I pieced together earlier
was for broadcasting purposes.
Tell them that's everything.
Sa-eon edited it and handed it over?
Bring your phone.
I have to check something.
I need to check for any signs of hacking.
How could you be so careless?
You earn a living with your hands.
It won't take long.
Are you going to the center?
Stay at home.
I have to leave after I shower.
Hacking? Why?
Because of the photo?
MOVE TO TRASH
POWER OFF
The candidate registration is coming up.
You've never dropped out
of first place in the polls.
You can continue like this.
It's all thanks to you.
Our campaign's PR line for the election
is very solid.
I like it.
Thank you for getting me
such talented people.
Don't mention it.
But don't you actually keep
the most talented one close at hand?
My son-in-law.
Spokesperson Paik.
I wonder how you will use him
after you keep him hidden away.
I'm quite curious.
This reminds me of when I used
to go hunting with Chairman Paik.
He possessed
remarkable instinctive abilities.
I could never match
my father's athletic abilities.
He was decisive and made quick judgments.
It seems Sa-eon inherited those qualities.
This is so boring.
We should tell them not to invite us
unless they're golfing.
Don't you agree?
Am I the only one who's bored?
What's so interesting?
That's hot!
- What's wrong, honey?
- What happened?
That's hot! I need ice!
- Ice!
- Get some ice!
I'll get the ice.
Did you make a mistake?
A mistake?
Would looking at someone else's phone
be accidental or intentional?
Come on.
Mr. Hong.
I'm sorry, but I'll get going.
I'm a bit sensitive to noise.
Ice. Bring it here.
Here you go.
You should sit down.
What do we do about this?
Let's see.
What if this leaves a scar?
I wouldn't have held back
if it weren't for you.
I see.
That's so cold.
OFFICE BUILDING FIRE IN YEOUIDO, SEOUL
Did you see it?
What do you think?
MASTER
DID YOU SEE IT? WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DON'T ACT ALONE FROM NOW ON.
So why did you leave me out?
I want to join in on the fun too.
Oh, a job?
A college friend? Were you close?
SANG-WOO
Hee-joo, it was great to see you today.
I was reminded of old times,
so I looked this up. Remember?
NURI DREAM CENTER
For Crime Report: Season 2,
we'll focus on unsolved cases.
Is there anything you haven't revealed yet
on your own channel?
Sir, do you really think
he'll reveal it on our show?
I do…
have one.
What is it?
Instead of asking what it is,
shouldn't you be asking
why I haven't revealed it yet?
Yeah, what is it
and why haven't you revealed it?
There's an orphanage
called Nuri Dream Center.
And I grew up there.
What?
First time seeing an orphan?
No.
Please continue.
So…
about 20 years ago, in the town
where the orphanage was located,
there was an enormous mansion
owned by a wealthy family.
That's when I first met him.
The young master from Seoul
came to visit the mansion.
His room was filled
with all sorts of toys.
We played there joyfully every day.
Until the day…
I saw something terrible there.
What was it?
What did you see?
Well…
Goodness!
The meeting's over.
I have plans for lunch.
- What?
- Excuse me.
What?
Did he just leave like that?
He just left?
NURI DREAM CENTER
NURI DREAM CENTER IS AN ORPHANAGE.
SANG-WOO
Let's eat lunch here at noon
this Saturday if you have time.
A cup of refreshing tea
to soothe an upset stomach.
- I'm on my way.
- Have a good day.
How refreshing.
The explosive device used is TATP,
a high-performance liquid explosive.
Despite its simple manufacturing,
it has immense explosive power.
Fortunately, the detonation device
wasn't fully activated in this incident.
Aren't the main ingredients
acetone and hydrogen peroxide?
That's right, so the police
are questioning nearby pharmacies.
What about the voice modulation?
Is it not done yet?
It's impossible to analyze
with existing software.
We're trying with a different version.
I apologize.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm asking for so much
over personal matters.
No, I just…
You entrusted me with this,
and I want to be of help.
Also, if there's someone threatening you,
it's my job to figure out who.
MATINÉE
Sa-eon, I hope you have
a pleasant day today!
And enjoy your lunch!
The seafood is great here.
Is white wine okay?
Na You-ri, reservation for two.
I'll show you to your table.
Do you have a private room here?
I'm afraid they're all full.
I see. What do I do?
A table in the open is uncomfortable.
What? Hey!
The interpreter!
You had plans with the interpreter?
Yes, we're friends from college.
Really?
I suddenly got plans to eat here too!
Right this way.
Okay.
Right.
By the way,
when my guest arrives later,
please try not to stare
too obviously, okay?
It could make him uncomfortable.
Well, enjoy your lunch.
What was that?
Is a celebrity coming?
Do I look puffy today?
Over here!
Isn't that…
What? What's he doing here?
He won't act like he knows me, will he?
Don't.
- Please, don't.
- Interpreter Hong Hee-joo?
There were no prints?
We checked the explosives, but nothing.
- What about local inquiries?
- We're still on it.
But which high-ranking official
in the presidential office
keeps requesting updates like this?
Goodness!
- Call 911!
- Someone call!
- Call 911.
- Okay.
- Evacuate everyone.
- Yes, sir.
- Bring a fire extinguisher.
- Okay.
Okay, okay.
Damn it!
Try this.
It's in season, so it'll be good.
It's good.
Good, right?
Do you like it?
Hee-joo and Sang-woo are college friends.
It seems like you like seafood.
Yes, I do.
By the way, Sa-eon,
how do you know Hee-joo?
She recently helped us out
with interpreting at the British Embassy.
I was hoping to treat you
to a meal sometime.
I'm glad we met like this.
I'm sorry if I intruded.
No, it's fine.
Thanks to Hee-joo, I get to have lunch
with you, so it's an honor.
A glass of wine?
I don't day drink.
Right.
Are you okay?
We can go if you're uncomfortable.
I'm okay.
You're good at sign language.
Yes, I am.
- Are you an interpreter?
- No.
Then what do you do?
Mr. Ji is…
Mr. Ji? What does he do?
- He's a--
- A doctor.
- What department?
- Department of Psychiatry.
Are you married?
Are you interested in me?
Yes.
Are you okay?
I have to use the restroom.
Okay, go ahead.
Excuse me for a moment.
What an interesting person.
I must be his type.
Of course not!
He's a married man.
You caught him?
Yes, he was apprehended at the scene.
They searched his residence
and found plenty of homemade bombs.
It's not him.
- I think it's the neighborhood arsonist.
- Pardon?
If he was watching the fire at the scene,
he's likely a pyromaniac
who gets a thrill from it.
So he's most likely the serial arsonist.
Is he being interrogated now?
Yes.
Man, you've got guts.
Set fire two days in a row?
I didn't do it yesterday.
You punk.
This is insane. I swear.
Why are you blaming me
and not catching that guy?
That bastard has no ethics.
How dare he do that in my turf?
Does that young brat
have nothing better to do?
"Young brat"?
Okay. I'm on my way now.
Why did you come here? How did you know?
You said you'd check for hacking.
Were you spying on me?
Why?
Are you hiding something from me?
What are you saying?
Do you suspect me and Sang-woo?
"Suspect"?
About what?
Whatever it is.
Sang-woo isn't that type of person. So--
Do you know him that well?
A college friend?
You said he was a good person.
I don't know.
I don't care about that.
To me, he's just some loser
who suddenly showed up around you.
Also…
if you know him so well,
what about me?
How much do you know about me?
Haven't we known each other
for about 20 years now?
Hong Hee-joo.
Tell me.
Do you know me well?
I suddenly had this thought.
I thought I knew you too.
But I don't think…
I knew you all that well after all.
DIRECTOR HAN JIN-E
I need to talk to you. Come to the center.
Excuse me, I have to go now.
- I'll pay.
- No, I'll get it.
Can I get your business card?
Sure.
Come if you ever need counseling
or feel any discomfort.
BLISS CARE CLINIC
JI SANG-WOO
- I'll see you again.
- Okay, Sa-eon.
Thanks for lunch!
Sorry, but the center called me.
I have to go.
Okay. You should go.
Good luck, Hong Hee-joo!
You can do it, Hong Hee-joo!
You got this, Hong Hee-joo!
2024 PRESIDENTIAL
SIGN LANGUAGE INT. HIRING
I knew it.
I knew you'd like it.
I don't like it.
Why not?
I know you've practiced signing
with Paik Sa-eon's videos every day.
Are you nervous about living out
your fangirl dreams?
Is it better after a divorce?
What? Divorce?
Why? Why do you ask?
Is your husband having an affair?
I think my husband wishes I were dead.
What?
My goodness. You had me there.
Hee-joo.
Did he tell you he wishes you were dead?
That means
he still really, really loves you deeply.
Hey.
When a couple truly separates,
they don't engage in heated arguments
or say things like,
"I wish you were dead."
They become indifferent
and walk back and forth saying,
"Are you not dead yet?"
Call me when there's a corpse.
It's a good reason…
for divorce.
You were right.
The man caught earlier was the arsonist.
But there was a small fire in the area
that wasn't reported to the police.
The explosion killed some stray cats.
Damn it.
You think it was done as a test?
Yes.
According to the arsonist, those were
the only two things he didn't do.
The park and our office building.
If he did that to animals,
he could have psychopathic tendencies.
How will you handle the call tonight?
We threw the bait,
so let's see how he reacts.
I've reset the equipment
in the new office.
Okay.
Also, look into this person.
Ji Sang-woo?
Do you know him?
Hello, Paradisers.
EARTHLY PARADISE
I'll start today's broadcast
with a cup of tea.
- When you see a psychiatrist…
- "Paradisers"? What?
It's a play on words with his name.
That's why his channel is called
"Earthly Paradise."
So he calls his viewers "Paradisers."
- Jeez.
- He has over 200,000 subscribers.
He mainly covers unsolved mystery cases
and criminal psychology.
- He's very popular among women.
- Why?
- Excuse me?
- Why is he popular among women?
I think…
it's his physique.
His physique?
He's serious about working out.
Especially the shoulder deltoids.
They're a work of art.
It seems this doctor
has a lot of free time.
And it seems, Mr. Park,
you do too.
What should I look for?
Do you have specific concerns?
It won't be too much to suspect anyone
who comes into view.
Find everything you can on him.
Yes, sir.
If you're seriously thinking
about getting a divorce,
you have to get this job.
You think it's easy for women
to earn a living alone?
Experience as a sign language interpreter
at the presidential office
ensures you can get a job anywhere.
The car's ready.
YOU'RE LISTENING TO 99.4 MHZ
You just listened to the song
requested by Song Hyun-joo.
Next, we have a song
requested by user 406-000-1290.
"Call Me Now" by Colin Sof.
Are you okay? I thought you had come out.
Does he want me to call?
Does he know that I have this phone?
Already?
Where are you going?
Here. There were no traces of hacking.
I asked where you were going.
- The convenience store.
- For what?
Beer and ice cream.
Anything else?
How does it feel
to have messed up so badly, 406?
So why did you drag your feet?
It's your fault
for taking my threat lightly.
Man, let's end this.
What will it be? Decide.
I want to ask you something first.
What do you gain if I leave Hong Hee-joo?
What do I gain?
What 406 gains from this?
What are you trying to achieve
by getting me to divorce Hong Hee-joo?
What do you mean?
It's not like you married her for love.
You don't even love her now.
If it's going to be like that,
just leave her.
Hello?
I guess you have no idea
how that sounds to me.
It feels like
your threats are
for someone else's benefit.
What's your relationship
with Hong Hee-joo?
Listen carefully, 406.
I will never give you what you want.
You're a crazy man
resorting to kidnapping, extortion,
and even bomb threats now.
Do you think I'd give Hee-joo to you?
I have no intention
of giving her up.
Wait, why won't you give her up--
I'm sorry. Let's end the call here
for today.
Hee-joo's waiting for something.
Hello?
What on earth…
What's he thinking?
I won't divorce you.
I'm saying this
just in case someone misleads you.
There's no divorce for me.
Whether it's a scandal or rumor,
I won't tolerate my name
being dragged through the mud.
That's why.
Everything you do…
is clumsy.
Did the official document
reach the center?
You're going to have to give it your all
to stand beside me.
Why do you want me by your side?
If I become the interpreter
at the presidential office,
you think you can handle it?
The entire world will know
my name and face.
You seem pretty confident, don't you?
I can assure you,
there's no one better than me.
What unfounded confidence is that?
You're not that experienced.
Experience isn't everything.
I can tell by a person's expression.
I know what you're going to say
and what you're thinking.
Really?
Then tell me.
What am I thinking now?
The guy who kidnapped you and threw
a bomb in my office knows a lot,
as I mentioned, right?
Yes.
It's true we may be better off
as strangers,
but I hate that.
I don't like that what he said is true.
I want to tell him,
"No, you're wrong."
"What do you know about us?"
That's what I'll do.
Lie down.
Come and lie down.
I won't bite.
Do whatever you want.
What? Are you afraid I'll jump you?
Dream on.
If I were going to,
I'd have done it already.
We've been together for years.
Wait.
Are you scared you might jump me?
Yeah, I could see that happening.
Don't come if you can't resist.
Don't turn your back.
It's rude to the person beside you.
He knew where my office was,
so the house probably isn't safe either.
But for tonight…
sleep without worrying.
And whatever happened
the day you were kidnapped…
just think of it as a bad dream.
What you heard then, too.
That you said to call
when there's a corpse?
Forget it all.
Don't read too much into it.
What do I do?
What should I do?
Mom?
Why?
Why did you survive?
Why are you unscathed?
You should've been hurt too!
Be quiet. Don't make a sound.
His biological daughter's deaf,
and his only son is dead.
But you're unscathed,
and if you upset the chairman,
we'll get kicked out!
Yes, Hee-joo.
Don't say a word.
Hee-joo,
you're so shocked
that you can't speak, okay?
Mom, that hurts.
Shut your mouth!
You can't sacrifice your voice?
Not every life holds
the same value, Hee-joo.
We…
We can only stay
if the chairman feels sorry for us.
Do you understand?
How long do I have to not speak?
Until you turn into bubbles.
You're the Little Mermaid now.
Crap!
Come on!
Hey!
What was that?
I almost forgot.
What happened with him?
Who?
You know, the guy who got a naked picture
of his wife from some crazy man.
Was it an affair?
- I don't know.
- It's definitely an affair.
He'd know if he checked his wife.
He didn't.
Why not?
To try and get evidence?
He might not want to.
What?
To find out for himself.
He's a pervert.
Normal people would've lost it
and dug right in for the truth.
"Who are you sleeping with?"
But he can't even check for himself.
What do you think?
It's true love.
He loves his wife.
He's got to be a pervert.
The weather's cooled down,
so it's bearable now.
Are you okay?
Goodness. Where's my head at?
I didn't bring a blanket.
I'll be right back, okay?
Let's have a moment of silence to honor
our patriotic martyrs and fallen heroes.
Bow for a moment of silence.
DAD
A video call?
Dad?
Sis!
How have you been?
Where's my phone?
Are you using it well?
Yeah, I know.
I know you took it.
You did well yesterday.
Sis, I like you.
You're quick to catch on.
Wait.
What about my dad?
Starting now, I'll ask you questions,
and you'll answer.
Sis.
Using that phone
means you're threatening
Paik Sa-eon, right?
But for what?
Well?
What are you asking for?
Answer me.
If not, I'm coming for that phone…
right now.
A divorce.
What?
That's right!
Sis, that night…
I'd be pissed too.
I swear, Paik Sa-eon is a total asshole.
So, Sis?
Call him.
Keep calling him.
Sis,
I like you. Do you know why?
Because you have the same goal as us.
So…
you can
keep the phone.
But…
you have to promise me.
No backing out…
in the middle.
You started this,
so you see it through.
Got it?
Sis!
Hello? Dad!
Let's go.
I hope he'll be okay.
Let's keep in touch.
Of course.
Hee-joo!
She's his daughter. Na Jin-cheol's… What?
Fortunately, he wasn't hurt.
He's sedated and asleep.
I'm so sorry.
I stepped away for just a moment.
He suddenly disappeared.
When the caregiver found your father,
he was alone.
And these were with him.
But since your father is unharmed,
they could belong to someone else.
For now, we need to investigate it.
Yes, will you come with us
to file a report?
Are you awake?
Call.
Call him.
Sis.
Goodness!
Are you okay?
Call him.
Sis.
- What's that?
- What?
I'll do it.
What's wrong with this?
What's wrong with this thing?
What's wrong?
What's going on with that now?
What's happening?
What?
You have to promise me.
No backing out in the middle.
You started this,
so you see it through.
Got it?
Sis!
Call him.
Sis.
What is it?
What's wrong?
Are you feeling sick?
Oh, dear.
Are you okay?
What was I expecting?
I was such a fool.
Has my life
ever been easy?
Why do I still have to bring
things like this
and teach you everything?
I can't do anything.
No one in this world is on my side.
What?
What is that?
What? Why are they coming towards us?
- Did we do something wrong?
- No way!
We didn't do anything.
Hello!
Hello. Thank you for your hard work.
You may leave now.
Pardon?
I'll come to the station
to file the report.
I'm sorry,
but what's your relationship with her?
We're family.
Excuse me?
She is…
my wife.
WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
I can't do this anymore.
- Let's go!
- To the president's office!
It's your chance to try
with your name on the line.
You should start thinking about
how you're going to handle
the aftermath if I get the job.
Finally, I want to test you on something.
Can you not speak at all?
You know what day it is today, right?
Do you know or not
that my sister is back?
Tell me if you're hiding anything.
Hong Hee-joo…
can make sounds.
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce