[Team Leader Baek Su Jeong]
[Moon Ga Young]
[Director Ban Ju Yeon]
[Choi Hyeon Wook]
[Yongsung's successor. [The new chaebol director?]
[Im Se Mi]
[Kwak Shi Yang]
[My Dearest Enemy]
[This series is fictional.]
[Characters and settings are fictional.]
[Chapter 8]
In that case...
thing...
Let me let you go.
Okay. I'll go.
Okay.
- Why...? - I think...
I want to ask you something.
Really? What is it?
It's a bit strange to talk here.
Shall we go for a walk?
I would be very happy.
You can ask me anything.
I will answer every question.
What did you want to ask me...?
What should I do with your belongings?
I've put it in my attic for now.
Don't you need to find a place to stay somewhere?
I am not sure.
If I were to take a position in my own name, the president might find out.
Ah, I understand.
If that's alright, can I leave them there?
I'll feel comfortable if I'm at your house.
That would also be a good excuse to see you.
You say such things without any shame.
I'll go inside then.
Ben...
I have something to ask you.
Really?
Yes.
What did you want to ask me?
I think you're very close to that woman.
Jin, do you love me?
We've been close since we were kids.
We met while playing a video game.
Was this the game where you met your first love?
Yes.
What is the name of that game?
I think you're close to Chef Kim.
Yes, he's my mother's friend-
Oh dear, are you alright?
It was a motorcycle.
Yes.
Anyway, we were childhood friends.
Ah, I understand.
Wait a minute.
So you asked him to ask questions about me?
I had no other option then.
You knew a lot about my secret.
Did they leave?
Yes, the cat is gone.
Was it a cat?
Maybe I overreacted.
A little?
Should we do this when there aren't many people around?
We might run into my father.
Being careful won't hurt.
Getting caught by someone at work would be worse.
There are a lot of people here, you know.
The headquarters employs 8,000 people, and including subsidiaries, the total number of employees is 100,000.
You never know when or where you're going to run into someone. Don't you agree?
You convinced me.
Wait.
- Let's go. - Is there no one around?
Yes.
I really need to leave now.
Drive home safely. Call me when you get there.
Okay. Good night.
Yes!
Peace?
Does that mean something like rock 'n' roll?
I love you.
This guy is crazy.
That's what it means in sign language.
Really. She knows how to make me laugh.
She knows how to drive me crazy.
[Grace]
Excuse me.
Yes sir. Do you need anything?
Alcohol? Water? Snacks?
Instead, could I have your number?
Sir?
I'd like to see you somewhere else sometimes.
[Lee Hyeong Geun, CEO of AZ Investment Securities]
I'm afraid that won't be possible.
Why not?
Because I'm a customer?
No. I don't care if you're a customer.
I'm simply not interested in you.
- D-You're not interested in me? - No.
Let me know if you need anything other than my number.
[Kim Shin Won]
[Grace]
[Unfollow]
[Unfollow Confirm]
I probably won't see him again.
Kim Shin Won.
- It's been a long time. - Yes.
Did we last meet at our last gathering?
Are you alone? Where's your girlfriend?
My girlfriend?
We broke up a while ago.
How many hours has it been?
Has it been at least 24 hours?
Joking.
I'm going to give this up.
Have you heard of Ha Jin?
Her husband cheated on her and they got divorced.
Crazy! Are you serious?
I never thought he would do that.
They had been campus couples since first grade.
I know. You can never truly know people.
I feel so sorry for him.
I am good.
- Ha Jin. - You came early.
Hey, I heard about your husband.
Are you really okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
At first I was angry, but I haven't felt any emotions since we divorced.
- Ha Jin. - What do you mean you're fine?
You don't have to put on an act in front of us.
Right.
No, I'm serious.
Divorce is not a trivial matter.
Those who cheat should be completely eradicated.
Hey, calm him down.
Hey...
Let's go. Let's go.
Huh? So we're meeting here now?
Would you like some sweets with me?
Meeting you here is a bit...
Does it feel like fate?
Yes.
I was angry because my friends were telling me to get married.
That's why I came up here. But you were here.
So, I guess...
I came here angry, too.
Why? Did your friends tell you to get married too?
Who would say that to someone who's recently divorced?
Ah, yes. That's right.
With my ex-wife...
I dated him for over 10 years, since first grade, and we got married.
You had been together for a long time.
Because we had known each other for a long time, I thought I knew him well.
But I guess marriage was another story.
He cheated on me in less than six months.
After he moved to another city.
What a stick figure.
I know.
He's a stick figure.
I was really fine after getting rid of him.
But everyone says I won't be okay.
Should I pretend I'm not okay?
If you're really fine, don't bother.
I know.
I wish they believed me like you believed them.
I was angry about things like that too.
I've been sincere in everything, but they all say I wasn't sincere.
You know how you feel better than anyone.
I know.
I know how I feel better than anyone.
Really...
I have always been sincere.
Do you want to sleep with me?
That you could sleep with me again, just like last time...
...but you said you didn't want to go out with me.
Do you still feel the same way?
If I said yes, would you reject me?
Yes, I refuse.
You rejected me, but you returned my kiss.
You should have pushed me.
There's no way I can push you away.
Do you like me that much?
This is not good.
You'll have to go out with me seriously.
Follow me too.
Don't you want?
I want to. Because I like you.
You said you had a meeting. What are you doing here?
I have a brief moment to see you.
- Was there no traffic? - No. I arrived safely.
Su Jeong.
When did you leave the house...?
Director?
Baba.
What brought you here today, Director?
Well, actually...
How are you, Dad?
I am good.
You saw me yesterday, you know.
Packages...
The packages in my room belong to him.
The company's confidential documents.
I understand.
Because Ms. Baek is the employee I trust the most.
That's why I keep them at your house.
Thank you for your permission.
We're just keeping it secret.
Meanwhile, why...
The document I need to check today happened to be here. That's why I'm here.
But on the weekend.
I understand.
You're a workaholic too.
You're definitely Yongsung's leader.
Actually, Su Jeong is a serious workaholic too.
He works until late hours and on weekends as well.
Unbelievable.
But you must like him because he works so hard.
Yes, me...
I love him.
Instead of standing here, why don't you come inside?
- What are you doing, Su Jeong? - Huh?
- W-Why...? - Help him get inside.
I'll take this out first.
It won't be a problem, right?
Come in.
Is this your room?
Yes.
Toggaengyi.
You kept him safe.
Certainly.
Don't you want the document?
You said you were looking for an important document.
Ah, Belgian.
I forgot. I need to find it now.
Key... Key...
He was around here.
It was somewhere around here.
Where...
I found it! The key.
The key point.
Come when you're finished. I'll cut some fruit.
Okay.
Did you find the document?
Yes, I'm looking.
You're trapped here.
Keep this place safe for me.
You're the smartest of them all.
Everything is well hidden.
I'm curious about something.
What's this?
I-I don't know. What could it be...?
Dad must be waiting. Go out and eat some fruit.
I am at home.
- Hey. - Hey, hey!
G-Get out of here.
Please go.
The bathroom door handle is loose.
Sometimes it opens even when it's locked.
It should have happened while you were inside.
I need to fix it immediately.
I'll fix it later.
You must have been scared.
I was scared, but...
No problem.
I haven't lost my dignity as a human being.
Okay.
Take some.
Why did you come to our house?
Here is an important document.
He came to pick it up.
Is it an important document?
Why didn't you just take it and leave?
Why did you mark your area?
- Marking my territory? - You little-
Baek Su Bin, why are you being so rude to the guest?
Why didn't you just wander around your apartment? Why are you here?
I am visiting my home.
Don't touch me. My hair is falling out.
Director, eat something. Here you go.
It's getting colder.
I'm sorry, but I have a meeting.
I'm leaving now.
Eat one anyway.
Okay.
I'm leaving now.
Thank you for inviting me.
Oh, okay.
What are you doing? Stop.
Are you two already dating?
Why did you invite him here so early?
This is inappropriate.
What are you saying? Didn't you hear my father? He was here for a document...
...I know. The fact that he's here means you're serious.
You fooled your father too.
Did you agree to sneak out or something?
Hey, you—big sister, what happens if you get caught doing this?
My dad and I are fine, but what if your coworkers find out?
The director's family will find out sooner or later.
Maybe he's sincere, but his family won't like you.
What if they splashed water on you and then dropped you an envelope?
Would you cry and say, "Just let us fall in love"? Is that it?
Are you watching TV series instead of studying?
We're not going out, I told you.
This won't happen.
And even if it did, it wouldn't matter.
- You're crazy. - Stop talking nonsense and get out.
Okay.
I'm sure you can figure it out.
But, Sister,
Really...
I don't want you to get hurt.
I'm worried about you right now.
I have a wonderful little brother.
Oh dear, who would marry her?
Isn't he the heir to your company or something?
You showed me your picture last time.
Great. What is he doing here?
He must have come to buy dessert.
Are the Chaeboller eating this dessert?
There are too many employees.
You said it would be difficult to get.
There are too many people inside.
I'm glad I ordered in advance.
Let's go.
It will be here in about five minutes.
Okay.
Chief Kwon,
You started in Yongsung 20 years and three months ago.
As expected.
That's absolutely true.
Meanwhile, my daughter is already in middle school.
Time really flies.
You remained loyal to the president throughout this long period.
It must have been possible because you genuinely respected her.
I'm glad you accepted this.
But why did you say that the president would visit me that day?
You went against his word and helped me. Why?
I didn't know...
I helped you, Director.
Just in case, I didn't want to delay her next appointment.
That's why I called you.
But in the end, something happened and it was delayed.
Director.
Yes.
I want someone to be Yongsung's successor, someone who will carry on his vision.
And I've never met anyone else who resembles him as much as you do.
At least not yet.
Well...
I hope you won't disappoint the president any further.
Don't worry.
This won't happen.
He is the CEO of Arteta Asia.
Ben Ban Ju Yeon.
I wanted to meet you earlier, but here we are.
This...
for your daughter.
I can't say no to that.
My daughter wanted to try this while she was in Korea.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I'm a bit forgetful.
I can help you from now on, right?
Sounds good.
I didn't ask you yesterday.
You said you didn't want a serious relationship.
Why did you change your mind?
At random.
I realized there was no reason for me not to see you.
You like me and I like you.
I just don't want anything complicated.
Depending on the relationship, you hope, you dream...
...you'll be disappointed, you'll deceive, and you'll be hurt.
Isn't this terrible?
If you're happy, that's good.
If not, forget it. That's all I want.
I thought it would be possible with you.
You are right.
You date someone to be happy.
He arrived.
Yes, I'm about to leave.
What about you, Baek Soo Jeong?
I'm going to work too.
I'll see you at work soon.
So you know we need to be more careful, right?
Did you forget?
I have kept my private life secret my entire life.
I'll leave them to guess.
We won't get caught. Don't worry.
But I caught you.
This means we are destined to be together.
You said we were unlucky.
Anyway, you shouldn't let on.
I won't let on.
Never.
I won't either.
Hello, Team Leader.
Hello.
Team Leader.
How did your blind date go?
Did you have a date?
- Excuse me? - You seemed to like him.
Really?
Assistant Manager Yang, you must be wrong.
I rejected him. Completely.
I cut it off completely.
I think.
I guess you can't impress every man.
I think an older man would suit you better.
W-Why...?
Because you're so confident in yourself, it makes you...
...an older person who is generous and kind would be more suitable.
Yes, yes.
And it shouldn't be too high-quality either.
Why is this?
Think.
He needs to support his career.
If he's obsessed with his reputation and success...
...if that happens, it will be very tiring for both of you.
Wouldn't it be great if we were both good at our jobs?
I didn't want to say it because it's so obvious.
You know the guy from the comic book you're talking about?
Is he the kind of guy who kisses you and then says he's forgotten you?
You can't date someone like him.
That kind of man is the worst.
Absolutely the worst.
What kind of main character is this?
Don't read comic books like that. They're bad for you.
I know. I know.
To be honest, I don't just want you dating someone at work.
That's why I don't want you to resign.
How could the assistant principal possibly be dating someone at work?
She said office romance is hell.
This is hell. Isn't it, Team Leader?
- Did I say that? - Yes, this is hell.
That's good to hear then.
It's impossible for him to do something like that.
Hell?
Why did I say that?
Na Na, where is Assistant Manager Yang?
He hasn't been here for a while.
Ah, in the director's office.
So, Director?
Direct-Director!
Team Leader Baek, who prints and copies like this these days?
It must be tiring.
For me.
For you too.
I'll pick it up when you're finished.
Okay.
Team Leader - this... - Director!
How can you have no practical skills at all?
How can you not know how to make a copy?
Look. Feed the paper like this, press the button, and the paper will come out.
The letters are black and the paper is white.
Go ahead and approve it.
Git.
Okay.
How will he survive in this world?
Team Leader, are you going to be a Director Killer again?
Hala varis o.
However, he/she needs to know how to make copies.
Doesn't he know how to do it?
I wasn't surprised. He didn't know how to grind either.
I had a hard time because he was clinging to me all morning.
Did he do the same thing to you?
- Yes. - Oh dear.
What a strange man.
I was scared just now.
You know I wasn't actually yelling at you, right?
I know how to make copies.
I did this a lot when I was an intern and a secretary.
I know. I know.
There's nothing you can't do, Director.
So you understand.
My stomach...
Now yell at me.
Say you were sorry before.
Yell at me and scold me.
How do you explain our being here then?
But still, how can I yell at you?
You used to be good at this.
Are they fighting again?
They seem close, too.
Really.
Director!
A boss shouldn't take offense at things like that.
You make a good boss by accepting criticism.
Do you understand? I asked if you understood or not.
Here we go again.
I'm witnessing a legend right now, aren't I?
Let's go downstairs before we get involved.
Yes. I think that would be better.
The office is dangerous. Let's go back immediately.
Its...
You're very good at improvisation.
Very, very good.
I had no other option.
I was just pretending.
Were your feelings hurt?
Why are you so good at getting angry?
Do you get angry when you see me?
Why? Because I'm not older than you and I'm not your type?
Why are you worried about such a comment?
No.
Didn't you prefer an older man?
At the farm, you mentioned the age difference.
You said I couldn't be your boyfriend and that you didn't see me as a man.
That's what you said.
THE...
To be honest, my first love was younger than me.
That's why I didn't want a younger man.
Because of a bad memory.
It's so frustrating.
How can I make you feel better?
You can do me a favor.
Should I get you some chocolate milk?
Or should I go to the arcade with you?
Am I a child?
In that case...
You can't ask me for a kiss or anything like that.
You're fond of this, aren't you?
- What did you say? - Why would I want something like that?
That's not true. Don't worry.
I'll tell you when something comes to mind.
Ok then.
I don't need a favor to do things like this.
[Yongsung Shopping Mall]
Is this what he means by kindness?
These are characters from my favorite comic books.
Their names are easier to memorize than dog names.
[Regis K. Landegre]
Very jealous.
I memorized them all.
He memorizes quickly.
Let's go.
What are all these things?
Is today a special day?
How am I supposed to eat all of this...?
Su Jeong, I have a boyfriend.
Suddenly?
When, where, and how did you meet?
He was a client of mine, and I think we became very strongly connected, both physically and mentally.
You said you weren't interested in going out.
But it's someone you know well.
Me? Who is it?
Kim Shin Won.
What?
From our design department?
Yes.
Impossible.
How about you and him...?
Are you really dating him?
No, he's a womanizer.
Are you talking about me by chance?
Chef Kim, w-why are you there?
Because I'm her boyfriend.
You can put them all inside.
Ok I understand.
I think he's not a boyfriend, he's a maid.
You are wrong.
If he cheated, he would be considered a womanizer.
They tend to start and end relationships in a clean manner.
I fell in love with this aspect of him.
You see me as someone who never makes mistakes.
Like this.
I understand.
A close friend told me.
That's why I thought it was true.
Anyway, you can't fool me. Never.
Of course I wouldn't cheat.
By the way, who is my best friend?
Well, I thought you and Director Ban were close.
How do you know we're close?
Most people seem to already know this.
Really. I tried to hide it, but I think it's obvious.
So, how's it going between you and the director?
Well, there's not much to tell.
We just get along well.
Don't you have a special relationship?
Oh, don't worry, Ha Jin.
Ju Yeon would never date a coworker.
The president will be in trouble if he finds out.
- Really? - Yes.
And Ju Yeon is a little cold towards people.
I think it would be good if he dated someone, a sweet and loving woman.
He's sweet enough to tolerate his personality.
This is the complete opposite of Su Jeong.
Right? The complete opposite of Team Leader Baek.
I know.
[My Other Half]
Yes, Director.
Did you quit your job?
Ok then.
Let's go on a date after work tomorrow.
The film, the famous restaurant or cafe.
I've heard that many people want to do this.
Is there somewhere you'd like to go?
I am too.
Now that I think about it, I don't like crowded places.
I'd like a quiet place.
- Really? - Yes.
Here I am, surrounded by people.
Why would I go to another crowded place?
Ah, I know where I want to go.
Hey, hey. Have you seen Yongsung's successor?
What?
He's young too.
I'm so jealous.
I need to be more careful.
[Yongsung Shopping Mall]
We have signed agreements with all the companies that will join our food division.
We can start the renovation on time.
Okay.
2. The team was unable to sign a company.
We are still negotiating the terms.
But we're finishing it.
Finish it as soon as possible.
Yes, we will.
Sales Team 1 should be happy.
Team leader Baek handled the hardest part.
You know we work very hard too.
If Team Leader Baek hadn't intervened, we would have handled it differently.
- Really? - Do you have time to chat?
I don't have one.
Strategy Team, how's the Botanical House show going?
We hired a performer.
Besides performance, this includes regular events...
I also thought about how we could use it.
I will summarize it and report it to you.
Okay, that sounds good.
That's all for the meeting.
Okay, that sounds good. I like you.
I wanted to say that, but I had to hold back.
See you at our next appointment.
You're very good at your job, Team Leader Baek.
Are you happy doing everything on your own?
I'm asking because I'm genuinely curious.
Did you sleep with Director Ban?
What did you say?
You seem too close.
He always says, 'It sounds good. Good job.'
I don't think she's told anyone else.
I think I'm the only one who works this much.
No.
You've always worked very hard.
But why is he the only one who loves someone as tough and stubborn as you?
Didn't you seduce him because he had varicose veins?
Are you sure you didn't sleep with him?
I said we weren't like that.
Really?
Never mind then.
Next time, regarding comments like these...
...would you be careful to do it in front of others?
I need a witness to sue you for defamation.
I can only tolerate a certain amount of nonsense.
These are the coolest clothes I own.
What kind of outfit is this...?
I had no other option.
Dressing in my own style was too risky for fear of getting caught.
But still.
You look like you're going to a date, not to work.
That's why I prepared this.
What did you prepare?
Change.
Is this where you wanted to come?
Quiet and distant.
I knew she enjoyed intimacy.
Actually, you're the one who enjoys this.
You were always the first one to kiss me.
I know.
We don't want to go to a crowded place and stand out. That's why we're here.
You too can go to a restaurant, a cafe, a movie theater...
...and you've wanted to go to places like that.
No, I came here because I wanted to.
People often go on dates by the Han River.
Ve...
We can hold hands like this here.
Do you like this song?
Yes.
Do you want to jump?
No.
I used to like this song too.
Why the past tense?
Because I can't love anymore.
Does this have anything to do with your first love?
Yes, I think so.
You must have loved him very much.
It takes up too much space in his life.
That's how horrible it was.
You don't need to worry.
The past is simply the past.
The song is innocent.
Start loving me again.
Okay.
What's so funny?
Are you meeting someone?
Please bring the menu!
The menu is here.
I'm not even the president. Why are you trying to hide it?
Be honest with me.
I will always support their relationship.
I fully support it.
Look at this.
You're not denying it.
Are you actually seeing someone?
- Yes. - With whom?
Who stole your heart?
Don't try to learn too much.
İncinirsin.
Is it nice?
How shallow.
I don't think so.
Of course it's beautiful.
Beautiful.
Everything...
Strawberries are delicious.
Everything about him is wonderful.
He truly loves me, and I love him too.
Is Baek Su Jeong the team leader?
Don't make ridiculous assumptions.
I've heard the radish kimchi here is fantastic.
Team Leader Baek O.
The food sector is the highlight of this project, but sales are more...
...to increase it even more, we also need to renovate the Luxury Wing.
Luxury brands have strong identities, so renovating the interior is challenging.
Especially Arteta.
If Arteta, the essence of the Luxury Wing, remains unchanged—no need to worry.
I've already spoken to them and resolved the issue.
- Excuse me? - I met with them over the weekend.
I've been interested in this for a long time.
The client I didn't get to meet at the party was the CEO of the Asian branches.
How long have you been thinking about this?
I've been thinking about this since the project started.
Engaging in aggressive public relations and a major image transformation...
...I needed Arteta's involvement to give permission.
Its...
Now you're impressed by me, aren't you?
- I'm not. - I think you are.
I swear I'm not.
Let's just say you are.
Because I wanted to impress you.
Move aside. We're here.
Here I am...
You spied on her while she was naked.
Do you know how scared I was?
You have a dragon tattoo on your back.
You were like a bully...
So, you were strangely dressed and spoke badly.
But you were in the director's office.
I don't like those kinds of fashion trends.
I don't even want to be near it.
What about now?
I don't care.
Because I love you.
How long have you liked me?
- Excuse me? - You must have hated me at first.
Which aspect of me have you started to like?
Do you usually ask questions so directly?
I usually don't know what's going on.
Because this is my first time.
But I want to know.
To be able to work on it.
So that you will continue to love me.
Until.
Come on. Tell me.
I noticed he was good at his job.
And my being busy doesn't bother you.
Can I save this?
Why would you record this?
Ve?
Ve...
Your password is funny.
I'm starting to find you a little cute.
What did you say?
It was supposed to be cool, not cute.
Say it again. Did you just call me cute?
Not cool?
Come on. You can be cute too.
No.
I'll give you another chance.
You're cute.
It was a long report.
Yes.
He then needs to go on a business trip.
That's why I had to report everything in advance.
I think so. I heard we're setting up a café and a stage at the Botanical House.
You must have needed time to talk about this.
Yes, that's also true.
So then...
Ju Yeon ve Su Jeong...
It seems to be coming out.
Ju Yeon said she started dating someone.
No matter how much I think about it, there's no one else besides Mrs. Baek.
- If so- - But...
I think it would be good if they continued to go out.
What if they find out who each other are?
I'm sure it will be a huge shock.
Since they haven't learned it, they may never know.
You Yeon...
He finally seems genuinely happy.
I don't feel like it...
To separate them.
I pressed it.
Thank you.
[My Other Half]
Yes, Director. Is the appointment over?
Yes, I'm at the hotel right now.
You must be tired.
I miss you.
We've been apart for a day.
We'll meet tomorrow evening.
But what if I wanted to see you right now?
Try to hold on.
I guess you don't miss me that much.
You have things to do tomorrow.
I don't want you to struggle because of me.
Of course I miss you too.
There's a comic book I want to read right now.
The first copy was released in 1996.
You can't even find it on the internet.
- Excuse me? - I can't stand it anymore.
I need to read it now.
But at your house.
I'll be right there.
It's not you.
I'm getting my comic book.
Okay. I'll find it for you.
Okay.
What a huge head.
[Black Dragon]
He acted as if he didn't like it.
But he kept it in a very precious way.
Is she a little ugly?
Where might the comic book be?
Su Jeong.
Why are you out? I told you to come out when I called.
Did you miss me a lot?
You're the only one who can set the Black Dragon free.
Please give me love...
And freedom.
This is why...
You're the Black Dragon, aren't you?
[My Dearest Enemy]
[Thank you to Yoon Park for his special participation]
I think I was very lonely again.
You said you liked me too.
I didn't know who he was at the time.
I am sad.
Could you be a little gentler with me?
There was an article on the office worker website this morning.
I heard that Team Leader Baek is going to marry the director.
- Is this true? - Baek Su Jeong.
Quietly remove him from the company.
It's not easy. It was expected.
So, let's give up.