[Bloom Life]
[2007]
Look, two flocks of pigeons are racing.
Look.
Nur's flock is impressive!
Will his pigeons win?
Sadiq's tumbler pigeons
are even better.
Uncle Nur definitely won't win.
That pigeon is flying towards us!
What are you waiting for?
Let's go after it!
Pigeons know the way home.
Uncle.
Grandma, Auntie.
Look,
you scared the dewdrops off my roses.
Where are the dewdrops? Let me see.
We finally caught it.
It's so cute, all white.
Arzugul.
Laili?
Come down.
This is the pigeon
that flew away from the flock?
You caught it?
[Episode 6: The Home Won't Change]
Why did you also plant a tree here?
I just picked it up on the road.
It looked half-dead.
If I can save it, it's a life saved.
Be careful.
Planting a tree creates a bond.
You have to water and fertilize it.
I'm already running a homestay here.
So I don't mind being "tied down" a bit.
Didn't you plant one, too?
This is my home.
What's wrong with me planting one here?
Besides,
I might not stay here forever.
Wait,
you accepted my job offer,
you can't just leave anytime.
♪ My little sapling ♪
So ugly.
Laili.
Ayisha, Cai, you're here.
What do you want to eat today?
What do you want to eat?
-Fried chicken and yogurt.
Okay, take a seat first.
Let's go.
Later, when Laili
serves all our food,
give her a heart sign
when you thank her.
The food is here.
Let me help.
-Thank you, Laili.
Who taught you that?
We learned it ourselves.
Yourselves? From whom?
Is your instrument shop very free lately?
Why does someone run two blocks every day
just to buy chicken wings?
No.
It's these two.
They said the food here is delicious
and begged me to bring them.
Right after lunch,
Brother brought us here
to eat.
Brother burned the eggplants last night
and mentioned Laili—
Eat fried chicken.
Laili.
What's wrong?
This is for you.
Burn ointment.
-We kept an extra for roasting lamb.
-Thank you.
Here.
When you apply it,
go clockwise.
You apply it for me.
♪ Woods, oh poplar woods ♪
What's wrong? What happened?
That was so loud.
What's wrong? What's that sound?
What's wrong?
What happened?
Batur, what happened?
The earth kiln.
Don't just stand there.
Throw water in it. Yes, throw it right in.
I told you to watch the kiln.
Where on earth did you go?
I...
Where did you go?
I thought
the temperature was stable,
so I went out for a bit.
You can't leave the kiln
while it's firing.
Don't you know that?
Ma'am.
I heard that other earthenware shops
installed electric kilns,
so I wanted to take a look.
Electric kilns fire fast and stably.
And people don't have to
watch them all the time.
I even got the phone number
of the electric kiln manufacturer.
Master, look.
Here is their business card.
Master, electric kilns are really useful.
Master!
Since the kiln cracked,
let's just replace it.
Batur.
Replace it?
Do you have any idea
just how important
this ancient earthen kiln is?
My great-grandfather
left it behind.
It's more precious to me than life itself.
You, kid,
are always looking for
the easy way out.
Haven't I told you
that our family
will never use those things?
Do you understand?
Other earthenware shops
have more orders than they can handle.
We're stuck with this broken earth kiln.
How can we compete with them?
Mom.
How much does it cost to fix the kiln?
I've got 400 saved up here.
This is what's left from breakfast.
-Mom, take it.
-No need.
It will be fine.
Trust me. It's really fine.
I can get all the rest
of the money together.
Our kiln will be fixed.
I'll figure something out.
This...
Timur,
have you ever seen a merlin
with your own eyes?
They move so fast,
catching little birds like a bullet.
Sometimes I wonder,
if
my son Asimjan were still alive,
would my daughter Laili
still be as lively and active
as she is now,
with the passion of a merlin?
Maybe it's time to break the rule of passing it
only to sons.
Why can't you get the hang of it?
The spout must be made higher.
Otherwise, the water
will flow out with no pressure.
Why are you just standing there?
Come here.
Come on,
you try one.
Come on.
Do it.
Slow down.
Good.
Very good.
Families making earthenware like ours
would originally only
pass the craft to sons.
But
you've loved making earthenware
so much since you were little.
I have
seen it all.
Nowadays,
more and more families
use machines to make earthenware.
I want to teach you
the most traditional craft.
Things made by machines
are all the same
and boring.
Only handmade earthenware
has warmth.
I can't
fully convey to you what it feels like
to touch the clay.
It all depends on your own understanding
and effort.
The water inside...
It's dry. Oh, good.
Dad.
Why did you buy this?
How can a girl like a flower
have hands full of cracks?
Dad, let me help you.
No need.
Give it to me.
You go practice.
And practice well,
okay?
Thank you, Zhou.
You got all these hard-to-find paints
for me.
You didn't have to deliver them in person.
It's fine, Auntie. I was afraid they
might get damaged in transit.
Don't mention it.
After all, Xia Zi
is my good friend.
Zhou.
Yes, Auntie.
Let's not tell Xia Zi about this for now.
I'm afraid she'll worry unnecessarily.
Don't worry, I won't tell her.
I'll sing a song I wrote myself.
It's my first time singing it.
Good!
♪ The night sky tonight ♪
♪ Is filled with beautiful dreams ♪
♪ In the grass of the valley ♪
♪ Who hid away time and space ♪
♪ Those long, lingering memories ♪
♪ Are so captivating ♪
♪ Searching for the lost self ♪
♪ What was it that you threw into time ♪
♪ What is it that can define you and me ♪
♪ Laili ♪
I didn't expect you
to write your own songs.
Music is all connected.
And Grandpa also wants me
to learn more things.
Actually, I've always wanted
to compose my own music.
Actually, me too.
I think besides those traditional jars,
I also want to make some
different things,
like putting my feelings
or my mood
into the clay.
I think it would be different.
Definitely.
And I believe you can do it.
Also, right now,
I have some motifs in my head.
A melody keeps playing in my mind.
-Do you want to hear it?
-What melody?
Yes.
Then I'll play it for you.
Okay.
What time is it?
Why are you singing?
Are you going to let people sleep or not?
You go first.
I actually have 2 pieces
of good news for you.
Tell me.
The first bit of good news...
Is it that funny?
I'm telling you seriously.
The first bit of good news
is that my father finally
agreed to teach me earthenware.
That's great!
The second piece of good news is
that now that I'm learning
the earthenware,
I don't have to marry Mulading anymore.
So you are off the hook.
But I don't want to be off the hook.
I like you.
I want to be your boyfriend.
This time, I mean it.
No more pretending.
But...
I'm not as pretty as Minawar.
And I'm not as smart as Arzugul.
I feel like I...
Grandpa told me,
"Choose a lover with your heart,
not your eyes."
I just like you the way you are.
I like you, too.
What?
What did you just say?
I... I said I like you too.
Say it again.
Say it a bit louder.
I said I like you too!
What did you say?
I said—
You what?
What?
She said she likes you, too!
♪ Girl, oh girl ♪
♪ Listen to a few words from me ♪
I like you.
♪ Could you please leave me ♪
♪ Your QQ number ♪
♪ If you are a big dinosaur ♪
♪ I'll be a little frog too ♪
♪ Let's not look down on each other ♪
♪ Let's just be friends ♪
♪ Darling, come on, come on, come on ♪
Grandma went out in the afternoon.
She hasn't come back yet.
Mom!
You look over there.
I'll look this way.
Grandma!
Grandma.
Why are you here?
I'm here waiting
for your grandpa to come home.
Your grandpa
went to Yarkant to collect taxes.
He was riding a horse,
carrying a hunting rifle.
How handsome he was.
In a few days,
he will come back.
I wonder if he returns,
will he be able to find our home?
Grandma.
Our home is over there.
No.
This is our house.
Look.
Isn't this pattern different from ours?
The color is the same,
but the pattern has changed.
If my husband comes back,
can he find our home?
When your grandfather comes back,
I'm worried he won't find his way home.
What if he can't find home?
Grandma's words
made me think about the direction
of the homestay renovation.
The carvings on the gate,
the smell of figs,
and the touch of old things
all help a wandering little pigeon
recognize the way home.
Hurry up.
The mooncakes are here.
Aunt Chang Yue bought these
especially for us.
Come on, everyone, have a taste.
Come on.
It's the Mid-Autumn Festival.
How can we not have mooncakes?
Chang Yue.
You haven't been
to our house for a long time.
Come have a taste.
Mom.
Aunt Jiang told you
to avoid "trigger" foods
and eat more vegetables.
It's a holiday today.
If Auntie wants to eat it,
let her have more.
Why are you giving her more?
Don't listen to her.
Leave my mom alone.
Come on.
Everyone, eat.
Everyone, have a taste.
You try some.
Come on, eat.
Come on, everyone, eat.
Eat while it's hot.
While everyone is gathered here,
I have some good news to share.
Our old inn
has been running for many years.
I have spent most of my life here.
My great-great-grandfather
was also born in this house.
When my dad was young,
he renovated it
a bit.
No one
loves this place more than we do.
As everyone knows,
our century-old house
can't keep up
with the outside development now.
If we just wait like this,
I'm afraid it
will be ruined in my hands.
It's so beautiful.
So pretty.
This is
a gift from me to Grandma and everyone.
The blueprint for the new inn.
Come, let me see.
Auntie.
Look how nice the design is.
It's so beautiful.
Dad, our house is in there, too.
Why does this look so familiar to me?
This is a sketch
I've been working on lately.
I made some changes
to the internal structure,
but the exterior is essentially
a recreation
of how it looked back in Grandpa's day.
That way,
Grandpa will never
lose his way home again.
Grandma.
The home won't change.
Please don't worry.
The home really won't change.
Does Grandma like it?
Yes.
She said, "The home won't change."
What are you doing
sneaking around?
Let me show you some good stuff.
Hey.
Why did you withdraw so much money?
We're starting work soon, right?
What the workers care about most
is this:
solid cash.
I find you're becoming
more and more like a Kashgar local.
Have you ever heard a saying here?
How much do Kashgar people
love doing business?
Even if there's only one person,
they'd sell things from their left pocket
to their right pocket.
It's...
They don't care about the result,
but the process.
As the inn's renovation begins,
everyone's heart
flutters with it.
Amidst the reluctance,
it is also full of expectation.
This century-old house embedded in
everyone's memory
will also welcome
its new life cycle.
Forty days have passed
in the blink of an eye.
She grows so fast.
So beautiful. Looks exactly like you.
Really?
Yes.
Come.
Let Grandma hold you.
Thanks for your hard work, child.
No, no.
Let Grandma hold you.
Let me hold you.
Come.
Use golden water
to wash our baby's hands.
Little feet.
Wash the little feet.
Little feet. All right.
Come,
Minawar,
look.
This is a gift
for my eldest granddaughter.
About this...
Next year,
when you give me a big,
healthy baby boy...
I'll keep it for him.
Let Auntie hold you.
So cute.
Her eyes look just like my brother's.
Come.
Is the baby sleepy?
Here, let me take her.
When Minawar was little,
as soon as she heard my lullabies,
she would sleep soundly.
Yes, yes.
♪ Sleep, my baby, sleep, my baby ♪
♪ Sleep, my baby ♪
Come, eat this.
Gangzi meat.
Eat.
Careful, it's hot.
We are already way over budget.
Let me do the math for you.
Now the doors, windows, stairs,
and other decorations—
Based on their current efficiency,
they won't be able
to finish it in half a year.
For the next six months,
we can't just spend money
without making any.
These masters
do work a bit slowly.
But slow work yields fine products.
Think about it,
which skilled master
doesn't have a temper,
right?
These pillars are
different from other things.
They will be with this house for decades,
or even centuries.
And for our homestay,
it's the woodwork that gives
the place its soul.
We must wait
for this.
At worst,
when laying the tiles,
we can make up for the lost time.
Boss,
we are off work.
Okay.
Thanks for your hard work.
See you tomorrow.
Alright.
Where are you going?
Having dinner with my mom.
You can eat this.
Well, you're going
to see Auntie?
Auntie, Xia Zi is going home.
You should pack up those things quickly.
Who is it?
W-Why are you back?
Don't you want me
to come back and eat with you?
I'm super hungry today.
Cook more noodles.
Whatever.
Anything is fine.
Okay.
What are you doing in such a hurry?
What are you packing?
I never had the chance to tell you.
I applied to go to
the Kizil Cave Institute
as a volunteer
to copy murals.
You are leaving Kashgar?
Are you selling the wood?
Stop bargaining.
Let's settle it like this.
Load the truck quickly.
We'll still do business in the future.
We are friends. Don't talk like that.
It has to be my mom.
She always manages to surprise me.
She has been
planning it for a long time.
She was worried you'd feel too lonely
being on your own in Kashgar.
You knew about this earlier than I did.
She told me not to tell you.
When I helped her
buy paint last time,
she told me to keep it a secret.
I was afraid you'd worry
about her heart
and health.
I was just thinking of you.
Tell me,
when did we start
looking out for each other like this?
You know, for the neck
of the instruments we make,
we use "male" wood.
"Male," as in male and female.
They are divided into male and female?
Yes, male.
Look, hold it like this.
If you want to grab it, do this.
Like this.
Because the male one is harder,
and the female one is softer.
They match better for the tone.
I feel that making earthenware is easier.
The clay is soft,
unlike this wood—
It's rock hard.
I give up.
I'm telling you,
it's these woods
that make the most beautiful sounds.
Then why do you like making instruments?
My family has been making instruments
for 7 generations.
So I was born to make instruments.
When I was young,
I was actually very envious
of kids who could play football
right after school.
Until I was...
thir...
right,
thirteen years old.
I made my first instrument.
When I plucked the string like this
and heard it hum,
I felt like the whole world
had settled down.
I understand that feeling.
It's like
suddenly your eyes
really opened,
and the whole world became bright.
It's like
I know
where I can go,
and where I will go.
Every time I make earthenware,
I feel like
I'm no longer Laili.
I become a different Laili.
I became
stronger,
calmer,
undisturbed,
and more focused.
Then you should be bolder,
and go create work that's your own.
Do you remember the song
I sang in the alley last time?
I've finished writing it.
Finished?
♪ We are lonely souls ♪
♪ Drifting in and out of the crowds ♪
♪ Confining dusk within the dawn ♪
♪ Waiting aimlessly
for the traffic lights ♪
♪ Suddenly, I never ask again ♪
♪ About the lingering warmth upon waking ♪
♪ This unexpected sincerity ♪
Aren't we just good friends?
♪ Makes each of our lives complete ♪
Ordinary friends.
♪ I can't quite describe it ♪
Long live our friendship.
♪ A sudden, unexpected surprise ♪
♪ Don't go away too fast ♪
♪ It truly exists ♪
♪ Thank you for your generosity ♪
♪ For making me believe in love ♪
♪ We are the lucky ones ♪
I think this material is really good.
It's perfect for our homestay.
Take a look.
♪ Mixed with complicated feelings
at times ♪
This one?
I think it's okay.
We can put it at the doorplate.
♪ The mornings we wake up together ♪
I feel like this one's not quite right.
If you think it's not right,
why call me over?
♪ Often leave me staring
at you in a daze ♪
You take a look for yourself.
♪ I can't quite describe it ♪
Xia Zi,
what do you think of Zhou?
Mom, it's been ages
since I've even been in a relationship.
♪ A sudden, unexpected surprise ♪
I haven't even figured out
my own life yet.
How can I start with someone else?
♪ Don't go away too fast ♪
♪ It truly exists ♪
Does this fig
have a heart
♪ Thank you for your generosity ♪
or not?
♪ For making me believe in love ♪
An extra 320,000.
I'll...
go back to my hometown.
For how long?
I don't know, either.
I need to raise money first.
Only after tearing the place down
did we realize the drainage
and gas lines all need redoing—
oh, and...
the water and electrical systems, too.
I'll go back first.
We'll pause the construction here for now.
I'll rush back as soon as I get the money.
Please take good care of my sapling.
Oh, don't worry.
I'll water it when I water mine.
What's there to worry about?
Congratulations on your
honorable retirement, Dr. Chang.
Thank you, Director.
Thank you.
Thank you, everyone.
Dr. Chang.
Congratulations on your retirement.
May you
unburden yourself,
start your new chapter afresh,
and find your inner path.