I'm Qingniao Group's founder
and chief architect, Shen Gu.
Regarding the recent rumors
about Minghui Group and Qingniao Group,
please allow me to clarify everything
as Xu Wanxin's husband.
Mr. Shen is actually the founder
of Qingniao Group?
That's a global tech giant
valued at hundreds
of billions of dollars.
Qingniao just broke through
quantum encryption patents.
Their infrastructure supports
23 percent of mobile services worldwide.
And the founder of that company
is Shen Gu. I can't believe that.
If that's the case,
it makes sense
why Qingniao stepped in
when we were facing the crisis.
We'll call it a day.
=Echoes of Gang City=
=Episode 19=
(Confession)
I'm Qingniao Group's founder.
I should've wiped him out back then.
When he came to Raymond
to look for funding,
he was a poor student.
I didn't expect him
to be the founder of Qingniao.
Grandfather.
Wanxin.
The Qingniao chairman
you met in Shen City was Shen Gu?
Why didn't you tell me?
Calm down,
Wanxin.
I know you feel hurt right now.
Why did he do this?
Is it because
we're in a contract marriage,
and he didn't trust me?
Or
is he like the Shen family,
after our company's research?
I can guarantee you
he didn't tell you
for those reasons.
Then why didn't you tell Wanxin
you're the president of Qingniao?
At first, I just wanted
to help her through the crisis.
I didn't expect
she would propose marriage.
I couldn't turn her down.
And after that,
I never found the right time
to tell her the truth.
There was never any contract marriage
between Wanxin and me,
nor any weighing of pros and cons.
I simply wanted to become her husband.
What if things didn't go your way?
What if she never fell for you?
If she doesn't love me,
she can leave anytime.
That's her choice.
That's what he told me.
I wouldn't lie to you.
He appeared so suddenly.
I thought
we fell for each other
after we got married.
Grandfather,
I don't know what to do now.
This is between the two of you.
You have to figure it out together.
I'm sorry.
Please allow me
to introduce myself again.
Let's go home and talk.
Shen Gu,
why did you choose to work with Minghui?
Wanxin,
the cooperation
between Qingniao and Minghui
was planned with me
by your dad before he passed away.
Minghui's biotech
and your AI
will take our tech sector
to the next level.
I've carefully reviewed
all your proposals.
They align perfectly with our vision.
But may I ask,
why were you so eager
to look for funding
and cut ties with Junlin?
You've worked together for years,
and there was even a marriage alliance.
Junlin Group
is indeed a powerful partner.
Shen Tingyuan is ambitious.
But his goal is to expand his business.
He has lost sight of the original purpose
of our cooperation.
And more importantly,
through my years of observation,
Shen Hao isn't right for my daughter.
I would never gamble
my daughter's happiness.
Thank you for trusting Qingniao.
Wanxin,
your dad has always been protecting you.
My dad did it for Minghui and me.
What about you?
What's your reason?
You.
All those so-called marriage alliances
and cooperations
are just excuses.
The only reason I did all this
was to stay by your side.
♪It feels like our souls are in sync♪
Wanxin,
I love you.
I just hope
you won't push me away.
♪As the stars flow,
fate holds this moment still♪
♪At last, your late reply arrives♪
♪At last, I hear your answer clearly♪
♪When you turn around,
I've always been behind you♪
♪As long as you're here, I have it all♪
♪The whole universe♪
Looks like my news
is more interesting than I am.
You're a big name
in both finance and the media now.
I had no choice but to notice you.
If you want to know something,
just ask me.
They'll be here soon.
Where's he going?
To get the wine.
This is for you.
Open it.
Dragon and phoenix
bring auspicious blessings.
A small gift from Madam Song and me.
Shen Gu,
take good care of her.
Stop it.
Hello?
Can someone help me?
Coming.
Let's go.
Shen Gu's identity is confirmed.
Mr. Lei Meng, what's your plan?
End all pressure on Minghui.
I'll unite Qingniao's competitors
into an alliance
and destroy their core business.
That way,
Raymond Group takes full control
of the industry.
Good.
I'll be relying on your guidance
and support in the future, Mr. Lei Meng.
Wait for my good news.
Lei Meng is gone. What do we do now?
Lei Meng
wants Qingniao dead
even more than we do.
Cheers.
I don't want to sound rude or anything.
We've revealed your identity, Mr. Gu.
But the negative publicity
around Ms. Wanxin and you
hasn't improved.
Producer Song, it seems your effort...
Sorry to let you worry, Lawyer Fang.
That's on me.
I thought about it.
Instead of letting rumors spread,
why don't both of you
clarify it together?
We can do a targeted
exclusive interview.
Wanxin, you host it.
Shen Gu will be the guest.
It's bound to draw a huge viewership.
It's a win-win.
Unless you have a better idea,
Lawyer Fang.
Or
do you want to give this opportunity
to another station?
I think...
Xi, that's a great idea.
Shen Gu,
what do you think?
If so, I'll leave Producer Song
and Anchor Xu
to arrange the interview.
Deal?
Cheers.
The meat is burnt.
We need to plan
the interview content.
Any requirements, Mr. Shen?
I'll follow your lead.
It's fine for Mr. Gu
to attend the interview.
Producer Song,
I think you should give me a toast.
I should really give you a toast.
- Right, Lawyer Fang?
- Of course.
I'll fill your glass.
Hey.
- Don't dodge, Lawyer Fang.
- Wait. I can't drink much.
Your tolerance is low?
It's not that. You're mixing drinks.
I don't drink mixed wine.
Don't do that.
I can't drink that.
(Gang City Financial News)
Good morning, everyone.
As the Junlin shareholders' meeting
approaches,
Mr. Shen Gu, founder of Qingniao Group,
will soon accept a financial interview
with Ms. Xu Wanxin from our station.
Thank you so much.
What are you smiling about?
It feels like a dream.
I never imagined
I'd be interviewed by you
as your husband.
We're recording, Mr. Gu.
Have some mercy on us
in the control room.
Save your sweet nothings
for later.
I knew it.
I wouldn't be the only victim.
Come on. Say hi...
Don't hang up, Mei.
Who let you in?
I'm his staff.
And?
I'm also his family.
I just came to check in on you,
Producer Song.
Look. Professional team
and professional you.
I can also take a quick look around.
I'll get you some coffee when it's over.
Alright. Everyone, get ready.
Three,
two,
one.
Start.
(Interview with Mr. Shen Gu,
founder of Qingniao Group)
Good afternoon, everyone.
I'm Xu Wanxin.
Today,
our studio welcomes
a very important guest.
Mr. Shen Gu, founder of Qingniao Group.
Hello, everyone. I'm Shen Gu.
Hello, Mr. Shen.
Thank you
for agreeing to this interview.
It's my honor
to be interviewed by you, Miss Xu.
Wanxin,
can you ask Mr. Gu to face the camera?
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on
no distance could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled
one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending
we face?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪