ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
Go and get changed first.
It will be fine.
Sang Yan,
how is your sister?
She's okay.
Let's talk to her over dinner.
We don't need to.
She knows her mistake.
She cried the whole way.
I already scolded her.
I think that's enough.
Do you think she's…
Duan Jiaxu said that guy didn't make any promises.
It was her wishful thinking.
With her proud personality,
if she said it's over, it's really over.
She would see it through.
Think about it.
Whenever she said she would stop binging anime,
she would stop.
Has she ever kept a plushie that she dislikes?
You're right about that.
It's her teenage rebellion phase.
It's normal to rebel once.
How about not criticizing her then?
Okay.
We'll pretend nothing happened during dinner.
As if she came home from school as usual.
We need to hold onto her ID card
and pay attention to what she does online.
We also need to take her phone.
Yes, we have to confiscate her phone.
Take this cold medicine upstairs to her later.
She wore a short skirt.
Don't let her catch a cold.
Okay.
YIHE UNIVERSITY
NANWU, YIHE, MAP TO MY DREAM
PURE MILK
Jiaxu.
I finally found my dream.
My dream is to get into Yihe University.
MY DREAM, YIHE UNIVERSITY
YIHE UNIVERSITY
DUAN JIAXU
Jiaxu.
Goodbye.
NOVEMBER 5TH, SATURDAY
GOODBYE, JIAXU
TWO YEARS LATER
So I've fulfilled my dream
and been admitted into Yihe University.
I've started a new life here.
I've attended military training
and I'm attending my lectures.
I've also made new friends
and met my lovely roommates.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to my vlog.
Today, I want to show you
the most beautiful view at my university.
So what could it be?
Hello, sorry about that.
Hi.
He's so handsome!
I'm so proud!
To the side is our lecture building.
Let me show you around.
Let's see who that cool girl is!
It's Yu Xin, the coolest girl on campus!
For her first cameo in my vlog,
-this is embarrassing! -You got in my way. Delete it.
Sorry about that!
I'll go and check on her.
Miss, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
Why are you carrying so many books alone?
My classmates are all busy.
I'm fetching books for my professor.
Where are you headed? I'll carry them.
The Digital Media Department up ahead.
Let's go then.
Thank you.
Sangsang!
Where's Wangwang?
Wangwang?
Let me show you my best friend.
-She's over there. -Why are you talking like that?
-Hi. -Who is this?
He's just--
Hi, I'm Jiang Ming in the long-distance running team.
I'm helping her carry these books.
So you're in the Sports Department.
We're in Digital Media.
We're all roommates.
Hello.
Since we've met, let's add each other on WeChat.
It's my birthday tomorrow.
Invite your friends to come to my party.
Sure, no problem.
Let me scan your QR code.
Sure, here you go.
Come on, scan his code.
She can forward it to us later.
Okay, I'll do that.
Then you can send me
the time and location later.
No problem.
I'll get that. Thank you for your help.
But…
It's okay.
Why don't you walk her there?
Go with her.
Okay, then…
It's that building.
Okay. Then we'll get going.
-Bye. -Yes, go ahead.
Bye.
-Come tomorrow. Bring your friends. -We'll wait to eat with you.
-Cut it out, will you? -What?
What are we having for lunch?
Anything will do.
Can you keep up with us?
No.
Yes, you can.
This place is pretty spacious.
-Yes. -I think my lipstick is too bright.
-Let me wipe some off. -Don't.
I think it's pretty.
I thought you weren't wearing any lipstick.
-Really? -It's this year's latest trendy color.
It looks good on everyone
Just look at her complexion.
It still can't be compared to mine.
Hey, Ning Wei.
Hi, Jiang Ming.
-Hello. -Hello.
This is my teammate, Chen Qiang.
Hi.
-Hi. -These are my classmates.
They're in the Sports Department.
-Hello. -Hi.
These are my friends from a school club.
-Hello. -Hello.
There are so many people here.
This is the birthday girl, Ning Wei.
These are her roommates.
-Happy birthday! -Happy birthday!
Thank you so much.
Since everyone is here, let's head inside.
-Okay, let's go. -Come on.
Let's go inside.
Come on.
Sangsang, today is my first birthday party
at university.
-The first one? -How do you want to celebrate?
I want
to eat well, have fun,
-and then party. -Control yourself.
CHAPTER EIGHT, REENCOUNTER
SAYING GOODBYE BEFORE MEETING AGAIN
Restless and fidgeting privileged guests
-Presumptuous and conceited… -Jiaxu, come.
-Come here. -Xiaoduan, sit here.
Why are you so late?
-I went to the restroom. -Sit down.
Xiaoduan.
Let me do the introduction.
She's my best friend, Xiaoxu.
She works in HR at a foreign company.
She was having dinner nearby,
so I asked her to join us.
This is Duan Jiaxu,
our company's chief programmer.
He's young and promising.
Isn't he handsome?
He is indeed handsome.
It's nice to meet you.
Hello.
Stop being awkward. Come.
Let's have a drink and become friends.
I know you don't drink.
We know you don't drink. Here.
Thank you, buddy.
Let's all have a drink together.
-Cheers. -Cheers to Xiaoxu.
-Here. -Cheers.
-Here, cheers. -Cheers.
Dear, what's the title
of the song that we just dueted?
-It's called… -"Like Falling Into a Sea of Love".
-Yes, that's it. -Don't stand around.
-Pick this song. -Skip the rest.
Xiaoduan, our offices are close together.
You two can meet up for coffee sometime.
-Sure. -I haven't heard you sing in a while.
Sing one for me.
The song is playing.
Xiaoxu, join in.
I want to live in your heart
-They are also happy fruit people -They are also happy fruit people
What do you usually like to do?
What do you usually enjoy doing?
Read comics.
Do you have any recommendations?
It depends on your preferences.
Do you like outdoor activities?
For example, hiking.
No.
What about amusement parks?
-Next time, do you want to-- -Hey!
It's my birthday.
Why are the three of you flirting here?
Hurry and sing and dance for me!
Go quickly. Hurry up.
Weiwei, happy birthday!
Happy birthday!
I'm going outside for some air.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
-Treat it as a friend passing by -Treat it as a friend passing by
Sang Zhi?
Did you start smoking?
I don't smoke. That's not mine.
I clearly saw it fall out
from your pocket.
You've picked up bad habits.
I'm confiscating it.
No.
I told you it belongs to my friend.
They may have misplaced it.
-If you don't give it back-- -You've even been drinking.
Just a little.
I'll put the rest aside.
It has been a while. You didn't even greet me.
Jiaxu.
Did you come here to have fun?
It's my roommate's birthday.
When did your military training end?
In the middle of last month.
You didn't visit me during the Golden Week holiday.
I had classes.
Classes during the holiday?
My mistake.
My part-time job.
I see. A part-time job.
Yes.
I used to work part-time too.
Other than working part-time,
I had to meet your teacher,
do your homework, and take you to school.
Ungrateful thing.
This kiddo has no conscience at all.
Well, it's fine.
Jiaxu.
You were already a senior back then.
I'm only a freshman.
I might be a little busier than you were.
Are you calling me old now?
Sang Zhi.
Take a moment and reflect.
What exactly did I do wrong to you?
I never said that.
Also…
I'm a grown-up now.
If you keep calling me a kiddo,
don't you think
it's a little awkward?
How old can you be?
You're still a kid.
Yes.
I'm still a kid.
Two years…
After two years,
you've indeed grown older
and weathered.
Sang Zhi, check your phone and see
how many messages I've sent you.
You didn't reply even once. Why?
It's like I said. I had classes.
Did you need to isolate yourself?
Of course I had to.
If I didn't,
how else could I get into Yihe University?
Fine.
It's past nine and you're still out.
I'm leaving soon.
-Get your things. I'll see you back. -It's okay.
I can go back with my friends.
That works too.
Sang Zhi.
It has been so long.
You've learned how to put on makeup.
You're indeed different from before.
Okay, this looks good.
Don't move.
Okay, change your pose.
I'll take a photo of you and the cake.
Sangsang, where were you?
We're all waiting for you. Come.
-That's right. -We're about to cut the cake.
I'm so sorry.
Come on, everyone. Gather around.
Come here.
Time to cut the cake.
-Light it. -Light the candle.
-Take a picture. -Take a picture.
Wait, hold on.
-Happy birthday to you -Happy birthday to you
Make a wish!
Make a wish.
Okay, here I go.
It's recording.
-Happy birthday! -Happy birthday!
-Cut the cake! -All right.
Let's move it over there.
There's more space there.
Weiwei, what time are we leaving?
I reserved this room until 11 p.m. Why?
Until 11 p.m.?
My mom will call me.
You're right. I've forgotten.
Why don't you go first?
How long will you guys stay?
We won't stay too late.
Anyway, you should go first
in case your mom calls.
Okay, I'll go back first.
Don't stay out here too late.
Okay, don't worry.
I'm going back first.
Remember to text us.
-Stay safe. -Be careful on your way back.
Come back early.
-Okay. -Okay.
-Okay, bye. -Take care.
Bring the leftover cake back for me.
-Just go. -A big slice.
Remember to text us when you get back.
Be careful.
I'm a grown-up now.
I'm no longer a kid.
How old can you be?
You're still a kid.
That old thing.
Do you mean me?
I suppose so.
I'm the only "old thing"
that you've met tonight.
I wasn't talking about you.
Then who were you referring to?
I was just mumbling.
So tell me.
Who crossed you and made you say that?
I would like to know too.
Jiaxu, the thing is…
You don't have to be nosy.
Wait.
Didn't you say
that you're leaving with your friends?
Let's go.
This old thing will see you back to campus.
Are you still cold?
No.
Jiaxu.
Where do you live?
Wenting Garden.
It's near the city library.
That's in the opposite direction
of the campus.
You will have to take a big detour.
Actually,
I could've gone to the metro station.
Then…
Young lady,
I just wanted to settle a score with you
while driving you back.
Actually…
Actually, that term
is considered civilized
in young people's vocabulary.
I think
it's not considered offensive, right?
How much beer did you have tonight?
One bottle.
Be more careful when you go out.
When you're out with strangers,
it's best if you don't drink alcohol.
They're not entirely strangers.
We're all students but in different departments.
Besides, my roommates were there.
I know.
I was just reminding you.
Why don't we
talk for a bit?
Why do I get the feeling
that you have something against me, kiddo?
I don't like it when you call me that.
Kiddo?
I am indeed five years older than you.
And after you're married,
your parents will still see you as a kid.
So do you want to be my dad?
That's not it.
I mean,
I'm already a grown-up, so…
If you keep calling me that,
I'll feel very uncomfortable.
Okay.
I get it.
Jiaxu.
What do you do now?
Sang Yan said you're a programmer.
Yes, I'm a game developer.
A game developer?
One of my roommates is a hardcore gamer.
What is your game called?
I can ask her about it.
A Dream of Jianghu.
By the way,
I just remembered something.
Did you choose Yihe University
because of your old online friend?
Am I right?
No.
No?
It's not because of that.
Yihe University's Digital Media program
is the best in the country.
And my scores were good enough,
so of course I came to Yihe University.
When I called your brother before,
he seemed quite angry about you coming to Yihe University.
I thought it was because of that old online friend.
No, it wasn't.
I…
I haven't contacted him
for a long time.
I'm glad to hear that.
My brother was angry
because I didn't tell him
when I applied.
But I did tell my parents
and they supported me in coming here.
I didn't know what kept him busy.
He didn't ask me anyway.
So I didn't tell him.
I thought he didn't care.
But after I finished applying,
he criticized me
and argued with me.
So of course, I argued back.
Besides…
Besides, I'm an adult now.
I know what I'm doing.
Yes,
Sang Zhi is all grown up now.
But you still see me as a kid.
You came all the way here by yourself
to attend university.
Come to me if you run into any problems.
Got it?
I was just joking with you earlier.
I know it's normal for people your age
to have your own activities.
I truly don't think you have no conscience.
But you did call me an old thing.
How is that not considered offensive?
A young lady should speak more politely.
Sorry, I won't say that again.
It's good that you know you're wrong.
When you have free time,
you can come to have a meal with me.
Is it here?
Make some honey water to drink
to avoid waking up with a headache.
Thank you, Jiaxu.
By the way,
I'm alone over here.
So when I heard your brother say
that you were coming here for university,
I was really happy.
Okay, go inside.
I'll head inside then.
See you, Jiaxu.
Good night.
By the way,
I'm alone over here.
So when I heard your brother say
that you were coming here for university,
I was really happy.
Why would he be alone here?
Isn't his home in Yihe?
Besides,
what about his girlfriend?
JIAXU
If you're ever out so late,
find someone to accompany you back.
SANG ZHI
Okay.
JIAXU
Sang Zhi, check your phone and see
how many messages I've sent you.
You didn't reply even once.
HAPPY NEW YEAR, I SENT YOUR PARENTS GIFTS
YOU GET ONE TOO, BUT DON'T TELL SANG YAN
Don't you find Chen Qiang
from the Sports Department a bit weird?
He giggles when he sees me.
Jiang Ming is in that department too.
He's a cheerful and nice guy.
Do you find him weird?
Well, he's not weird.
But Jiang Ming
already likes someone else.
-Is that so? -Yes.
Really?
I don't know.
I know.
I didn't drink a lot.
Sang Yan, can you stop yelling at me?
What's so funny?
Sangsang, after you left last night,
Jiang Ming kept asking if you would be safe.
He's quite a nice person.
Has he contacted you?
I haven't checked my messages yet.
JIANG MING
If you're ever out so late,
I can accompany you back.
JIAXU
If you're ever out so late,
find someone to accompany you back.
What did he text you?
Show me.
He didn't say anything.
Is there something that you can't share
with the girls of Dorm 202?
Well, there is actually something.
But it's not about me.
It's my friend.
Sure, a friend.
My friend liked her brother's friend
when she was young.
Her brother's friend later started dating.
Then she gave up on him.
But they ran into each other recently.
So she doesn't know what to do.
Her brother's friend?
How old is he?
He graduated from university two years ago.
That would mean
he's about 24 to 25--
He's 24.
What's his job?
My brother said
he's a programmer who develops games.
Game development?
I'm an expert in that.
That's right!
Yu Xin.
Have you heard of a game called A Dream of Jianghu?
A Dream of Jianghu is this year's most popular game!
And I'm playing it now.
-Is it this? -You're not a gamer.
I need to recommend it to you.
This game can be considered
the hottest mobile game of the year.
Whether it's the characters, scenes, or plot design,
you can say they're all top-notch.
Do you see that?
Did he develop it?
That means he is impressive.
Wait a minute. This isn't the point.
The point is,
does he have a girlfriend right now?
That's right.
Does he?
I don't think so.
You don't think so?
So does your friend still like him?
I don't think so.
You don't think so?
Then it's simple.
If yes, go for it.
If not, treat him as an ordinary friend
and chat once in a while.
What's the fuss?
What is your friend worrying about?
She's worried
that this guy
only sees her as a little girl.
So how old
was your friend
when she had a crush on him?
She was in high school.
That's normal.
You were underage at the time.
If he liked you back then,
he's the one with a problem.
Don't interrupt.
Sangsang,
describe this guy to us.
He's handsome.
He had good grades.
He's very interesting to talk to.
He's…
What?
Very charismatic.
He's handsome and charismatic.
Then how did you two meet?
He's my brother's best friend.
He often came over to our house.
Based on your description,
he definitely has a girlfriend.
It has to be so.
Case closed.
You don't even know him.
Don't go yet. Let's talk some more.
Wangwang, come on.
Time to study.
You guys are such mood spoilers.
Forget it.
I'll go and focus on my great endeavors.
Don't come back too late.
Okay.
Be careful.
-Bye. -Stay safe.
Bye.
Welcome.
Excuse me. Where is the honey?
Sir, it's in the last aisle.
Okay, thank you.
HONEY
-Thank you. -Have a good night.