[whimsical theme song playing]
[whimsical theme song continues]
[twinkling chime]
-[air hissing]
-[ball pops]
[whimsical theme song continues]
[song concludes]
[fox squealing]
NO TAIL TO TELL
Maybe it's because I'm human now,
but my heart keeps racing
for no reason whenever I look at you.
I guess this is what
humans call romantic feelings.
What?
[chopsticks clatter]
Si-yeol,
I think
I need to date you.
[gong clashing, echoing]
-Wait, hold on.
-[perky music playing]
Do you even know
what you're saying right now?
Well, you're not bad-looking,
and I'm not embarrassed
to be seen with you.
-By the way, which Kang clan are you from?
-What?
Don't you know your clan branch
and generation?
[wobbly chime]
You are from a noble lineage, right?
Did any of your ancestors
hold an official post?
Seriously, what are you talking about?
[Eun-ho] As I told you before,
I've tried everything
that looked even remotely fun
while living in the human world.
Except for one thing.
-And you're saying that's--
-Yes, dating.
I avoided dating, just in case
it made me want to become human.
So I've gone out of my way
to avoid men all these years.
-[wobbly squeak]
-But I don't need to do that now.
I might as well try dating you
since I'm already human
until I turn back to normal.
So, Si-yeol.
Go out with me.
[music concludes]
Are you making a move on me right now?
No, this is an order.
Cooperate if you want to go back
to your normal life.
[echoing plop]
Do you like me?
-[fox screaming]
-Are you insane?
How dare a mere human
think such a thing? [clicks tongue]
-[quirky music playing]
-It's just that
you're qualified enough
and not embarrassing to be with.
That's about it.
Besides, it's not like
you'd dare reject me,
so there's no problem, right?
Why wouldn't there be a problem?
No one starts a relationship like this,
not when you don't even like me.
[scoffs] What's the big deal?
It's not like all humans date
because they're madly in love.
We'll be back to normal soon anyway,
so it's not like we'll be dating for long.
Jeez, stop arguing with me
and just cooperate.
[music rises]
[sighs contentedly] I'm actually
pretty excited about this new hobby.
Hope we get along, honey.
[echoing chime]
[scoffs]
[giggles]
-[music fades]
-[fox squealing]
EPISODE 8
THE HOBBY CALLED LOVE
-[birds chirping]
-[trees rustling gently]
[grunts softly]
[upbeat quirky music playing]
[chuckles softly]
[echoing birdsong]
[gasps, yelps]
What are you…
-[echoing chimes]
-[Si-yeol] Why are you here?
What's with you?
Did you sleep well, baby?
Seriously, what's wrong with you?
It's way too early for this.
Just act normal.
[echoing piano notes]
[wobbly whoosh]
What do you want now?
Come here. Let me lie on your arm.
Who told you to get up already?
Way to kill the mood.
-[wobbly whoosh]
-[echoing plop]
[groans] My neck hurts.
Muscle cramp.
[music concludes]
[Eun-ho chuckles softly]
[Si-yeol sighs]
-[hisses]
-[wobbly boing]
What are you doing?
-Ah!
-[intriguing music playing]
[sighs] Fine, whatever.
I give up.
[clicks tongue] Here.
[sighs]
-[echoing honk]
-[hisses]
What now?
[chopsticks clattering]
-[wobbly chime]
-[Eun-ho] Read the room.
[clicks tongue]
Open wide.
-Me?
-[fox yipping]
-Open up.
-[sighs]
-[wobbly squeak]
-[echoing plop]
Does it taste different
when I feed it to you?
It's still just a rolled omelet.
Why would it taste different?
Really?
But shouldn't it be different
when you're in a relationship?
Actually, same here.
Whether you feed me or not,
it tastes exactly the same.
[sighs] What am I doing wrong?
That's why I'm telling you
to stop with all this.
Why would I stop? We just started.
Should we try holding hands?
[gags, coughs]
-[echoing ding]
-[Si-yeol coughing]
Hold my hand and I'll give you some water.
[Si-yeol] What? [coughs]
Come on.
[wobbly whoosh]
[breathing heavily]
Jeez.
-[echoing plop]
-[Si-yeol coughs]
Here, drink.
-[coughs, groans]
-[music concludes]
Seriously.
Si-yeol, how about a date today?
What?
Let's go on a date
after we're done for the day.
Isn't that what all couples do?
-[giggles]
-[tender music playing]
-[music fades]
-Give me a break.
Stop obsessing over this "couple" thing.
[Eun-ho] What, is your hand that precious?
[scoffs]
It's not like
it'll wear out if I touch it.
It'll rot away when you're dead anyway.
So… [clears throat]
…what do you mean, "done for the day"?
Are we volunteering
at the nursing home again today?
Yes.
Good deeds don't show results
overnight, you know.
You have to do it for at least a week
to see if it actually works.
[breathes deeply]
Plus, there's something else
I want to look into while I'm there.
Look into what?
What happened yesterday.
I've been trying to remember,
but I have no idea who that old man is.
[mysterious music playing]
Judging by his reaction,
he seems to have been a client of mine.
But I don't get why he'd hold
such a grudge against me…
[sighs] …which just really
rubs me the wrong way.
[Si-yeol] Hm.
But how would you even find that out now?
His memory seemed pretty shot to me.
Well, he clearly remembers something.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have
reacted that way.
If I go ask him,
maybe I'll get something out of him.
[music fades]
[Si-yeol sighs]
My grandmother is unbelievable.
I'm here to visit, and she leaves
to hang out somewhere else?
[clicks tongue]
I'm the only one who always misses her.
Well, of course.
She probably saw you every day.
Stop whining
and pull the sheet tight on your end.
[wearily] Jeez, the work is never-ending.
[groans] Why are there so many beds?
We're almost done.
This is the last room.
What? Already?
What's with that reaction?
I told you I had to ask
that old man something.
But why isn't his room here?
[Si-yeol] Hey.
You're right.
VOLUNTEER CLEANING CHECKLIST
His name isn't even on the list.
You there.
[care worker] Yes?
Do you know where Mr. Hwang Dong-sik is?
Ah…
Mr. Hwang Dong-sik passed away last night.
Pardon?
He passed away.
[ominous music playing]
[ominous music continues]
-[echoing jingle]
-[ominous whooshing]
[faint eerie wailing]
[hawks, spits]
[eerie echoing whoosh]
[ominous music continues]
[coughs]
[coughs harshly, retches]
[tires screeching]
[retches]
[groans]
[panting]
[exhales heavily]
-[rain pattering]
-[thunder rumbling]
[eerie echoing whoosh]
FUNERAL HALL
[music fades]
REST IN PEACE
[quiet chatter]
[Dong-sik's son] Please, have a seat here.
Thank you.
What brings you all the way here?
Well… [inhales deeply]
We went to the nursing home earlier
and heard the news about his passing.
[sighs]
I had something to ask.
-To me?
-That's right.
I was going to ask him directly.
But since that's no longer an option,
I'll just have to ask you instead.
I'm not sure…
[wife] Please, help yourselves.
-Honey, sit here.
-Okay.
So, did you know my father-in-law?
I'm trying to find that out.
[gong clashing]
[echoing chirp]
Oh… [chuckles awkwardly] By the way…
just so you know, she grew up abroad.
So she hasn't learned
how to speak formally yet.
What are you talking about?
[whispering] Look, pick one.
Either speak politely
or just play along with what I'm saying.
Stop making things awkward.
-Play along with what?
-[quirky music playing]
-[echoing plop]
-[echoing squeak]
-[echoing chime]
-Fine. Whatever.
[inhales deeply]
I'm actually
from the City of Angels.
City of Angels?
[Eun-ho] It's a city in America.
I think they call it Los Angeles now.
[echoing rattle]
Gosh, I'm not sure
where she's going with this.
Why is this funeral so shabby?
Didn't your family used to be well-off?
Wait, how would you know that?
-[music concludes]
-Because he was my client.
-Pardon?
-[pensive music playing]
They say wealth lasts
three generations even if you go broke.
Why are you living like this?
It's making me uncomfortable.
[scoffs] Well-off? Yeah, right.
When I married into his family,
they were so poor that they didn't have
a matching set of anything.
I wasn't lying about our wealth.
I'm serious.
When I was a kid,
we had a chauffeur and lived
in a two-story house with a yard.
Sure. Whatever you say.
I wonder what happened to all that wealth.
I'd sure love to see it for myself.
Well, my father…
-Forget it. What's the point anyway?
-[clicks tongue]
[sighs deeply]
Don't just stop all of a sudden.
Go on. I'm curious.
Tell me about your father.
[Dong-sik] You want us
to sell you our new drug?
THIRTY YEARS AGO
WORLD PHARMACEUTICAL
I'm sorry, I can't.
Even if you doubled your previous offer,
I would never--
[inhales deeply] Ten times.
[pensive music continues]
Excuse me?
Not double.
I'm offering ten times more.
Think it over carefully, Mr. Hwang.
When it comes to new drugs,
they're worthless
if they fail the clinical trials.
[straining] Isn't it better…
[heavy thud]
…for you to take this money
and walk away, Mr. Hwang?
Doesn't your company lack the funds
to get through
Phase 3 of US clinical trials?
Sell that drug to me.
[sighs] What a waste!
He should've sold it back then.
[Dong-sik's son] What do you mean?
I mean, he held on to that drug
instead of selling it
and ended up failing, didn't he?
That has to be
why our family ended up like this.
[Dong-sik's son] He sold it
for ten times the price.
How much was it again?
Well, in today's money,
it was enough
to buy a building in Gangnam.
Really?
Then where did all that money go?
He lost it all.
[Si-yeol] All of it?
Was he scammed or something?
Or did he gamble it away?
No, it wasn't anything like that.
Apparently, those clinical trials ended up
being a huge success a few years later.
But that was the problem.
Why was that…
My mother said…
that my father became a bit strange.
Like a man possessed.
He wanted to make a new drug
that was even better than the one he sold.
He poured money into a hopeless project
and got into debt.
He lost both the company and the house.
But his entire life,
he'd never talk about it.
I don't know the full story myself,
but selling that drug like that
must've haunted him for life.
[music fades]
Excuse me, I'm sorry to interrupt.
Sir, as the chief mourner,
you need to select a coffin.
Here are the different types--
We'll take the cheapest one, please.
-Our finances are a bit tight.
-[funeral director] I understand.
[sighs]
So,
did anything come to mind?
[Eun-ho] Yes.
That old man wasn't my client.
[Si-yeol] Really?
Actually, hearing the story,
it didn't sound like his life
went south because of you.
No.
It was because of me.
What?
[somber dramatic music playing]
Si-yeol, go to that ATM
and withdraw some cash.
Let's leave some condolence money.
Sure.
How much?
We don't have much money left.
Would 50,000 won be enough?
Don't be cheap. Take everything out.
You said it's not even that much anyway.
Then what are we going to live on?
It makes no difference. Just give it.
You seem to have no idea
how scary being broke can be.
How can anyone live without a single…
Okay, whatever.
We'll figure it out somehow.
And if possible…
tell them to use that money
to get the best coffin.
[somber dramatic music continues]
[running footsteps]
["Geum-ho"] Sis!
What did you just do?
What do you mean?
I was just standing here.
Why are you making such a fuss?
I just gained spiritual power.
[music rises]
What?
It was a tiny, microscopic,
practically invisible amount,
but I thought I should tell you
since it was still a gain.
You tried doing good deeds for days,
but no power was building up,
so I thought I was being scammed.
You gained spiritual power?
Just now?
[Si-yeol] Hey.
When did you get here?
I just gave them the condolence money.
It took a while
because they were refusing to take it.
Anyway, what's going on?
[Eun-ho] Si-yeol.
I think I finally know
what we have to do.
[music crescendoes]
[music fades]
[chuckles softly]
[traffic rumbling]
[Eun-ho] This place is incredibly fancy.
He must've made a fortune.
Hey, what are you doing?
[intriguing music playing]
Can't you tell?
I'm looking around.
[sighs]
[twinkling chime]
[music rises]
[Eun-ho] You know, back in the day,
this place used to sell things
like ointments and stomach medicine.
It was just a local pharmacy.
Over time,
it became a pharmaceutical company
and made quite a bit of money.
Enough for the owner's son
to become my client.
But that should've been it.
That was the limit of the wealth and fame
this family could ever enjoy.
Do you know how this company
became such a world-renowned corporation?
[Chairman Kim]
Not all new drugs are the same.
Some drugs are
more profitable than others.
Like treatments for obesity or hair loss.
Just imagine if someone developed those.
So, what are you getting at?
Are you asking me to just whip up
a miracle drug for you?
-Do you really think that's possible?
-No, that's not it at all.
[cabinet slides opens]
Please, just take a look at this.
What's this?
NEW DRUGS
[Chairman Kim]
Once this passes clinical trials,
it'll rake in all the money in the world.
It's a paper on a blockbuster new drug.
But the thing is… [clears throat]
…our company wasn't the one
that developed it.
Forget all the complicated details.
Just tell me what your wish is.
I need to know if the clinical trials
for this drug will succeed or fail.
I need to know for sure.
So this chairman already knew
the new drug would be a success,
and Mr. Hwang Dong-sik sold it
without having any idea.
-[guard] Excuse me.
-[music concludes]
How can I help you?
I'm here to see the chairman.
-Pardon?
-What are you doing?
Right.
Now, look me straight in the eye.
-[twinkling chime]
-[echoing whoosh]
Where is the chairman right now?
-[man] Nice shot!
-[woman] Great shot!
[man] That was a powerful swing.
[chuckles]
[sighs contentedly]
[wind whooshing]
[wind howling eerily]
What's with the weather all of a sudden?
Hello, Mr. Chairman.
-Who are you?
-[fox squealing]
-[tires screeching]
-[Chairman Kim] Hey, stop!
[tense music playing]
What do you think you're doing?
Stop this cart right now!
[music intensifies]
[Chairman Kim grunting, groaning]
-[grunts]
-[tires screech]
-[twinkling chime]
-[fox squealing]
[exhales deeply]
[music concludes]
[mysterious music playing]
The nine-tailed fox?
What on earth is going on here?
Welcome, Chairman Kim.
Sit.
I'm here because I have business with you.
[tea pouring]
Hwang Dong-sik is dead.
[Chairman Kim] Hwang Dong-sik?
Don't you remember him?
You made a wish to me 30 years ago.
Oh, him.
You're not complete strangers.
At least go and pay your respects.
You don't have much time left
on this earth either.
Doing a good deed wouldn't hurt.
[chuckles]
Okay, I understand.
How much should I give?
[Eun-ho] Hm…
I think something
other than money would be better.
Something else?
A building.
I saw your company's building earlier.
It's quite fancy and looks pretty nice.
You don't mean
our corporate headquarters, do you?
You want me to give that
instead of condolence money?
[chuckles softly] Why?
Do you have a problem with that?
Technically, your company only grew
big enough to build that building
because of Hwang Dong-sik,
the old man you stole that drug from.
-Stole?
-[unsettling music paying]
I paid
a fair price for that drug, didn't I?
[laughs]
Come on. Let's be honest, Chairman Kim.
He wouldn't sell at any price,
but I made it happen for you,
didn't I?
Hey.
Stop being so stubborn
and just sell the drug or whatever.
-[fingers snap]
-[twinkling chime]
[Eun-ho] If it happens to fail,
it will completely ruin you.
Doesn't it make you anxious?
You're enjoying the success
that old man should've had.
Don't you think it's a fair amount?
[Chairman Kim] Except
I already paid you a high enough price
when I made my wish.
How can you do this to me now?
[chuckles]
Chairman Kim.
Since we've maintained
a good relationship for such a long time,
you must've forgotten
exactly who I am
and how easily I can ruin your life.
[twinkling chime]
[loud bangs]
Does it look like I'm here to negotiate?
-[gulps]
-[music concludes]
[Si-yeol] So, fixing the misdeeds
you committed in the past
is the will of Heaven?
What you just did was also part of that?
That's right.
I saved kids' lives
and did endless community service,
but I didn't gain any spiritual power.
But yesterday, we gave that old man
every penny we had,
and we got an immediate response.
What else could that mean?
-We didn't even give him much, though.
-The amount doesn't matter.
What matters is
that I gave him everything we had.
But do you think that old man
will really hand over a building
just because you said so?
Of course.
As long as he doesn't find out
I've become human,
he can never disobey me.
Hm. I've tamed him well.
I'm sure you have.
Anyway,
let's just wait and see what happens.
In the meantime,
can we go to the buffet again?
[wobbly chime]
[quirky music playing]
[scoffs]
The thing is,
I'm completely broke right now.
Can't we just ask that old man
for some money?
You already took his building,
so that should be nothing, right?
You really think that'd work?
I'm trying to do good deeds
so you can become human,
but you want me to shake down
a human for personal gain?
I guess you're right.
[scoffs]
I'll take you to the buffet
once I make some money.
Okay.
In fact, I was just about to make some.
[echoing chime]
Make money? You?
How?
You said it yourself.
All I know is soccer,
and I don't have any other skills.
So, that's how I'm going to make money.
-[music concludes]
-[players chattering]
Hey, how badly do you think
we'll lose today?
I don't know, maybe 4-0?
If we're lucky, we might lose 3-0.
Man, what's wrong with you guys?
We could tie.
[Gyeong-hun] Stop talking nonsense.
How can we tie
against a second-division team?
-Don't be ridiculous.
-[Beom] Seriously, why did the coach
schedule such a ridiculous practice match?
This isn't even practice
with such a skill gap.
Tell me about it.
Getting crushed by guys like that
won't make us tougher.
It'll just wear us down.
Wait.
Number 7 over there.
Isn't that him?
The former national team forward.
-[Gyeong-hun] Oh!
-[Jeong-bae] It is him.
-It's really him.
-No way!
[Yong-gil] Damn it!
[papers rustling]
Are you guys out of your minds?
You went over to the opposing team
before the game even started,
wagging your tails
like a bunch of neighborhood mutts,
just to get some autographs?
-[quirky music playing]
-Coach, you're crumpling the paper.
[wobbly boing]
[echoing clang]
[Yong-gil] Unbelievable.
Get your heads in the game.
Listen up.
What's our goal for this season?
-[wobbly chime]
-[mouths]
[wobbly boing]
[mouths]
Damn it, it's escaping last place!
Every time I go to a coaches' meeting,
I'm too embarrassed to even show my face!
Even if we can't get to the middle
of the fourth division,
we sure as hell can't finish last!
I know exactly
-what you're all thinking.
-[music concludes]
[Yong-gil] "Gosh, this practice match
is going to be tough."
"Why would he match us up
against a top second-division team?"
That's what you're thinking, right?
-[goofy music playing]
-[Yong-gil] Well, let me tell you.
I had a reason for choosing them.
All right.
Our strategy for this season
is defense.
[wobbly boing]
I'm not asking you guys to win.
Then what?
Just sit back.
Sit and lie down, even.
You don't even have to attack.
If they don't score a single goal,
then there's no way we can lose.
-[Beom] Oh.
-[Gyeong-hun] Ooh.
-[gasps]
-[Chi-su] Mm…
You see?
You get it now, right?
It doesn't matter if they're
top of the second division.
Just block them!
-[players chattering]
-[goofy music continues]
-[player 1] Block him!
-[player 2] Move fast!
[player 3] Hurry up!
[players groan]
[Beom] Hey!
It's okay.
Hyeon-su, get out there!
[Yong-gil groans wearily]
-Damn it, I'm losing my mind.
-[music concludes]
Jeez.
[chuckles]
We've got ten guys defending,
and we're still
giving up goals left and right.
[laughs]
You guys must be feeling generous!
Very generous, damn it.
[chuckles]
Is this funny to you, you punk?
[wobbly chime]
What?
[daring music playing]
[Gyeong-hun] Hey, Si-yeol.
KIM GYEONG-HUN
What are you doing here?
And what's with the getup?
Coach, you said I'm still
on the team roster, right?
Well, yeah.
Do you want to win?
What?
I mean,
at this rate,
I don't know when I'll be able to return.
But I need to stay in shape,
so I might as well play anywhere.
So, I'll play for you.
What are you even saying, you punk?
You're out of your mind.
You said your wish was promotion.
I'll make sure you move up…
[echoing squeak]
…to the third division.
-[music concludes]
-[echoing chime]
WISHING FOR DAEHEUNG CITIZENS FC'S VICTORY
There's nobody here.
I know, right?
Why are they even playing
when no one is watching?
-Such a waste of energy.
-[whistle blows]
[sighs]
Anyway, where is Si-yeol?
[whistle blows]
-[Gyeong-hun] Kang Si-yeol, let's go!
-[player 1] Si-yeol, you can do it!
[player 2] Let's go, Si-yeol!
Stay focused!
[gasps] Si-yeol's here.
[uplifting pop song playing]
[whistle blows]
[uplifting pop song continues]
-Over here.
-Why pass it now?
[uplifting pop song continues]
-[whistle blows]
-[players cheering]
[scoffs]
[players cheering]
[cheers]
Hey, look at the score! We're losing!
Come here, let me give you a kiss!
Hurry and get back in position!
["Geum-ho"] But didn't you say
they're doing well
if they put the ball in there?
Why is Si-yeol so angry?
Because he has a bad temper.
-[chuckles]
-[song concludes]
[tense music playing]
INTENSIVE CARE UNIT
[eerie echoing whoosh]
[groans]
[eerie musical sting plays]
[shaman] I'm sure you know
that your body is falling apart.
When that day comes,
all the spirits you've devoured
will tear your soul to pieces.
They'll slash, tear, and crush you.
They'll chew you up and spit you out.
Unable to die, yet unable to live.
That's the fate that awaits you.
[chuckles softly]
[retches]
-[Do-cheol panting]
-[eerie echoing whoosh]
[grunts]
[music fades]
[Yoon] Hey!
Man, you've become
quite pathetic yourself.
I'd heard you were close to death,
but look at you,
coughing up blood and collapsing.
[sirens wailing in distance]
This hospital belongs to our foundation.
I told them to look out for you
just in case,
and they notified me right away.
I've been looking for you,
but I had no way of contacting you.
Why were you looking for me?
There's someone I'd like you to meet.
[siren wails]
-That's it.
-[upbeat pop song playing]
What on earth is happening right now?
I don't know.
[Yong-gil] Is this score for real?
How many minutes has it been
since Si-yeol went in?
It's been about 13 minutes.
Gosh, that hat trick.
He's totally insane!
[both chuckle]
[upbeat pop song continues]
-Nice.
-Yes!
Hey! What are you guys doing?
-Aren't you going to block Number 10?
-[laughs]
That guy's going to lose
his voice soon. [chuckles]
-[whistle blows]
-[Gyeong-hun] Hey, Ref!
-That's a foul.
-[groans]
[Yong-gil] Are you blind?
Watch the damn game!
[upbeat pop song continues]
[whistle blows]
[Yong-gil] Ref!
You, Ref! Do your job!
[upbeat pop song continues]
I've got the whole defense on me.
How are those idiots not scoring?
Unbelievable.
I haven't even run that much.
How out of shape am I?
I'm already worn out.
Si-yeol!
[upbeat pop song continues]
-[groans]
-[gasps]
Damn it!
[pants]
[sighs wearily]
I can't keep going like this.
[upbeat pop song continues]
[Eun-ho] Hey, Si-yeol!
Get a grip. You're losing!
[scoffs] Man, that temper of hers.
I'll never hear the end of it if we lose.
[sighs, sniffs]
[breathes heavily]
-How much time do we have left?
-They gave three minutes of added time.
I think this is the last chance to score.
Really?
Damn it.
All I'm asking for is just one more goal.
[upbeat pop song continues]
-[echoing thud]
-[players yelling]
-[song fades]
-[groans]
That was a total foul!
-Penalty kick!
-[players] Penalty kick!
[player] That's a penalty.
You have to call it.
-Ref!
-[whistle blows]
-Yes!
-[players] We got a penalty kick!
Penalty kick!
[players clamoring]
[whistle blows]
KANG SI-YEOL
[soft daring music playing]
Stay calm. Don't cheer. Don't get nervous.
-[mutters]
-Here he goes. Please…
[players cheering]
[triumphant music playing]
Kang Si-yeol!
[whistle blows]
[both cheer]
[players cheering]
[music concludes]
That's our Kang Si-yeol!
I knew you could do it!
Why didn't you play like this before?
[exhales deeply]
[whispers] Don't.
What's with the mood in here?
Coach, hold on a second.
-[goofy music playing]
-Seo Beom, what the hell was that earlier?
[hesitates] Me?
Who makes that pass at that moment?
You should've waited.
Draw the defense in first,
then make the pass!
And you!
Bae Jeong-bae, right?
Why didn't you take the chance
to cut inside when you had it?
[shouting] When I drew the defense
out to the side,
you should've exploited the space!
Unbelievable!
[Si-yeol sighs]
Did I misread the score?
Did we lose?
No, we tied.
We did, right?
Then why does it feel like we lost?
Tell me about it. You'd think we lost.
-We didn't win!
-[echoing yelp]
Where's the fight? Where's the hunger?
You're all just slacking off.
Don't you guys want to win?
Are you okay with losing?
Gosh.
[whispering] I'm going
to step out for a second.
Coach! Where are you going?
-Well--
-[Gyeong-hun] You can't leave.
Explain this to me, Coach.
[shouting] With 13 minutes left, 4-0?
And how are you guys excited about this?
You!
Look at the size of you.
How are you so bad at defending?
[music concludes]
Si-yeol was absolutely incredible today.
Don't you think so?
[tender music playing]
Well, that's the bare minimum.
He is a pro soccer player, after all.
I don't know why everyone's making
such a big deal over a few goals.
[chuckles]
Bang!
Oh!
-[chuckles]
-[music fades]
-[echoing twang]
-[echoing boing]
Anyway, aren't you leaving?
How long are you staying?
Beat it!
[Gyeong-hun] Man, I'm really late.
I'm heading out first, guys.
-Good game!
-[group] Catch you later!
[door opens, closes]
Hey.
Did you pay Gyeong-hun back?
Money? What for?
You abandoned his car
on some back road in Gyeonggi Province.
He said the towing fees were huge.
Didn't he mention it?
Oh, I didn't even think of that.
I'll pay him back.
Tell him to sit tight
now that I'm back on the field.
I'll have the cash in no time.
While we're on the subject,
how much am I worth again?
-[wobbly boing]
-Why am I so broke right now?
Did you just ask
what the payout is if you die?
Did you take out a life insurance policy?
-[quirky music playing]
-No, my paycheck.
How much do I make a week?
-What?
-Weekly pay?
It's the fourth division,
so it won't be much.
Do I make about two or three million won?
-[echoing chirp]
-Are you crazy?
Even less? One million, then?
A million won a week?
Who do you think you are, a pro?
You've never earned a weekly wage.
It's not a weekly wage?
I guess they pay
an annual salary in Korea.
I mean, it's not like
I've ever played in the K League.
You're not on an annual salary.
You get paid per game.
-Per game?
-Yes.
It's 50,000 won per game,
and 300,000 for a win.
What are you talking about?
That's it?
What about a base salary?
[Chi-su] There isn't any.
Our team doesn't even pay for training.
Actually, compared
to other fourth-division teams,
we're in pretty bad shape
since we're always in last place.
So you're saying
if there are four games a month,
that's 350,000 won times four.
[wobbly whoosh]
Only 1.4 million won?
Your math is way off.
We can't win every game.
We lose almost all of them.
It's 50,000 won times four,
so it's 200,000 won.
-[music fades]
-Hey.
You at least get that 200,000 won
because you're a starter.
Look at Gyeong-hun.
He's just a backup goalie.
When was the last time he played?
Was it last year?
Yeah.
Then how much does he get paid?
Nothing.
He trains like crazy,
but he doesn't get paid at all.
That's why he's out
doing delivery gigs day and night.
Do you get it now?
You ripped off a poor kid like that.
[Si-yeol] Then how do you guys survive?
You can't live on 200,000 won a month.
We all have part-time jobs.
Except for Jeong-bae.
-[car engine revving]
-[cash register ringing]
Forget about the sports car guy.
So you guys have jobs
other than playing soccer?
Then how can you focus on training?
So stop giving them such a hard time.
They're all just
trying their best to get by.
I'm heading out.
-See you tomorrow.
-Take care.
-[door opens, closes]
-[soft pensive music playing]
[sighs]
Hey!
What took you so long?
I've been waiting forever.
[Si-yeol] Oh, sorry.
But why are you alone?
She left.
I see.
[soft pensive music continues]
What's going on with you?
[Si-yeol] What?
I mean, you played pretty well today,
but you look so dejected.
Did that Coach Park give you a hard time?
[sighs, clicks tongue]
It's not that.
[inhales deeply]
I've just got some stuff on my mind.
And most of all,
I didn't make any money.
Even if it was a practice game,
I thought I'd at least get paid.
[Eun-ho] So it was about money?
Don't worry about it.
I can just make that money myself.
Besides,
you looked pretty cool out there today.
[scoffs]
Right, like you're going to make money.
Wait, then what do we do
about our date tonight?
-What?
-[Eun-ho] Don't you remember?
We couldn't have one last night
because it was too hectic,
so we agreed to go on our date tonight.
Are we postponing it again?
Well, we can just go some other time.
What's the rush?
You said it was just
a hobby for you anyway.
Damn, we should've kept some cash
instead of giving it all away.
Man, where can I get some money?
[Jeong-bae] Hey, Si-yeol!
-[music fades]
-And your girlfriend!
-Why are you guys still here?
-[twinkling chime]
[Eun-ho] Si-yeol.
Isn't that the guy who was
driving that fancy sports car?
[Si-yeol] Yeah.
I heard his family owns
a famous galbi restaurant in Seoul.
[menacing music playing]
[echoing chime]
-[knuckles crack]
-[music fades]
[Si-yeol sighs]
[door opens]
[sighs]
[door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
-[chuckles softly]
-[tender music playing]
What are you staring at?
-Do I look weird?
-What?
No, of course not.
It's just that… [clears throat]
…I guess expensive clothes
really do make you look good.
[giggles]
Right?
I need to get back to my old self
and buy this in every color.
[chuckles softly]
[inhales deeply]
Anyway, where are we going?
Do you have a plan?
[inhales deeply] A plan?
Hm…
Oh! I just thought of something.
-What is it?
-Namsan.
Namsan is the ultimate
date spot, after all.
[soft upbeat pop song playing]
Jeez, you've been going on about a date
since yesterday morning,
so I was wondering
what kind of grand plans you had in mind.
Was Namsan all you could come up with?
How cliché.
I'm not looking for anything
out of the ordinary.
I want a totally cliché, classic romance.
And where else would we go but here?
Well, when you put it that way,
I guess you have a point.
Since you're human now,
it's time to do everything you wanted.
[chuckles]
Hm…
Oh! That! I've always wanted to try that.
It's a classic, right? Let's go.
[soft upbeat pop song continues]
So we just write our wish on this, right?
That's about it.
[Eun-ho] Hm…
[soft upbeat pop song continues]
MAY OUR LOVE LAST FOREVER
LET'S COME BACK IN TEN YEARS!
[scoffs]
Wait, what's this?
I thought you wanted something classic.
EUN-HO, KANG SI-YEOL
BACK TO HOW WE WERE
This is a wish. I have to be realistic.
What other wish
could possibly be more important?
I'm just saying.
Did you have to bring us
back to reality on this?
Are you pouting
because my wish wasn't romantic enough?
[scoffs] Who's pouting?
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm just playing along for your sake.
Why would I be pouting?
Fine, I'll just do something
more classic, then.
[soft upbeat pop song continues]
-[Eun-ho] Is this better?
-[twinkling chime]
What are you doing?
A heart between us?
You said a wish has to be realistic.
What if this jinxes it?
[scoffs] You worry too much.
Once things are back to normal,
we'll go our separate ways.
This heart doesn't mean anything.
This heart won't matter at all by then.
Hey, you didn't have to go that far.
[Eun-ho] Whatever.
Let's just hang this here.
Goodness.
Hang it or don't. I don't care.
[Eun-ho] There.
[soft upbeat pop song continues]
[chuckles]
[both chuckle softly]
-[song concludes]
-[door keypad beeps]
Dad, I'm home.
[door lock beeps]
Do we have a guest?
[ominous music playing]
Oh, you're home?
[breathes shakily]
What are you doing here?
How did you get in here?
Where's my dad?
He's just over there.
Dad!
Dad.
Wake up!
What did you do to my father?
[clicks tongue]
[Do-cheol] He's just unconscious,
that's all.
Man, I feel refreshed.
Even the shower's amazing
in a fancy house.
[Woo-seok] Answer me!
What did you do to him?
[Do-cheol] There's no need to worry.
He'll be fine
once he wakes up from his little nap.
By the way, I heard you lost your memory.
[Yoon] I told you
I knew someone
who can help with this kind of thing.
Meet Jang Do-cheol.
He's a shaman. [clicks tongue]
A male shaman.
A shaman?
[Yoon] What,
did you expect me to bring a priest?
All you want is
to get your memory back, right?
[music fades]
I said we should eat something nice
since we're out anyway.
What's wrong with pork cutlet?
Isn't it totally a classic?
Besides, how much were you planning
to spend on borrowed money?
[cutlery clatters]
[gentle music playing]
[Si-yeol] Here.
Look at you being so cooperative.
It's just manners.
It's second nature to me. [clears throat]
Still, I like it. It's also classic.
Mm.
Si-yeol,
isn't there anything
you've wanted to do on a date?
I don't know.
I just wanted something normal too.
Not having to date inside a car
or hide my face.
Something like holding hands
and walking down a crowded street.
I've never done that before.
Really?
I was hoping for some fun ideas,
but that's it?
-[music concludes]
-Living as a celebrity must be exhausting.
I can just do whatever I want
and erase people's memories.
[echoing jingle]
[tense music playing]
[groans]
[groaning]
[discordant buzz]
[Eun-ho] Erase that human's memory.
Erase it.
[echoing jingle]
["Geum-ho"] Sis, I found a way!
I found a way for you to turn back
into a nine-tailed fox.
-[breathes rapidly]
-[echoing jingle]
How about it? Do you remember now?
[Yoon] Mm.
Tell us.
What do you know?
[Woo-seok] Well…
[breathes shakily]
She said she became human.
What?
That nine-tailed fox.
She's just an ordinary human now.
[music fades]
Si-yeol, hold my hand.
What?
This was the date you wanted to go on.
We're on a date,
so let's hold hands as we walk.
[scoffs] Oh, come on.
Seriously, how long
are you going to keep this up?
[clears throat]
[chuckles softly]
You know, it's strange.
What is?
[Eun-ho] I mean, until recently,
my heart would race,
and I'd get nervous around you.
But now
that we're actually dating like this,
my heart doesn't race anymore,
even when we're holding hands
or I'm lying on your arm.
Is something wrong with our relationship?
Are you saying this doesn't
make your heart race at all?
[Eun-ho] Not at all.
Are you toying with me?
But I actually had fun on our date today.
I think I'll remember it for a long time
because it was so ordinary and classic.
Speaking of memories,
when things go back to normal,
are you going to erase my memory too?
[Eun-ho] What?
You just said earlier
that you'd do what you want
and then erase the memory.
[tender music playing]
I mean, I ended up
learning too much about you.
So, like you did to Woo-seok
and that old man,
I wondered if you'd just erase mine too.
Why would you suddenly ask that?
Because of what you said
about going our separate ways
once everything is back to normal.
[Eun-ho] I'm going to erase it.
To me, human friends
have always been disposable.
I have my fun,
and then I wipe the slate clean.
That way,
things don't get emotionally messy.
It's cleaner that way.
Hearing that makes me feel a bit sad.
It doesn't make you sad?
It does.
It's obvious that I'm special to you,
but to me, you're also…
a pretty special human.
You're the first human friend I've had
who didn't feel disposable.
Of course it'll be sad
after I erase your memory.
Then don't erase it.
I can't.
Why not?
Because then your life won't be normal.
For a human to live a normal life,
memories of switched fates
and a nine-tailed fox becoming human
are better forgotten.
So, erasing your memory
is my final gift to you.
[sighs]
What if…
I don't want to be normal?
What?
If you're just going to erase my memory
and be the only one
who remembers this moment…
then I should be allowed to do
at least this much, right?
What do you mean…
[tender pop song playing]
[tender pop song continues]
SPECIAL APPEARANCES
BY KIM HONG-PA AND OH MIN-SEOK
[tender pop song continues]
EUN-HO, KANG SI-YEOL
BACK TO HOW WE WERE
-[fox squealing]
-[twinkling chime]
NO TAIL TO TELL
-[Si-yeol] Let's date. For real.
-[exhales]
[Si-yeol] Don't think about running.
Let's do this right.
Eun-ho, should we go on a trip?
[Do-cheol] Then who erased your memory?
[Woo-seok] There was someone else there.
He told me to wait and do nothing,
but what the hell is he doing?
Here. I made some money.
[Si-yeol] Wait, what did you do to get…
[Eun-ho] I'm on a mission
to do good deeds right now.
Hey, Si-yeol!
Hyeon Woo-seok collapsed!
-[player 1] Woo-seok!
-[player 2] Hey, Woo-seok!
[Beom] They say he might die.
[tender pop song continues]
Subtitle translation by Susanna Kim