(Siren Wailing)
"I'm such a fool."
"Such a fool for you."
"And you had me down and blue all for you."
(Music)
"Oh, one day."
"I hope you'll be running back to me."
(Faint Music Playing In Background)
DO-KYUNG
(Paper Rustle)
(Footsteps)
Here you go.
(Paper Rustle)
It’s so pretty!
This is why I only order
when you’re working!
(Chuckles)
Your arrangements are
way better than the boss’s,
you’ve got that touch.
You can come anytime from now on.
I’m taking over the shop.
(Gasps)
So you’ll be the boss?
Yes.
(Claps)
Congratulations!
(Bell Ringing)
Are you ignoring my calls?
We’re late.
(Chair Screeching)
(Sighs)
Why do you bother buying flowers?
They’ll wither anyway.
It’s fine.
That’s just how my friend talks.
Hello.
Going on a trip?
Yes.
Where?
Backpacking through Europe,
here and there.
Are you taking flowers to the airport?
It’s my mom’s birthday,
but I can’t be there, so...
I see.
Thank you.
Come back soon.
(Chimes)
Jealous much?
As if.
Come on, you’re late.
(Up Beat Music)
(Tyres Screeching)
(Thud)
The rental shop was cleaned out,
that’s all they had left.
It’s not about what I wear,
it’s about how much I make today.
(Snickers)
Oh please.
Moron.
(Tyres Screeching)
Look how busy Hwajoong Market is.
Thank God it’s my last day. I’m so done.
(Click)
I told you not to smoke in the car!
I opened the window!
Put it out!
Just one drag.
Put it out.
Come on, just one drag!
The car’s gonna reek!
It already reeks of cigarettes.
Stop being a bitch, just put it out!
Let me get a drag.
Unbelievable.
(Crackles)
Give it back.
You bitch, I’ll kill you.
Come on!
Your precious car is so damn clean.
(Tyres Screeching)
Someone’s gonna get hurt.
Is she insane?
You always amaze me.
Dobby!
I lost 7kg thanks to this.
You’re so much faster than overseas orders.
If you like it so much, spread the word.
30% off per referral!
30%? Okay, I’ll spread the word!
Later.
Bye.
You’re a natural,
you were made for this job.
It’s just business.
Hurry up and drive.
(Engine Roaring)
(Tyres Screeching)
(Footsteps)
(Thud)
Ye-seul’s clocking in.
(Footsteps)
(Car Door Closes)
(Car Door Opens)
Dobby!
(Sighs)
Shit...
Got a lot of gigs?
Get out.
Don’t be like that.
I got you a sweet gig
in the capital markets.
I’m busy, get out.
No, it’s cold out.
Are you insane?
All you ever have are sketchy gigs.
This one’s clean.
Get one of your goons to do it,
don’t come at me.
Cops are sniffing around like crazy lately.
I got no one.
But you’re squeaky clean.
And despite that temper,
you got no priors too.
Shut your face.
I’ll pay double!
Should I call the cops?
(Gasps)
Okay, okay.
Be a chauffeur all your life.
(Car Door Closes)
Millionaire in a million years!
(Fabric Rustle)
(Car Door Closes)
Fucking moron.
(Indistinct Chatter)
(Indistinct Chuckles)
(Footsteps)
(Locker Door Opens)
Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors! Okay!
(Paper Rustle)
(Thud)
(Indistinct Chatter)
Rock, paper, scissors! You suck at this.
The self-made goddess returns.
She lives off beans and
rice working as a florist.
Her skills are next-level.
Ye-seul!
You should get dolled up at the salon,
it doesn’t cost much.
Like hell she will.
She saved up like crazy,
so she’s retiring end of this week.
She took over the flower shop,
and deposited $700,000 for a house.
Hwa-jin, aren’t you jealous?
It’s pathetic to be jealous.
Stop!
I’m not jealous.
Once she’s gone, I’ll be the ace.
Bullshit.
You’ll make chump change
running a flower shop.
Can you live on that?
I want to sleep at night
and work during the day now.
Like normal people.
Anyway, give me a smoke!
Dammit.
Take it easy.
Thank you.
That blue “No Escort”
bracelet is annoying as hell.
- Ye-seul.
- Yeah?
Your face isn’t giving today.
- You’re giving less.
- Shut up.
PHOTOS: ON THIS DAY
7 YEARS AGO TODAY
What is it?
(Clatter)
Isn’t that Ga-young?
How is she doing?
Remember when she first brought you here ―
I’m sure she’s fine.
Right, probably.
Who is she?
She was a legend around here.
I heard she blackmailed
some Japanese ambassador.
Why don’t ambassadors
ever come to our shop?
I don’t care for government
officials or foreigners.
You know jack shit.
Ambassadors don’t even
get checked at customs.
Perfect for luxury shopping trips.
Boss arriving in 7 minutes.
Standby, Sang-ok.
Alright, let’s get ready!
The boss is coming!
You know we got a new boss, right?
A new boss?
“Blackjack” made bank in the
Philippines off sports betting,
he just came back and bought
up Gangnam joints, including ours.
So, who’s gonna work the boss’s room?
It’s an important meeting
with a basketball coach.
Let’s stay sharp.
(Door Opens )
The plant at the entrance.
Sorry?
It’s wilting.
All green except the
second one from the front.
If you can’t manage it, just get rid of it.
And space the pots evenly.
Yes, sir.
Now.
Right now? Of course!
(Footsteps)
(Door Opens)
(Door Closes)
(Footsteps)
Sit.
(Untesil Clinking)
(Gasps)
(Groans)
Sir, basketball’s tough.
It’s really tough.
It looks like a team sport.
But depending on which
players you use and when,
the whole flow of the game can shift.
(Scarpes)
Hey.
Don’t drag the glass.
(Chuckles)
Boss, you’re so sensitive.
Move.
(Faint Music In The Background)
(Chuckles)
You, switch seats with her.
You two switch.
Yes, sir.
(Footsteps)
(Sips)
That’s why you need a
seasoned coach like me.
And with my team’s ace,
Han-wook, on our side,
we can control the game however you want.
He’ll follow my orders to a T.
Sir, trust me and invest in us.
(Untensil Clinking)
(Scoffs)
Looking down on me like that,
what a rude little shit.
65 to 59, loss...
I got it all, asshole!
Once the big money hits, you’ll be mine!
I’ll make you rich!
I’ll save you.
- I’m on your side, okay?
- This way, sir.
Have a good night!
(Thud)
(Sighs)
Isn’t it funny?
Who’s saving who when we’re all the same?
(Faint Music)
Your life is yours to save.
(Footsteps)
(Road Noise)
Thanks, hon!
(Car Door Closes)
HUNDRED PERCENTER Congrats
/ Payout Rate: 2.60 / Winnings: $910
- Who the fuck cares if he’s the boss?
- Yes!
(Car Door Opens)
(Screams)
(Gasps)
Nice! It’s my lucky day,
(Car Door Closes)
I got you as my driver.
Get out, I’m booked up.
You pick and choose your clients now?
I’m seriously hurt.
What is the matter with you?
Wipe it.
(Rustle)
Wipe the floor!
Dammit!
(Sniffs)
Wipe it clean.
Dammit, treating me like
shit because you’re retiring?
Do you even know who I just drank with?
Basketball coach Choi Chul! And Blackjack!
65 to 59, his team loses.
Bet against his team.
(Gasps)
You’ll win the bet 100%.
Ye-seul was there too, ask her yourself...
Hey!
(Taps)
(Sighs)
Let’s just go, drive...
(Notification Beeps)
CHOI OFFED HIMSELF!
(Suspense Music)
HE TURNED OUT TO BE A HOUSING SCAMMER!
(Door Opens)
(Weeping)
(Thud)
That fucker took off.
(Indistinct Screams)
Ye-seul!
(Pants)
You signed a lease for Mr. Choi’s condo,
right?
Weren’t you moving in this week?
Look at this, is this true?
(Pants)
All girls in Hwajoong Market got scammed!
Does anyone know
where this motherfucker is?
- MEMORIAL ROOM: CHOI SEUNG-BEOM (MALE, 31)
- It was all a setup!
He baited girls like us with cheap leases.
(Footsteps)
He gambled away your money!
This fucker’s really dead?
(Paper Rustle)
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
(Thud)
(Paper Rustle)
What are you doing? Get up!
Dammit!
Out! Get out!
Please leave!
(Footsteps)
Get the hell out!
What the hell do you think
you’re doing at a funeral?
(Slaps)
Goddammit!
No!
Is she insane? Please stop!
(Screams)
Fuck off!
(Paper Rustle)
Let that go! Let’s just talk!
I said stop it!
(Glass Clink)
(Glass Shatters)
(Click)
We have to survive somehow.
Let’s hang on with the flower shop deposit.
(Rustle)
Hey.
Did you drink with Blackjack today?
What about it?
Nothing.
(Phone Vibrating)
(Footsteps)
YD GANGNAM BANK: $100,000 WITHDRAWN
Dammit!
(Door Opens)
They don’t have much time left.
Hurry and take a seat.
Goddammit...
(Thud)
(Television Noise In the Background)
What was that for?
Do-kyung, why is our bank account empty?
(Television Noise In the Background)
(Clatter)
(Sighs)
You didn’t bet it all on this, did you?
(Television Noise In the Background)
Come sit down.
You’re full of shit.
Sit down for a sec!
What the hell for?
Look at this!
Look at what?
I bet against them, and if they lose
by six points, we win it all.
That’s total bullshit...
It’s a sure thing.
How much deeper are you gonna bury us?
I’m trying to keep us from getting buried.
(Television Noise In the Background)
Have you ever seen me bet this much before?
This is insane...
You know this tip is legit.
You heard that coach yammer to Blackjack,
didn’t you?
I’m so done with you!
Look at it!
We’ve got this in the bag!
(Television Noise In the Background)
Almost there.
65 to 59,
just gotta keep the six-point gap.
65 to 59.
He’s bringing in Lee Han-wook for a win.
Kinda late to sub in your best player.
Lee is replacing Hong Dong-myung.
Lee takes his shot!
Lee Han-wook’s 3-pointer! It’s short.
He misses his first shot.
Coach Choi brought him in late,
so he must be feeling the pressure.
No, don’t score!
Lee is on the move, he’s got the ball.
He aims for the rim!
Lee Han-wook again!
- Don’t you dare.
- Lee Han-wook shoots!
(Thud)
Lee shoots and misses.
Yes!
Fuck yes!
(Fabric Rustle)
Holy shit!
Hey, hey!
Did we win?
Yes!
So? Did it work?
(Screams)
(Sighs)
We did it! We fucking did it!
I told you it’d work.
One shot and we’re back on top!
(Gasps)
Thank you, thank you...
Thank you...
Thank you God, thank you...
- CASH OUT REQUEST
- I just need to cash out.
Cash out, cash out.
(Gasps)
What’s this?
What is it?
This isn’t funny, cut it out!
NOTICE: We took all the money. Thanks
for the love. Report us if you want LOL
(Crackles)
(Caller Ring)
Yo, Dobby. What’s up?
Can I still do that gig you mentioned?
Gig? What gig?
(Smirks)
The gig you mentioned! Can I still take it?
(Laughs)
Word is you and Mi-sun got wiped out.
You talked big about retiring,
now look at you.
Total crash and burn.
(Laughs)
Give me three times the pay.
(Sighs)
Then I’ll do it.
The gigolo bar at 9 tonight.
(Dialer Tone)
(Footsteps)
You’re late!
Piss off!
Don’t be like that, these people are busy.
(Footsteps)
Bottoms up!
(Gasps)
Having fun?
- What’s up?
- Hey, Seok-gu!
Ye-seul, these gents are my business bros.
Over there is my big boss,
CEO Ahn Joon-min.
He’s never been to these high-end bars.
Boss! How do you like her?
She’s the hottest chick here.
But a total train wreck.
(Click)
She’s hot but dumb as fuck.
(Chuckles)
Fine, fine, fine!
I’m kidding, come in.
(Crackles)
Move.
Go away.
(Glass Clinking)
- Scoot over.
- Excuse me, watch your feet.
Ow! You stepped on me!
Move over!
- Alright, alright!
- Seriously?
I set this up to intro a great
biz opportunity to Ye-seul.
Boss, cheers!
Mr. Ahn.
How is it? Killer, right?
(Laughs)
Ye-seul.
Me and my bros will help you
launch your Only fans career.
We’ll take care of it!
Forget about the scam, just be prepared.
(Laughs)
Ye-seul.
Wear the red! Escort a little!
Accept reality and know your place in it.
(Crackles)
(Thud)
I’m outta here, guys!
Enjoy yourself, boss!
You ladies take care of my bros.
Cash pops here!
(Chuckles)
(Indistinct Chatter)
(Vehicle Passing By)
(Rap song playing in the background)
Christ...
(Thud)
I might not be able to
come here for a while.
All of a sudden?
My husband’s getting audited.
He secretly moved his cash
to Gyeonggi somewhere.
I’m broke, I can’t come here now.
(Scoffs)
(Tap)
This is way too random.
Are you breaking up with me?
(Click)
(Thud)
Baby, let’s meet up somewhere else,
privately.
(Chuckles)
(Gasps)
Guys like us get flagged
if we meet clients outside.
You’re broke. You sure you can handle me?
(Dips)
(Water Splashes)
(Glass Clinks)
You little hustler!
How much have I spent on our time and bond?
Put out that cigarette, you fucker.
(Thud)
(Gasps)
Okay.
(Glass Clinks)
Okay, baby.
Let’s meet up outside.
How bad did your husband fuck up
for you to not be able to come here?
Seung-won.
Snap out of it.
Just do as I tell you.
Fuck, I got her wasted
like there’s no tomorrow...
The fuck.
So, gentlemen, make any money lately?
It’s been fucking forever since I got laid,
man.
(Chuckles)
No trust fund bimbos in a bit?
Hurry up before you’re dried up, moron.
Go get’em bimbos!
You came here yourself?
I got some business too.
Appointments with
clients are all about safety.
You should take Blackjack’s $700,000.
Pay off the loan sharks and your debt.
(Spits)
Rob him and get killed?
Idiot, you’ll die one way or another.
If it’s the last train,
might as well ride first class.
Fuck off.
Give me a smoke and lay out the details.
(Gasps)
Dude.
My client is Blackjack’s wife,
and she said he stashed $700,000 in
slush funds in Gyeonggi somewhere.
You should wipe him out.
You’re actually serious?
I’ll handle the digging.
You seal the deal and take 60%.
(Scoffs)
Deal.
Okay.
(Footsteps)
I’ll be in touch.
(Door Opens)
Use the goods, she'll spill everything!
(Whistles)
(Door Closes)
(Faint Music)
(Door Opens)
(Groans)
Hey, Dobby.
Sit beside me.
(Laughs)
Just look at you.
Do this gig right,
and you’ll be rolling in cash.
(Plastic Rustle)
Here.
(Thud)
(Laughs)
(Gasps)
Drive safe!
(Whistle Blowing)
$2,000 a shot?
(Boiling)
That’s capitalist
romance in the best sense.
(Glass Clinking)
Shall I throw in another
$2,000 for another round?
(Boiling)
(Scoffs)
(Chair Creaks)
(Footsteps)
(Rustle)
(Glass Clinks)
(Boiling)
(Groans)
(Tyres Screeching)
Baby, let’s go.
Babe!
Babe, babe!
Give me a hand?
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Baby!
Get up, come on.
Get the fuck up!
Let’s go, alright.
(Engine Roaring)
What’ll I do without
seeing this pretty face?
I can quit drugs, but I can’t quit you.
So, baby...
That thing you mentioned,
can’t we just take it?
That thing? What’s that?
Your husband’s slush fund.
If we get that,
we can meet freely outside too.
You know where it’s hidden, right?
I dunno!
Don’t be like that.
You must have a clue.
Nope!
Okay, okay. I really love you.
I love you, baby!
So much!
(Chuckles)
I love you, love you!
(Gasps)
My hubby bought some land in Gyeonggi.
So, the place where he
buried the $700,000 is...
(Pucking)
Stop! Pull over for a bit!
(Tyres Screeching)
Fuck. You okay?
You okay, baby?
(Footsteps)
Babe?
(Pucking)
(Tap)
(Clatter)
(Phone Notification Beeping)
Call me when you get the location.
I’ll have everything ready to go.
Ye-seul’s video debut is coming tonight,
get hyped.
(Chuckles)
Is it?
(Rustle)
(Tyres Screeching)
Hey, where the fuck are you going?
Easy there, hold on. We’re almost there.
So close, almost there.
Keep it together! Hold on!
(Footsteps)
Got a headache, eh?
(Chuckles)
Let’s take a break and make some art.
Let go!
It’s fine, good girl.
- Let go of me!
- It’s alright.
Let go!
(Screams)
(Thud)
(Groans)
(Sighs)
I let go, bitch!
(Glass Clinks)
Get off your high horse and
work it while you’re still in demand!
(Glass Shatters)
(Gasps)
(Pants)
Give me a cigarette.
(Clicks)
(Crackles)
Seok-gu’s gonna steal Blackjack’s money.
$700,000 in cash.
Same as what we lost.
I’ll steal it and pay you back,
so don’t worry.
(Clicks)
(Crackles)
That son of a bitch is no joke.
If we screw up, we could die for real.
You said we gotta survive somehow.
Can you do this shit for four more years?
(Crackles)
"Through the dark we will
be riding dusk till dawn."
Let’s do it together.
I’ll dig into him a bit.
"Dusk till dawn."
(Up Beat Music)
You think Seok-gu’s already grabbed it?
So what’s the plan?
Disarm him.
(Tyres Screeching)
(Car Door Opens)
(Car Door Closes)
(Tyres Screeching)
That place is also Blackjack’s?
Yeah.
Watch out for that bitch next to him.
“Bull” cleans up all his dirty work.
She’ll make you a cripple or disappear.
(Footsteps)
Here I go.
(Car Door Opens)
Mi-sun.
Make sure he doesn’t see your face.
Okay.
(Footsteps)
(Up Beat Music)
(Indistinct Chatter)
(Glass Clinking)
(Foosteps)
(Up Beat Music)
You’re here?
Can’t you be on time, goddammit.
Fucking hell.
Yes.
(Chair Creaks)
(Screams)
That OCD of yours! So fucking annoying!
Boss, why are you so damn picky?
No matter how much I drink here,
I never get drunk!
Isn’t that weird?
Is it because the chicks are hot?
But the more you drink,
the more sober you get!
- Welcome back, sir.
- Hi.
Good evening.
Give me my leftover bottle from last time.
Sexy whiskey, sexy chicks!
I’ll have it ready.
You got hotter.
- Hurry, hurry!
- You’re too much!
How does she get hotter in just two days?
(Sniffs)
(Rustle)
(Footsteps)
Excuse me.
May I sit down?
Dayum! Welcome, welcome!
(Footsteps)
Sit down, join us!
Wow!
Wearing black lingerie?
Black panther vibes!
- So hot.
- Baby!
- Holy shit.
- Hi, baby.
I like you, approved!
Be my wife tonight, honey!
Pour me a drink!
(Faint Music)
(Glass Clinks)
That's it.
So weird, you’re too weird.
You seriously have OCD or something, right?
Do you lose your shit if
someone touches your shit?
I get so turned on if
someone touches my shit!
Touch me, touch me!
(Laughs)
(Thud)
(Faint Music)
Get your own bottle.
You’re being an ass.
How could you be so
rude to our black panther?
Let me treat you then, have my drink.
What a douchebag.
Don’t be cheap, you’re fucking loaded!
You’re buying my drink!
You hit the jackpot with that condo scam!
And you got rid of that
son-of-a-bitch Choi...
(Rustle)
Alright...
(Thud)
(Slurps)
Honey, let’s get out of here.
Let’s go have fun! Honey, let’s have fun!
Wonderful!
Oh yes!
"Na-na-na-no, no-no-no-no."
(Crowd Cheering)
Showtime!
Honey!
"...click the floor."
"Eyes that whisper,
"You've been here before"."
"Smoke in the air, the lights turn low."
"Her story's a secret, only shadows know."
"Behind the glass, where dreams collide..."
Take that mask off.
"...wears her mask, but can't..."
Why?
Drinking with a chick
hiding her face kills the vibe.
"A glass of champagne, and a..."
I think it’s more fun this way.
"Welcome to the cabaret."
"Where shadows dance and fade away."
"Her smile may shine,..."
Am I drinking to entertain you?
"A fleeting..."
Then let’s go shot-for-shot.
If I lose, I’ll take it off.
"Na-na-na-no, no-no-no-no."
(Thud)
(Glass Clinks)
(Liqour Pouring)
(Crowd Cheering)
(Thud)
(Taps)
(Crowd Cheering)
(Slurps)
I’ll get the location from his phone.
(Thud)
Get it done in 30.
Or I’m moving in.
(Liqour Pouring)
(Crowd Cheering)
(Thud)
(Taps)
(Slurps)
(Engine Reving)
(Pounding Footsteps)
Sorry to bother you, boss...
(Whispering)
(Sighs)
(Chair Creaks)
(Footsteps)
(Crowd Cheering)
(Pounding Footsteps)
Are you the car owner?
Sorry, I bumped into it while backing out.
I wrecked an expensive car, dammit...
I’ll get insurance on it right away.
It’s alright.
There’s no number posted,
at least give me your contact.
(Footsteps)
It’s fine.
Don’t change your mind later,
I’ll file it properly ―
Shit...
I said it’s fine, fuck off.
(Footsteps)
Fucking hell.
What a fucking asshole.
Don’t come crying later,
you son of a bitch!
Fuck it, fine by me.
(Car Door Opens)
(Car Door Closes)
(Beeps)
(Suspense)
(Thud)
(Engine Reving)
(Tyres Screeching)
(Metal Creaks)
(Clatter)
(Spits)
(Clicks)
(Crackles)
(Phone Vibrating)
You know your shit.
She’s spilling everything!
Blackjack bought a piece of land
to start a private cemetery.
Getting tingly? Right?
(Laughs)
It’s near Wangsan,
called Cheongong Cemetery.
They rushed it, so no CCTV,
no fucking nothing!
(Digging)
(Grunts)
(Sighs)
Where are you going?
(Digging)
Shit! I can’t do this!
Is this even the right place?
Look, that’s a compactor. This is the spot!
Shut up and keep digging.
Goddammit...
(Grunts)
(Digging)
Fucking shit!
What was that?
(Digging)
(Grunts)
(Gasps)
- Hey!
- Oh shit!
(Taps)
(Zips)
(Rustle)
(Gasps)
(Giggles)
(Taps)
(Pants)
(Gasps)
(Wood Crunch)
(Pants)
(Clatter)
Hang on...
There’s something else under this.
(Wood Crunch)
(Intense)
(Vehicle Passing By)
It was supposed to be only $700,000.
(Chuckles)
(Gasps)
$700,000?
That’s gotta be a few million bucks!
(Gasps)
It’s all blood money anyway,
sucked out of girls like us.
We deserve it.
Yeah, and Blackjack was Choi’s backer.
He won’t let us off
even if we only took half.
We’ve got one life to live,
go hard or go home.
Right, go fucking hard.
(Chuckles)
(Gasps)
Stupid ass.
(Snickers)
Shut up!
(Thud)
(Chuckles)
(Vehicle Passing By)
It’s Seok-gu.
What?
(Sighs)
Fucking bitches...
(Tyres Screeching)
PLUG
It’s Seok-gu.
(Phone Vibrating)
Shit, what do we do?
(Caller Ringing)
(Engine Roars)
(Honking)
(Distant Honking)
What do we do?
(Gasps)
Let him take the cash.
What?
Lose the $700,000.
What the hell for?
(Sighs)
You trust me, right?
Just stay put, I’ll handle it.
Those fucking whores.
(Honking)
Fuck...
(Vigorous Honking)
(Tyres Screeching)
(Car Door Opens)
(Pants)
Jesus Christ.
(Metal Thud)
(Footsteps)
(Spits)
(Sighs)
(Clicks)
(Crackles)
(Blows)
(Thud)
(Screams)
(Chuckles)
Open it.
Open the window!
(Window Rolling Down)
(Sighs)
Is it fun stealing my money,
fucking bitches?
(Thud)
- What money?!
- You cunt!
- You serious?
Here it is! You little bitch.
- Come on!
- What a load of bullshit.
(Thud)
Open up! Open!
Where are you going?
(Pounding Footsteps)
Mi-sun!
Hang on, my leg’s stuck!
(Pants)
(Pounding Footsteps)
(Grunts)
So fucking slow, are you high or something?
(Pants)
Let go.
(Grunts)
I said, let go!
(Rustle)
Pretty please!
(Grunts)
Crazy bitch. Shitting yourself?
(Screams)
(Grunts)
Die, you son of a bitch!
What the fuck is wrong with you!
(Pants)
Fucking bitch!
(Snaps)
Hey, hey!
Cunt!
(Rustle)
Dobby.
(Grunts)
Goddamn.
(Thud)
No more driving for you.
Don’t!
(Gasps)
(Footsteps)
Take this and get lost, you piece of shit!
(Grunts)
(Pants)
(Zips)
(Gasps)
(Chuckles)
(Pants)
You think you’re my rival?
(Zips)
Don’t kid yourself!
(Pants)
Moron.
You should’ve chosen a better partner,
Dobby.
(Chuckles)
I’m off.
(Pants)
(Grunts)
(Footsteps)
You poor ass bitches!
(Gasps)
Millionaire in a million years!
(Chuckles)
(Gasps)
(Tyres Screeching)
That’s it!
(Pants)
(Thud)
What a dumbass!
(Gasps)
He’s a fucking clown!
(Pants)
(Rustle)
Are you out of your mind?
Why go overboard just to lose the money?
So he won’t get suspicious.
That prick thinks we only had $700,000.
He needs to believe that for us to survive.
(Sighs)
We did it.
(Chuckles)
(Clatter)
(Car Door Closes)
- YOUR GRAVE’S BEEN ROBBED
- While Blackjack is chasing Seok-gu...
- YOUR WIFE KNOWS WHO DID
- IT ...we need to get out with the gold.
How are we supposed to sell all this?
(Thud)
Choi Ga-young.
(Strecthing)
Let’s go to mom.
(Groans)
(Strecthing)
(Grunts)
(Groans)
(Gasps)
(Sighs)
(Plastic Rustle)
(Chuckles)
(Clatter)
I forgot there’s nothing to eat at home.
How about kimchi fried rice?
(Thud)
Where’s my kimchi?
(Refrigirator Door Closes)
(Clatter)
We used to love kimchi fried rice.
(Gasps)
Smash the kimchi in the frying pan,
(Thud)
throw in some rice and
splash some oyster sauce...
(Thud)
Put the scissors away.
You look insane.
(Thud)
(Clatter)
(Chair Creaks)
Mom.
We came to ask you for a favor.
A favor?
That dirt you have on
the Japanese ambassador.
Tell us about that.
Dirt...
(Thud)
(Sighs)
(Chair Creaks)
That’s too bad, it’s love.
Do we look like we’re joking?
(Thud)
Are we laughing?
Do-kyung!
(Gasps)
I gave birth to you at 15,
how dare you talk to me that way!
Half a million.
I’ll give you half a million.
Move a bag to Japan for us.
Triple your offer.
Then I’ll do it.
Fine, triple.
But not right away.
I’ll pay you in Japan.
(Groans)
(Gasps)
Fucked up big time, huh?
(Thud)
(Sighs)
(Clatter)
(Taps)
(Sighs)
These are precious.
(Chuckles)
This is true romance.
(Glass Clinking)
(Groans)
(Chuckles)
(Gasps)
(Rustle)
First, go get new passports here.
No point keeping your identities.
How did you find out about this place?
(Water Running)
(Gasps)
Maybe I should leave with my daughters too.
(Chuckles)
(Crackles)
(Blows)
(Footsteps)
What are you doing alone?
(Crackles)
(Blows)
Don’t get involved with her.
Get what we need and cut her loose.
(Crcakles)
(Sniffs)
(Sighs)
When I first came to the shelter,
it felt good.
Like I was finally an adult,
living on my own.
When I came to Seoul with your mom...
...it felt like I was studying abroad.
At the shelter, when she told me I
could be her daughter from then on,
and that we should live together...
It was the first time
I felt like I had a family.
That’s why I was happy, moron.
(Crackles)
At least she was fair.
Do you remember?
She cut a towel in half
and made us share it.
(Tredmill Running)
It is impossible to know
where this sticky pit came from.
Any creature that falls in
senses death approach.
(Tredmill Running)
(Thud)
(Footsteps)
I’ll start with the gigolo bar, sir.
Honey... Please...
(Whimpers)
Dump her.
(Road Noise)
(Phone Vibrating)
(Glass Clinking)
(Thud)
(Slurps)
(Gasps)
Mom.
I’ll do it for you.
(Gasps)
My darling, Mi-sun.
(Humms)
(Groans)
Do you remember?
On my first day of work,
you did my eye makeup for me.
Yeah...
(Groans)
You said my eyes had to look pretty.
(Gasps)
I always...
...liked you...
(Gasps)
...way better.
Do-kyung won’t understand
me until I’m gone for good.
(Sighs)
(Groans)
Mom, listen.
(Whimpers)
Don’t mix alcohol and sleeping pills.
Okay?
(Groans)
(Phone Vibrating)
LET’S MEET
(Thud)
The ambassador texted me.
(Rustle)
I’ll be back.
(Chair Creaks)
(Sighs)
Do-kyung.
Make sure you get mom’s passport too, okay?
Leave the car behind.
Seok-gu knows our car.
(Scratching)
Mom’s asleep, so I need to go now.
I’m off.
(Footsteps)
(Door Opens)
(Door Closes)
(Beeps)
(Door Opens)
(Door Closes)
(Beeps)
(Elevator Door Slides Open)
(Footsteps)
(Beep)
(Door Opens)
(Bell Rings)
(Footsteps)
(Door Closes)
(Rustle)
(Door Opens)
(Bell Rings)
(Door Closes)
(Footsteps)
You want me to smuggle a bag
in exchange for deleting my video?
Why should I trust you?
Then who can you trust right now?
Women like you take
a mile if I give an inch.
So, I changed my method.
Never give that inch.
(Clatter)
You don’t even go through customs,
you worry too much.
Hey!
Delete the original video first.
We’re all dead if we
don’t make it to Japan.
This will go viral instantly.
No!
(Thud)
You crazy bitch!
(Panicks)
(Whimpers)
It’s a private account.
Only I can see it.
(Whimpers)
(Pants)
(Footsteps)
May I help you?
(Thud)
(Grunts)
Who are you?
(Door Opens)
- What is it?
- I...
(Footsteps)
(Door Closes)
Which fucker got in bed
with Blackjack’s wife?
You’re my bitch today.
Shit!
(Thud)
What the fuck?
(Chocks)
Get the manager...
Was it you?
You... bitch...
(Taps)
(Chocks)
(Thud)
(Zips)
(Sighs)
(Chuckles)
(Rustle)
(Phone Vibrating)
I told you not to call me, asshole.
Watch your own back.
(Chuckles)
Why’s he silent?
(Thud)
(Footsteps)
(Gasps)
(Glass Shatters)
Shit!
(Thud)
(Grunts)
Goddammit!
(Screams)
Where’s the gold?
What gold?! You motherfucker!
For a bastard like you,
dying today is a blessing.
What are you talking about?
(Grunts)
I’ll tell you! I’ll tell you!
(Crackles)
I didn’t come for ―
I know you didn’t come for fortune telling.
You came to get on a boat.
Sit.
(Footsteps)
(Taps)
You know Hwajoong was
built on cold yin energy, right?
(Gasps)
People like us tend to gather
in places with strong yin energy.
I don’t know what your story is,
but your world won’t
change even if you leave.
So, how many servings?
(Creaks)
Write down their names.
(Scribble)
(Thud)
(Paper Rustle)
(Crackles)
(Screams)
(Groans)
(Coughs)
I can live with the fact
that gigolos fucked my wife.
(Footsteps)
But fucking with my money?
(Coughs)
(Pants)
(Thud)
(Footsteps)
Bull is so impatient,
she cut off the gigolo’s
tongue before he could talk.
(Clicks)
But he gave us your name before he croaked.
Boss,
I think there’s been a misunderstanding...
Don’t cut out the
tongue too soon this time.
You got the money back!
(Whimpers)
There’s no need to go this far!
How about the thigh?
(Thud)
(Slits)
(Screams)
(Groans)
Quiet! Quiet!
(Whimpers)
Please spare me this once...
I never even saw the gold, I swear!
- How about the Achilles tendon?
- Yoon Mi-sun! Lee Do-kyung!
Yoon Mi-sun! Lee Do-kyung!
Those bitches stole it.
They’re the thieves!
I just thought about it, that’s all!
Can’t a guy just dream for once?
(Groans)
(Snickers)
I know them well!
(Gasps)
I’ll be your lapdog and
sniff them out for you!
(Pants)
(Whimpers)
No! No!
Cut it.
Sir!
(Screams)
He’ll be on a plane to Japan in two days.
And the passports?
(Footsteps)
Shit, the car.
(Gasps)
(Pouding Footsteps)
(Rustle)
(Clatter)
(Door Opens)
(Pouding Footsteps)
(Pants)
(Gasps)
(Sighs)
(Sniffs)
(Caller Ring)
GA-YOUNG
(Footsteps)
(Sniffs)
(Sighs)
(Phone Vibrating)
- It’s a beautiful night!
- Choi Ga-young!
(Gasps)
How could you take that?!
Where’s the gold?!
Do-kyung, mommy’s retiring today.
You’ll get hurt if you take everything.
Wait right there.
(Sighs)
I’m going to kill you, you fucking hag.
(Disconnecting Tne)
(Gasps)
(Groans)
Gonna be one hell of a day, finally.
So cute.
(Phone Vibrating)
By the way, kiddo, the gold is...
You have no clue what
you got yourself into!
It’s our little secret!
What the fuck are you saying?!
(Gasps)
(Footsteps)
Here comes mommy dearest!
Come on.
Let’s go.
Where the hell do we find her?
I know her.
She’ll never leave Hwajoong Market.
(Gasps)
(Faint Music)
I heard Seung-won went missing.
That sucks.
Damn, I love this haircut.
Our shop’s ace fell off the grid.
The fuck do I care?
Alright, boys.
We got a VIP.
Come and greet her properly.
- Sure!
- Certainly!
(Door Opens)
No intro necessary, she’s a legend.
Say hello.
- Hello!
- Evening, ma’am!
Hello!
Greet her properly!
Hello, ma’am, I’m Jae-pil.
I sing really well.
I’m Young-jae, your new side bae.
Hi, baby, I’m Yeon-sung ―
(Faint Music)
(Phone Vibrating)
Dude!
A woman with gold bars came to the shop.
GOLD BARS? YOUNG?
Old bimbo who’s been
here too long and reeks like it.
(Gasps)
I told you I’d be your lapdog.
(Chuckles)
(Engine Roaring)
(Vehicle Passing By)
(Beeps)
(Pounding Footsteps)
(car Door Opens)
Not here.
(Car Door Closes)
(Groans)
(Thud)
(Sighs)
Over here! This way. Come on in.
(Footsteps)
Just through here.
(Grunts)
(Footsteps)
(Rap Music Playing In Background)
Wait here.
Room S. There!
(Rap Music Playing In Background)
They might slip out the back,
so I’ll wait there!
(Crowd Chatter)
- Take it slow, baby.
- Knock it off, will you?
(Indistinct Chatter)
(Chuckles)
- This is so good! Try one!
- Hold this, it’s fucking heavy.
Bottoms up!
We’re getting lit tonight!
(Faint Music)
Everyone out.
(Thud)
(Pounding Footsteps)
(Indistinct Chatter)
(Glass Clinking )
(Door Closes)
(Faint Music)
And you are?
(Footsteps)
(Chewing)
(Untensil Clatter)
(Slaps)
(Coughs)
(Gasps)
(Groans)
The gold.
Take me to your boss.
Got nothing to say to a lapdog...
(Door Opens)
Choi Ga-young!
(Grunts)
(Thud)
(Gasps)
Hurry!
(Grunts)
(Groans)
We gotta go!
(Pounding Footsteps)
(Thud)
(Door Closes)
(Pants)
(Thud)
Let go!
(Slaps)
Get your shit together!
How dare you come here.
(Thud)
Who’s saving who?
You have to save yourself!
(Sighs)
You’re a softie.
(Slaps)
A complete softie, Do-kyung.
Lee Do-kyung.
You know who I am.
(Taps)
Live life however the fuck you want.
That’s how I’m gonna live mine.
Go.
Go find the gold.
(Footsteps)
I’m abandoning you. Go.
Go!
(Whimpers)
(Footsteps)
(Door Opens)
(Gasps)
(Sighs)
Thieving bitch!
Fucking cunt.
Where is it?
(Gasps)
You crying?
(Chuckles)
Did mommy scold you?
(Thud)
Where the fuck’s your mommy?
Where is she, bitch!
(Grunts)
(Thud)
Cunt...
(Grunts)
(Thud)
(Pounding Footsteps)
Bring the gold back!
(Car Door Opens)
(Pounding Footsteps)
(Pants)
Where’s mom?
I think I know where the gold is.
Let’s go.
You were supposed to bring her back!
(Pants)
I’m done.
Once I find the gold, I’m out of here.
Let’s go.
(Thud)
What’s with you?
We have to take her...
Fine. Do whatever you want.
(Whimpers)
I’ll handle my own shit, okay?
(Sighs)
(Footsteps)
(Thud)
(Car Door Opens)
(Car Door Closes)
(Engine Roaring)
(Engine Reving)
(Tyres Screeching)
(Pounding Footsteps)
(Pants)
(Gasps)
(Slosh)
(Grunts)
(Gasps)
Hold tight. It’s your lifeline.
(Grunts)
(Groans)
Your body will slowly harden.
(Grunts)
Where’s the gold?
Pull me out, then I’ll lead you!
(Pants)
Wrong answer.
If I tell you, you’ll kill me now!
(Grunts)
(Groans)
(Footsteps)
(Pants)
(Gasps)
(Chuckles)
You laugh? Is this funny?
(Groans)
(Gasps)
With this,
even memories you never
had will come rushing back.
(Grunts)
(Injecting)
(Whimpers)
(Thud)
Hwajoong Station!
Locker 12!
(Beeps)
(Sighs)
(Taps)
INCORRECT PASSCODE. PLEASE TRY AGAIN.
(Gasps)
(Sighs)
Check locker 12 at Hwajoong Station.
(Gasps)
What’s the passcode?
The passcode... is...
7... 1... 6...
21...
(Pants)
(Screams)
(Thud)
(Grunts)
(Groans)
Thanks for everything.
(Gasps)
(Grunts)
(Groans)
(Screams)
Fucking disgusting.
(Groans)
(Sloshes)
(Whimpers)
(Footsteps)
(Gasps)
(Wheels Rolling)
(Footsteps)
(Beeps)
(Door Opens)
(Door Closes)
(Footsteps)
See this?
I found the gold.
I tried my birthday as the passcode
but that didn’t work.
Yours didn’t work either.
Do you know what it was?
123... 123.
When I was a kid,
she made me run deliveries.
She said no one ever suspects
a kid with pills or whatever...
(Gasps)
Locker 12 at Hwajoong Station.
I wondered what she
meant by “our little secret.”
But I knew,
the second I held her hand and ran.
Anyway.
You can have this.
(Footsteps)
(Sniffs)
Come on.
What is it?
Mom’s dead.
What?
(Sobbs)
I said mom’s dead!
(Gasps)
Do-kyung, she’s dead!
(Sobbs)
She’s gone!
I was so scared, I couldn’t do anything...
(Sobbs)
I told you we should go together, didn’t I?
I told you...
(Sobbs)
...that we should go together...
(Sniffs)
(Sobbs)
We should go together...
She was gonna die anyway,
why be so dramatic?
(Sniffs)
Take the gold and fuck off.
You wanted her dead too, didn’t you?
Take the fucking gold and fuck off!
(Sobbs)
(Tyres Screeching)
(Vehicle Passing)
(Thud)
You’re a softie.
(Slaps)
A complete softie, Do-kyung.
(Zips)
Lee Do-kyung.
Live life however the fuck you want.
(Sniffs)
That’s how I’m gonna live mine.
(Sighs)
(Sniffs)
(Vehicle Passing)
(Fire Crackling)
(Door Opens)
(Door Closes)
(Fire Crackling)
It’s a clusterfuck.
Blackjack’s looking for you two.
(Fire Crackling)
Just stop and leave.
It’s what Ga-young would have wanted.
(Fire Crackling)
(Door Opens)
(Door Creaks)
(Footsteps)
(Fire Crackling)
(Glass Clinking)
(Footsteps)
(Thud)
(Crack Whirls)
(Liqour Pouring)
(Fire Igniting Loud Flame)
(Fire Crackling)
We can’t leave Hwajoong.
No, we won’t leave.
(Fire Crackling)
Not until we fuck those assholes up.
(Liqour Pouring)
(Fire Igniting Loud Flame)
(Fire Crackling)
(Blowing)
(Door Slides Open)
You fucking bitches.
How dare you show up here?
Get over here!
(Thud)
I’ll kill you!
You think I’m done, right?
You think I’m finished?
I don’t fucking die, bitches!
Once I’m all patched up,
I’ll rip you to shreds!
You dirty sluts ― What’s that?
We’re giving you a chance here.
Do-kyung, don’t do that.
Stop it.
Don’t push that!
You fu ―
(Screams)
Shut up, you’re being too loud.
The cheat sheet you
got following Bull around.
Give us that.
Shut your fucking face.
Then I’ll give you gold.
Give us that cheat sheet
and we’ll fuck up Blackjack
for what he did to you.
Water!
(Gasps)
(Thud)
(Grunts)
(Water Trinkles)
(Groans)
(Slurps)
(Coughs)
(Blowing)
(Gasps)
Blackjack just launched a new site.
(Beeps)
There’s a big game coming up in a few days.
Word on the street is,
he bet everything he has
on losing by 6 points or more.
Get caught betting on your own game,
you get stabbed just
within an inch of your life,
that’s the rule.
Making a bet like that?
Guy’s scared shitless.
And you know us,
we don’t take hits lying down.
(Tense Music)
He’s fucked if Choi Chul’s team wins.
GA-YOUNG Why’re they so late?
Hurry up already.
(Indistinct Chatter)
Why’d they call us all the way here?
(Crackles)
When’s the makeup reservation?
(Indistinct Chatter)
Hurry up.
(Claps)
Quiet, quiet!
Girls!
- Attention please.
- What’s the holdup?
Hwa-jin, $80,000.
Ga-eul, $52,000.
Ye-jin, $120,000.
And Dal-ja, $90,000 ―
Ye-seul, what the hell?
Why’re you reading out our debt?
You think we forgot we’re drowning in debt?
You called us here to remind us of that?
What’s the point of this?
Let’s go! Leave!
(Indistinct Chatter)
Mr. Choi,
who scammed us with our housing deposits...
The guy pulling his strings was Blackjack.
- Blackjack? Really?
- It wasn’t Choi?
What?
Quiet!
- That guy we saw.
- Yeah, that asshole!
That’s how he keeps all of us on a leash.
And that motherfucker...
...killed my mom.
Are you for real?
Shit, he crossed the line.
I’ll tear this ledger to shreds.
So, do me a favor.
(Pants)
(Thud)
(Sighs)
What?
We went all-in on the game.
Losing side, like you said, sir.
(Gasps)
(Tense Music)
Leak the intel to powerful,
greedy clients and get them to bet.
Say it’s a fixed match,
so they’ll win no matter what.
(Up Beat Music)
WIN BY 6
Alright, let’s see what you’ve really got.
Go flaunt it.
(Trunk Opens)
(Clinks)
(Up Beat Music)
(Click)
ANOTHER DAY, ANOTHER GOLD FLEX.
YOLOING THRU UR GOLD.
(Up Beat Music)
ANOTHER DAY, ANOTHER GOLD FLEX.
YOLOING THRU UR GOLD.
(Up Beat Music)
(Ball Bouncing)
Feels unfair, doesn’t it?
Intentionally missing shots.
(Ball Bouncing)
I retired.
As for you...
How long are you gonna let
your coach pull your strings?
WP, on a 3-game losing streak,
is trying to break it with CM back home.
Losing streak aside, their recent
play has been very disappointing.
Their struggling ace Lee needs
to step up in this crucial game.
This match will need both teams,
not just Coach Choi, to be set on winning.
In games like this,
late moments and clutch plays
matter more than the first half.
Lately, the team has been falling
behind when Lee is subbed in.
It’ll be interesting to see
how things unfold today.
Lee Han-wook is subbed in at
this crucial 4th-quarter moment.
- That’s Lee Han-wook!
- We’re excited to see...
...how Lee Han-wook performs today.
Right off the bat,
some unnecessary tension.
He needs to be careful.
Now, a technical foul is called
due to that unnecessary action,
and a free throw is awarded.
Lee Han-wook’s been struggling
with his free throws lately.
I told you before.
(Tense Music)
Your life is yours to save.
If you get used to losing,
(Ball Bouncing)
you won’t be able to win when you want to.
Free throw for the tie.
He scores! It’s tied!
WP evens out the score after
trailing behind the whole game!
He nails it with laser focus
even with the pressure.
After scoring the free throw,
Lee Han-wook is on fire.
Lee Han-wook drives to the rim.
Driving layup ― and one!
As a team!
- Now WP takes the lead!
- Take it slow, easy.
He’s back on the prowl.
After the hand-off,
he sinks another three-pointer!
Three-pointer by Lee Han-wook!
Good!
The game completely flips now.
Lee, who’s been struggling,
is dominating tonight.
Hell yeah.
His energy is unstoppable.
Every shot slices through the rim.
Tonight, Lee Han-wook is back
as the player we know and love.
He’s leading WP with
an incredible performance.
Victory is within reach.
The star shows up when it counts!
(Crowd Cheering)
89-78.
WP’s Lee has been resurrected.
They close out the game with a win!
The super-ace has risen again.
Lee Han-wook is back!
(Crowd Cheering)
(Footsteps)
Boss, the girls are all ghosting us.
So there’s no revenue...
(Footsteps)
(Glass Clinks)
Open your mouth.
Boss...
(Footsteps)
Sir, we tracked down the
girls working at other bars.
(Footsteps)
Open your mouth.
(Tense Music)
Say “ah.”
(Footsteps)
(Tense Music)
SANG-OK
(Phone Vibrating)
(Scoffs)
Hey, Sang-ok.
It’s been fun till now.
But playtime’s over.
I’ll drop a pin for your mom’s grave.
Get your ass there
before I grind up your friend’s faces.
(Beeps)
See you soon.
(Footsteps)
(Whimpers)
(Tyres Screeching)
(Engine Roaring)
(Thud)
(Vehicle Approaching)
(Tyres Screeching)
(Footsteps)
(Car Door Opens)
(Clinking)
(Thud)
(Car Door Closes)
(Footsteps)
(Thud)
(Zips)
I brought your gold.
So let the girls go.
Cut her hand off.
(Thud)
(Clinking)
(Footsteps)
(Engine Roaring At Distant)
Let them go.
Do-kyung, run!
Just run!
Are you all okay?
Yeah, everyone’s okay.
Take care of yourself.
(Engine Roaring At Distant)
(Wheels Rolling)
(Thud)
(Car Door Closes)
Goddamn bitch!
(Tyres Screeching)
(Footsteps)
Open up!
I said open the goddamn door!
(Tyres Screeching)
Motherfucker, stop!
(Tense Music)
(Tyres Screeching)
(Footsteps)
(Spits)
(Tyres Screeching)
You fucking cunts!
(Engine Reving)
(Tyres Screeching)
Where’d that fucker go?
Yoon Mi-sun!
(Groans)
Mi-sun, hey!
(Car Door Opens)
(Grunts)
(Thud)
(Rustle)
(Grunts)
You fucking bitch.
(Gasps)
(Thud)
(Grunts)
Die!
(Thud)
(Grunts)
(Coughs)
Shit...
(Grunts)
Say hi to your mom for me.
(Pants)
You son of a bitch!
(Grunts)
No!
(Thud)
(Grunts)
Let go, asshole!
Do-kyung!
(Pants)
(Sloshes)
Let’s go.
(Gasps)
Let’s end this.
You think you could ever leave Hwajoong?
(Gasps)
(Chuckles)
(Thud)
(Grunts)
(Pants)
(Groans)
(Footsteps)
(Sighs)
(Whimpers)
(Sloshes)
(Footsteps)
Is it okay to leave him like that?
No.
(Footsteps)
Of course not.
(Scoffs)
(Footsteps)
(Up Beat Music)
Coffee!
(Sighs)
You’re so high maintenance.
(Phone Vibrating)
(Slurps)
Dude!
PIN: BLACKJACK STUFF URSELF W GOLD, SEOK-GU
Cold-hearted bitches...
This is how I get my gift?
Let’s go get my gold!
When’s the last time we
walked like this at this hour?
(Footsteps)
Feeling a tinge of regret?
(Scoffs)
You’ve got that look on your face.
Shut up.
(Siren Wailing At Distant)
Hey.
(Footsteps)
There’s really nothing left?
Nothing.
Don’t bullshit me, not even a penny?
Not a damn thing!
You steal shit all the time
but couldn’t grab one bar...
(Footsteps)
Where the hell would money
even come from right now?
(Footsteps)
What would you do with it anyway?
Go on a backpacking trip, asshole!
Screw that, you don’t even have a backpack!
I can buy one!
Your dreams are so half-baked.
(Footsteps)
(Scoffs)
What are we gonna do now?
What else? We live.
If you were to go backpacking,
where would you go?
We’re flat broke. Why bother asking?
(Chuckles)
Wait. You have something!
"There's a man in the sky."
"Taking me up for a ride."
"Oh, I thought it was heaven, babe."
"Every night I prayed."
"Oh, you ain't no saint."
"No, you never came."
"My, my!"
"You're taking me up for a ride."
"No, I ain't a fool."
"So don't act like you're innocent."
"You just like the view up there."
"Must be magnificent."
"I'm not your little rag doll."
"You can't bring me up."
"Just to bring me down."
"Best believe you and
I aren't so different."
"Read between the lines."
"I'm not so articulate."
"I'm not your little rag doll."
"You can't bring me up."
"Just to bring me down."
"So why'd you never call me?"
"Or lend a hand when I was falling?"
"I tried and tried but can't figure out."
"If you are against or for me."
"Man in the sky, the sky."
"There's a man in the sky."
"Taking me up for a ride."
"Oh, I thought it was heaven, babe."
"Every night I prayed."
"Oh, you ain't no saint."
"No, you never came."
"My, my!"
"You're taking me up for a ride."
"I am standing in the harsh wind."
"The blue waves are calling me."
"I want to leave for somewhere far away."
"Carrying myself within this freedom."
"Wave, please take me away."
"To that endless sea far away."
"Just as my heart sways."
"I want to dance with you."
"Even if I lose my way
in the deep darkness."
"I will find it if I follow the waves."
"If I live by going with the flow."
"I will eventually arrive."
"Wave, please take me away."
"To that endless sea far away."
"Just as my heart sways."
"I want to dance with you."
(Vocalizing)
(Music)