SIX YEARS EARLIER
[speeding car approaching]
[tires squealing]
- [rap music playing on stereo]
- You feel that beat there, little man?
Feel it! Move!
Ahh! Feel it!
Mm. Little man, take that.
My man!
Cut it out, Nat!
[Nat] Relax, I got this!
Dance, little man!
This is too fast!
Well, I'm the one driving to Mama's
and I say you're both being losers!
[Annabelle] Let us out, now!
[screams] Nat!
[loud crash]
[bittersweet music playing]
Where is Dylan, Mama?
At the morgue.
What happened, Annabelle?
Uh…
Did Nathanaël murder my boy, Annabelle?
[softly] Mama…
What happened?
Tell me what happened Annabelle
or the police will.
I didn't do anything.
There was a stray on the road.
I tried to avoid it.
Was there an animal on the road?
No.
[Nat] Mama, I swear it was an accident.
[bittersweet music continues]
We were playing around
and the little demon came out of nowhere.
- It wasn't my fault.
- Enough, Nat.
You're sad?
You'll forever live
with a heavy sadness all alone.
No one can help you anymore.
[Nat] What?
You'll never see your brothers
or sisters ever again.
You are no longer welcome in my house.
[bittersweet music continues]
- [music fades]
- [insects chirping softly]
[Kingsley groaning softly]
[Kingsley softly] Take this.
Hide the packages.
[Léo softly] Where?
- Who makes your bed? Cass or you?
- No one does.
- Then put it there.
- Okay.
[Kingsley wincing]
Fuck.
[groaning softly]
What are you doing?
- Nothing, go back to bed.
- What happened?
[exhales] Nothing, don't worry.
- You need a hospital, King.
- No way.
- You might lose that leg.
- No hospital.
[Cassandra sighs]
[Kingsley wincing]
- Apply pressure.
- [groans]
Wrap this around your leg.
You'll still need stitches.
[thrilling music playing]
The white rooster. That's him there.
[man] I know him.
You do?
Yeah, back in the day,
he'd go fishing with my old man.
[thrilling music continues]
Fast, follow.
Hey, kids! Don't fuck with me!
I need to get home!
I have my old rooster with me.
- Hey! Let go! Stop!
- [rooster clucks]
Joé, are you out of your damn mind?
What are you doing?
Hey, let go! Are you crazy?
[Kylian] Grab the rooster, grab it.
[music stops]
See you, Milord.
Hold on.
[man] Stop moving.
What the hell is this?
[in Spanish] Cockfighter!
You stole from me.
And now you're a damn snitch too, huh?
Little bitch.
You think you're safe in your country?
Guys, I'm offering
a reward of 1,000 dollars…
to whoever brings me that son of a bitch.
Screw that white rooster of yours,
you Martinican fucker.
[in English] He's employed, I think,
by your Venezuelan friends.
Maybe.
He has a white combat rooster.
He's real easy to spot.
[man] Yeah, this guy talks too much.
So you're doing this for the money?
Nah, it's not that.
I want to meet the cartel.
[chuckles softly]
That's bold of you, Milord.
Those men don't play any games.
I'll be contacting you.
Uh…
This man belongs to you.
Keep him for now.
I hope you thought this through,
'cause this is rubbing me the wrong way.
Where you get that video, bro?
On social media,
you just need to look for it.
[rooster clucks softly]
Stop it. Chill out, guys.
It looks bad, but it's fine.
Where's Léo?
He's sleeping.
- Let him rest.
- Go wake that child.
We got in late last night.
Leave him alone.
He's going to school.
- Wake Léo, would you?
- [rooster crowing]
How are you?
What's this?
I'm babysitting.
What happened?
What happened is that he got the children
mixed up in his games.
- I came first to the grown ups, didn't I?
- Is that what you have to say?
- Uh, yeah.
- But who did this to you?
- Don't think you can question me.
- I'm asking the questions, bro.
Move, we're stepping out to talk.
- I'm not going anywhere.
- Get up.
Go on outside then. You're going alone.
[clicks tongue] Wow, that smells heavenly.
Can I have some, Cass?
You guys, on the other hand, are assholes.
This little guy needs sleep.
Look how exhausted he is.
- Poor thing!
- I'm gonna fuckin' bust your face.
Go ahead, brother. Indulge yourself.
Kids, go outside for now
and play while we speak.
[Mathis] You're in trouble.
- Léo, last night, what did you do?
- Don't you say a word.
- Cass, may I have one?
- Léo, I'm asking you a question.
Shouldn't you be asking him?
Hey, don't forget that I'm the adult.
I'm the one asking questions.
- Answer me, please.
- Marvin, stop torturing him like this.
King, you best quit disrespecting me now!
[Ambre] Hey, Marvin, enough! Cut it out!
[Marvin] Wow.
Léo, what did he
force you to do last night?
- Nothing, we just stole some drugs.
- Tell me how he hurt himself.
It was Vincez that stabbed him.
- Vincez?
- Yeah, the guy who invited us.
But he suddenly got very mean.
Vincez, SherKhan's cousin?
Léo, stop. [clicks tongue]
How do you know Vincez, bro?
Fucking stop.
- Continue, Léo. I'm listening to you.
- He was gonna kill King.
- And so?
- And so I knocked him out, that's all.
Knocked who out?
No way you knocked him out!
Léo, cut it.
I shot that motherfucker. I saved King.
Boom, in his face.
He won't mess with the Lafleur family.
Please say you are joking.
- Wait, did you have a gun?
- No gun.
He's mixed up in the head right now.
He's all shook up, yeah. Ignore him.
[Ambre] Was it Mama's gun?
What gun did he fire with? Was it Mama's?
You aren't up yet?
It's almost half a million. Consider that.
You mean you swiped half a million?
I told you already
that I don't answer to you.
We all answer to someone.
You stole SherKhan's money
and shot his cousin?
- You made off with how much?
- There's so many packages.
- [Kylian] Where are these packages?
- Don't speak, Léo.
- Confession's for church.
- Mama's gun is now gone.
I put Mama's gun in my bag.
[Marvin] Fuck,
did you shoot someone, King?
You mean you'd rob them unarmed?
He shot nobody. Don't twist it.
I'm the one that saved you
and shot the pistol.
You allowed Léo to use Mama's gun?
Don't get back up, King.
I'll knock your ass out.
[doorbell ringing]
[woman] Hello! Are you Marvin Lafleur?
Yes, what is it?
I'm here on behalf
of the juvenile court to investigate.
To see how you all are doing
after your mother's passing.
May I come in?
We were about to head out for groceries.
[lighter clicking]
We're gonna be changing that.
[rooster crowing]
Is that a rooster?
It was Mama's. We're gonna be selling it.
Oh, I injured myself
while fixing the garden.
Who sleeps here?
It's the kids' room.
I'd like to speak with the children.
Thaïs as well, please.
- Hello, children.
- [kids] Hello.
Could I sit next to you?
Well, may I?
Tell me who's looking after you lately?
Cassandra.
- Is she the oldest sister?
- No, Annabelle is.
She's very tired right now.
She's been crying today.
- [Ambre] What do you think will happen?
- Foster homes for the kids, probably.
- What?
- That's not possible.
Completely impossible.
Hold on.
Can they just remove them like that?
Yes, if they think we're negligent,
or believe that the kids are in danger.
But they are in danger.
- Right, King?
- Damn, you won't drop it, will you?
Go fuck yourself, bro. Seriously.
I'm not finished with you, King.
Just wait.
I think you want them to be taken,
don't you?
Remove all us inconveniences
from the peaceful life you want.
Fuck off, Kingsley,
or I'll break your damn face.
What? Anybody else want to speak?
Does this concern only us? Hmm?
Start speaking up.
You're all a part of this family.
Did I help with killing someone?
Killing?
No one died.
Don't panic, Cass. It'll be okay.
No one knows I was there.
You got anything to say?
Truthfully, King,
I think robbing SherKhan was a lousy idea.
[Ambre] It doesn't help us at all.
He's dragging us down. Just forget him.
I've got to go work.
You got work too, Kiki.
You also goin' to work.
And you too, sunshine.
If we act as a team,
we can provide for the family honestly.
[sarcastically] Okay. Super. Perfect.
Best of luck.
- [sighs softly]
- [pensive music playing]
- [pensive music continues]
- [monitor beeping softly]
Jerome.
[laughs softly]
We were looking last night for you.
I spoke with your man
at the surveillance center.
- [man] You don't know what happened?
- Nah! Do you?
We'll find out, because you're gonna tell.
Depends on who talk first.
I suggest you stay on my good side
and lay low.
Or you can deal with Ducos instead, hmm?
Find the fuckers that did this.
- [kid laughing]
- SherKhan took a bad beating, guys!
- No way!
- [laughing]
[girl on phone] Oh, but wait.
That's not even the worst of it.
His cousin found
the thugs that robbed him,
and was shot
while the robbers escaped unharmed.
[kids laughing on video]
That's the type of buzz
we have to stay away from.
Just look on as a spectator.
- Your brother's not part of this, right?
- Why would you say that?
He has a reputation as a thief.
That's impossible.
We were at home together.
[laughs softly]
Is that your story for the cops?
Look, our mother was buried last week,
so we're grieving as a family.
We lean on each other for support.
You're orphans.
It's not my problem…
except if your brother
and you are affected.
Then it's my problem.
Make sure the container is prepared for us
before we move the product.
- Understood?
- Watch how you talk to me.
I said it would be ready, so it will be.
Get out now.
[door opens and closes]
[inmates chattering]
DUCOS CORRECTIONAL FACILITY
- Are you serious? You always hound me.
- You stop.
The children?
The kids might not understand yet.
They're lucky to have many siblings.
It will help ease things.
Hey now, son. Please don't cry.
Stop crying.
Don't weep like a woman. Man up, brother.
[Kylian] Hmm.
My mom passed too.
You're not alone, brother.
Life just isn't fair. End of story.
I empathize with you,
your siblings pain, I truly do,
but this will transform you to a man.
Okay?
Kylian, you've just gotta
take life by the balls
or it will fuck you up.
Now, choose, will you step up or what?
Maybe.
Be firmer. Otherwise, life will beat you.
They'll separate us from Thaïs,
Nolan, even Mathis.
Maybe that's what's best for them.
Their father did pass away
many years ago, right?
Perhaps they'll find a foster family.
Think about it.
No.
Mama wanted us to be together.
Okay, and the older kids?
Are they missing in action?
What the fuck are they doing?
Marvin, King, Annabelle,
what have they done?
Dad, what can we do here?
What can we do? Mind your own shit.
Okay?
Focus on you.
And forget about helping the kids.
Okay?
They'll live their lives.
Also, I sincerely hope
you didn't come here for a handout.
I got no money.
Nah, money's no issue.
You still running the dope business,
by chance?
I can scale up, you know.
Meaning?
Scale up, you know?
You gotta tell me more, my son.
I'll tell you when things shape up,
I promise.
Son, you always aim too high.
"When things shape up," you say.
[woman on PA] Manager needed
at register five, please.
Too expensive.
[clicks tongue]
Yo.
Where have you been, yo?
[sighs] I was busy.
Daytime isn't for jerking off.
We gotta grind, bro.
Drive the buggy.
How are you gonna
sell the stuff you stole?
Don't worry about it.
- You got at least 20 kilos, right?
- How'd you know?
You said half a million.
That's ten kilos or more.
You know the prices too?
Do you have a plan?
This suddenly interests you?
"Lousy idea"
was your description of my plan.
It is if you get busted.
And I don't want you
behind bars for that, King.
So what's your plan?
Gonna sell it in Paris.
How?
Have a woman stuff it up her coochie.
Just kidding.
You know how we make babies, right?
- But do you know a girl that--
- I'll find one easily.
In Paris, you need a hook up.
No improvising.
[sighs] You know what?
Stop asking me all these questions.
You seem suspicious, bro.
[King laughs]
[Kingsley] Oh, right. We need
to try to fix the one we have for now.
Everything's fine, bro.
Thanks to King, we can buy the best stove.
The price doesn't matter.
Hey, miss!
Come here.
[woman on PA] Clean-up needed
on aisle four, please.
Which one is the most expensive?
Most expensive?
Yes, the best of the best.
- Gas or electric?
- Gas.
The best of the best
is that one over there.
It's called a range.
And it costs 3,989 euros.
Have we met before?
Um, no.
Margot.
Do I know you?
A story on Insta.
[chuckles]
Do you need anything else?
A woman.
- A woman?
- To do a thing.
What thing?
Your break coming up soon?
So no more gas stove?
I also want to talk to you.
- About what?
- You know, about some things.
My break's coming up.
Meet me outside.
- What? Do you want her to--
- Let me handle it.
Seriously, King, this makes no sense.
I know.
Okay, velvet tongue.
You want something?
How long you worked here?
An eternity.
How much you bag?
It depends, mostly. About 1,200.
A blowjob or two jumps it to 2,000 maybe.
[both laughing]
A trip to Paris.
2,500.
Easy, fast, well-paid.
With two nights at a hotel too.
Seems he's not on board.
Don't mind him.
So this is what you're asking me?
And low-balling me, my guy?
I'm not an idiot.
I'm the one
taking all the risks for 2,500?
[scoffs] Mmm-mmm.
What about 3,000?
You must be an amateur.
You should've offered 4,000. With that…
You find me when you're ready
to be a real bandit.
Kingsley, right?
[laughs] A story on Insta.
So, was that your super plan?
You're mad crazy.
What do you know, brother?
This isn't quantum mechanics.
This is the street, man.
And what do you know about the streets?
You don't implement basic rules.
Your mouth stays shut.
Your family isn't involved.
And for fuck's sake, bro, trust no one.
- And that means no one!
- [laughs] Hold up.
You must think you someone else.
Are you suicidal?
You mind your business and keep out of it.
["Taudis" by Mercenaire & Jozii playing]
[plane flying overhead]
Jerome.
[laughs softly] Pretty bracelet.
Tsk.
You may be out of merchandise,
but we still have a deal.
My boat just left empty without goods.
So, you're gonna pay up what you owe me.
[sighs]
Real quick,
I can get back what they stole.
Spare me the details, please.
I don't give a fuck about your thief.
You have two weeks to pay.
Remember, I saved you before,
I can send you back.
Like that.
[sighs]
[monitor beeping regularly]
Who did this to you?
[groans softly]
- [groaning]
- [monitor beeping rapidly]
Who did this to you?
- [groaning]
- [monitor beeping rapidly]
[sputters]
[intriguing music playing]
Hello, ma'am.
Hello.
I'm here to visit someone named Vincez.
You must have a chaperone
for you to be able to see him.
Could I know
if he's holding up all right, please?
[woman] What's his last name?
Do you think I'm dumb?
Attempting to screw me over?
[alarm beeping]
I'm fucking SherKhan!
Talk, you little shit!
- [grunts]
- [alarm subsides]
[monitor beeping rapidly]
I'll be back.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to remember, but I don't know.
All I know
is that he was shot in a robbery.
[woman] All right.
All I can tell you is that he's alive…
and he's no longer in intensive care.
[Cassandra] Thank you.
[tense music playing]
- Don't I know you?
- I don't think so.
I seen you, what's your name?
I'm talking, where you going?
[tense music continues]
Hold up, kid!
Don't run here, sir.
- [music fades]
- [keyboard clacking]
What do your parents do?
Mom works at Fort-de-France City Hall
and my dad is a plastic surgeon.
All good. I'm done.
- So all of you have this ring?
- All of us above 16 years old.
So when you reach the age of consent.
[laughs]
What's on it?
Ignore that. Just an evil curse.
That true?
You got a guy?
No. No guy.
[laughs softly]
- You've never done it?
- [scoffs]
- You think I'm an amateur?
- [laughing]
[laughs]
["Love Baw" by Jkevlar & Océane playing]
[R&B song continues]
[song continues]
[knock on door]
- [Fatso] He's in there.
- [song continues playing]
[muffled grunting]
[phone vibrating]
LILY
Yummy
[man] What do you think we should do?
We can't hold him prisoner forever.
[Kylian sighs]
What is it?
What?
Are we doing pickups
for the Venezuelans now?
And we had to pick up
a friend of my father's?
No, no pick-ups. Not for the Venezuelans.
Good, because this is our turf here.
They got a problem, they can go.
We're not their puppets, brother.
You feel the same?
Yeah, I do.
[sighs]
Okay, listen.
I've thought out a plan.
I know a docker.
Thanks to old man,
I got a meeting with the Venezuelans.
Making a deal with them means two or three
hundred kilos of cocaine per month.
You know how much that'll fetch in France?
Nine million.
Don't want to be in on this? Go then.
Free your father's buddy and beat it, bro.
Drop it.
You sure they want the old man?
No, I'm not sure.
They may be furious
I'm leveraging him for a meeting.
So?
So what? Isn't the money worth it?
[darkly intriguing music playing]
No!
[darkly intriguing music continues]
[in Spanish] The package!
Who is Milord?
[in English] Get on.
[darkly intriguing music continues]
[darkly intriguing music building]
[music fading into background]
[in Spanish] A kid.
Are you kidding me?
[man] No, he's really special.
[in English] So you wanted
to meet me then, Milord?
I don't even know you
and you got me a gift?
You brought me a snitch?
You thought you'd apply force
to have the upper hand?
No force here.
I'm offering.
[woman] So you're offering?
[muffled screaming in background]
[muffled screaming continues]
You know, meeting me
means you'll soon be killed.
You know that?
Do you want to die?
No.
I also have a present for you.
[Kylian shudders]
Oh fuck!
[woman] Thanks to you,
he'll never talk again.
[box clatters]
You don't like it?
Pull your pants down.
What?
Pull your pants down, I want to see
if you got a pussy or a dick.
No pussy here.
I want it verified.
You moan and whine like a bitch.
Pants down.
Show me yours, I'll show you mine.
You're how old?
I'm sixteen.
[in Spanish] Sixteen?
[in English] I demand more than half a ton
per month or I don't move my men.
Can you handle that?
Yes.
Don't fuck me over or I'll slaughter
both you and your family.
We'll start off with a small job
and see how you manage.
Marco will come in a few days to see you
and he'll tell you how we'll proceed.
[in Spanish] Kiddo!
[in English] You forgot something.
["RCDDAB" by Walton & Kalash playing]
[in Spanish] Come on!
EMERGENCY
- [in English] Let's go.
- ["RCDDAB" continues playing]
Go on, boss.
They'll take care of you here.
[insects chirping softly]
[man yelling in distance] You dirty whore!
I'm gonna put a tire around your neck
and set it on fire, woman!
[whimpering]
[man loudly] I'm gonna make you
a pretty necklace, Anna bitch!
- [objects banging]
- No one will want to look at you anymore!
I've come to destroy your face, Annabelle!
I don't need Mama's forgiveness anymore.
And she's no longer here to protect you.
You filthy two-faced bitch!
Just wait, you'll pay for this!
Fuck you, you lying shit!
- Dark is here, he wants to kill me.
- What?
- He'll break in, we have to leave.
- [door banging]
- [Ambre] Oh, hell no.
- [Nat continues in background]
[Nat yelling] You filthy two-faced bitch,
you'll pay for this!
Your life is gonna turn to shit too,
Annabelle! Just what you deserve!
You're good for nothing
except sucking dick!
- [door opens]
- Get lost!
- Or what?
- Or I'mma whoop your ass!
[scoffs]
Nervous? You want some help?
Nat, you're plastered. Get outta here.
No, this is my home.
Well, well, well.
- Just look what we got here.
- [lighter flicks]
- Get lost!
- [Nat grunts]
Stop!
Ahh!
- Stop it you dirty, Judas! Leave me alone!
- Don't ever come back.
JUVENILE JUDGE'S OFFICE
[judge] Good morning.
- You'll have to share the chairs.
- [Ambre] No problem.
Thanks.
What are you doing here?
Well… [clears throat]
To begin, I'm sorry for your loss.
I wanted to first have a conversation
with just Cassandra,
Léo, Thaïs, Nolan, Mathis,
because they're primarily
affected by this procedure.
You may have realized that,
after several concerning reports,
I requested a child welfare investigation.
Today, our goal is to determine whether
some of the children will be relocated
for a provisional period to
your Aunt Régine, who's stepped forward.
- Did you? Of course you did.
- Not surprising she volunteered.
- [judge] Please, quiet down! Shh!
- [all arguing loudly]
Marvin, Kingsley, Annabelle, being of age,
what are your opinions and thoughts?
- Marvin?
- We want to stay together.
What do you mean, "together"?
What solutions do you propose?
Because it seems that Cassandra's bearing
all of the daily responsibilities alone
and she's only 14.
We're trying to get organized.
I need more information.
Well, I'm at home when possible.
Marv and Ambre too.
We manage. Everyone is fed well.
We laugh, we cry sometimes.
We're pulling through.
Léo regularly misses school.
I'm not sure if you knew.
Kylian as well.
Well, it's been difficult lately.
It's been… a shock.
Right. Understood. I agree.
Annabelle?
Yes, I agree.
Annabelle, you, um…
you're enrolled
in a baking program, right?
Right. Well…
I'm taking a small break at the moment
because of how hard
our loss has been for us.
Well, look, the problem is that if
you all stop working and going to school,
there's no viable path forward.
- The gas stove, was that replaced?
- We're working on it.
[judge] All right. Hmm.
- It's been leaking for a while.
- It's been years since we've seen you.
I spoke with your Mama often.
- [scoffs] Okay, then, Auntie.
- [Marvin laughs] This never ends.
[judge] Marvin, do you have
any alternative or credible solution
in lieu of placement
with your Aunt Régine,
who can prove that she has no other kids
and a double income as well?
- Well, for now, uh…
- [Kingsley clicks tongue]
What are your resources,
financial and tangible,
to support both minors
and grown-ups among you?
Without, evidently,
skipping school or finding mischief?
What mischief?
No, we don't
go seeking mischief ever, judge.
Well, that's good.
Because, let me tell you,
that would be inadmissible.
"Inadmissible."
[judge] So you have no resources?
We'll have some soon.
Well, I'm listening, what are they?
I don't know,
maybe we'll reopen the stand Mama had.
We'll figure out something.
You will, I'm sure.
It's temporary.
Just for now.
It's best for everyone.
[wistful music paying]
All right, listen.
You'll be back here before you know it.
But you must make a promise to King.
Act up and torment
dear Auntie and Uncle, all right?
What?
Right.
Wreak havoc, have fun.
- It's open bar for you, okay?
- Mmm-hmm.
Never clean up your room. Pee in the sink.
[both laughing]
Oh, and don't forget,
fight with your cereal at breakfast.
And your vegetables at dinner, all right?
Later, alligators.
I'll see you very soon, okay? Take care.
- Take care.
- [wistful music continues]
[somber music playing]
[Kingsley] I'm right,
you bunch of assholes.
They'll be back in no time. You'll see.
They won't know what hit them.
Because apparently, "Mr. Isn't Wrong."
[clicks tongue]
Just wait, you'll see.
Seriously.
Just wait.
Who will transport all this?
Gotta ask around.
Oh.
- Can you see anything?
- Mmm-mmm.
No.
That'll go through customs?
Check this out.
On X-ray, you can't see jack shit.
Now, I'll pack some rotten pineapples.
Those dogs won't smell a thing.
I'll be the mule then.
Really?
Yeah, I want out this place.
- [customers chatting indistinctly]
- [keyboard clacking]
[clerk] You booked
an extra checked bag, correct?
That'll be a total of a hundred.
Oh no. It should've been paid already.
Right, apologies.
Please go ahead
and place your first luggage here.
[woman on PA] Attention, please.
Passengers on flight number 617
departing at 1:50 p.m.,
you are requested
to proceed to boarding at gate four.
[machine beeps]
[woman on PA] Again,
passengers on flight number 617,
please proceed to gate number four
at 1:50 p.m. for immediate boarding.
[machine beeps]
[clerk] The second baggage.
[tense music playing]
[heart beating]
[tense music continues]
[upbeat music playing on stereo]
[indistinct chatter]
[Lily] Now we flip the first card.
One, two, three.
[kid] I'm gonna win.
[man] Tell him
we need to do some road work
and the road will be closed for two days.
[woman] Will two days be okay?
With what he owes me, it'll be fine.
You'll see soon.
I've hired his son over at Ducreux.
- [dog grunts]
- [scoffs] Scram, you shit!
[dog whines]
Get your filthy paws off me! Get lost!
- [grunts]
- [dog whines]
- Get lost!
- [kid] Here, boy. Here, boy.
- Get him out of here!
- Oh no.
[kid scoffs]
Come on, let's go, boy.
Come here, boy.
Stay here.
Here, Alex.
Take some red snapper if you want.
Don't tell Damien. Keep it simple.
[woman] Okay.
- [grunts] You want to play, you fucker?
- [dog whining]
[kid] No!
- [Alex] Son of a bitch!
- [woman] What are you doing? Let him go!
- Let go of him!
- Stop!
Enough, Alex! Alex, Stop!
- You'll kill him, stop that, Uncle!
- Mama!
- [kid] Mama!
- [both] Alex!
Alex, stop!
Try and stop me. [straining]
[upbeat music continues on stereo]
We'll get them back.
That's a promise.
Do you trust King's plan at all?
No. I don't believe it'll succeed.
We have other options.
You think so?
King's plan isn't good, but maybe…
imagine the plan executed better.
How so, better?
Nice and neat, fine-tuned.
Not overly ambitious.
Discreet.
We do it once, properly,
planned well, but then we stop.
Rest in peace,
Marilyn Lafleur and Dylan Lafleur.
They were both murdered,
dug up, then ripped apart again…
by their brother and by their son.
Yeah.
Just leave it alone.
That's not you.
That'll never be you.
[bittersweet music playing]
[Ambre singing somber rap song]
Here you are, sir.
SOLD
[somber rap song continues]
FOR THE CHILDREN OF MARILYN LAFLEUR,
THE HEALER WHO SAVED MY LIFE
[somber rap song continues]
MARGOT
You have my number. Now what?
[somber rap song continues]
PEACE
[somber song fading]
- Jocelyn?
- Your father has a message for you.
- He wants 50% percent of your profits.
- Screw him!
[Kylian groans]
An anonymous letter for the judge.
Bye-bye, little brothers and sisters.
Forget ever seeing them again.
Dirty money, the grown kids
sent to Ducos prison, no more family.
He wants 50%.
- 50%!
- ["DIX" by Evil P playing]
I shot that asshole in his face.
Boom! In his mouth! For real.
I ride for my fam, understood?
I'm armed! So don't fuck around, fuckers.
We're inadmissible.
- [imitating gun firing]
- ["DIX" by Evil P continues playing]
IN MEMORY OF MIREILLE SAINTE-ROSE
["DIX" by Evil P continues playing]