Previously on Seducing Drake Palma
Daddy...
Mommy...
Someone hurt your princess.
Hey, Drake.
You’re only my boyfriend
in front of Sheen and Kei!
Just in front of them!
You think I like you?
Keep dreaming. You’re ugly.
Drake actually said that?
Drake has guts!
Sorry. It was a juicy gossip.
You needed to know because
we’re partners in crime, right?
Aren’t you curious
why they were holding hands?
So what if there’s something
between her and Drake?
Oh my god, oh my god!
Ahh!
Oh my god, Lord!
What the heck!
That’s scary.
Ahh!
There it is, there it is!
Ah!
Who’s there?
Who is it?
Ahh!
Come on, Alys!
Your face, bestie! I can't—!
You think that’s funny?
Bestie, your room is insane!
It’s bright outside,
but it’s pitch dark in here.
And look at your decorations,
it’s giving cult vibes!
You really haven’t changed.
Ahh!
What is this?
Don’t throw it!
Wait, why are you here?
What?
You’re so dramatic.
This better be good gossip, okay?
Spill it!
Bestie!
I saw Drake kissing Aunt Katrina.
What?
For real? Seriously?
Is that true?
Yes! I saw them last night.
I knew it.
Katrina is really
a cradle snatcher!
I don’t think so, Bestie.
Aunt Katrina seems young,
she looks in her twenties.
And she’s so gorgeous, right?
And she’s really nice, too.
I wouldn’t be surprised
if Drake likes her.
Ew!
Okay, fine.
She’s pretty...
She seems sweet.
But bestie,
she’s Uncle Steve’s fiancée!
And I don’t care if
she’s just in her twenties.
All I know is she’s a two-timer!
And that’s not acceptable, bestie!
And it’s a father and son combination?
It’s disgusting, bestie!
That’s really gross!
[retches]
Why are you affected?
Well, what can we do?
Can you do anything?
I can do something.
Just wait and see,
Alys Zyril Perez.
I love you, Drake Palma!
What’s happening?
What happened to you?
We’re going to be late.
I went ahead because
you took so long in the shower.
Bestie, I barely got any sleep.
Your voodoo dolls
were watching me all night.
Are you blaming them?
Be honest with me.
You barely slept because
of the voodoo dolls,
or you dreamt about...
Aya!
If I know, this is the only thing
you think about.
Ma’am?
Uh, Sir!
Sorry, Sir!
- What the heck, Alys?
- Whatever!
- You’re so irritating!
Good afternoon, everyone!
I am Miss Sabalero,
and I am your new
Entrepreneurship teacher.
Our first project
for the school year
will be a business case report.
I want you to group into three’s,
and your groupings will be
until at the end of first quarter.
Are we good?
Yes, ma’am!
Okay, class.
You may now group yourselves.
Psst, psst.
Let’s be partners.
What else is new?
We’re going to collect another F.
Are you forced?
Do you have a choice?
Don’t worry, bestie.
We’re going to pass.
Really? Can I rely on you?
It’s not me, bestie.
Him.
Aya, seriously?
Don’t be dramatic!
I heard Drake
gets straight A’s.
We’ll definitely get an A.
So, are you game?
Okay, fine!
Yes!
Gabriella Pineda.
Alys Zyril Perez.
- Drake –
- Wait!
We haven’t told him yet.
You think it’s okay with him to join us?
Okay, hold on.
Psst!
Hey. We’re group mates, okay?
He looks mad.
You’re wrong, bestie.
Silence means yes!
He agreed to be in our group.
Touch-move!
I already submitted it.
You can’t take it back, I have the key.
It’s so early,
and I’m already haggard.
And Aya won’t stop bugging me.
Why does dismissal take forever?
Here’s what you asked for.
Oh my god.
Sorry for the delay.
I didn’t understand what you said.
I’m sorry your messages
are confusing.
Is it my fault?
Sorry!
I’m just kidding!
Stop saying “sorry” all the time!
Say “sorry” when
you’re doing something wrong.
- Okay, sor–
- Ah!
Mmm... mmm...
I mean, do you need anything else?
Yes, all good.
By the way, what did you
say to the student council adviser?
I said…
I needed help with the
acquaintance party program.
Nice!
Thanks, CB!
Let’s do this again sometime.
What does “CB” mean?
“Cry baby.”
You’re always crying, right?
Sorry.
I said stop saying sorry!
Sorry— Oh!
Okay, fine!
Thank you!
High five!
- High five?
- High five.
What are they talking about?
They never talk without me.
And they’re doing high five?
Aya!
Settle down, everyone!
We’re about to start!
Sit down, guys!
Did you talk to Sheen?
Huh?
When?
Ma’am, this is from the
year level coordinator.
Mr. Palma, and Ms. Perez.
Yes, Ma’am?
Please go to the
student council room.
What are you planning?
Go ahead, you’re excused.
Okay, Ma’am.
And for the rest of you,
we will have a pop quiz!
Wow, my karma came quick.
What are we doing here again?
We didn’t get any instructions.
I knew it,
I’m talking to nobody.
He’s unbelievable.
He can sleep anywhere.
I’m leaving.
Hey.
Are you okay?
You look like you’re
having a nightmare.
You’re sweating.
But the air from the air con is strong.
Hey, are you okay?
Are you still alive?
Oh, you’re burning up.
Drake, you have a fever.
Hey.
Can you make it to the clinic?
Drake!
You’re burning up.
Great, he made me his nanny.
But I feel sorry for him.
He’s really sick.
He can’t get up.
Oh no!
You’re sweating--
It’s okay.
You’ll be okay.
What if he gets pneumonia?
But my Mom says,
prevention is better than cure.
That’s right.
You just don’t want his
condition to get worse, okay?
Let’s go, Alys. You can do it.
You’re not a pervert.
You’re just a concerned citizen.
Ahh!
Uh...
Oh!
Are you okay now?
How are you feeling?
Bestie, time to go home!
Thanks.
What happened, bestie?
You’ve been hanging around
here too long.
You planned this,
didn’t you?
Of course not!
Am I part of the student council?
I only realized now
how nice their room is.
Fancy.
Cool.
Let’s go home, bestie!
That weirdo actually
knows how to say thank you.
Bestie, let’s go.
Good morning, sunshine!
Good morning!
Aya!
It’s Saturday, and you’re
already being annoying!
Get up, Alys,
let’s seize the day!
What do you want?
We’re going out. Hurry!
We didn’t plan anything.
Exactly! But now, we do.
Wherever it is, I’m not going.
Alys, I already told
Uncle Steve we’re going!
What?
Aya, what did you do?
I told him we’re having lunch with them
because of our group project!
What group project?
The business case report.
It’s better to be early
than being hardworking, right?
We should brainstorm now
for our business case report.
My parents won’t allow it.
It’s weekend today.
Family day.
Alys, you know how much
your parents love me, right?
I already asked for their permission.
I have nothing to wear.
It’s laundry day.
Alys, come on!
Your mom got your outfit ready.
Aya!
Alys, seriously!
You’re so annoying, Aya!
Should I start screaming now?
You’re so annoying!
No! Don’t! Stop screaming!
- Okay, fine!
- Ugh, Aya!
- Come on already!
- Aya, seriously!
We’re already here!
Thank you!
Aya, Alys!
- Good morning!
Just wait here.
Drake is still sleeping.
I’ll just wake him up.
He doesn’t want to get up.
It’s Saturday today.
Alys was also like that earlier.
- Hey! Aya, seriously!
- It’s true!
You’re really a
perfect match for my son.
- Come in, feel at home!
- Is it not true?
Okay, thank you!
- Hello!
- Hello, Aunt Katrina.
Sorry for disturbing
you on a Saturday.
This is for our school work.
Of course!
Does Aki know you’re here?
Who?
Sorry, I mean Drake.
I’m just used to
calling him Aki.
Okay.
Alys, Aya...
Drake’s just taking a shower.
He’s making himself handsome.
You know, his girlfriend’s here.
Yieee!
Don’t be shy, Alys.
Uncle Steve totally accepts you!
Right, Uncle?
Of course! I consider her now
as my daughter-in-law!
Right, Katrina?
She even introduced herself
as Alys Perez soon-to-be Palma!
Is Aunt Katrina jealous of me?
The stunning woman?
Well, I can be fierce, too.
Alys.
- Hey!
- Ouch.
Uncle Steve is
asking you something!
Oh, sorry.
What was it again?
He asked how you and
your Drakey baby met.
Ah…
Well, he transferred
to our school,
and became my classmate.
That’s it.
How about you two?
How did you and
Aunt Katrina meet?
We met at school.
You were classmates before?
Oh, no. She used to
teach at Drake’s school.
She just started teaching then.
I was still trying to move on
when Drake’s mom died.
It’s a long story.
But Katrina helped
me to move on.
Now, we’re getting
married in October.
Oh my goodness!
Oh, your boyfriend’s here!
Aren’t you two
going to kiss, or hug?
No “hi”, or “hello”?
Aren’t you happy
to see each other?
Hi.
They’re still shy, Uncle.
- Because there’s an audience!
- Aya!
Alright, I’ll get back to work.
Hon, can you get the
papers I need to sign?
Sure, hon, I’ll bring
them to your office.
Alright.
Come on, let’s go meet Drake.
Thanks, hon!
By the way, you can do your
business case report in Drake’s room.
Dad!
Oh, wow. It’s unbelievable,
he can talk.
Well, your room is clean, right?
You are okay working
in Drake’s room, right?
Of course, Uncle!
We’re okay with it. Right?
- Uh...
- [scoffs]
Go ahead and get started!
Okay, Uncle!
Go, go.
Wait up!
Hey!
Hurry! Go after him!
- Hurry!
- Ouch!
Wait! I might fall!
Take it easy.
This weirdo is so spoiled.
His room’s practically complete—
he has everything.
What more could you ask for?
But why does it still
feel so flat and boring?
I wouldn’t be surprised if
his personality feels the same.
Because with all this stuff,
his world looks
cold and lonely.
Thank you, Drake!
What is this?
What’s inside this?
Drake, can I borrow your laptop?
Hey, did you ask for his permission?
I already did.
Did he answer?
He didn’t, right?
You know what you
need to learn?
How to decipher Drake Palma 101.
Lesson one:
if you ask and he doesn’t
answer, that means yes!
If he doesn’t want to,
he would’ve taken the laptop
right away.
Oh my, don’t tell me
you like Drake?
Are you crazy?
Dream on.
What’s that?
Is that for real?
Shh! Keep it down!
Your snacks are
ready downstairs.
Aya, can you help me
bring them up here?
Help him, hurry!
Okay, Uncle.
I’ll be right there.
- Come back right away.
- Yes!
Where’s Aya?
I told her to hurry up.
Aya!
What are you up to now?
Look at this one,
he’s just sleeping.
Was he able to read all of these?
Probably yes.
Because he’s smart.
Hey, this looks good!
Maybe we can use this for
our business case report.
Ow!
What’s that noise?
Great. They finally went home.
Ouch!
Sorry for the mess.
I’ll clean it up.
Come here.
Hey! What are you doing?
[scoffs]
Here.
Don’t move, troublemaker.
It will sting.
Okay?
He’s so close!
What do I do?
Just close your eyes, Alys.
Right, close your eyes.
Then what?
I can’t close my eyes
the whole day.
Lord, what have I
gotten myself into?
Oh no, is that my heartbeat?
Hey, keep it down.
Ouch! Let me do it!
- It’s time to eat.
- Oh!
Give me that!
Whatever, Aya!
Good thing you
finally met your match.
I think you and Alys
look good together.
But I want you.
Aki, no.
I’m about to marry your dad.
Then why are you
still here with me?
Like right now.
We always talk in the wee hours.
When everyone’s asleep.
Doesn’t it mean anything to you?
Kat, be with me.
Cut the engagement.
Drake, you don’t understand.
Sorry, Mom.
I’m doing this all for you.
Good morning, bestie!
Did you have fun yesterday?
Alys, one. Katrina, zero!
Oh my god!
What’s happening? Oh my god!
No way!
Erase, erase! No!
Where are you, bestie?
I really want to go home!
Should I wait for you?
I’ve been here for a while now.
What’s taking you so long?
Come on, Aya.
Ah!
Troublemaker.
You okay?
Did your knees get hurt?
Don’t move.
Hop on.
Huh?
Your house is nearby, right?
Show me the way,
I’ll walk you home.
Thank you.
Dela Cruz, Lance Miguel.
De Joya, Albert.
Alys Zyril Perez.
I knew it, we’re soulmates.
Can you believe it, bestie?
We both got F’s!
You’re crazy.
We both failed and
you’re happy about it.
- Go, sit down!
- Fine!
Okay, listen up!
By the looks of it,
some of you will need
to take tutorial sessions.
And it will begin tomorrow.
You better tell your
parents about this.
Those who received F’s
will take the said classes.
while those who received
A’s will be the tutors.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir!
I will be posting the
pairings later this afternoon.
What’s all the commotion about?
Let’s go, bestie. Let’s check the list.
I’m so excited.
Since when do tutorial lessons
become exciting, bestie?
Let’s go!
Wait! Just wait!
- Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Would you look at that?
Drake’s your tutor.
You’re really meant to be!
Nice! I don’t need to
be a matchmaker anymore!
Why is Sheen my loves
your tutor?
Oh, CB’s my tutor!
What is CB?
Cry baby.
Because he’s
always crying over Kei.
He’s acting like they’re married.
Excuse me!
Hey, you! Don’t mess
with Sheen my loves!
I can’t promise that, bestie!
You’re really something!
What’s your problem?
Do you want me to whack you? Let’s go!
I don’t want that Drake Palma
to call me dumb.
I’m actually nice, okay?
I’m still at the Demographics part
and I already feel like crying!
Oh, that was a good dinner.
Well, someone’s busy studying!
I have to.
I’m part of the
tutorial program.
Wow, so proud of you, princess!
So, who’s the lucky student?
I’m the student.
Sorry, Mom. Sorry, Dad.
You know what?
Just think of it this way—
through the tutorial lessons,
at least you’re reviewing early
for college entrance exams, right?
Well, Alys,
you know the dream, right?
You need to get into
St. Collete Academy. Yes?
Yes, Mom.
Just focus. We know
you can do it, okay?
Okay, Mom. Thanks.
Alright. Just study well,
study hard.
I’ll leave you be.
I’ll go ahead, okay?
- Thanks, mom. Good night.
- Good night!
Love you!
You got this, sweetheart.
Good night.
Thanks, Dad.
You can do it.
So, what did your mom say?
Of course, she got mad.
She asked why I’m always
part of the tutorial program.
I told her, just think
of it as free tutorial.
It saves money, right?
Makes sense!
- Yeah, true.
- I’m clever, huh?
- You’re totally insane.
- Right?
Look who’s here!
Boring!
You’re not the stars
of Mean Girls,
so drop the attitude.
Whatever, Miss Whoever You Are.
My name is Aya.
[laughing]
Losers.
- You’re cheap.
- Losers!
- Let’s go, girls.
- Yeah, go.
What a waste of time.
Ahem!
By the way,
don’t you dare seduce Drake
during your tutorials, okay?
Excuse me.
Why would I have to
seduce Drake Palma?
He’s already my boyfriend.
- Wow!
- Boyfriend?
Boyfriend?
You think I’d believe that?
I’m not dumb, okay?
Right!
He’s my partner for
the acquaintance party!
Partner?
[girls laughing]
Okay then, Miss Pathetic.
Show us.
Bye!
I’m so proud of you, bestie!
But how are you going to
tell your boyfriend about it?
Let’s go, Alys!
You can do this!
You can do it!
You can do it! Let’s go!
Um...
Drake…
You know...
About the....
Acquaintance party.
Um...
No.
Huh?
No? As in?
No, as in I won’t
go to that party!
Ah!
Ouch.
That hurts.
It hurts being rejected
by your crush.
Crush?
I have a crush on Drake Palma?
Oh no!
Shhh!
This can’t be happening!
But seriously…
do I have a crush
on that weirdo?
Thank you, Sir! Bye!
What are you doing here?
What else?
I’m stressed at home.
My mom keeps on asking
about the color of Kei’s dress,
so she can buy me
a matching tie.
That’s it?
You should’ve just called me!
We’re not even partners.
She doesn’t want to.
Sheen…
What about you?
Do you have a partner?
As if.
I don’t have one.
What if we go together?
I mean… we’re best friends, right?
You don’t want to?
Crazy! Of course I do!
Are you serious?
We’re partners now?
It’s a date.
It’s a date!
- You want to practice?
- Sure.
- Let’s try it out.
- Alright, let’s go.
I think I’ll go with
this pink one, Mom.
Perfect! That’s actually the
one I was hoping you’d pick.
I think it will
look best on you!
So, final answer?
- Yes, Mom, final answer.
- Great!
Okay, I’ll let my team
work on this one.
By the way, do you have
a partner for the party?
I don’t need to know the name.
I just thought it would be cute
if he’ll match your outfit, right?
Okay, I’ll work on this one tonight.
You get some rest now.
Good night, my dear!
Good night, mom. Thank you.
Hello?
What did you pick?
The one I showed you!
Nice! Good choice!
Wow, for the first time,
you’re supportive, bestie.
But guess what?
I have better news for you.
What?
Guess who my partner is!
You got Drake to go with you?
Who cares about Drake!
He can do whatever he wants.
Sheen my loves is my partner!
What? CB?
Yup!
As they say, good things
come to those who wait!
Hello?
Aya, you there?
Ugh!
Presenting, my not so baby
girl anymore– Alys Zyril Perez!
You look amazing, princess.
Thank you, Dad!
Thank you, Mom!
I’m so excited!
You guys are the best!
Are you ready, baby?
Yes! I’m so excited!
Are you okay, baby?
Yes, mom. Of course!
Have you heard from Sheen yet?
I think he’s just
stuck in traffic, Dad.
Can I wait outside?
So I can see him
when he gets here.
Yeah, it’s okay.
No problem.
Let me know if you
need anything, princess.
Thanks, Dad. Thanks, Mom.
Am I dreaming?
Hey.
Let’s go.
Ouch! Let me do it!
Is that her heartbeat?
- It’s time to eat!
- Oh!
Give me that!
Or mine?
On the next episode of
Seducing Drake Palma
My date’s so
handsome tonight, right?
What can you say, Kei?
You ditched me!
Aya said you were
going with Drake.
So I went with her instead!
Drake!
Maybe you just forced
him to go with you.
Drake, everyone’s staring at us.
Don’t mind them.
But–
I can hear the jealousy in your
voice because Drake is my partner.
I'm the queen of the night.