(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(Lee Hee Jun, Park Hae Soo)
(Kwak Sun Young)
(Song Geon Hee, Suh Ji Hye)
(Yoo Seung Mok, Bek Hyun Jin)
(Heo Jeong Do, Jung Moon Sung)
(Scarecrow)
(This program was supported by the MSIT and KCA.)
(The characters, locations, institutions, groups...)
(in this drama are a work of fiction.)
(Child actors and animals featured...)
(were filmed safely with expert supervision.)
In return,
you have to tell me your story too.
It's no fun if I do all the talking.
You tell your story, and I'll tell mine.
Let's complete our story together.
"Our story..."
Yes. Us.
First, tell me about the person you said you hated the most.
When you first met and why you grew to hate him.
Come on, hurry.
You didn't hate him from the start, did you?
In my experience,
a feeling like hatred doesn't just come out of nowhere.
For it to build up, there needs to be a foundation.
Something like friendship or love.
Only when those feelings are crushed is hatred born. That's what I mean.
(Scarecrow)
(Episode 4)
It was definitely strangulation.
But something about this is off.
What do you mean, sir?
What's different from the others...
is the chest.
It was slashed to pieces with a razor blade.
This is a first.
Was that done while she was still alive?
Yes.
We found this inside the body.
Her private parts were stuffed with this.
What is that?
What's this?
It's a bribe.
(Operating Room)
Just drop it and go.
This isn't your case anymore.
Cha Si Yeong.
Si Yeong.
I've got to catch that son of a gun.
Let's catch him ourselves.
"Ourselves?"
Yes.
Ourselves.
Will you be a friend with me?
I hear you're a good student. Me too.
We should be friends.
I don't need friends.
Then what about money?
Will you tutor me?
I'll pay you.
I can't pronounce it.
It's "pi." Let me see.
Go on, solve it. That's it! That's it.
Hey, you got it!
What?
You got it right!
You're a really good teacher. Even better than my math tutor.
That's because he is not good at teaching.
- I'm going to the bathroom. - The bathroom?
- Try to solve this one. - Okay, got it.
Here, try this.
This is delicious. Where'd you get this?
A friend gave it to me.
What a nice friend. Ask for more, okay?
All right.
Eat up.
- You're leaving? - Yes, I'm off.
Tae Joo.
Yes?
Hey, in the future,
let's go to the same college.
Sure.
Get home safe.
Right.
Gosh. I forgot this.
I guess I'll just give it to him next time.
Why are you so late?
- Feed Sun Yeong. She's whining. - Mom.
Can I go to college?
Sure. As long as you pay your own way.
Si Yeong.
- You got something on you. - Don't touch me.
You're filthy.
What's wrong?
Why didn't you tell me?
That your mom's a bar hostess.
You want me to tell everyone...
what you really are?
Everyone else deserves to know.
Please, don't tell them.
I'm begging you.
Then will you do whatever I say?
Yes.
No matter what.
Anything.
(Bang Gyeong Mun Clinic)
Si Yeong.
Let's catch him ourselves.
"Ourselves?"
He said "ourselves."
I like the sound of that.
Let's do it.
("Police Let Suspect Slip Through Their Fingers")
Take a look at this.
Apparently, this is what the serial killer looks like.
We haven't even seen a single hair on his head.
- Does this make any sense? - We did find his hair.
And we even got his blood type from it.
And you're proud you found his blood type? Big deal.
We're looking into ex-cons with similar priors,
- so we'll catch him soon, right? - Darn it.
What did we find this time?
What did you find?
Nothing significant, sir. A strand of hair, body hair,
and the blood from the clothes are all Type B.
Chief Kim, you got a problem with me?
- I said, do you have a problem? - No, sir.
It doesn't look that way to me. Spit it out.
Sir.
About Kang Tae Joo's resignation, could you hold off on accepting it?
Jeon Kyung Ho's medical report was fabricated, and...
How can you say that after seeing this article?
Who let him get away? Kang Tae Joo! That's who!
Yes, Chief Heo, Kangseong Police.
Yes.
One moment, please. Sir.
Hello?
Who's this?
Yes. This is Park Eun Gyu, Chief of Police at Kangseong.
Yes, Commissioner. Go ahead.
Pardon? Kang Tae Joo, you said?
No, that can't be right.
His resignation hasn't even been processed yet.
Heard you're back. How?
Maybe the chief's just been too busy with official business?
Apparently, my resignation hasn't been processed yet.
Is that possible?
- Hey! - Gosh!
Hurt? Follow me.
Hey, what the hell is going on? Tell me everything.
You're short-staffed anyway, so just take it as a win.
That's not the point, you fool. For a mere sergeant's resignation,
- why involve a commissioner? - A commissioner?
What?
- You're just hearing this now? - Well...
What's the commissioner's name?
Cha Jun Young. Commissioner Cha. How do you not know him?
He's the youngest commissioner ever. He's assigned to the Blue House.
He's a serious heavyweight.
A commissioner...
That's incredible.
Hey. Seriously, he's not your connection?
Let's just say he is. You're not entirely wrong.
What is he talking about?
A commissioner getting involved over one darn sergeant? Pathetic.
My apologies.
This Kang Tae Joo, or whatever his name is,
he'd better be worth the trouble.
He will be.
And about the Kangseong Serial Murders.
Don't let anyone else handle it. You finish it yourself.
Your father is running for election. If you can't help,
at least don't be a liability. Am I wrong?
I'll take it to heart.
Good. Make sure you do.
I hear you're seeing Chairman Kim Tae Seob's daughter.
She's a really wonderful woman.
Come on.
You too? You want to get into politics?
Cha Si Yeong.
Don't try to run with the big dogs...
if you can't keep up.
I thought you'd know your place. Is that really so hard?
I just don't get it.
The list of Min Ji's belongings. You have it, right?
Not yet.
Her whereabouts on the incident day? Did you look into it?
Not on that either.
Then what the hell have you done?
You are the guy who quit and then came crawling back.
I don't think you're one to talk.
What's with that kid?
Has he lost his mind?
Park Dae Ho.
Outside. Now.
Rookie.
Just say you're sorry. Beg for forgiveness.
Beg for what? Since you've started it, go all in.
That son of a...
The kid's got guts.
He really does.
Eat up.
Tell me. Why are you pissed at me?
- I'm not. - Don't give me that.
What is it?
Honestly,
I was disappointed in you.
You just gave up so easily.
When you first got here,
I finally learned what to look for in a case,
how to approach a suspect.
I started to figure all that stuff out.
I wanted to learn more, I wanted to get better.
And I really wanted to catch the culprit with you.
And I just assumed you felt the same way.
- But then you just... - I just bailed on you.
But...
I didn't take quitting lightly.
It was an incredibly hard decision.
And...
coming back was even harder.
I...
had to give something up to come back.
- What did you give up? - You don't need to know about that.
The other day,
I saw Min Ji.
She told me not to quit.
She asked who would catch the killer then.
She told me to be the one to catch him.
Can't you stay on the police?
You have to be the one to catch him.
It's a bribe. Eat this, and please think it over two more times.
Promise. Bye!
So is that why you came back?
No.
It's just that if I don't catch that bastard now,
I don't think I can live with myself.
That's why I'm back.
So cut me some slack, will you?
It's not my place.
I'm sorry for complaining to you.
And I'm glad you're back.
Hey, this is actually really good. Eat up, man.
Okay.
(Dae Ho Chinese Restaurant)
(Holding the National Community Leaders Assembly)
(Kangseong County)
Hey, Detective Kang.
I'd almost forgotten your face. How many years has it been?
You haven't aged a day. You look exactly the same.
- Is your son out of the army yet? - He got out ages ago.
You are saying like you actually care about him.
Hey, what's with the bill? We had two bowls.
Why should you pay for my son's meal?
- Your son? Who's that? - Him.
This is my family's place, Dae Ho Chinese Restaurant.
You didn't know?
He's my junior, so I'm paying. Here you go, ma'am.
It was delicious. Thanks.
We're off.
Mom, I'm heading out.
Hey, wait up!
Look at him, so eager.
(Dae Ho Chinese Restaurant)
Hey, wait up!
("Exclusive: Photo of the Kangseong Serial Killer")
There might still be a way.
- What way? - I'll tell you...
when I'm sure.
I'm going to make sure you can catch the culprit, so just you wait.
That's harsh, Seo Ji Won.
("Police Let Killer Slip Through Their Fingers")
("Investigation at a Standstill")
("Local Residents' Frustration Grows")
Hey, don't get the wrong idea. I didn't write that article, okay?
I know well you lost the killer then because of me.
So why would I write that article? It makes no sense.
It had your byline.
The editor-in-chief changed it without even telling me.
Look, I'm not here to argue about that.
So just give me the photos.
Here you go.
By the way, why didn't you tell me you and Mr. Cha were classmates?
- It's not a big deal. - He wants to get to know you.
He must've sent me that audio file to help you, right?
- No cameras were on the scene. - Right.
I hid it partway through so the killer wouldn't notice.
- Why are you only telling me now? - What else was I supposed to do?
The police found nothing that day. You were backed into a corner.
Why tell you to find a camera the killer might've already taken?
This is that bastard?
Yes. It's blurry, but see this? He's covering his face.
But Kim Mi Yeon never said anything about that.
So he only covered his face in front of me?
Why?
This handkerchief looks familiar.
It's pretty unique, but...
it's not enough to identify the killer.
Fair enough.
You're requesting a leave of absence?
The kids will miss you so much.
- I feel awful. - Don't be. Rest up and get well.
Okay.
- I'll get my things later. - All right.
- Thank you. - Of course. Go on.
You've been so busy lately, haven't you?
At this rate, I'm going to forget what you look like.
I'm sorry. I should've been more attentive.
The cases just keep piling up.
I know it's because of your cases.
I'm not that unreasonable.
But still, a phone call just to check in...
You're right. I'll call you every day.
Maybe not every day...
Just whenever you think of me.
Then I guess I'll have to call every day.
Stop. You're making me blush.
You're such a tease.
Are you heading home?
I'll give you a ride.
I don't want you to go out of your way.
It's no trouble.
I just want to spend more time with you.
Oh my, Hui Jin.
- It's been a while. - Who's this?
Prosecutor Cha Si Yeong.
A prosecutor?
Gosh, I didn't know there was a prosecutor this handsome.
Girl, you really know how to pick the good man.
Thank you for the compliment.
So if you're a prosecutor, you have single colleagues, right?
- I do. - Then you should set me up!
I will.
Si Yeong is so busy these days, I doubt he has the time for that.
The Serial Murders, you know?
He's the prosecutor in charge.
- Still, if he has time... - Si Yeong, you're busy, right?
We should get going.
See you around.
I take it you two weren't very close.
Was it that obvious?
Extremely.
How embarrassing.
We were close in middle school,
but we just sort of drifted apart.
You just "sort of" drifted apart?
I found out...
her mom was a mistress.
So classless.
If I'd known sooner, I wouldn't have been her friend.
So, where did you park?
Actually, I'm sorry.
I completely forgot I have a meeting this afternoon.
I'm sorry, but I really have to get going.
You can get home on your own, right?
I'm really sorry.
Si Yeong.
What was that?
(Certificate of Merit, Cha Mu Jin)
(Plaque of commendation, Cha Mu Jin)
From now on, you'll be living here with your father and your brother.
What do you think?
A brother?
Si Yeong, you need to study hard just like your brother.
Okay?
- Mom. - Yes?
Who's that?
- Excuse me, sir. - Yes?
Take that down. Now.
- No, not that one. The picture. - Right.
Oh my gosh, are you okay?
Yes. Thank you.
Are you all right?
- I'm fine. - You're not hurt?
No.
- Thank you. - Are you sure?
Yes, I'm fine.
Wait, aren't you my brother's friend?
But are you really okay?
I should get you to a hospital, just in case.
No, really. I'm fine.
What?
I told you I'm fine.
Where is that lovely sound coming from?
It sounds like you're not so fine.
(Bread, Italian Bakery)
Here, have some.
You didn't have to get all this.
It sounded like quite the emergency.
A case of extreme hunger.
Gosh, this is so embarrassing.
To think I can still get hungry at a time like this...
It's a little pathetic.
"A time like this?"
I'm on leave from school.
Why is that?
Is it because of Jeon Kyung Ho?
I thought he quit.
It has nothing to do with that.
I just wanted to take a break.
I haven't made any specific plans yet.
Please don't say anything about this to my brother.
(Bread, Italian Bakery)
Sun Yeong.
You barely ate, so I had it packed. I added extra Castella.
You like Castella, don't you?
(Bread, Italian Bakery)
How did you know that?
Tae Joo always got lots of snacks to give to his little sister.
The guy who always let him bring the snacks.
So you remember.
You must have been a great friend to him.
Me?
It's not every day someone looks out for their friend's little sister.
You think so?
Let's go. I'll give you a ride home.
No, that's okay.
I'll just worry if I don't.
I'm not comfortable getting in a car alone with a man.
I'll enjoy this. Thank you.
- Then... - You go on ahead.
Take care.
You bastard.
What the hell? What are you doing? Who are you?
- What is your deal? - You hit Sun Yeong, didn't you?
Do you have any idea what you put Sun Yeong through?
I'm a victim here too. And I didn't mean to do it...
- You son of a gun... - I was wrong.
Please, forgive me. I'm begging you.
Sun Yeong is the one you should be apologising to.
You don't really know her, do you? That means you're being played too.
I saw her flirting with another guy with my own two eyes.
Shut up.
No, I'm telling you, she's a total slut!
She sleeps around with anyone and everyone.
- Shut your mouth! - What the?
Geez, get off me.
You son of a gun.
Die. Die, you son of a gun.
Die.
(Stockings are wrapped around her neck.)
He covered the face?
Why?
Sergeant Kang. You should see this.
This is...
Where did you find this?
We found it about 200m from the scene.
That's right.
This is Min Ji's.
It's a scarecrow.
Don't you think this is a sketch of the suspect?
- What did you leave behind? - My art tube.
My drawings are in there.
You're saying this was at the scene?
You remember these students, don't you?
Yes. This girl. She was here a couple of days ago.
- Is this what you wanted? - Yes. Thank you.
It's pretty late. You'll be okay getting home alone?
I'll be fine. The bus will get me home in no time.
Good night.
(Kangseong Bookstore)
Jeez, she should get home earlier. It's so dangerous these days.
It's starting to rain.
I can't just let her go.
I'll give her an umbrella...
- and go home. - Okay, sure.
(Umbrellas 50 Cents)
(Kangseong Bookstore)
Around what time was that?
It was right before closing, so a little before 8pm?
- When did he get home after that? - Gi Beom? He didn't come home.
What?
He does that a lot. He hangs out with friends and...
sometimes crashes at their place.
Gi Hwan, where is Gi Beom right now?
Hey, what's gotten into you?
- Hey. - Lee Gi Beom!
- Welcome. - Lee Gi Beom, come on out!
- Detective Kim. - Detective Kang.
What brings you here, Detective Kang?
This is our case.
What case is that?
You know Jeon Kyung Ho, right? The guy you had a run-in with.
Yes. What about that bastard?
He was assaulted and hospitalized. They say he's unconscious.
- Don't tell me the suspect is... - That's right. Lee Gi Beom.
What? My brother, Gi Beom?
So, where is Lee Gi Beom now?
Gi Beom...
- Let's step outside and talk. - But...
- Go back inside. I'll call you. - But...
So let me get this straight.
Our main murder witness is their assault suspect?
Yes. And it seems he's on the run.
Jeon Kyung Ho again? Seriously?
Isn't he just putting on a show? He's a pro at faking his records.
They're saying he's unconscious. This isn't like with Detective Kang.
I need to step out for a moment.
Where's the fire? Where are you off to again?
You have a visitor.
- You can all head home for the day. - Yes, sir.
Min Ji's last stop before her murder was that bookstore?
Kim Min Ji and Lee Gi Beom could've been together.
We need a statement from Gi Beom.
About that,
I hope we can close Jeon Kyung Ho's case with a settlement.
Like you said, the victim has to press charges.
I need you to smooth things over with Jeon Kyung Ho's side.
Think you can do it?
You want his charges dropped so we can have him all to ourselves?
Okay.
I'll take care of Jeon Kyung Ho's side. You go find Lee Gi Beom.
See?
It's easier when we work together, isn't it?
You do your job, I do mine. Isn't it great?
Why me?
There are other capable detectives out there.
There are only a few people I trust.
You trust me?
How about you try trusting me for once?
I have to go. I have a lot to do.
Wait.
Don't you think you're overlooking something?
Based on everything you've said,
Lee Gi Beom sounds more like a suspect than a witness.
Or am I wrong?
Ji Won!
- Why so dramatic? What is it? - This is serious.
What is?
An attack put Jeon Kyung Ho in a coma.
What? Who did that?
They're saying Gi Beom did it.
Who?
- Attempted murder? - It's because...
There were signs of strangulation on his neck.
And his condition is quite bad.
What about the suspect? Is he in custody?
Not yet.
Sun Yeong!
Ji Won!
What are you doing here?
I was just dropping off some underwear for my brother.
Did you hear about Jeon Kyung Ho too?
He and I have bad blood, but I still feel bad about it.
To have that happen to him.
Don't let it get to you. It has nothing to do with you.
Still, they said it was attempted murder.
Do you think someone was really trying to kill him?
You don't think he would...
- What? - What?
I mean, it's not that easy to kill someone.
- Gosh. - Gosh, it's so hot!
- Geez. Way to be clumsy. - Gosh.
Did you get burned?
- I'm fine. - You should go. Take care.
- Yes, get home. - Okay.
- I'm going. - Bye.
Die.
Help! Somebody, please help!
Sun Yeong.
You...
There! Someone collapsed over there! Hurry!
No one will think to look for you here.
Don't do this, Sun Yeong.
You and I...
We're nothing to each other anymore.
Then why did you do it?
Why would you go that far for me? Why?
I'm going to turn myself in.
I'm the one who did this.
I'll take responsibility.
But what if they find out you were part of the protest?
They said the student president vanished without a trace.
But...
For now, just hide here,
and see how things unfold. All right?
Let's run away.
What are you talking about?
If you get caught now, you'd be framed for a murder attempt.
What?
You're finally awake.
Oh, dear.
What are you doing here?
I heard it's an eight-week recovery.
No. What a shame.
You reaped what you sowed.
Did you come here just to mock me?
That's harsh. I came because I was worried.
Anyway, why did you even go there?
What did you want with Kang Sun Yeong?
To tell her what a bastard you are.
It was you who told me to counter-sue Kang Sun Yeong for false claims.
And you spun it into an affair. It was all you, Cha Si Yeong.
And that woman, completely clueless, was acting all chummy with you.
How can you look her in the eye and smile? How?
What's it to you?
Huh?
Listen up.
As for this assault, you just had a bit of bad luck.
You just tripped and fell.
So drop the idea of pressing charges or anything of the sort.
Nod if you understand.
Why should I? So you can screw me over again?
Not a chance. My uncle is the county governor!
Right.
I can make that title of yours, "the governor's nephew," disappear.
You hear me?
Want me to have your precious uncle put in handcuffs for bribery?
Go on, ask him if you doubt me. Do you think I'm bluffing? Ask him.
Now. You need to give me an answer.
There you go.
Why are you doing this to me? What did I ever do to you?
I have nothing against you personally.
But it's a favour for a dear friend, so my hands are tied.
Your face got pretty banged up.
Take care of yourself. Quietly.
What else do you want? I said I would do whatever you say!
That...
That... No.
No. Darn it.
Let me ask you one more thing.
How did you know about my mother?
Was that also...
Cha Si Yeong?
This one...
- Gosh. - Thank you.
It's okay. It's fine.
The culprit's hanky and Sun Yeong's are the same?
How can that be?
See? He's covering his face.
But Kim Mi Yeon never said anything about that.
So he only covered his face in front of me? Why?
This handkerchief looks familiar.
No way.
(Local News Desk)
This can't be happening.
(Letter of Resignation)
I had no idea you were the commissioner's brother.
From now on, don't go through the commissioner.
If you need anything, just come to me directly.
I'm just a prosecutor. I can't do that.
- Then, I'll deliver this myself. - Of course.
- Is that all right? - Yes.
Go ahead and shred this.
Anyway, why did you even go there?
What did you want with Kang Sun Yeong?
(Jeon Kyung Ho)
To tell her what a bastard you are.
It was you who told me to counter-sue Kang Sun Yeong for false claims.
And you spun it into an affair. It was all you, Cha Si Yeong.
(Jeon Kyung Ho)
How did you know about my mother?
Was that also...
Cha Si Yeong?
Cha Si Yeong was the one who first...
brought up your family's background.
Now that I think about it,
it was all just bait.
(Kang Tae Joo: Son of a Bar Hostess)
Hey! Out of my way!
Hey, Kang Tae Joo!
Hey, I took care of that whole Jeon Kyung Ho thing.
He won't be bothering you anymore.
And I took care of your resignation letter too.
So now you can just focus on your investigation.
What? Is something wrong?
Why did you do it?
- What? - Why did you do that to my sister?
And what do you get out of it?
- It's a misunderstanding. - A misunderstanding?
Right. You won't believe anything I say, will you?
But I was just trying to help you in my own way.
That's bullshit.
Hey, Tae Joo.
Don't you trust me?
You know, that kind of hurts. After all the effort I'm making.
All right, then...
why did you do that to me back then?
- Back then? - Yes, back then.
I begged you.
I got beaten to a pulp,
and I grovelled. I did everything.
I begged you not to say that one thing. But...
why did you do it?
You can't answer, can you?
Because there was no reason.
It was just a game to you.
Does that even matter?
What?
It's all in the past.
- The past? - Tae Joo. The past is the past.
What's important is what we'll accomplish together from now on.
Why should we let something so trivial hold us back?
Look, I said I would treat you right from now on.
I'm trying to start over, so why must you always spoil things?
Tae Joo.
Come on, just give me a break.
I swear I'll do right by you. Okay?
Hey, Kang Tae Joo.
Why does it have to be...
now of all times?
Forget it? Who are you to tell me to forget?
You think I want to remember any of that?
Cha Si Yeong.
I'll make sure you never forget it either.
You're the one who messed with me.
Both then, and now.
Tae Joo.
I found the owner of the handkerchief.
Come on.
A handkerchief?
The owner?
This is Sun Yeong's?
- See the embroidery? - Yes.
Sun Yeong embroidered this herself.
The only person who'd have one just like it is Lee Gi Beom.
Hold on.
(Report)
You're thinking what I'm thinking, right?
No, that's crazy. There's no way.
No way. He is...
There's no way he'd do that.
Hey, you're here.
- Hi. - Hi.
By the way, Sun Yeong stopped by earlier.
She dropped off some underwear and socks.
You were talking about Jeon Kyung Ho with her.
Did you tell her first, Detective Park?
No, she already seemed to know.
- Sun Yeong knew about him? - Yes.
- How? - I just assumed you told her.
- Hey, Detective Park. - Yes?
Get every available officer right now.
- Search my house for Lee Gi Beom. - Yes, sir.
- Go on. Go, go! - Right.
- Hey. - Tae...
Tae Joo, I dropped Sun Yeong off. Let's go check on her.
(Police ID, Kang Tae Joo)
We can't take the intercity bus.
We have to find a way to get to Huisong Station first.
We'll catch a train from there.
Gi Beom.
Gi Beom, what are you doing?
Gi Beom, open this door!
Gi Beom! Gi Beom!
Gi Beom!
He must have gone to the bus stop.
Sun Yeong? Sun Yeong, are you okay?
Open your eyes. Come on, open your eyes.
Sun Yeong.
Sun Yeong, Sun...
Tae Joo, here.
Hey, what's with that outfit? Don't walk home alone at night.
Sun Yeong.
- Tae Joo! - Ji Won, you stay here.
- I'm going with you. - Others are arriving. Explain.
Sun Yeong!
Kang Sun Yeong!
Sun Yeong, please!
- Who's there? - It's me, Tae Joo.
Cha Si Yeong?
Was that a gunshot you?
Hey!
Hey, Sun Yeong! Sun Yeong!
- What happened? Hey, Sun Yeong! - Don't worry. I think she fainted.
- Hey, Sun Yeong! - He was after her.
Sun Yeong, wake up.
Sun Yeong!
Hey, Cha Si Yeong.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Cha Si Yeong.
Hey, hey! What's going on? Are you okay? Hey, Cha Si Yeong!
I...
I actually knew.
That you always packed snacks for your sister.
What are you talking about? Save your breath, you bastard.
Back then...
If you hadn't gone just to give her that,
- we would've been okay, right? - I said shut up, you bastard.
- Feed Sun Yeong. She's whining. - Mom.
Can I go to college?
Sure. As long as you pay your own way.
Father?
I...
I thought you...
I thought you were my father's son.
But...
I can't stand having brothers, you see.
Being friends is one thing, though.
- I'm dizzy. - Hey, darn it. What's happening?
Hey, come on. Snap out of it.
No. Hey, hey, you son of a gun. Snap out of it!
Please. Hey, snap out of it.
Hey, Cha Si Yeong.
It's good for your health and curing the diseases including...
The prices are very affordable.
- That's it. - That's right.
Yes, that's absolutely right.
Gotcha.
You son of a gun.
It's like...
Gosh. It is...
- What is it? - It's about...
(Quiet Please)
You can't come any further.
(Surgery In Progress)
(Restricted Area)
Si Yeong.
Please don't die.
(Operating Room)
Please.
Come on, just tell me. Okay?
You trusted him at one point, didn't you?
Never. Not even once.
Come on. Then how could you team up with a guy like that?
You're no fun.
I can tell you're lying.
Are you still in contact with him?
No.
Do you know how he's doing now?
I don't.
Another lie.
Gosh, you're not a very good liar, are you?
This is so one-sided.
This is your last chance, okay? No more lies.
Otherwise, you are not allowed to visit me.
Joining forces with your friend...
How was that a turning point in your life, Professor?
For the better?
Or for the worse?
For the worse.
I lost everything.
Lying again.
Wait, that's the truth.
Absolutely everything.
(Scarecrow)
- Sun Yeong, who was it? - Don't tell me you suspect Gi Beom.
- If it's not Lee Gi Beom, then who? - It's all just circumstantial.
You're still not convinced that Lee Gi Beom is the killer?
A murder case?
How many victims is that now? Is this town even safe?
Do your jobs right!
He escaped the scene and hid in Lee Ju Hee's house.
His movements and the timeline match up perfectly.
You still don't think Lee Gi Beom is the one? Even after this?
Are you telling me you suspect Gi Beom too?
Yes, Gi Beom is a suspect in the serial murders.
We have to find him, ma'am.