=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 21=
Your favorite cilantro.
I don't understand why
you'd like that taste.
It smells so good.
You don't like it?
Simu,
didn't we agree to live as mortals?
No spirit power.
Come on, eat.
Simu,
the 17 Prefectures have been restored,
and you're no longer the Sovereign.
In the future,
we'll settle here,
okay?
Okay.
A life like this
might not be so bad.
Duan Shunxi,
I like being with you.
Have some more.
Hot.
Come on, try it.
How is it?
You don't like it?
I even found this.
Celery leaves,
pine nut crisps,
sesame crisps, and rock sugar.
So delicious.
How can you not taste it?
Next time, I'll just...
Don't.
No next time.
Please spare me.
Eat the one you already bit
in your hand.
Eat it.
Is it good?
Are you mad?
You don't want to talk to me?
♪Spring comes; ice and snow thaw♪
Apologize.
But I did nothing wrong.
It took me all afternoon.
Honestly.
Can't you let me have this once?
Alright.
I won't force you to eat
something you don't want.
That's more like it.
♪Borrow mortal warmth♪
Let's go view the full moon
at Mid-Autumn.
In the Void, all spirits wail.
You've never truly admired
the full moon.
We're just making up like this?
So easily?
I'm very easy to appease.
♪With light, carefree words,
still shining bright♪
♪A pot of wine in fleeting dreams♪
♪A brief life dares seek eternity♪
The fruit sold quite well today.
My long walk was worth it.
♪Let me savor this fleeting joy♪
♪May I roam drunk in dreams
and never forget♪
♪Please ferry me once through this life♪
Don't you love going to war?
No fear of death?
Now, you deserve
all these wounds.
Thank you.
Hold me.
Foxy,
I won't let anything happen to you.
Do you hear me?
I was too selfish.
I kept you by my side
in the Mortal World.
It must have been painful.
I like staying by your side.
I like being with you.
These were my happiest days.
You were born
before I was.
You stayed the same,
while I'd grown old.
I only regret
that I couldn't
stay…
Simu, stop.
I won't
leave you on your own.
I won't leave you
all alone.
Foxy,
it's alright.
It's alright.
You don't have to live in pain
for me anymore.
You can leave in peace now.
Simu,
I'm sorry.
Duan Shunxi,
you've already done more than enough.
Truly.
Thank you for staying by my side.
Duan Xu.
Foxy.
Duan Shunxi.
Duan Shunxi,
I take back what I said just now.
Please don't go.
Please.
Please don't leave me behind.
Duan Shunxi,
please don't go.
I take back what I said just now.
Don't go.
All things in this world fade fast.
I'm the only undying
and unending one.
Foxy.
Duan Xu.
Duan Xu,
wake up.
Duan Xu.
Simu.
It's me.
I'm holding your heart again.
How nice.
He Simu came to take me home.
This is the first time in my life
that someone has come for me.
Jiang Ai, what are you after?
Why did that mortal
lose the soul candle?
Are you in league with Bai Sanxing?
What you should worry about now
is if Her Grace won't appear,
how are we to deal
with the other Lords?
If anything has happened to He Simu,
I will never let you off.
Simu actually split the soul candle
and rekindled it for Duan Xu.
(Zhaomu Pavilion, the Void)
Duan Xu.
Can you hear me?
What did you see in your dream?
Foxy,
I don't like seeing you like this.
Wake up, please.
Yan, Yan.
Yan, with you in the Void,
I can stay longer in the Mortal World.
Don't move.
You've drained too much spirit power.
He is no mere mortal.
He is my spell bearer.
He belongs to me.
I want him alive.
So, he will not die.
This morning assembly is being held
outside Her Grace's bedchamber.
This is unprecedented.
Desire has clouded judgment.
At this early hour,
we received word
from Her Grace to change the venue.
What happened?
It must involve that mortal.
The Right Hand can bear this?
The Right Hand is here.
- Your Lordship.
Why hasn't the Left Hand come?
It may also involve that mortal.
Your Grace,
all Lords are here.
Lately, you've been working hard
on the spirit ascension,
but some, to carry out the decree,
falsified the register.
Please calm your anger, Your Grace.
Your Grace, please forgive us.
The Right Hand
has punished this already.
I will not pursue it further.
Those with other motives
will face annihilation.
If there is nothing more, dismiss.
- Yes.
Let's go.
Your Grace,
I ask for an audience.
Speak outside.
That mortal is in your bedchamber?
None of your business.
So, Your Grace,
it was because of that mortal
that today's venue was changed.
Are you questioning me?
I wouldn't dare.
But that mortal broke
into the Nine-Square Maze Prison.
He also preoccupies you,
making others think
you're indulging in pleasure
and neglecting governance.
Today,
the Lords have voiced complaints.
If this goes on,
the outcome will be dire.
If they are dissatisfied,
just kill them.
Yan Ke,
is it that they are dissatisfied,
or is it you?
Simu,
you know I meant no such thing.
I have your best interest at heart.
- I…
- As the mere Right Hand,
just stick to your duties.
Do not overstep.
The moment he set foot in the Void,
he deserved to die.
To protect your authority,
allow me this one overstep.
Let this be the last time.
As the mere Right Hand,
just stick to your duties.
Do not overstep.
The mere Right Hand?
The mere Right Hand...
So, in your heart,
I am only your Right Hand.
Don't move.
You've spent too much spirit power.
You've drained too much spirit power.
Simu,
thank you.
Yan.
How dare you?
Please, forgive me.
Just do what I told you to do.
Stop defying me at every turn.
Simu,
thank you.
If I wanted to kiss you now,
would you allow it?
Bite me.
What's wrong?
Duan Xu.
Duan Xu?
How bold of you.
You defied the Golden-wall Decrees
and fled to torment mortals.
Seize her.
Your Lordship.
Yan Zhang of Xuling Temple.
You defied orders time and again
to go to the Mortal World
for one mortal man.
Was it worth it?
Destroy me if you must.
As long as my body endures,
I will go back out again.
He is only a tiny mortal.
You were never meant to be together.
He betrayed me.
I will never spare him.
As long as my body remains,
my hatred for him
will never fade.
What do you intend to do to him?
What do I intend to do to him?
I will flay him and break his bones.
I will make him wish for life,
yet never find release in death.
Even if I face annihilation
with arrows through my heart,
I will never regret it.
In that case,
hand this man over to me.
What do you think?
It shall be as you wish.
This is the jade pendant
I once gave to that man.
What did you do to him?
He was cut down piece by piece
and met a slow, agonizing end.
A slow,
agonizing end?
Good.
Well done.
My vengeance is fulfilled.
Good riddance.
How did you evade the decrees
and manage it?
You can't take revenge,
not because the rules forbid it,
but because you're not powerful enough.
I'm not powerful enough?
As long as you hold enough power,
you can have
everything you desire.
Your Grace, don't worry.
He is just feverish.
Once he absorbs
Ice Jade's spiritual energy,
the heat toxin will fade.
Do you want to save Bai Sanxing?
Please, calm your wrath.
I was led astray for a moment.
I never meant to harm
Mr. Duan.
For a moment?
I'd say this was planned long ago.
Still, it's good you had the nerve.
Otherwise, I'd never have let you
serve as my Left Hand.
Remember:
There won't be a next time.
You may rise.
That child
truly tugs at one's heart.
When he has nightmares,
he does not even cry for help.
In the Prison,
even when the soul candle was cut in two
and went out,
he was still telling me
that if he made it out alive,
I must tell him of your past.
Your Grace,
this child
has truly fallen for you.
They say ten fingers
are tied to the heart.
Does that mean I'm holding your heart?
So, this was why
he fell for me?
♪Falling down like snow♪
♪Joys and sorrows of the mortal world♪
The fingers are tied to the heart.
♪The forms and hues of the mortal realm♪
He entered the Prison
to get to know you
and to share your burdens.
From what I can see,
you were not untouched.
Your concern and indulgence for him
go far beyond those for anyone else.
Simu,
you have feelings for him.
♪Dawn and dusk rise and set♪
♪Longing to meet, yet parted by destiny♪
♪Let me wander through♪
♪Light and dark, without turning back♪
♪Wander to the other shore
with the lantern♪
♪Accompanied by eternity♪
♪As all things turn and flow♪
♪Whether I stay or go, I'm all alone♪
♪As stars shift and change places♪
♪A century is like a dream♪
♪Let me journey across them all♪
♪Without reincarnations♪
♪A lone lamp shines on the other shore♪
♪Accompanied by the abyss♪
Duan Shunxi.
♪Moments may last♪
It truly feels
like you've gripped my heart.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪