[Rongcheng Group]
This is the place
that vulgar man mentioned.
I want to be a vulgar man too.
Then we need to find
that vulgar businessman,
and get the money
piled up in his house.
Why don't we just search
for his address online,
like we did with that fat guy?
That fat guy was showing off.
When the reporter interviewed him,
he insisted on
being filmed biking to work.
That's how I found his house.
But those big bosses
are much more low-key.
You can't find out
where they live at all.
Then why didn't we
just follow him home that day?
You have the nerve to ask?
If you hadn't
gone to pee in the woods,
would he have gotten away?
Can we still find his house?
Why not?
Who doesn't go home after work?
That big boss has dinners
every night.
He still has to go home
after dinner, right?
What if he goes for a bath
after dinner?
He still has to go home
after his bath, right?
Then it'll be dawn,
and he'll go straight to work.
Have you heard
the story of Yu who removed the mountains?
If he doesn't go home
and goes for a bath today,
we'll follow him tomorrow.
If he doesn't go home
and goes for a massage tomorrow,
we'll follow him the day after.
If he doesn't go home
and goes for a foot wash the day after,
we'll follow him the day after that.
Does he have that many activities?
No matter how many activities he has,
he has to go home eventually.
We'll just keep following him.
As long as he goes home,
we can follow him to that place
piled with money.
Then...
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 8]
Since you guys grew up together,
whether it's true or not
doesn't make sense.
Why did you report Zhou Rong then?
Because of love.
Hello, Yibo.
Hello, Qi.
There's a new movie out recently.
Do you want to go see it?
I'm not going.
Maybe another day.
I'm too tired today.
Then get some good rest.
You suspected
Zhou Rong and Zhou Qi
were having an affair,
so you wrote this report letter?
[report letter]
I treated you like a good brother,
and you stab me in the back?
This is too much.
[report letter]
Then nobody gets to live.
Nobody gets out alive.
Then nobody gets to live!
I am a police officer.
Don't run to this area!
It's dangerous here!
I am a cop!
[I hereby report this under my real name.]
The name is
unavailable.
The last digits of the ID number
match;
the leading digits are missing.
Chief Zhang,
it matches.
If it matches, it's right.
If only I hadn't sent it out,
none of this crap would have happened.
So it's because his girlfriend
was having an affair with his best friend.
I'm not gossiping.
I just want to figure this out.
It's my fault.
It's all a misunderstanding.
Mr. Rong is so successful in business,
handsome,
and single.
No surprise he's a bit of a flirt.
People are bound to misread him.
[My only love, Qi—
I hurriedly leave, just as I…]
Qi,
[Gently I came; in haste we met,
and in haste we part.]
none of this has anything to do with you.
I'll leave all my savings to you.
The password is your birthday.
[Mr. Rong]
Hello?
Fire that Shanshan for me.
I never want
to see her at Fenglinwan again.
Who?
Shanshan from the PR department,
the one who lives in
the same building as Qi.
What do you mean?
That girl went on a date
with me last night,
and she ate fried leek dumplings.
But the whole world knows
I can't stand the smell of leeks.
My mouth
still tastes like leeks.
Mr. Rong,
you were on a date
with Shanshan last night?
Who else?
Just because
of this?
Yes.
Maybe you won't believe it,
but I really can't live without Qi.
Only she can make me feel
the dignity of a man.
And then?
Couldn't you just cancel
the delivery?
At first,
that's what I thought.
But...
Welcome to Jiangcheng Express.
Safe, fast, and reliable—
that's our promise to you.
For faster shipping
and tracking,
please visit our official website.
For shipping, press 1.
For tracking, press 2.
For customer service, press 3.
Hello.
How can I help you?
Hello?
I sent a package by mistake.
I need to get it back right away.
Bring your ID
to our station,
explain the situation,
and once verified,
-you can get your parcel back.
-I…
I'm at
Yiyuan Haoting residential community.
Where is
your express
station?
Hurry up, okay?
Please wait a moment, sir.
I'll check it for you.
So
the report letter
went to the provincial capital.
You chased it to the provincial capital
to get the report letter back.
Your package
is already out for delivery.
Don't worry.
I have the package with me.
You can bring your ID to find me,
or wait at the station.
No need.
I'll go to you.
[Name: Lu Yibo]
Is it you?
On behalf of the organizers
and the staff of today's event,
I would like to warmly welcome
all the guests present here.
Great!
Eight!
Seven!
Six!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One.
Believe it or not,
I'm telling the truth.
I can swear to God.
Then why did you write
in the report letter
that he was related to
Lu Zheng's death?
Because when Lu Zheng died,
I acted on impulse
and wanted to frame him
with a felony.
But the case
had already been officially settled.
That's why I wrote the report letter
to you, Chief Zhang.
Everyone in Sanjiangkou knows
when Chief Lu had his accident,
you said,
we should doubt our doubts.
Your...
According to what you're saying now,
you and Zhou Rong are childhood friends,
you wrote a report letter against him,
and the letter contains
some fatal accusations.
Now you're telling me
none of these are true
and it's a misunderstanding.
This hardly dispels our suspicions.
It's also out of envy and jealousy.
Yes.
We are childhood friends.
Mr. Rong,
Ye,
Bowen,
and I.
But I actually hate them.
What do you mean?
Not to mention Mr. Rong.
He's the boss of Rongcheng Group,
a famous entrepreneur in Sanjiangkou.
It should be him.
Bowen is doing well these years.
He's making a lot of money.
Before Ye died, he was the captain
of Sanjiangkou CID.
He had a successful career
and power.
Who takes me seriously?
Aren't you a somebody?
Wait,
I'm just saying at least you are
the general manager
of Fenglinwan Hotel.
You have a big business.
You only see the surface.
I'm just an employee.
Fenglinwan Hotel was invested by Mr. Rong.
I'm just his legal representative
earning a fixed salary.
You are the legal representative
of his company?
This is not illegal, right?
Then according to what you said,
you also hold a grudge against
Ye Jian, don't you?
I hate myself more.
I'll tell you something
that I shouldn't.
The night Ye Jian was murdered,
he used his last ounce of strength
to write down three words.
It's a name.
There's a "Yi" in the middle.
Chief Zhang,
don't scare me.
Ye
couldn't have written my name.
It doesn't make sense.
You know enough already.
One last question for you.
Answer truthfully.
Go ahead.
The night Ye Jian was murdered,
did he come to Fenglinwan Hotel?
Fenglinwan is an entertainment venue.
To avoid suspicion,
-he didn't even come to the opening.
-Answer my question.
No.
Lu Yibo
is definitely not telling the truth.
But he didn't look like
he was lying.
Chief Zhang,
how about we find some time
to invite Zhou Rong
to the station for questioning?
Lu Yibo only admitted
that the person he reported was Zhou Rong.
Now he says he was smearing Zhou Rong.
He also took the report letter back.
We have no evidence.
Calling Zhou Rong in like this
would just tip him off.
Could Zhou Rong already know
about Lu Yibo writing the report letter?
Definitely not.
Think about it, Chief.
If Zhou Rong knew
Lu Yibo reported him,
he would skin him alive.
Could he still sit there
drinking tea?
We finally
found a breakthrough.
And now it's closed again.
Chief Zhang.
Wang.
Good evening, officers.
Let's go, Wang.
No, maybe she's just
being polite.
Before we came,
didn't you say
that the night gave you
dark eyes?
But I use them to look for the light.
So where is the light?
Lu Yibo insists on denying it.
The report letter
doesn't constitute evidence.
Ye has never been to Fenglinwan Hotel.
Chief Zhang,
how do we investigate this?
Keep moving forward,
constantly pursuing that golden hope.
I still think
that Lu Yibo's report letter
appearing at the explosion scene
is too much of a coincidence.
♪ Doubt ♪
It can't be a coincidence
that this report letter was found
at the explosion scene.
♪ Doubt ♪
Is it possible
that someone wanted to
stop Lu Yibo from delivering the letter,
even trying to blow him up?
Doubt, Doubt, Doubt
We need to check the files
on the provincial capital explosion.
These two incidents
shouldn't be connected, right?
Check the files
on the provincial capital explosion.
Mr. Rong, are you still mad at me?
Are you done?
Mr. Rong doesn't want to kill you.
Ren,
stop joking around.
We are driving out of Sanjiangkou.
Can you find
a nice and scenic place
before you kill me?
To tell you the truth:
Mr. Rong wants to give you
a chance to make up for your mistakes.
What do you want me to do?
Do you know anything about music?
What kind of music?
Percussion
with drumbeats.
Mr. Lang!
Mr. Lang,
you walk so fast.
I had a hard time catching up.
This is...
This is your...
My what?
Bill for this month.
So I have to pay
when I come to Fenglinwan Hotel now?
No, Mr. Lang.
The store has been losing money.
This is a new rule.
Just sign it for me.
Where is Lu Yibo?
Mr. Lu?
I haven't seen him. I don't know.
Call him.
Let him tell me himself.
Mr. Lang,
please don't make it difficult for me.
Qi.
Ask her if you don't believe me.
Come here.
Mr. Lang, what's wrong?
Let's chat.
Let me see the bill.
Okay.
How could you not know
where Lu Yibo went?
Officer,
Yibo is a guy
who really likes to play around.
He plays games
and goes fishing.
When he's having fun,
it's common for him to disappear
for two or three days.
You can't reach him for a couple of days.
Don't move.
Just sign it.
If you can contact him,
tell him we came looking for him.
There are still a few details
about the provincial capital case
we need to confirm with him.
Okay, officer.
We won't bother you anymore.
Take care, officer.
Hello. The number you have dialed
-is powered off.
-Qi.
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed
is powered off.
Wen?
Why are the police
looking for Yibo?
Yibo and I
grew up together as brothers.
Is there anything you can't tell me?
Wen,
tell me,
if Yibo did something
to let Mr. Rong down,
but he truly realized his mistake,
would Mr. Rong forgive him?
What do you mean by that?
I don't know anything.
Tell me
what exactly Yibo did?
How did he let Mr. Rong down?
This is your last chance.
If you mess it up,
I will really find you
a picturesque place to bury you.
Don't, bro.
Go.
Before the matter is done,
don't contact anyone.
Is it that simple?
It is that simple.
Ren,
what's Zhu Yifei's background
anyway?
Am I in any danger?
Ren!
Is anyone here?
Only the dog is home.
Who are you looking for?
Hello,
I'm from Rongcheng Group
in Sanjiangkou.
No, no, no.
I'm here to buy something from Uncle Fei.
Ren arranged it.
[Huo Zheng — Zhu Yifei's subordinate]
Is it turned off?
I turned it off on the way here.
Don't mind it, brother.
It's just the rules of the game.
Wait here.
Sir.
Excuse me,
do they sell chimes here?
Uncle Fei.
Fish food.
Are you Zhu Yifei?
Yes.
[Huo Zheng — Zhu Yifei's subordinate]
But we are
legitimate businessmen.
The goods you want
are not available.
Sorry for making you come for nothing.
Brother, please give me the phone back.
It's mealtime.
Let's eat together.
I'll pass on the meal.
Business may fail, but friendship remains.
If I don't invite you to stay for a meal,
and word gets out,
they'll say I have no manners.
Hello?
Did you see the goods?
No.
Then why are you still there?
Boss Zhu invited me to eat.
How about
you come here yourself, Ren?
Ren?
Eat, Yibo.
It was Mr. Rong who gave you the chance
to negotiate the deal.
Turn off the phone.
Hello, it's me.
Hu Jianren,
is Zhu Yifei reliable?
I know he hasn't failed
all these years.
It's just that if the deal falls through,
no one gets out.
But I just want to know
if he has the goods right now.
Uncle,
it's been a long time.
It should be about time.
Now is the perfect time
to simmer the soup.
Since they are here,
they can't leave empty-handed.
What if they only want the chime bells
and nothing else?
Then for the next pot,
we'll simmer them.
Black tiger palm mushroom
and chicken soup.
Have a taste
while it's hot.
That's the taste.
To be honest,
it's my first time eating tiger paw.
Whether it's the right taste,
I don't know.
But it's a really good soup.
Tigers
are national treasures.
Do you really think
I'd chop off a tiger's paw
just to make soup
for you?
I'd rather stew you instead.
Just kidding.
This is a kind of mushroom
called Black Tiger Paw.
Understand?
Then this is just
ch- chicken stewed with mushrooms?
Let me tell you,
this kind of fungus
is extremely precious.
Its price
isn't necessarily cheaper
than a real tiger paw.
But the soup made from it
is even more delicious
than a real tiger paw.
Try it again.
Young man.
There are some things in this world
that you can't force.
There is always a substitute.
Right?
Yes.
Thank you.
Well...
What are you doing?
This...
Wh- What's wrong?
What's wrong, young man?
Do you know what this is?
Ru kiln porcelain.
Ru kiln porcelain?
It was from the Song Dynasty.
Only 67 pieces have survived
in the entire world to this day.
And you actually
spit bones into it.
Are you going to sell this to Mr. Rong?
Is this one of those
67 pieces?
This is
the 68th piece.
Not long ago,
a friend of mine
salvaged a sunken ship
from the Song Dynasty
in the Indian Ocean.
This item
was found in the ship.
[Ping'an Province
Antique Appraisal Center.]
It's the appraisal certificate
issued by experts.
[Provenance: Northern Song Dynasty]
Mr. Rong.
Lu Yibo is still waiting for news.
I don't care whether it's a set of chimes
or a plate,
or whether it's iron or bronze.
Your only goal
is to satisfy Fang Yong.
Understood.
[Alarm clock][5 minutes]
Mr. Fang.
Why are you here?
The stuff you wanted
is ready.
Mr. Zhou asked me to come over
to get you a rack.
Otherwise, there will be
nowhere to put it.
So he told me to come
and take the measurements.
Come in.
Okay.
Look,
where should we put the stuff?
Right here.
Put it here.
Alright.
Mr. Fang,
can we make this shelf
out of chicken-wing wood?
I'd prefer Phoebe zhennan.
We don't have Phoebe zhennan.
Is old rosewood okay?
Red sandalwood.
Red sandalwood at the very least.
Okay.
Then red sandalwood it is.
What are you doing?
Measuring the windows.
Measuring the windows?
Getting the dimensions of the windows
so I can order reflective film for you.
Reflective film?
If we don't put up reflective film,
people outside
might be able to see inside.
If they see
these antiques, that's one thing.
You could just say
they're family heirlooms,
and no one could say anything.
But if they see
Han Dynasty bronze chimes
hanging on this red sandalwood rack,
and report you,
how would you explain it?
And over here.
If it were up to me,
outside here,
I'd add another security door.
When someone comes to the door,
you close this door first,
before opening the outer door.
That way, the people outside
won't be able to see inside.
The way it is now,
when a delivery guy comes,
they can see
the chimes inside at a glance.
If someone sees it,
it'd be a huge deal.
You'd be doomed.
Also...
Sorry, I need to take this.
[Alarm clock]
Hello?
We don't want that Ru kiln plate anymore.
My friend chose the chimes in the end.
Okay, thanks.
Okay.
By the way,
our...
No.
Do you want the black film
or the silver one?
What?
Did you just say
a Ru kiln plate?
What Ru kiln plate?
A friend of mine abroad
just salvaged
a Northern Song sunken ship
from the Indian Ocean.
The ship is full of porcelain.
The most amazing part
is that there's a large
Ru kiln plate.
A Ru kiln plate?
Is it real?
It's real.
They hired
experts from the National Museum
to appraise it.
Oh, right,
this was even on the news.
Look.
Here.
This...
Is it currently in the country?
Yes, it is.
How did it get in?
This friend of mine
specializes in helping others
transfer assets overseas.
He takes this plate abroad
to auction it,
and someone here
buys it for 200 million.
That 200 million
then leaves the country in a "legal" way,
and the plate
comes in "legally" as well.
But this is money laundering.
The plate wasn't really sold.
It's still his.
So he's in a hurry to find a buyer.
Why am I telling you this?
I'm getting off topic.
For the reflective film,
should we use black or silver?
I want the plate.
I don't want the chime bells anymore.
I want this Ru kiln plate.
Mr. Fang, you...
you...
We already agreed on this.
Well...
You don't want East New Town anymore?
Yes.
Understood.
Then,
the Ru kiln plate it is.
And get a red sandalwood box
to go with it.
Okay.
Uncle Fei,
please help me out.
In all of China,
no,
the whole world,
is there anything you can't get?
I can't help.
This set of chime bells
was fixated on you for a while.
Is there a special reason?
That's the boss's idea.
He wants the chime bells.
I want a plate.
The plate!
He wants a plate now!
Okay.
Then,
let's talk about the price.
Uncle Fei, look,
how about five million?
Zhengzheng, see him out.
Don't.
I don't know the market.
Why don't you name a price instead?
At the last Ru kiln auction,
that item
was smaller than mine.
It sold for
300 million.
Thr...
300 million?
I'm doomed.
I'm completely doomed.
I'm doomed, Uncle Fei.
My budget is really
far off from yours.
Let me tell you the truth.
If this deal
falls through,
my boss definitely won't let me off.
I'll lose my life!
Don't.
-He'll kill me.
-Don't.
Don't cry.
Our budget
is too far from your price.
Actually...
You can bargain.
What is the maximum
your boss can offer?
The most he can give
is 20 million.
Deal!
This...
It's a deal?
Hello, Ren.
I'm bringing the money now.
Take a good look at the item.
Don't spend 20 million
to buy a fake plate.
Understood.
Don't move!
What's wrong?
You're pissing me off, you know?
The biggest taboo when inspecting goods
is passing them hand to hand.
If you don't hold it well,
and he doesn't catch it,
who is to blame if it breaks?
Whose fault is it?
Put it down first.
Gently.
Put it down.
You're really pissing me off.
You want to see it?
Sure,
but no hand-to-hand passing.
After it's put down,
pick it up yourself,
look at it slowly,
and appreciate it slowly.
Then,
if I hand it to you, don't take it.
I have to put it down,
and you pick it up yourself.
Understand?
Understood.
Uncle.
Ren,
it really wasn't my fault.
If I had broken it,
could I have walked out?
Fang Yong has agreed.
Mr. Rong is also rushing us.
What are we going to give them?
Zhu Yifei said
he has other items.
That 20 million deal
still has to go through us—
otherwise they really won't let me out.
Uncle,
the plate is already glued back together.
If worse comes to worst,
let's find a fool
and sell it to him cheaper.
Call someone
right away.
Tell him to come here
right now.
I heard
he has a set
of Han Dynasty chime bells.
Who?
Liu Bei.
[Liu Bei — tomb raider]
Thanks, Uncle.
Bei,
I heard
you dug up some treasure.
Chime bells?
And it's a complete set.
A complete set.
A set of 9.
It's too risky,
not easy to sell.
I know.
I've been holding onto it for half a year.
Uncle,
give me a chance to make a living.
Alright.
Bei,
just because of your handsome face,
I'll figure something out.
But the goods must be authentic.
I'll go get it for you right now.
Uncle.
So impatient.
What is it now?
Lu Yibo just called,
asking what else
we have on hand.
Anything will do.
Tell him
we have the chime bells he wants.
But
the price is a bit steep.
Wait.
How much does that bastard Liu Bei want?
We haven't negotiated yet.
No matter how much he asks for,
I plan to sell it for 43 million
to Zhou Rong.
How much?
You think I want to?
The plate was broken for nothing?
I'm going to sell it to him for double.
Isn't double
only 40 million?
There's also the brothers' share.
They can't work for free.
Do you have any compassion?
You always think of everything, Uncle.