[Fated Hearts – The Fall of the Fierce General of Jinxiu]
Who dares to be so noisy?
[On-set of "Fated Hearts"] [Ning Fei arrives looking for someone]
Feng Suige.
One, two, three.
Talk to you.
Now… now.
[Learning needle removal from the Chinese medicine master]
Right now you're…
you're still poking inside.
Then I pull it out—
slowly.
He told me to—
don't.
A bit slower.
A little slower.
Right.
[Always trust the professionals]
Okay.
Let's do as the teacher says.
He told me to do this.
I guess this is it.
It's that kind of stress response.
Seeing them—
reminds me of the past.
Crazy.
Insane.
[He's sick]
A stress response.
Three, two, one—
Action!
[Wakes up after the needle is removed]
[Xueying reporting a complaint]
Do you know—
there's someone named Ning Fei?
He claims to be your brother.
He just came looking for you,
but Feng Suige beat him up.
He's pretty badly hurt.
[My brother was beaten!]
Xueying,
go check on him for me.
[Angrily questioning]
I heard—
you attacked my own kin once.
Yes.
[Readily admits it] [I, Feng Suige, own my actions]
Why did you act without even asking?
Back then—
[So angry he trips over his words]
What's going on?
Sorry.
You spared my life once,
and wanted me to cooperate,
so I could recover my memories sooner,
and help you uncover
who in Susha was the traitor.
Then why stop me today, of all days?
[Finishes a long line in one breath]