Your sister's off to the capital.
It's not like Tongzhou.
So you take good care of her, all right?
Don't worry, Grandma.
You're very kind, Mother.
I'm humbled.
I know life isn't easy for you.
Just
take care of yourself.
That's the greatest gift
you could ever give me.
I've heard what you've been through
these past few months in the capital.
You're a smart girl.
But remember this.
No matter how hard things get
from now on,
don't ever carry it all alone.
You just let me know.
I will, Grandmother.
Mother.
That Mrs. Ji is finally gone.
Yesterday,
all I wanted was a little piece of that pinkish gauze
for a trim.
The mistress hadn't even said a word,
and she gave me a dirty look instead.
She starts going on about how cold it is
and why would anyone use gauze.
Then she says I don't know the value of anything.
Pfft!
An outsider,
coming into our Gu manor
and telling everyone what to do.
Unbelievable.
Mother,
please don't cross Mrs. Ji.
She's even tougher than the mistress.
And honestly, the fabric thing is secondary.
My coming-of-age ceremony next year
is what really matters.
Have you asked the mistress
how much silver the palace will give?
Well.
My lady asked.
The mistress says by the rules,
the palace can only give two hundred taels.
She'll add another hundred
from her private purse.
So my lady thought
we add seven hundred ourselves,
and make it a thousand.
We can't do that.
You worked so hard
to save that money.
We can't just throw it away.
Besides,
that would only
be a thousand taels.
But I heard that
for my eldest sister's coming-of-age ceremony,
they spent over ten thousand.
Lan,
her coming-of-age ceremony
was all paid for
by the Ji family.
We didn't spend a single tael.
Just because my mother's family isn't powerful,
I'm supposed to keep my head down.
I'm a concubine's daughter as it is.
If my coming-of-age ceremony
is too shabby,
people will only look down on me even more.
And when it's time to find a match,
what kind of good family would want me?
But honestly, my mother's family isn't bad at all.
A fourth-rank official in the Court of Imperial Sacrifices.
Even if he's retired,
that's still way better than the Ji family,
who are just merchants.
I don't understand what my mother was thinking.
Just for the sake of Father,
she abandoned her own parents
and married him as a secondary wife.
Miss.
Here's a letter from our young lord.
Could you give it to Miss Gu?
Thank you.
Sure.
Changshun.
Second Miss.
That man just now
was from the Marquis of Changxing's residence, wasn't he?
Miss Ziling, sharp eyes.
Yes, he's from there.
He came
to deliver an invitation to the eldest Miss.
Just as well.
I'm heading to the main house
to find her for dinner.
I'll give it to her for you.
There's only you at the gate.
You can't leave your post.
Fair enough.
Thank you very much, Second Miss.
[Thank you for saving me outside Baoxiang Temple.]
[Tomorrow between 9 and 11 AM,
I will host a banquet at Linxia.]
[I await your arrival.]
[I knew it.]
[There's something between the young lord and my eldest sister.]
This one seems thicker.
Yeah, and the color is nicer too.
Madam.
You wanted to see me?
Yes, come sit down.
I made a few pairs of
knee pads,
all stuffed with goose down.
This pair is for Yao.
And
this one is for Rong.
He's almost back,
isn't he?
And this pair
is for your father.
I've already prepared a calligraphy scroll
for Rong
as a welcoming gift.
You don't need to go out of your way
to prepare anything in my name.
As for Father,
if you want to give him something, just do it.
You don't have to say it's from me.
I understand how you feel.
But
Rong is your own brother.
You didn't grow up together,
so it's easy to be distant.
Antiques and calligraphy
are nice,
but they're also
a bit cold.
Something made by hand
carries more heart.
Right?
As for your father,
he may have his faults,
but he's your own flesh and blood.
If word gets out that you've been cold toward him,
people will only blame you.
And besides,
Your marriage can't wait any longer.
He is an official,
and knows a lot of people.
If he would just help a little,
finding a good match would be much easier.
[Marriage talk again.]
[And the mistress still thinks
he can be counted on.]
Yao has just started at Cunshan Academy.
I wonder how he's doing.
Since the knee pads are already made,
I should send them to him
as soon as possible.
Maybe I'll go to the academy
tomorrow.
Sounds good.
This crossbow is nicely done.
Give him ten taels.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, my lord.
If you can extend the range
another fifty paces,
I'll give you a hundred.
I'll get right on it, my lord.
My lord,
we're supposed to meet Miss Gu at nine.
Shouldn't we go?
What's the rush?
Let her wait.
Yes, my lord.
Fine.
Look at you, so impatient.
Let's go.
It's already an hour past the time.
Why isn't she here yet?
Maybe
she got held up on the way.
It's not far anyway.
Send someone
to the Gu household to meet her.
Yes, sir.
Miss.
I told Luo Gui'er not to wait.
He should find a place out of the wind
and come back in an hour
to pick you up.
Our young lady is Miss Gu.
She's here to see Mr. Chen Xuanqing.
Would you mind letting him know, sir?
Please follow me inside.
My lord.
What happened?
Where's Gu Jinzhao?
Miss Gu,
she went to the academy.
The academy again.
Top Scholar.
A Miss Gu is outside
asking for you.
Miss Gu?
The one
who was here with Ms. Ji last time.
Are you sure she wants to see him?
Not me?
She didn't mention you, sir.
Got it.
The other day, your grandmother and Miss Gu
came to my house.
I lent her a book.
She's probably here to return it.
But I just remembered
the lecturer needs to see me.
He told me to wait for him.
I really can't leave.
So
maybe you could help me out?
Go see Miss Gu
and get the book back for me.
Would you?
I can't go to her.
You know my cousin's temper.
Since she didn't ask for me,
if I showed up,
she'd be furious.
So here's what we do.
Send someone else
to see her.
Tell her you got held up
by the lecturer
and can't come.
Then have her give the book
to that person
to bring back.
What do you think?
Sounds good.
Miss.
Miss Gu.
Mr. Zhang.
Long time no see
since the Chen house.
Anyway,
Xuruo got called away by the lecturer,
won't be back for a while.
He said
you have a book for him.
You can just hand it to me.
So he sent you to pick it up?
That's right.
One moment, please.
Much obliged.
My pleasure.
Well, well. A touching scene of young love.
I thought you were so busy.
Turns out you're here meeting some other man.
Greetings, my lord.
I think you've misunderstood.
I was just...
Are you following me?
Don't
flatter yourself.
I just happened
to pass by
and saw you here,
messing around with a man.
That's all.
So this is the one you've set your sights on?
Nonsense.
Are you cured now
and looking for a fight again?
You saved me once,
and now you think you can walk all over me.
Don't forget,
if it weren't for my help,
you'd already be a married woman
in the Liu family.
So that's why
you didn't want to marry into the Lius.
You went through all that trouble begging for my help.
I thought you had high standards.
But after all that,
this is the kind of man you're after.
No matter how bad your reputation is,
you don't just settle for
the first thing that comes along.
Who I choose
has nothing to do with you, my lord.
But
you are the Crown Prince's companion.
Shouldn't you be with His Highness?
Why do you spend your days following me instead?
If you're well enough,
go back to your duties at the palace.
If you're still unwell
then go home and rest. Leave me alone.
What's the matter?
Upset that I caught you in the act?
Boring.
I have things to do. I'll take my leave.
What are you doing?
Trying to leave, are you?
Li Xianhuai.
Now,
go look into this man.
I want to see
what kind of brilliant scholar
has caught
our Miss Gu's eye.
Yes.
Wait.
My lord, you've misunderstood.
There's nothing between Miss Gu and me.
Miss Gu,
please
explain to the young lord.
Please.
My lord.
Mr. Zhang
has done nothing to you.
Why are you investigating him?
I'll look into whoever I want.
What's it to you?
Li Xianhuai.
Yes.
Wait.
If you have a problem,
take it out on me.
Don't bully Mr. Zhang.
He just passed
the provincial exam,
and
he can't withstand your scrutiny.
If people find out
he's offended you,
they'll
trample him.
How will
he ever take the imperial exams
or become an official?
You're worried about his future.
I remember now.
I've seen you
at Chen Yanyun's place.
Yes, yes.
I had the honor of meeting you, my lord.
Let me ask you something.
If you gave up the imperial exams
and became a staff officer in our marquisate,
would you be willing?
Don't push it too far.
My lord, are you serious?
What if I am?
Mr. Zhang,
what are you doing?
Don't tell me
you're giving up the spring exams?
Miss Gu.
To be honest, passing the provincial exam
was pure luck.
It's all thanks to my ancestors.
I know my own limits.
I have no strength left
for the exam path.
Even if I sat
for the spring exams,
I'd get nowhere.
A fifth rank post
in the marquisate.
Why wouldn't I be willing?
Well,
if I could serve you, my lord,
I would gladly give up the spring exams
and follow your command.
What a shame.
I was just joking.
Why are you taking it so seriously?
You.
How could you do this?
How else could I
show you that
people don't always act the way you expect?
You said if I investigated him,
I'd ruin his exams
and career.
But
this man doesn't even have the confidence
to sit for the spring exams.
I dangled a little bait
and he jumped at it.
With that kind of character,
even if he became an official,
he'd just be a useless seat warmer.
Come to think of it,
I just happened
to uncover a mediocre talent
for the court.
How wonderful.
You.
Oh no!
What is it?
What happened?
Mr. Zhang got into a fight
and coughed up blood.
He's been taken to a clinic.
What?
Why are you staring at me?
How was I supposed to know he's that fragile?
You're not blaming me for this,
are you?
Who would dare blame you, my lord?
You're
from a noble house.
Raised in privilege your whole life.
Of course you wouldn't understand.
A casual promise from you
is a chance most people couldn't earn
in several lifetimes.
And
a casual retraction from you
is enough
to make a man cough up blood.
Maybe
even kill him.
What are you talking about?
In fact,
people your age
are either working the fields,
studying by candlelight,
or fighting at the front.
Working their fingers to the bone
to feed their families.
But you?
You eat, drink, and entertain yourself all day.
Lazy and wandering.
Living off your ancestors' glory.
Producing nothing.
You contribute nothing to the country or its people.
How dare you speak to me like that!
Miss.
Jinzhao.
- Stop it.
- Jinzhao.
Miss.
This academy is a place of sages.
How dare you act so recklessly,
my lord?
You dare hurt our young lady?
- Insolent!
- Qingpu.
Ms. Chen.
Second Brother.
Let him go.
He's just a madman.
It's not worth going against him.
Enough.
Let's take care of your injury first.
Split it fifty-fifty.
So by my math,
we only need
another hundred and fifty taels.
Or
let's make it an even two hundred.
But here's the thing.
You and your sister didn't grow up together.
Might feel a bit distant.
Distance isn't a problem.
The more distant,
the more expensive the meeting gift has to be.
Why else would I spend five taels
on that jade bracelet?
It's for the eldest sister.
It's called fishing, get it?
She'll have to give something back.
Gold, jade,
antiques or calligraphy,
as long as it's worth more than two hundred taels,
I win.
The eldest miss is loaded.
Maybe
she could even take care of that little matter
for us without breaking a sweat.
Shut up.
Yes, sir.
I'm an idiot.
- That matter.
- I'm an idiot.
Not a word of it must ever get out.
You hear me?
Understood.
I promise I won't say a thing.
I promise.
Not a word
about what happened today.
Yes, miss.
Miss,
hurry to the main house.
Young Master Rong has returned.
Wasn't he not coming
until the end of the month?
Go tell the mistress
I'll be there as soon as I change my clothes.
Yes, miss.
Mother.
How did you get so thin?
Your cheeks are sunken in.
Have you been studying too hard?
The eldest miss and the second miss are here.
I'll have to fatten you up.
Rong.
Greetings,
big sister.
You've grown so tall.
Quite the handsome young man.
Big sister, you're beautiful too.
Like someone out of a painting.
Second sister.
You're back.
Everyone, please sit.
Weren't you coming back at the end of the month?
Why the early return?
That was the plan,
but the teacher suddenly came down
with a bad cough,
so he let us out early.
I wrote about it
in my letter to second sister.
Didn't she tell you?
I thought
you wrote to Mother as well.
So
you only wrote to me.
It's my fault,
big sister.
should have told you.
No harm done.
Either way,
Huaiyuan is all ready for you.
Did you bring gifts
for your sisters?
Yes.
Shuangli.
Big sister.
This one is for you.
That's thoughtful of you.
I just picked it at random.
The luster looked good,
but I wasn't sure
if it would suit you.
It's perfect.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
What a beautiful ivory concentric ball.
You actually carved it?
Did you carve this
yourself?
Yes.
Mother, look.
- Let me see.
- It wasn't that hard.
No,
but what matters is the thought behind it.
That's worth
more than any gold or jade.
Last time,
I mentioned
I wanted an ivory concentric ball.
He said he'd make me one.
I never thought
he'd actually pull it off.
Who would have guessed
you had such skill?
I made another one.
This one is for you.
But it's not finished yet.
Once it's done,
I'll bring it to you.
I have a gift for you too.
Qingpu.
Go on, open it.
What is it?
It's a pair of knee pads.
It's getting cold.
You can wear them when you write.
Your sister is so thoughtful.
She made these
herself.
It's not gold or jade.
Just a little something from the heart.
Miss,
didn't you already give him a pair of knee pads?
Why add this painting?
You saw it yourself.
The moment he saw those knee pads,
his smile froze.
Clearly, he didn't like them.
So
I might as well
give him this rooster fighting painting.
It was meant for him anyway.
Miss, you're so good to Mr. Ji.
But from what I can see,
he seems closer
to the second young lady.
They grew up together.
Of course
he's closer to her than to me.
You actually carved a concentric ball
for the eldest sister?
As if I have that much free time.
I just said it in passing.
It's all your fault.
Why did you have to show off
in front of her?
I wasn't showing off.
I was just happy
and said too much.
Anyway, she didn't say anything.
Yeah.
But all she gave me
was a lousy pair of knee pads.
So,
you've been sucking up to her
because
you're hoping for something expensive in return.
Isn't that fair?
I went to all that trouble
picking out that bracelet for her.
And
she fobs me off
with cheap knee pads.
Look at you, counting every penny.
Well,
let me ask you something.
Do you have any spare money
lately?
No.
You haven't even heard how much.
I don't have any.
I only get two taels a month.
Barely enough for face powder and hair oil.
What do you need the money for?
I.
Nothing.
I have my reasons.
What reasons?
Well, since you don't have any to lend,
don't ask.
Miss,
why is Ms. Ji so short of money?
He even borrowed from the second young lady.
He's still studying,
no drinking,
no parties.
He shouldn't
need that much.
Anyway,
none of my business.
Miss,
are we still giving him the painting?
Of course not.
I'm not going to beg her.
Besides,
a good painting like this
is better off with me.
Be careful, miss.
Your arm is still hurt.
Oh, right.
Go get that outfit
I was wearing.
What are you looking for?
The notes
I wrote in that book
I borrowed from Mr. Chen.
I took them out
and hid them in my sleeve.
Then Ye Xian hit me
with his whip.
And now
they're gone.
[That feeling of being a guest in your own home.]
[I know it well.]
[Whenever it gets me down,
I cheer myself up.]
[Being a guest in your own home isn't all bad.]
[Since I'm the guest,
if anyone asks to borrow money,
absolutely not.]
[The most important thing
in life
is learning to comfort yourself.]
[Every night, tell yourself:
blame yourself less,
find others' faults more.]
[If that doesn't work,
go to Linxia,
order a feast,
and eat.]
[Still unhappy?]
[Eat again.]
[Until you're stuffed
and can't think straight.]
In fact,
people your age
are either working the fields,
studying by candlelight,
or fighting at the front.
Working their fingers to the bone
to feed their families.
But you?
You eat, drink, and entertain yourself all day.
Lazy and wandering.
Living off your ancestors' glory.
Producing nothing.
You contribute nothing to the country or its people.
My lord,
we should be going.
Let him go.
He's just a madman.
It's not worth going against him.
My lord,
the next guests
will be here any moment.
Linxia has already been booked
by someone else.
Why don't you ask the young lord
to clear the place?
Who told you to ask me to clear out?
My lord.
Yes, you.
You want me to move?
Get lost.
But.
Ms. Chen.
My respects to you.
Young lord.
So you're the one who wants me to move?
Where?
You think I don't want to?
You think
I enjoy eating, drinking,
and lazing around all day?
Do you think
you know me so well?
Gu Jinzhao,
you don't know a damn thing.
My lord,
let's go back.
Get out of my way.
You don't understand anything.
Teacher.
How's your injury?
I didn't mean to hurt you.
Let me see.
Who is that man?
Ye Xian, heir to Marquis Changxing.
Does it still hurt?
Isn't that the one with the heart condition
who can't join the army?
Can't ride a horse,
can't fight.
If he never earns any merit,
he might not get the title.
Then the Changxing line
would die out.
Why doesn't he
just have more sons then?
You think he hasn't tried?
It's not that he won't,
it's that he can't.
How dare you!
Take them back.
Yes, sir.
My lord.
Let's go.
Come on, my lord.
Please.
Let's go home.
Teacher.
This way.
Jiuheng,
since you manage the Eastern Palace,
tell me,
what do you really think of Ye Xian?
I hear
he gets along quite well with His Highness.
I was about to say, teacher.
In my view,
Ye Xian shouldn't
stay close to His Highness.
Come on, eat.
This classmate of mine grew up poor.
After the new year,
his sister is getting married to some local rich man.
He's worried her dowry
will be too shabby
and she'll be looked down on.
So he came to us for a loan.
Mother never likes
getting involved in such things.
And Father is even worse.
I don't have any money myself.
So
I had to come to you.
How much do you need?
Two hundred taels.
That much?
That's not a small sum.
Give me a few days.
Let me see what I can scrape together.
All right?
I.
Well.
Alright then.
I'll be going now.
Miss,
Yunting from Mr. Chen's side is here.
He said
the seventeenth is Mr. Chen's birthday,
and he'd like to invite you.
He also wants to know
how your injury is doing.
Really?
He actually said
the seventeenth is his birthday?
But that day at the academy,
he was right there,
yet he sent someone else to see me.
Now he's inviting me himself.
I don't know what to make of it.
Maybe last time,
he couldn't come out
to see you alone
because your brother was around.
I think so too.
Then have Yunting ask him.
We'll meet
on Yong'an Bridge.
okay?
I'll go ask him.
My lady wants to meet
on Yong'an Bridge
on the seventeenth.
Got it.
Young Master Rong is here.
How are you managing this room?
Not even a cup of water.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Idiot! Idiot!
Are you trying to burn me alive?
Forgive me, my lord.
Hot?
Then let it cool down.
What's the rush?
Who put you in a bad mood?
You come here to take it out on me.
Don't ask.
Let me guess.
Father's not home.
Mother spoils you too much
to let you suffer.
So,
it must be eldest sister?
Bingo.
No wonder.
Actually,
no one dares cross her.
She doesn't even put Father
in his place.
You'd better stop provoking her.
Why should I?
She's the eldest miss, sure,
but I'm the eldest young master of the Gu family.
What happened?
Tell me.
Why bring up something so shameful?
Miss! Miss!
Young Master Rong.
What...
Where have you been all morning?
Not a proper person
in the room.
And because of that,
our young master burned his mouth on tea.
Now he's throwing a tantrum at me.
Miss.
What's going on?
Why so secretive?
Did you hear clearly?
Every word.
I just heard something
about eldest sister.
I'm not interested in her business.
Not interested at all?
This person
might just become
our brother-in-law someday.
What?
Brother-in-law?
Who?
Chen Xuanqing.
On Yong'an Bridge.
That new bridge
I haven't seen it yet.
Great.
Alright then.
I'll go give Miss Qingpu an answer
in a bit.
Miss Qingpu said
Miss Gu is already thinking about
what birthday gift to get you.
You told her
my birthday?
Yes.
You're meeting Miss Gu on the seventeenth.
Isn't that because
you want to spend your birthday with her?
I picked the seventeenth
because the academy is closed that day.
You.
Anyway,
it's already said.
I think
Miss Gu is quite nice.
Pretty,
wealthy,
and generous.
Way better
than those noble ladies.
Enough.
That's a young lady.
Don't gossip about her like that behind her back.
I'll head back now.
Wait.
Wait,
you forgot.
Today the old lady
asked you to come home.
Right.
I forgot.
Let's go.
Ever since you became a Top Scholar,
people have been lining up
to propose.
I know
many well-bred young ladies
in the capital
have their eye on you.
Grandmother.
I.
Never mind.
What do you think of
Yu Wanxue?
The Yu family may not be as high ranked as ours,
but they've been scholars for generations.
Your uncle Yu
is a man of pure character.
He and your third uncle
have been close friends for years.
We know each other well.
And
Wanxue
is a rare, fine young lady.
What do you say?
Well,
what does third uncle think?
He's the one who picked her.
And I agree.
It does seem like a good match.
As for the Yu family,
they want to wait until after the new year
to exchange the birth certificates.
But of course,
you have to have your say.
It's your marriage.
My lord,
you're finally awake.
What time is it?
Just past nine in the morning.
You drank too much yesterday.
You slept
a full fourteen hours.
What about Gu Jinzhao?
Greetings, my lady.
Xian,
you just woke up?
Someone come.
Help him wash up.
And pack a few changes of clothes.
Yes.
Xian,
I've already sent word
to your sister.
You'll go over there in a bit
and stay at Daxin for a few days.
What happened?
Your father just returned from court.
His Majesty dismissed you
from your post as the Crown Prince's companion.
What?
This.
Did you ask Father
to beg His Majesty?
No, of course not.
I did think about it before,
but you didn't want it.
Your father also said
it was a good path.
So
I dropped it.
But
who would have guessed that
today His Majesty suddenly told your father that
since you have a heart condition,
you should stay home and rest.
He also said some other things.
Anyway,
right in front of all the civil and military officials,
he embarrassed your father badly.
Luckily,
the Earl of Yongchang came to discuss something with him.
You need to leave
before he comes to his senses
and starts yelling at you again.
My lord.
Chen Yi.
Young lord.