Sony Live Exclusive
[Introducing music]
[Intense music]
[Train chugging]
[Traffic jarring]
[Footsteps]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Train announcement]
[Footsteps]
[Traffic honks]
[Announcement]
[Escalator whirring]
[Train speeding]
[Train chugging]
[Water dripping]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Train speeding]
[Train announcement]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Train speeding]
[Train chugging]
[Train announcement]
[Train slowing]
[Train halts]
[Suspenseful music]
[Train announcement]
[Speaker beeps]
[Suspenseful music]
[Train door shuts]
[Train chugging]
[Suspenseful music]
[Tense music]
[Breathing heavily]
[Suspenseful music]
[Train chugging]
[Footsteps]
[Intense music]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Chink]
[Thuds]
[Knocks]
[Beeps]
[Whirring]
[Distant music playing]
[Tense music]
[Suspenseful music]
[Intriguing music]
[Amusing music]
[Traffic speeding]
[Traffic moving]
[Intriguing music]
[Vehicle speeding]
Hello.
- Hello.
[Happy music]
Toh Ti Ani Fuji
Come on. Shake your hands.
Shake your hands.
Come on, breathe.
[Laughing]
A little ahead. Towards the edge.
- Okay.
[Laughing loudly]
Ma'am, you'll have to wait that side.
- No, please wait.
Okay, okay. Sorry.
No, waiting on the bridge is too risky. She'll have to go.
- Wait. Please wait.
You've put on the
helmet. You are safe now.
I told her about us.
- Whom?
Kriti! I told Kriti.
[Laughing
I told her that things have
been happening between us.
Why? Did I ask you
to tell her or leave her?
I wanted to try to
get serious about us.
But why are you
talking in the past tense?
[Panting]
When am I going to try it now?
[Laughing]
Come on, now. Let's get ready.
The only thing left is the jump.
There's no need to be scared.
Step ahead. A little ahead.
[Laughing]
Please don't forget me.
[Crossing the heart]
[Tense music]
[Panting]
[Breathing heavily]
[Grins]
[Smiles]
[Breathing heavily]
[Adventurous music]
[Bangs]
That's it? Only two
boys fell for you?
[Laughing]
Not enough to only like me. They
have to like my mother as well.
We're a package deal, you see.
[Laughing heartily]
[Coughs]
[Laughs]
Are you looking at your
reflection in the spoon?
[Grumps]
[Chuckles]
Did she feel giddy
again today? Hello?
Did she feel?
Okay, okay. Good.
[Moving]
Yes, the tremors are common.
Just put on the television for her.
She won't really watch but
at least she won't bother you.
Hello? Hello?
[Footsteps]
[Stands still]
You do enough for your mother.
What is enough?
There's no such thing as 'enough'.
It's okay to choose
yourself once in a while.
You need not feel like
such a criminal about it.
[Thuds]
Will you please stop constantly staring
at your reflection? What a bore.
[Chuckles]
I'm not sure if Vismay
heard me clearly.
[Stretching]
He's sweet. The poor thing.
Not as much of a
poor thing as you think.
[Wind blowing]
Why is that funny?
It's not going to be just one. I'm
planning to start a whole chain.
So, you are going to start a whole chain of gyms.
- No. It's a body sculpting studio.
That's the same as a gym!
- No!
[Laughing]
The focus will be on fitness
and the shape of the body.
That is the same as a gym.
- No.
[Laughs]
Why don't you tell
me about your plan?
[Water dripping]
I just want to give away
all my things and set off.
[Water splashing]
Where to?
- Anywhere.
Never stop at any one
place. Just keep going.
[Taps the metal]
All my bags are packed, I'm ready to
go. I'm standin' here outside your door.
Cause I'm leavin' on a jet plane,
Don't know when I'll be back again.
[Humming]
What happened?
Hey, what's the matter?
Let me see.
What is it?
[Tense music]
Don't go.
Where am I going?
- I mean ever.
Don't ever go anywhere.
Just be with me. Always.
[Chuckles]
I'm serious.
[Tense music]
Never leave me. Promise?
- Okay.
No. Say it. Say you promise.
I'm not going to?
- Say it.
[Tense music]
Okay. Promise.
Still doing translations?
I've been doing a lot of
subtitling work recently.
Films and other things.
So, are you in Tokyo on a holiday or...
- No, on work.
The same thing?
[Chuckles]
[Both chuckle]
[Footsteps]
Wow. The plan changed?
It just did.
[Grins]
So, what do you do now?
I do? things. I keep busy.
[Other language]
Excuse me ma'am,
your table is ready.
Thank you.
[Indistinct chatter]
[Footsteps]
Cheers.
- Cheers.
[Sipping tea]
[Thuds]
Ma'am.
- Thank you so much.
[Clutter]
The people here seem peaceful.
- A little too peaceful.
[Indistinct chatter]
You won't even catch them chatting on the train.
- No, I mean they seem content.
[Indistinct chatter]
Do they?
- Hmm.
Actually, if they had toilet seats like
these everywhere, anyone would seem content.
[Chuckling]
[Chuckle]
[Giggling]
I sat on the commode in my hotel?
Such a wonderfully warm seat.
And so many options for washing your
bum! I've never been more grateful.
[Laughing]
How are you still single?
[Clutter]
[Indistinct chatter]
Who said I am?
- You're not?
I am.
[Indistinct chatter]
And you?
[Tense music]
[Chuckling]
[Pensive music]
Enough. I'm done.
- Have more, come on.
It's sake. You won't feel cold.
Come on. Down it.
Drink it!
Cheers.
- Cheers.
[Laughing]
Hmm.
[Sighs]
By the way, what's with the policy
of not talking about your work?
[Chuckles]
What?
There's no policy.
Then?
I don't want to tell you.
Why?
Because you always judge.
Wait, hold on. 'Always'?
When was the last time we met?
Yes, okay, sorry. You used to.
But a person's true nature
never changes, right?
[Sighs]
[Indistinct laughter]
What?
- Your mind is made up. Leave it.
[Indistinct chatter]
Oh no. Okay, fine. I'll tell you.
- No, no, no? I don't even want to know.
Why wouldn't I want to share it with you?
- Who knows?
Come on.
- No, no, no, no. I don't want to know anymore.
Now, I want to tell you. Listen to me!
- No, no, no!
[Laughing]
[Laughing loudly]
[Soft music]
[Soft music continues]
[Harmonious music]
[Train chugging]
[Train chugging speedily]
[Footsteps]
[Train bell]
[Tense music]
[Ambulance siren]
[Train speeding]
[Footsteps]
[Heavy strides]
[Indistinct chatter]
Hello? I'm glad you called.
[Footsteps]
I'm sorry. I got carried away?
[Train chugging]
Right now?
[Footsteps]
Sure, okay.
I'll be right there.
[Footsteps]
[Long strides]
[Knocking]
[Tense music]
[Footsteps]
[Chimes]
[Door shuts]
[Footsteps]
[Door opens]
[Tense music]
[Footsteps]
[Door closes]
[Tense music]
[Stops]
[Sighs]
[Wipes eyes]
[Tense music]
[Suspenseful music]
Hello!
Hi!
Where are you?
[Squealing]
Who is it? Who is he talking to?
[Distorted voice
We're not missing you! He's lying!
Are you at home? Are you at home?
Yes.
[Loud music]
[Loud music playing]
Hold, hold, hold.
What did you want?
I want you? here? now.
Hello!
Right now. Right here.
[Muffled voice]
[Beeps]
[Dialing tone]
[Groans]
[Voice on phone]
[Grunts]
[Clutters]
[Voice on phone]
[Breathing heavily]
[Grunts]
[Monitor beeps]
[Groans]
[Breathing heavily]
[Shivering]
[Exhales]
[Sighs]
[Clangs]
[Whirring]
[Chugging]
[Clangs]
[Whirring]
[Crow caws]
[Soft cry]
[Bee buzzing]
When my uncle died, my cousin stopped
being able to listen to music.
Hmm. The universe
always maintains its balance.
Yes, when something is destroyed,
something else is created.
My uncle died in the Kedarnath
floods. We didn't even get to see him.
[Clangs]
At least you got to say a final
goodbye. At least you were prepared.
Lavender perfume reduces stress. Especially when
you're sad. Especially when you've experienced loss.
Balance. It's about balance in the universe.
- When one leaves, another arrives.
[Sprang up]
[Heavy footsteps]
[Footsteps]
[Door shuts]
[Knocks]
[Knocking loudly]
What's wrong?
We're sorry if one of
us said the wrong thing.
Listen? just come out. Let's talk.
You should be with people right now. Why
have you locked yourself in there alone?
[Knocking]
At least say something.
I'm getting worried.
I'm pregnant.
[Chuckles]
[Garbles water]
I said I'm pregnant.
[Sips water]
Aren't you going to say anything?
[Clears throat]
Yes, of course I do.
[Mummbles]
[Unlatches door]
[Running]
[Footsteps]
Wait.
This way, Ma'am.
Please.
- Thanks.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
[Soft music]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Clangs]
[Soft music]
Thank you.
Ma'am, sake.
- Thank you.
Cheers
Yes, Sir?
[Shifts chair]
[Pulls chair]
[Lifts glass]
[Thuds]
Are we going to talk?
Wait, let me order first.
Yes, sir?
Uh!
Salmon?
And? Tuna Sashimi
- Thank you, Sir.
[Soft music]
Can you take off your sunglasses at least?
- Why?
[Shifts chair]
[Footsteps]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Children giggling]
[Door opens]
[Clangs]
[Pouring water]
[Clang]
[Clangs]
[Spray]
[Clang]
[Scraping]
Kartu, why aren't
you saying anything?
I'm watching.
Why don't you show him our home?
What's there to show?
Don't you understand? I'm
asking you to show him the house.
You can start.
Tell him your friends' names.
Hmm.
Tomoki, Ayano, Riko, Kiho.
And what's her
name? Your girlfriend?
Masako.
[Chuckles]
Aren't you going to eat?
- No, I'm a pescatarian.
What's that?
- I only eat fish.
It's just a phase.
[Clang]
Are you an old friend of Ma's?
- Yes, I am.
From school?
- No.
So, not that old.
[Shakes head]
[Clang]
I should get going. I have got a meeting.
- Oh...
Don't you want to see the house?
[Exhales]
Sure.
- Let's go then.
[Picks toy car]
[Footsteps]
[Sighs]
His name is 'Table'.
This is where I study.
His name is 'Bed'. This
is where I sleep and read.
His name is 'Rug'. This
is where I draw and read.
His name is 'Cat'.
Her name is 'Window'.
Nice. You have a lovely room.
Wow.
Isn't this Mount Fuji?
Yes. Fuji is my friend.
This mountain?
- Yes. Fuji and I are very close.
Did you make this drawing?
- Yes. It took me three whole days.
Kartu, you liar! It was already on
the wall when we moved in here.
Your friend is wonderful, Kartu.
Hold on.
Only my Ma and my
Pa are allowed to call me
'Kartu'.
And Nori-ba chan. And Haru-ji chan.
And my friend Tomoki. And
my friend Fuji-san, of course.
I'm sorry, Kartikeya. I'll keep in mind.
- It's okay.
Are these your friends too?
- No! That's my Ma and Pa.
They are very old
friends. From school.
His name is Vismay.
[Tense music]
It's not all that shocking.
We grew up next door to each other.
No one knows me like he does.
So, you married him. Wow.
I was completely alone
after you cut me off.
I had no one else in Pune.
I was alone. So, I made the
decision to shift here with him.
What?
- Nothing.
Say it.
- It's nothing.
I'm happy to see that you got
everything you ever wanted.
I got none of what I wanted.
Here, take this.
Aren't you coming home?
- No.
Why not?
- You've given me enough to digest.
That's not fair.
- Sure, that's not fair.
Congratulations. Whatever. Bye.
[Tense music]
[Sighs]
[Clangs]
[Motor whirring]
[Straps]
[Thuds]
Her cupboard is emptied.
[Footsteps]
[Whirring]
We don't have to do this all today.
We can do it later.
[Tense music]
No. Today is fine.
[Clangs]
You have been looking after
your mother for all these years.
Do you even know any other kind of
life? Weren't you a mother to her?
I can imagine myself as a mother.
Are you immediately going to
take on a new responsibility?
But then I'm being selfish, right?
- Yes. And why not? Please be selfish.
So, we're both saying we
don't want this right now?
I'm saying?
[Vehicle speeding]
We'll do whatever you want.
She cannot always be the one to make the difficult decision.
- I'm trying to be sensitive.
Okay.
[Car speeding]
[Car honking]
[Thuds]
[Clinking]
[Tearing]
[Clang]
[Door opens]
Hello. How are you?
- Good.
Are you sure you want to go ahead with it?
- Yes.
Okay, then. Lie down. I'll explain the procedure to you.
- Okay.
We will first put your legs in the
stirrups, then anaesthetize your cervix.
It is called a para-cervical block.
After that, we will use a rod...
Here?
- Yes, please. Lie down.
A rod will be inserted and then we will
clear everything using a suction tube.
It's a short ten minute procedure.
Let me know if you feel
uneasy. And don't be afraid.
Is the block done?
- Yes, ma'am.
[Indistinct chatter]
Okay. Get the instruments ready.
Drum. And the cap and mask.
- Yes, ma'am.
Okay, let's start.
[Tense music]
[Sweeping]
[Sighs]
[Grunts]
I can't imagine what
is going to happen.
She is allowed to be confused.
She should tell him.
[Birds chirping]
[Footsteps]
[Pouring liquid]
He is his son. He
has the right to know.
[Inhaling]
I'm confused.
Are you really?
Or are you going to ask for advice and
then as always do exactly as you wish?
Is that what I do?
You said you didn't know where
to go. I said let's shift to Japan.
You asked if we should get married. I said
okay, but I wanted to work on our relationship.
Then you said we should get married but let's
not get involved and keep each other trapped.
Yes, but I...
- When I asked you why get married at all.
You said, “For Kartu's sake.”
If you didn't want this,
you shouldn't have agreed.
I was alone. I was afraid. So, in the moment,
I did what I thought was right for Kartikeya.
I had made it absolutely clear to you that
I felt nothing for you but friendship.
Did you or did you not make me agree to what you wanted?
- Stop!
The last thing we need is the two of you fighting.
- Yes, please.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, too.
[Birds chirping]
If he hadn't come here out of the
blue, everything would have been fine.
But he has come.
[Birds chirping]
What are you going to do now?
[Tense music]
My arm is asleep.
[Indistinct chatter]
Rub your nails together.
I thought this was supposed
to help with falling hair.
[Indistinct chatter]
Oh, yes. That's right.
I'm off.
Let me know if you need anything.
[Indisinct chatter]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Door creaks]
[Door shuts]
[Indistinct chatter]
You'll stay, won't you?
- Of course.
[Indistinct chatter]
Dinner?
I'm not hungry.
- Me neither.
[Indistinct chatter]
[Footsteps]
[Rattling]
[Indistinct chatter]
If we make it through
this, we can face anything.
[Indistinct chatter]
We're not through this yet.
[Grunts]
I'm saying that whatever is happening
to us, is a meaningful experience.
[Indistinct chatter]
And?
What about it?
Why do you immediately have to attack
me? Try to understand my point.
[Indistinct chatter]
[Sighs]
[Exhales]
You're right. It's a meaningful
experience. What do we do about it?
[Indistinct chatter]
[Footsteps]
[Sitting]
What can we do?
Let's get married.
[Indistinct chatter]
Done.
Sure?
- Of course. I'm not going anywhere.
Let's do a registered one.
- Perfect. As it is I hate my relatives.
[Indistinct chatter]
Shall we do it tomorrow?
- I'll ask Appo and Betty if they'll be our witnesses.
You have to apply first. Then they
give you a date for the registration.
Whatever the
process is, we'll do it.
[Hugging]
Great.
- Done.
Done.
[Indistinct chatter]
Or should we live together first?
Even this is a good
option. What do you think?
[Door opens]
Come in.
[Footsteps]
[Claps]
It's big.
[Sighs]
[Clinks]
[Stamps]
[Knocks]
Black money.
[Footsteps]
Will there be enough
light on the ground floor?
It's cloudy today. Look at
how many windows there are.
[Latch creaking]
Is this a common area?
- No, it's yours. Private.
[Footsteps]
[Bottle rolls]
Do people throw down trash?
- Oh, no. These are cultured people.
The kitchen is quite cramped.
Is there a gas pipeline?
Almost. The pipe's been laid
all the way till the square nearby.
So, there isn't.
- No, not yet.
[Echo]
Bedroom.
It's spacious.
- Yes.
[Switching light on]
[Clangs]
[Metal clangs]
Bed.
- No, no. Bed.
[Clangs]
[Pushing window glass]
There's a strange odour.
You can smell the
sewage in the bedroom.
It is what it is. The house
is good, the landlord is good.
Most importantly,
he is open-minded.
What's that supposed to mean?
It's not supposed to mean anything.
It means he is tall and handsome
and smart and generous.
What's the deposit?
- Finalize it first. We can figure the rest later.
Give us a few minutes to discuss it. We'll let you know.
- Sure.
[Door shuts]
Why're you behaving so
pleased in front of him?
Why will he ever reduce the rent?
Who cares?
- I do.
You like it, right?
I can imagine us
drinking tea out there.
I can imagine us doing a lot more.
[Kissing]
[Sighs]
[Grunts]
[Dazed music]
[Groans]
You have a condom?
- I don't even have my wallet.
Do you want to get
me pregnant again?
[Sighs]
[Exhales]
[Tense music]
Sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
[Sighs]
[Exhales]
Sorry, sorry.
I'm sorry.
That was unfair.
[Sighs]
[Breathing heavily]
[Exhales]
It's a lovely flat.
[Breathes in]
Yes, it does feel like home.
[Soft music]
"Let me, for a moment,
rise and kiss the sky."
"Wrapped in the hush of your
thought, my body fills with colour."
"There is fear. And yet,
something certain beneath it.
"If we walk together,"
"where could we not reach,
what sky could hold us back?"
"Don't go?
My love, don't go."
"Body to body, we catch,
we burn, we become smoke."
"Shame loosens, slips away,
fades into air.'
'Your lips, a slow poison,
sweet, dissolving.
"And in this city of hearts, nothing
but smoke, everywhere just smoke.'"
"Body to body, we catch,
we burn, we become smoke."
"Shame loosens, slips away,
fades into air."
"Your lips, a slow poison,
sweet, dissolving."
"Body to body, we catch,
we burn, we become smoke."
"Don't shut this door now,
Don't look elsewhere,"
"Come back, here,
to where you belong, to me."
"Don't drift away again,
Refuse nothing,"
"Tell me what you want,
just all of it."
"Let us hold each other, steady,
you in me and me in you."
"Let us live this wanting,
restlessness,"
"again and again,
yet again."
"We met and stayed,
pressed close, no holding back."
"All the ifs and buts fell silent.
A new tremor ran through the body."
"Everyone before you,
just noise, false, forgettable."
"And you, as you are, even now..."
"The way you smiled,
the way you stood before me,"
"shame slipped away,
slipped away the pride."
"Yesterday dissolved,
tomorrow dismissed,"
"There is only this,
this moment, this breath, now."
"Don't leave.
Don't turn back."
"And look into me,
deeper, deeper still."
"Further in.
Further, until you fill me."
"Within me."
"Only within me."
"No more going deeper now,
no more talk of love."
"No knots, no fixing,
no ties, no holding."
"Love. Just a beautiful intoxication.
Uncontained, unclaimed."
"No cages, no shut doors.
No holding on. Let me breathe."
"No footsteps to follow,
no tides to answer."
"No debts, no promises.
No sentiment, no judgement."
"No feeling to name,"
"No healing to chase,
no ceiling above."
"I am open, I am free.
Completely, entirely free."
"Body to body, we catch,
we burn, we become smoke."
"Shame loosens, slips away,
fades into air."
"Your lips, a slow poison,
sweet, dissolving."
"And in this city of hearts, nothing
but smoke, everywhere just smoke."
"Body to body, we catch,
we burn, we become smoke."
"Shame loosens, slips away,
fades into air."
"Your lips, a slow poison,
sweet, dissolving."
"And in this city of hearts, nothing
but smoke, everywhere just smoke."
[Vocalizing]
[Soft music]
[Munching]
[Clangs]
Were you at Poona
Club the other day?
When?
Day before yesterday or
maybe a day before that.
[Inhales]
Maybe.
Anand told me. He even said 'hi'
to you but you were distracted.
It was probably Bridge night.
[Footsteps]
It's a good thing
you didn't wait up.
Hello.
Farooq has responded.
I've forwarded it to you.
I'll check.
Sorry, we had to cancel yesterday's plan.
- What plan?
We were going to
come over yesterday.
Oh, is it?
I told Mom?
He's an important guy. And was
hyper excited to meet yesterday.
He really insisted
and I couldn't say no.
Water.
My new proposal's been receiving a good response.
- Good.
I mean it's the same plan.
Body building.
It's not just body
building. Body sclup -?
It's going to be a body-sculpting studio.
- Body-sculpting studio.
It's going to be grand.
There's going to be a
three-floored building
with trainers and
dieticians and many other things.
It's not as simple as it seems.
And I don't just want to do it in this
city. I want to start a whole chain.
How much money do you need?
[Inhales]
I'll manage.
Did you give the car for servicing?
[Tense silent]
The car?
No. It slipped my mind.
What do you do?
I'm a translator.
[Tense silent]
Meaning?
Meaning? I translate.
[Tense silent]
Marathi to English, Spanish to
English, German to English, etcetera.
Why?
[Sighs]
[Munching]
Good money?
- No, not really.
So then?
I mean not at the level at
which I am currently working.
And I haven't yet
explored all my options.
Why not?
I'm not sure.
If you interrogate her, how
do you expect her to open up?
There should be
some comfort level first.
Let her get comfortable, she'll
answer you in five languages.
[Phone vibrates]
Excuse me.
[Shifts chair]
[Water splashing]
[Exhales]
Is he coming back?
- Not if you're going to start crying again.
We're never coming here again.
- Okay, let's not.
I feel physical pain from
being around that man.
I don't know how Mom tolerates him.
I've told her so many times to leave
him; that I'll support her if she does.
I don't want that man in my life.
- Why did you have to speak for me?
I was trying to defend you!
- I was doing just fine.
But it was for you!
[Sighs]
See!
We're fighting because of him!
[Car beeps]
[Car door shuts]
[Muffled cry]
[Sniffs]
You're too good for me.
He could see it.
I think everyone can.
- Okay, enough. Let's go home.
[Staring]
[Encouraging look]
Let's never look at his face again.
Okay. Never again.
Hi!
[Clangs]
[Birds chirping]
Did you change the display again?
Yes, you asked me to.
No, I said keep all the Tsukudani
at the bottom and the
boiled beans on top.
That was yesterday.
Not yesterday. I
told you this morning.
[Clangs]
What you just had
was Shiro Miso. Okay?
[Chuckles]
The one before?
Uh.
Komi? Kome Miso?
- Yes! He's a professional.
[Chuckles]
You should try some eel.
Try the Yamato simmered
eel with Tsukudani.
When do you leave?
In another two days.
Come back towards the end of
March to see the cherry blossoms.
And we have to go to Fuji.
- Of course.
I'm home.
Fuji-san is everywhere. On walls,
on T-shirts, on thousand yen bills.
You can see Fuji from anywhere.
Tokyo Tower,
Shinkansen, even the plane!
But if you're not lucky,
you won't see it at all.
It's a moody mountain.
Just like that, it will
decide not to open
its heart to you.
And if you're very very very lucky,
on a clear day,
you can see it upside down,
reflected perfectly
in the lake below.
I am sorry, but I really don't
understand what can happen
by just looking at it?
A lot can happen.
As you share a
silence with Fuji-san,
[Grins]
You may be able to hear yourself.
[Tense silence]
The mountain can help you see
something you've been blind to.
[Tense music]
Ma?
- Hmm?
May I say something?
Hmm.
He is a good guy.
What was he like
when you were friends?
[Sighs]
He was?
The sweetest boy that I met.
Why didn't you stay in touch?
[Sighs]
Because we had a fight.
- Over what?
Hmm.
It was a grown up fight, Kartu.
[Sighs]
You won't understand yet.
- Okay.
[Sighs]
Are you cold?
- Yes.
Come.
[Footsteps]
[Muffled rustling]
[Sighs]
[Clangs]
Ma?
- Hmm?
May I say something?
[Gulps]
I think he likes me.
[Stares]
Obviously. Everybody likes you.
[Sighs]
That's what you think.
But some of my classmates
don't like me. Okay?
Okay.
Let's tell him to
come to Tokyo again.
Okay. Let's.
For sure?
Hmm.
Not sleepy?
- No.
[Clock ticks]
Shall we read something?
- No. You are tired.
Umm.
Let us.
[Paper ruffles]
[Sighs]
[Exhales]
[Rustles]
So?
For four thousand years, the
volcano had remained quiet.
Hmm.
But recently,
something inside it began to stir.
[Knock]
[Door opens]
[Clangs]
[Laughs]
[Dancing]
Spic and span.
[Whistles]
Clean, clean, clean.
Sparkling clean.
[Thuds]
Nice.
Not bad.
- I know, I know, I know.
You are drenched.
My bike broke down
and it was pouring.
Weren't you supposed to go to the office only once a week?
- Yes.
[Sighs]
So then, how come today?
It's a complicated copy.
It's some report for the comparative
study of three pesticides.
What's for dinner?
Pasta!
[Moves hand]
Nice.
[Jumping]
[Thuds]
[Clicks]
[Clangs]
[Unwrapping]
[Rattling]
[Clangs]
[Sizzling]
[Stirring]
[Knocking]
[Clangs]
[Opens the cover]
Shall I help?
- No.
What should I chop?
[Singing]
[Singing/Groaning]
Why do you have so much
energy at this time of the day?
'I have the power!'
[Sizzling]
[Thunder rumbling]
[Spread]
[Clangs]
[Thunder rumbling]
[Grunts]
[Thunder rattling]
[Sighs]
I need money.
A lot of it.
[Sighs]
[Breathing heavily]
I have to return all the money I
borrowed through my mum's treatment.
I have to return money to
relatives. I have to repay the loan.
Okay.
- It's a lot.
Okay, okay. Calm down.
[Sniffs]
I can understand the stress. But?
There's no need to panic.
We'll manage somehow.
This is the last thought on my mind when I
go to sleep and the first when I wake up.
[Sobbing]
We'll figure it out.
- How?
[Sizzling]
There's always a way. Money
isn't worth thinking about so much.
[Sizzling]
[Munching]
Let's ask dad?
Whom?
It's a negligible
amount for your dad.
And we'll return
every penny. We will?
What?
You know how much
I despise that man.
You have a right to that money. Why
should we have to beg for it elsewhere?
Why can't we find a way on our own?
How are we going to do that?
Please tell me. I'm all ears.
What do we do?
- How can I come up with an instant solution just like that?
But there is always a way.
Like there was with your funding?
I pay the rent. I
pay all the bills.
I pay the maid. I cover most
of the household expenses.
I am translating anything
that comes my way.
I have no relief.
I'm sick of negotiating, of begging people to pay me 40
paise per word instead of 25; if not 40, 35 at least.
[Tense music]
[Water splashing]
[Sighs]
[Tense music]
How do you manage your expenses?
The eating and
drinking out? Petrol?
Mom sends some money each month.
Very little.
You won't even have to meet him.
Please, please, please? please!
I promise I'll repay him as soon as possible. I swear.
- No.
[Sobbing]
[Tense music]
Okay.
We'll figure it out.
[Sighs]
Are you ready?
[Jarring]
Take the card on top.
Look closely. Memorize it.
- Done.
Now fold it. Give that to me.
Hey, hold on to this.
Fold it. - Yes!
Give the card back.
- Oh, I have to give it back?
Obviously. I'm not looking at it.
Come here.
Are you eating something?
- Not at the moment, no.
Open your mouth?
Whoa!
[Laughing]
Now I am going to reveal to you what the card was.
- Yes.
[Indistinct chatter]
It was not a card with a digit.
- That's right.
And it was a red coloured card.
Oye-oye!
[Indistinct chatter]
It was a card of hearts.
Whoo!
And it was a king!
- Where's the proof?
It's right here.
Open your mouth, please.
[Chuckles]
Open?
Whoa!
[Cheering]
The pizza is here.
- Guys, listen! I am not done with the tricks yet.
No, please! Siddhu, listen?
[Grunts]
[Coughs]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Sits]
[Knocking]
[Door opens]
[Singing]
You okay?
[Pulls]
[Kissing]
[Singing]
[Groaning]
[Laughs]
[Sighs]
What's going on?
[Singing]
[Sighs]
[Cheering]
[Applauding]
Mount Everest.
- Village.
[Grunts]
Bonfire?
- Tree?
Tribals.
Warli painting.
A triangle?
- Evolution!
Five, four, three, two, one!
Time up! Your time's up!
You lose! It's over. It's done.
What was the word?
It's Africa!
[Laughing]
[Indistinct chatter]
How is this Africa? You've
drawn everything except Africa.
These are the pyramids right here.
These are people dancing.
[Laughing]
[Clapping]
Sit down. You need a break.
You need to rest for ten minutes.
Why didn't you just draw the map of Africa.
It's basic. Everyone knows that much.
That's so basic. Isn't it so basic?
What does your T-shirt say?
[Chuckles]
Paraguay.
- Paraguay.
Paraguay. Betty, put on
the world map, will you?
[Indistinct chatter]
[Chuckles]
Enough now, you guys lost.
- Here is the world map.
Where is it then? Paraguay?
Look for it.
Why don't you show us?
- These two are playing their own game.
[Chuckles]
Come on, tell us.
Where is Paraguay?
Exactly where it was yesterday.
[Squealing]
No, no. This isn't time
for your comedy. Show us.
Let it be. Who gives a
shit about Paraguay?
Come on. It's so basic.
Why don't you Google it?
Do you want to? Paraguay?
Okay, okay. Okay.
Tell me, is it a country or a city?
[Soft whisper]
A country?
- Yes, 'a country' question mark? Or 'a country' full stop?
Come on!
Okay, guys enough. Enough, enough.
It's the capital of Argentina.
Got it? That's it. Done.
I had forgotten.
- It's okay!
It can happen.
- Of course, it can happen.
It's not! It's not the
capital of Argentina!
[Laughing]
Just say you don't know.
What's the problem?
If you don't know, you
don't know. So, what?
Okay, okay. Last question guys.
What language do
they speak in Paraguay?
Go for it.
Mexican? Italian?
Adriatic? Or Spanish?
Or none of the above.
[Chuckles]
Go for Phone-A-Friend.
Call your dad.
[Squealing]
Sorry.
Okay, okay, silence. So which
language do they speak in over there?
He's feeling shy.
[Whispering]
[Gulping]
What was the third option?
- What was it indeed?
I think it was 'Adriatic'.
- Adriatic.
[Chuckling]
[Laughing]
Adriatic is a sea.
[Chuckling loudly]
[Laughter]
[Chuckles]
[Loud laughter]
[Laughs]
Bye.
- Bye.
Take care.
- Bye, Betty!
[Footsteps]
Hey, bye.
- Bye.
Take care.
- Yes.
See you.
Let's go, guys.
- Let's go.
The keys?
See you on the new year's eve. Bye.
Do you have them?
Let's go.
Come on.
[Footsteps]
What happened?
Was there news about the funding?
[Thunder rumbling]
Okay, come on. Get in the car.
We'll go home and talk. Let's go.
[Footsteps]
[Thuds]
[Sad music]
How can you treat me like this?
[Tense music]
[Thunder rumbling]
Such hatred?
[Tense music]
This much?
[Clangs]
So, the entire car is made here?
Most of its interior parts are.
Different auto components
are made here in the press shop.
We weld them together and
send them to the company.
The final assembly happens
in the respective companies.
[Clangs]
It's Sunday today.
- So?
I thought you called
because it was a holiday.
Can't I wish to meet
you on a working day?
[Clangs]
How is work?
- Great.
Good. So where are you opening the first studio?
- Good morning, Sir!
Thank you for not calling it a gym.
Where do I come for the opening then? When is it?
- Calm down. I'm not there yet.
You must have ordered the equipment by
now, right? Have you secured the space?
I have a couple of options in mind. But I
haven't confirmed anything in person yet.
As long as the money is sorted,
everything else falls into place.
It is as good as done.
Where is the finance
coming from finally?
There are a couple of
people. It's all happening.
Let's see. It'll happen.
Consider it done!
What if it doesn't work?
- What?
What if the plan doesn't work out?
I don't have the option to fail.
Why not?
- I just don't.
Everyone has the option to fail.
If you realize that things are not working
out despite trying your level best,
it's okay to give up, you know.
That's not a possibility for me.
Have you called me here
to convince me to give up?
What's wrong with giving up?
Why must every single person have a success story of some kind?
- They must.
Why?
- Because they must.
[Clangs]
But why?
I don't have an explanation.
No, that's not okay. If you think everyone must have
a success story, you have to be able to say why.
Anything can be made to seem sensible
if you say it at gunpoint like this.
[Machinery sound]
So, what I am saying
does seem sensible to you?
[Tense music]
Leave me alone.
[Machine clanging]
[Clanging]
What is the problem?
Your father is a diamond merchant.
At least four more generations in your
family need not work at all. Why bother then?
[Machine clanging]
Do you only work to
be able to make money?
[Machine clangs]
Absolutely not. But I know why I
work. I'm asking you why you do.
[Machine clanging]
[Machine whirring]
I want to prove a point.
To whom?
No one.
[Clanging]
[Footsteps]
[Whirring]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Clang]
Thank you very much.
How's work?
[Ruffling]
Could you please take the Octopus?
I won't be able to eat it.
[Soft music]
Give it to me.
[Clang]
Work?
- All good.
It was tough initially but
this year our company has released two
new games into the international market.
Hmm.
How come you turned to video games?
Once I stopped trying to prove a
point to anybody else, it found me.
[Munching]
And how was the
meeting you came here for?
Not bad.
They've agreed to let us use
the new software they've developed.
Congratulations.
[Chopping]
Could you please
also take the Shrimp?
Sure.
[Soft music]
[Clang]
[Clincking]
[Clutter]
[Thud]
I don't want to come in
between the two of you.
[Soft music]
What should I do?
[Clang]
It hasn't been easy for her.
[Sighs]
She has taken a lot of
time and effort to build her world.
Now, Haru-san, Nori-san, Kartu and
I together make her whole.
[Inhales]
So, you're not going to
be able to pick and choose.
'I'll take the Tuna
but not the Octopus.'
[Tense music]
'The Salmon is okay
but not the Shrimp.'
[Tense music]
Not possible. Okay?
[Suspenseful music]
[Clanging]
[Thuds]
I'm taking all the papers.
You know our bank manager?
Banerjee?
- Banerjee, yes.
He said that the
meeting is just a formality.
The loan should come through.
Consider it done.
[Sighs]
[Rubbing hands]
[Footsteps]
Let's buy a new laptop tomorrow.
A brand new one.
Hmm.
Umm.
[Clock ticks]
Hey? Hey!
Shall we celebrate today?
Fuji-san. Noon.
[Smooches]
[Smooching]
[Kissing]
Yes.
[Exhales]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Soft music]
[Clang]
[Stirring]
[Soft music]
[Munching]
[Door shuts]
[Tense music]
[Door opens]
[Clangs]
[Switch on]
[Gulps water]
[Gulping]
[Closes the lid]
[Clangs]
[Sobs]
[Tense music]
[Sniffs]
[Sobs]
[Muffled sobs]
[Sighs]
[Tense music]
[Sniffs]
[Sighs]
Yes, Vismay?
[Tense music]
[Intense music]
We have to take care of
this plaster for six weeks.
Make sure it doesn't get wet.
[Ambulance siren]
[Footsteps]
[Sighs]
His arm is fractured.
But the doctor has said there's nothing
to worry about. It should be better soon.
Well.
The bank manager
was being uncooperative.
So, he lost his temper and smashed
his glass table with his own hand.
Please don't say anything to him
right now. We'll talk to him later.
What sense does it make, if in a fit of
rage, you end up causing harm to yourself?
[Cutting]
[Clang]
[Tearing]
[Wrapping]
[Pouring water]
[Sniffs]
[Tense music]
[Sobs]
[Soft music]
[Sighs]
[Tense music]
[Water splashing]
Kartu?
[Tense music]
[Water splashing]
[Clangs]
Hey, champ.
[Grins]
[Kissing hand]
[Kissing]
[Hugging]
If you had to leave so soon, why
did you even bother coming back?
[Nods]
[Holding tight]
[Footsteps]
[Door closes]
[Clangs]
[Sits]
Vismay?
- Not okay.
Once you let him into Kartu's life,
every decision from that point
on, will have to be Kartu's own.
[Sighs]
[Rustles]
I've known Kartu since he was born.
[Intense stare]
I've brought him up along with you.
Whatever you decide,
I cannot walk away
from Kartu's life.
I mean, I refuse.
[Tense music]
He is as much my son
as he is the two of yours.
[Tense music]
[Walks]
[Opens door wide]
[Tense music]
[Footsteps]
Hey, hi!
How cheap can you be! You know
how much it bothers me, don't you?
You know how much I can't stand it!
You know it! You know!
Hey, control yourself!
You! Don't interfere! This
has nothing to do with you!
Wasn't I clear enough? What part did you not understand?
- Hey! Hey, stop!
I told you clearly!
Don't you understand?
Shut up! Let me go. Leave me be!
Don't you get it? Don't you get it?
[Clangs]
[Breathing heavily]
[Sighs]
Sorry.
- Sorry.
[Sighs]
[Birds chirping]
Is it such a problem for
you to see my side of things?
And then you have the audacity to tell my Dad to
not tell me about the money you borrowed from him.
He didn't listen to me, did he?
- Mom told me.
Did you try to see
my side of things?
Did you even notice
me working my ass off?
It's so humiliating to constantly
have to take on substandard work.
[Birds chirping]
[Awkward silent]
Do you even understand
the concept of money?
[Birds chirping]
People spend their whole lives trying to make money and still?
- Oh, shut your trap!
[Birds chirping]
Enough.
[Tense moment]
Let's put an end to
this. It's not working.
[Tense music]
[Sobs]
[Birds chirping]
[Sighs]
[Tense music]
Okay. Let's stop.
What do you do when you get angry?
I never get angry.
[Footsteps]
Shut up.
[Chuckles]
I don't. Really.
Nothing makes you angry?
- Nope. Ask anyone.
Ever since I was a baby, I just don't get angry.
- Liar!
Hey!
[Birds chirping]
Go ahead. Try to make
me lose my temper.
[Footsteps]
To tell you the truth, whenever
I get angry, I feel like crying.
[Birds chirping]
Even I cry sometimes.
- Really?
[Indistinct chatter]
To tell you the truth, I
cry at the drop of a hat.
I cry a lot. Ma
says crying is good.
[Footsteps]
Your Ma is right.
[Birds chirping]
What was Ma like back
when you were friends?
[Tense music]
She was hardworking.
And very funny.
[Chuckles]
And she was a chatterbox.
When she doesn't have answers, she uses her hands a lot.
- Does she? How?
Like this.
Like this?
- Yes.
Did she do that back then too?
Maybe. I didn't notice.
[Train chugging]
[Train speeding]
[Bell]
How soon can I be discharged?
Well, for now just take it
slow and get lots of rest.
My wife is alone at
home, that's why?
If you stay calm and get your rest properly,
we could let you go by tomorrow afternoon.
Please behave yourself!
Luckily it was not a
fracture, it is a contusion.
Ah that's a relief!
He is a mischievous boy, this one.
Now be a good boy!
Be a good boy!
[Machine whirring]
Kartikeya?
What's going on?
Are you trying to trick me?
Listen?
Is it okay if I don't
brush tonight?
[Exhales]
Okay.
But you won't tell her.
You don't tell her either.
[Phone vibrating]
Hi.
[Folding clothes]
Everything is fine.
I locked up at the shop and
handed the key to Nori-san.
We had dinner on the way
home. And Kartu is fast asleep.
[Soft chuckle]
Have you put your phone for charging?
- Yes.
Umm-mm.
I don't know how I would have
managed today if it weren't for you.
It's not such a big deal.
Give me a minute, please?
I've made milkshake.
- Milkshake?
[Whisper]
[Footsteps]
[Clang]
Kartu makes for the best company.
We've been getting along well.
Really?
- Yes, really.
[Cradles the phone]
[Paper ruffling]
[Tense music]
Are you going to tell him?
He needs to know.
[Tense music]
I remember when Kartu
and I
went for our first walk together.
[Chuckles]
That tiny little
palm gripping mine.
[Sighs]
My heart melted.
That's when I thought
for the first time, I might be
able to love unconditionally.
Kartu gave me this car because I'm in the hospital.
He said, “Haru-san, you shouldn't feel alone.”
[Chuckles]
[Hands shivering]
You can see he
loves the boy already.
If it is so obvious,
why can't he see it?
May be he is scared.
[Breathes in]
Some people don't see
things on their own.
They've to be shown.
Umm.
[Tense music]
Kartikeya?
It's very late now.
I'm switching off the lights.
You need to sleep now. Okay?
[Tense music]
[Footsteps]
[Switch off lights]
Come here.
[Footsteps]
What is it?
Listen?
- Hmmm.
It would be okay if you
called me Kartu now.
[Sighs]
[Tense music]
[Sobs]
[Sighs]
[Tense music]
[Grins]
[Hugs]
[Kissing]
Five minutes. I Promise.
Okay.
- Okay.
[Footsteps]
[Punching keyboard]
[Jumps]
Chef special Chicken Afghani and Baigun Bhaja
will be ready in an hour. Just one hour.
Have you diced the onion?
- Yes.
Where is it?
Inside.
Inside where?
On the kitchen counter.
- Where on the kitchen counter?
It's right there. Just look.
- Okay!
I'll just have a quick shower.
No, no. Just cancel it then.
Yes, cancel it and
refund the money.
Yes, okay.
Who was that?
- Leave it.
Come on.
What did you want a refund for?
For the cake.
Our cake?
- Hmm.
Sorry?
- Yes.
Why?
- They didn't have a baked one.
Come on.
I pre-ordered it day before yesterday. Why
do they accept orders if they can't deliver?
Look here. Which one?
So, which one have you ordered now?
- No cake.
[Clicks]
What do you mean no cake?
I mean I haven't
ordered any cake instead.
[Bends]
So, there's no cake coming?
- No.
[Nods head]
So, what are we going to cut then?
[Chuckles]
We can cut the chicken.
I hate those disgusting
gelatin cakes.
[Pulls]
[Downtrodden]
You could have checked with me once.
- It's fine. Just let it go.
I wouldn't have
minded a gelatin cake.
You don't even eat cake. I don't know why you're whining.
- I wanted one today.
Today may not be important
to you, but I'm excited about it.
Oh, please. What is this mood?
'My cake'. 'I like
it'. 'I don't want it'.
So selfish.
You don't give a rat's ass about the other person.
- No, I don't.
Exactly. You don't. The
other person doesn't matter.
It doesn't concern you.
You don't even notice.
You don't want to listen to the other person at
all. Everything has to centre around I, me, myself.
Who cares about anyone
else? They're empty-headed.
They're too dumb to care about.
And what about you? “I'm such
a victim”. “No one listens to me.”
“Nothing ever works out for me.” “My Dad is
this; my Dad is that.” “My Mom is this...”
But you still want to
drive your Dad's car!
[Clangs]
What had I asked you
to do with the onions?
What?
[Shakes pan]
The onion.
When I said I'd cook chicken, what
had I asked you to do with the onions?
What did you ask for?
You said dice them.
Did I ask you to
slice it or chop it?
[Tense moment]
Oh, did you specify?
[Sizzling]
I had clearly asked
you to slice the onions.
[Sizzling]
Okay, maybe you did.
- Not, not maybe. I had asked you to slice the onions.
Okay, fine.
[Sizzling]
Why didn't you listen to me?
What have I done then?
- Look at what you have done.
You have chopped it.
How does it matter? It
was whole and now it isn't.
[Clang]
Seriously?
You have no respect for me.
- What did you say?
If you want me to hear, you're going to have to speak louder.
- You do not respect me!
[Bangs the ball]
Why? Because I didn't cut the onion the way you wanted?
- Yes.
Yes.
[Bangs the ball]
Okay. Next time, I'll make sure it is chopped.
- Not chopped, sliced!
[Splash]
[Footsteps]
[Patting]
Okay, sliced.
[Hugs]
[Insect creaking]
Happy second anniversary.
[Sniffs]
Let's not talk about
onions anymore.
[Insect creaking]
[Animal calls]
Systematic desensitization.
[Insect creaking]
What?
This? this thing that you do to me.
[Insect creaking]
It is systematic desensitization.
Don't throw nonsensical
jargon from Instagram at me.
Ignore anything the other
person ever says or asks for.
Until they start to
believe they're unworthy.
That they don't deserve
to be treated well.
If that's the case, why
don't you leave me.
Get up, come on. Leave me and go. We're not
bound to each other. Come on, get up. Leave.
Go, get going now.
Go!
As depressing as it is to be with you,
it is more depressing to be alone.
Whose problem is that?
- It's mine!
[Dog barking]
[Insect creaking]
It is my problem. So
then? Yes, it is my problem.
[Insect creaking]
[Dog barks]
Why should I respect you?
[Insect creaking]
[Dog barks]
'Why'?
- Yes. Why?
[Dog barks]
What about you is
worth taking seriously?
[Insect creaking]
Is there nothing?
- What is?
[Sobs]
[Sniffs]
Do you not get anything from me?
- What do I get?
[Sobs]
How much more will you take?
[Sniffs]
How much more?
[Sits]
I feel empty.
[Sobs]
[Sniffs]
I can only give if
I'm left with anything.
[Insect creaking]
[Clangs]
Don't be in a hurry.
[Sniffs]
Think about it
carefully and seriously.
[Sniffs]
What do I get from you?
[Insect creaking]
You're constantly cursing your Dad.
He gave me money, at least.
[Insect creaking]
He asked about my well being.
When have you ever supported me with anything?
- Do the two of you talk behind my back?
He asked me if the pressure
from the loan is any less.
[Sobs]
Did it occur to you to ask?
[Sniffs]
[Insect creaking]
Return the money you borrowed.
[Tense silent]
How does it concern you?
[Insect creaking]
Where's your phone?
[Clangs]
What?
- Transfer the money to me right now.
[Clangs]
What are you doing?
Return the money.
- My phone isn't in there.
[Clutters]
What did you do with the money?
What do you mean? I returned it to
the people I had borrowed money from.
All of it?
- Most of it.
And the rest?
- It's in the bank.
Where is your phone?
[Clanging]
[Insect creaking]
Where is it? Where have you kept your phone?
- I won't give it to you!
Return the money. Return it.
- I do plan to return it. But to your Dad.
What is my Dad to you even?
If we're not going to be together,
what is my Dad to you?
Oh, I see. So now we're not going to be together, are we?
- Just return the bloody money!
[Sobs]
I won't return it.
Not today, not tomorrow, not ever.
Let's see what you do.
[Sobs]
[Cracking]
Give me your phone.
[Tense music]
- Let me go.
Give me the phone.
- No, I won't.
Give it to me.
- No!
Give me the phone. Give it.
Give the phone.
What is the password?
- Not going to tell you.
What's the password? Tell me the password.
- No. Never.
Give me the password.
- I am not going to. Don't you get it?
Tell me the password.
- No!
[Clanging]
Tell me the password. Tell me the password now.
- Put down my laptop.
Tell me the password.
- Put down my laptop, please.
Password.
- Please put down the laptop.
Tell me the password.
- Put down my laptop first.
Tell me the password!
- Put down my laptop.
Password.
- Put the laptop down!
Give me the password. One last time.
- Put down my laptop!
Leave it. It's my earning.
Just give me the password.
[Tense music]
I am asking you the last time.
- Put the laptop away first.
Password.
- Put the laptop down. Put it down please.
Put it?
[Dismantaling the laptop]
[Bangs]
[Thuds]
[Clanging]
[Tense music]
[Sobs]
[Sighing]
You are a curse.
[Sighs]
Nothing can remain alive near you.
[Tense music]
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Where are you going?
- Leave me, let me go.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
- Let me go. Let go!
I'm sorry.
- Leave me.
You promised you would
never leave me. Please!
[Muffled cry]
[Yelling]
[Sobs]
[Yells]
[Screaming]
[Tense music]
[Screams]
[Sobs]
[Tense music]
[Sobs, Gates creaks]
[Sobs]
[Yells]
[Clangs]
[Clicks]
[clangs]
[Door shuts]
He's asleep.
I'm almost done.
- Okay.
[Clangs]
If I came back in a year, would Kartu recognize me?
- Of course. Why wouldn't he?
Actually, one year is a long
time for a seven year old.
[Clangs]
[Pouring water]
Why do you want to meet him again?
[Covering the lid]
[Footsteps]
Why did you come looking
for me the other day then?
[Scraping]
I'm starving. Can we start?
[Smiles]
[Clangs]
[Sputtering]
[Munching]
Umm.
[Clang]
Vismay is a good guy.
It's not as easy as it looks.
[Laughs]
[Chuckles]
What?
I want the best for you. Do
you not find that believable?
[Grins]
I do.
[Chuckles]
I honestly do.
When did we stop
listening to each other?
I don't remember.
How is it going to
help to remember?
[Chuckles]
[Smoking]
Everyone and their mother-in-law did a post
mortem of our relationship after you left.
Oh, God!
[Laughs]
People acquire exceptional clarity when they
are analysing other people's relationships.
[Laughs]
[Sighs]
How can the very thing one fell in love
with, become so frustrating afterwards?
[Sighs]
[Grins]
We lived under the same roof
but led two very different lives.
[Chuckles]
And they overlapped less and less.
[Tense music]
[Lift whirring]
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
[Exhales]
[Water splashing]
[Footsteps]
[Door clangs]
[Tense music]
Hi!
Please meet me once.
- No.
[Sobs]
I won't ever force you to again.
- No.
I promise.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Please meet me. Just once. Please.
- No.
Please.
[Tense music]
Fuji-san. Tomorrow.
Okay.
[Sobs]
[Tense music]
[Exhales]
[Motor whirring]
Hello? Hello. Hello!
[Music]
We were supposed to
meet today. I waited for you.
When will you leave me alone?
[Music]
I have something to tell you.
Please listen to me. Please listen?
Please listen to me.
Could you, once and for all?
♪ Once and for all,
kindly go to hell ♪
Hey! What's the matter?
I'm pregnant.
[Tense music]
I said I'm pregnant.
Can't you see? What are you some kind of moron?
- Hey!
Hey!
And I don't want to have
an abortion this time. Please!
Hey!
[Music]
Hello! Can you hear me?
[Tense music]
This is what happens.
It's not enough to
want to remember.
What happens if both people
remember the same past differently?
I know I behaved badly.
Not a single day goes by when I don't
regret my behaviour from that time.
But the fact remains that not once did you
try and see the situation my point of view.
I...
- No.
I would share so many ideas
with you about my studio.
And I could see it clearly in your eyes
that you had absolutely no confidence in me.
What on earth was that idea even?
[Laughs]
Even you let it go, didn't you?
- Sure, I did. I did. But that's not the point.
You could have said to
me once, “You are capable.”
“If not this, then something else. But you
will make something of yourself for sure.”
[Sighs]
But you? what was it you said?
“What do I get from you?”
And, “Why do you
deserve to be respected?”
[Sighs]
Did you once say, “Sorry, you have a lot on your
plate. You're carrying a very heavy burden.”
How is that going to occur to anyone under so much pressure?
- And was I not under pressure?
When you abandoned me and refused to associate with me in
the end, did you know what kind of a condition I was in?
I don't think you ever loved me.
Actually, I think all you
ever felt was hatred.
Sometimes it's hard to tell the difference
between extreme love and extreme hatred.
[Staring]
[Clang]
[Shaking]
[Laughs]
[Room shaking]
[Sighing]
[Laughing]
[Breathing heavily]
[Door opens]
[Clangs]
You okay?
So, the sleeping rule
only applies to me alone?
No.
- I don't want to sleep.
So, then what do you want to do?
What do you want to do?
Dance.
[Chuckles]
You want to dance?
Okay. Here we go.
[Chuckles]
Which dance?
- Put me down first. How can I dance like this?
Sure, you can. Sure, you can.
Yes, you can.
My favourite song!
- Is it?
[Music]
[Song]
[Vocalizing]
[Soft music]
Ma, this is a dormant
volcano, right?
Hmm.
So, there is lava inside?
Yes.
[Soft music]
We should leave.
You have a flight to catch.
[Tense music]
Let's stay for a bit.
Just a little bit longer.
[Water rippling]
[Tense music]
[Bell]
[Soft music]