=Eight Hundred=
(Year 1995)
If there are no problems, just sign it.
Kaiming, technically,
as a technician here at the mine,
(Agreement on Compensation for Termination of Labor Relations)
you aren't on the early retirement list.
But you haven't really been
coming to work these past two years.
The mine leadership
is in a difficult position.
I know.
Sir, but my...
My wife just passed away.
Please give me another chance.
Your wife passed away two years ago.
The factory has already
been very understanding.
The factory is struggling now, too.
There's really nothing we can do.
Listen to me.
Just sign it.
At least you'll get some money.
(Huo Kaiming)
Who are you?
I'm Huang Liang.
I came here specifically to find you.
I don't know you.
I'm here...
I'm here to offer you a job.
You're a man who knows technology.
At my place,
I won't mistreat you.
But there's one thing
I have to say upfront.
I run an illegal coal pit.
In Fengyang,
you can't let anyone know.
Eat up.
After you finish eating,
I'll take you for a tour of the pit.
Then, we'll go to the village
to find you a woman.
This is the safety supervisor
of my mine.
Tonight,
just make sure you take good care of him.
How about having
these two girls serve him together?
I guarantee
your supervisor will be satisfied.
You two had better be sharp.
Hey, let's go get a massage.
I know a lot of techniques.
Are you new here?
I haven't seen you before.
Are you from Yunchuan, too?
A fellow townsman!
What's your name?
Huo Kaiming.
And what's yours?
Jiao Yuqin.
(Three months later)
Try drinking some of this.
Be good.
Kaiming,
I'm pregnant.
What did you say?
Do you
not want it?
Of course I want it.
I've been married for so many years
and never had a child.
I thought no one would be there
to take care of me in my old age.
I'm so happy.
Then,
will you marry me?
I will.
We'll go register tomorrow.
Good.
I have a house here.
I'll provide for you.
I don't want to stay in Fengyang anymore.
Why?
Doing the work I do,
everyone around here knows me.
If people see me
out on the street later on,
what will the child do?
Then, what should we do?
Come back to Yunchuan with me.
In the past two years,
I've saved a bit of money.
We can borrow
a little more from relatives.
We can start a small business.
No matter how hard life gets,
as long as our family
is together, it's fine.
Alright.
I'll sell the house here.
That way we'll have money
for the business too.
Good.
That's wonderful.
I'm finally having a baby.
That's wonderful!
This is the money from the house.
Work one more month,
and once I get my salary,
we'll go back to Yunchuan.
You're not eating?
There's no time.
I'm going down the shaft.
Wait a moment.
Drink your medicine before you go down.
Oh, right.
Take this too.
What is this?
It's also for your bronchitis.
Take these two together.
It'll be good for your throat.
You're so good to me.
This medicine
really pips me up after drinking it.
Is that so?
Mr. Huo!
=Episode 5=
(Death Benefit Bride)
That's impossible.
This medicine shouldn't do that.
She added something to it.
She said it was medicine for bronchitis.
Bronchitis medicine?
Liar.
You must have bewitched her.
You scum
who sell drugs!
Mr. Huo,
don't get so worked up.
You said Jiao Yuqin
gave you the medicine in a bottle?
How else?
Otherwise, how would I know
the medicine in your bag was this kind?
Since last year, I haven't allowed those
who take goods from me
to sell them by the bottle.
A couple of days ago, I saw
someone holding a whole bottle.
Are you talking about the person
who was burned to death at Beimianling?
None of your business.
Just tell me,
when can you find her?
Why do you
insist on finding her?
Even if I find her for you,
what could you possibly do?
For every one I find,
I'll kill one.
Everyone who lied to me
must die.
Did Chen Hui send you?
The person has been contacted.
Are you sure it's him?
Positive.
What's this for?
When he arrives,
it'll be easier to contact you.
Where's Jiao Yuqin?
(Yingxiong Welcomes You)
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
♪Perhaps there are
too many things I don't understand♪
♪Maybe it's my fault♪
♪Perhaps everything
has slowly passed us by♪
♪Maybe there's no need to say more♪
♪Never thought
you and I would end like this♪
What is this?
Give me the bag.
What are you doing?
You sold the medicine
to Jiao Yuqin, didn't you?
Are you crazy? Who's Jiao Yuqin?
- I don't know her.
- Is it you?
Keep your voice down!
I'm telling you, give it to me!
What are you doing?
I won't give it to you.
♪Maybe there's no need to say more♪
♪Never thought
you and I would end like this♪
♪No certainty in my heart♪
♪Just remembering the promises we made♪
♪Time and again, those impulses♪
♪Don't break my heart, be gentle again♪
♪I don't want to see your silence♪
Tell me what you saw at the time.
I went to a friend's house tonight,
and I was coming back a bit late.
Just as I reached the road ahead,
I saw a fire over here.
I rushed over to check,
and I found
someone lying inside.
It scared me to death.
I called the police immediately.
Did you see anyone else at the time?
No.
Chief Liu.
What's the situation at the scene?
The body was already
charred when we arrived.
Master.
Did you record the statement
of the person who reported it?
Yes.
Master, could this be related to
the Beimianling body-burning homicide?
It's hard to say right now.
This is the second body-burning homicide
in Fengyang Town
in a short period of time.
We'll have to wait
for the autopsy results.
I contacted Tang before I came.
She'll arrive
tomorrow morning at the earliest.
We need to find a place
to preserve the body first.
Limin,
hurry up and contact the mortuary
at the Workers' Hospital.
Okay.
Easy does it.
Based on these blood spatters,
the killer should have
stabbed the victim here
and burned the body.
So you're saying
the body was moved?
Look.
There are clear drag marks here.
It means someone
dragged the body over.
That's what I don't understand.
If the killer murdered him there,
why drag him all the way here?
It doesn't look like the killer's doing.
Look.
The plants in this area
show clear signs of being burned.
But the area around the body doesn't.
This person likely
wanted to pull him out of the fire.
So there was a third person at the scene?
As long as we find the third person,
we'll know who the killer is.
What's wrong with your eyelid?
It keeps twitching.
Sticking something on it.
It's potassium manganate.
It's the same as
what was on Yu Susu's body.
Anything else?
Fingerprints are a no-go.
The autopsy will have to be done
back at the municipal PSB.
Wait.
Forceps.
Master,
this is a pager casing.
Chief Liu,
we can find
the third person from the scene now.
(Buying Pagers
and Cell Phones at High Prices)
Boss, I have a pager here.
See if you can take it.
I can't guarantee it can be reconnected.
Anyway, I found it.
Just give me what you can.
I'll call a friend over to take a look.
He's an expert.
If this thing is good,
he'll even pay a higher price.
Chen?
It's me, Sun,
from behind the Commercial Building.
Aren't you buying those
pagers that can't be transferred?
I have a young fellow here who has one.
Why don't you
come over and check it out?
Keep him there.
I'll be right there.
Wait for me.
Okay.
How much longer for your friend?
Almost here.
Any minute now.
I'm not selling it today.
Wait a bit longer.
Where did the pager come from?
I found it.
Think carefully!
I really found it.
Really.
Not talking, are you?
What's going on?
This really has nothing to do with me.
It really has nothing to do with me.
I didn't kill him.
I really didn't kill Lu Yuan.
I really didn't kill him.
I really didn't.
How did you know
the one who died was Lu Yuan?
Speak!
What exactly happened?
Yuan.
The brat called me.
I'm going to get the money.
You have to come with me.
What am I going for?
I suspect this brat
is going to play dirty with me again.
Don't you remember
he did that last time?
You just find a place to hide.
If things go wrong,
you just shout loudly.
After it's done, I'll give you 2,000 yuan.
Later,
I hid in the bushes.
I thought if anything happened,
I'd rush out.
But I didn't expect that person to just
kill Lu Yuan right away.
Then, he poured
something on him.
The fire just erupted.
When the fire first started,
it was even purple.
I didn't dare come out
until the man drove away.
I wanted to save him,
but the fire was just too big.
So I...
Did you see what the killer looked like?
That day,
his headlights were so bright
that I could only see a silhouette.
He seemed a bit taller than Lu Yuan,
but I really couldn't see anything else.
Could you see what car it was?
It seemed to be a red sedan.
Yes.
A red sedan.
How did you know Lu Yuan?
We met at the video hall.
He often watched videos alone.
He looked pretty lonely,
so I thought I'd keep him company.
Tell the truth.
I am.
He was a tube popsicle vendor.
I always bought them from him,
and we often ate them together.
That's how we met.
Did Lu Yuan eat tube popsicles too?
Did he tell you
who his supplier
actually was?
No, really.
He never told me
who his supplier was.
I swear,
never.
I never expected
the victim to be Lu Yuan.
Looking at Guo Liansheng,
it really doesn't seem like he's lying.
Big guy.
This is Lu Yuan's pager number.
Go check the call records immediately.
Okay.
Chief Liu,
I suggest
we search the whole town
for red sedans.
And we need Guo Liansheng's cooperation
to create a composite sketch of Lu Yuan.
Conditions here
are too limited.
We can't find a sketch artist.
I'll coordinate with the municipal PSB.
We'll send him there for the sketch.
That would be great.
Once we have Lu Yuan's sketch
and find out his real identity,
we'll be one step closer
to the truth of this case.
(One year ago)
Help.
Liang.
Help...
He's alive.
Pull him up!
Let me go.
I won.
I'm done.
Alright.
Stop wailing.
Liang...
Liang, I beg you.
Let me go, please.
Let me go, Liang.
Let go.
Don't freaking beg me.
Listen here, Huo Kaiming.
Your wife took
250,000 from me.
That was the price for your life.
But now that you're alive,
don't you have to give
that 250,000 back to me?
Liang,
I beg you,
I beg you...
Don't beg me.
I'm begging you, Mr. Huo.
I'm the victim here.
You guys cheated me out of my money.
You guys conned me.
What would you do if you were me?
I wouldn't dare con you, Liang.
Yuqin must have thought I was dead,
that's why she took the money.
She must have gone back to our hometown.
Let me go find her.
I'll bring her back from home
and give the money
back to you, okay, Liang?
Huo Kaiming,
can you clear your head for a second?
Jiao Yuqin conned you too.
You think after she conned you,
she'd go home and wait for you,
just waiting for you to come back
and take the money back?
No.
Liang,
Yuqin wouldn't lie to me.
She wouldn't lie to me.
She's pregnant with my child.
I didn't see that coming.
You're quite the romantic, aren't you?
Fine.
You know, I'm a reasonable man too.
Come here.
Look, I have an IOU here.
Put your thumbprint on it,
and I'll let you go find her.
(IOU)
Liang, three days?
That's too short.
I'm giving you three days.
Find this person for me,
and get my 250,000
back for me.
I'm a man of my word.
Here's your travel money.
Now get lost.
Get out.
(Yunchuan)
Excuse me, sir.
Could I ask you something?
Is there someone
named Jiao Yuqin in this village?
Jiao Yuqin?
Her whole family died over a decade ago.
She was married off
when she was seventeen.
Married off at seventeen?
That's right.
That's impossible.
Is there anyone else
with the same name, another Jiao Yuqin?
No.
Just her.
Do you know
where she moved to?
No idea.
Go ask over there.
Jiao Yuqin!
Who are you?
Does Jiao Yuqin live here?
What do you want with her?
Jiao Yuqin.
- What are you doing?
- Jiao Yuqin!
It's Huo Kaiming.
What are you doing? This is my house!
- Jiao Yuqin!
- Don't you dare start anything!
Jiao Yuqin!
Come out!
- Jiao Yuqin, are you there?
- What do you think you're doing?
Sir, I'm not here to cause trouble.
I'm just looking for Jiao Yuqin.
Tell her to come out and talk to me.
What's your relationship with her?
I'm her husband.
She's even pregnant with my child.
That's why I'm so desperate to find her.
That wretched woman.
She ran off after being
married to me for six months.
And she's pregnant with your child?
Don't be so hasty.
No, no.
That's impossible.
She's my wife.
How could she have married you?
When are you talking about?
That was several years ago.
Well, that's even more wrong.
Even more wrong.
Sir,
take a look.
Is this the woman you're talking about?
This isn't Jiao Yuqin.
This one is Jiao Yuqin.
Look closely.
This is Jiao Yuqin.
Then, who is she?
Who is she?
How should I know?
I think
you're just like her.
You're both fools.
Yuqin,
you must have been conned.
Liars,
go to heck.
(Glycerol)
Chief Liu,
our leads kept going cold before.
But we've finally made some progress.
Limin found
Lu Yuan's call records.
Those guys selling Peidun Cough Syrup
won't be able to escape now.
Let's hope so.
During this time,
you've worked hard.
Chief Liu,
if there's anything I did
wrong before,
please don't mind.
I did have
some opinions about you at first.
Especially when I first arrived in town,
that time the truck driver's father
came to ask you for help.
Hongbing,
it's just a small token.
About my son's matter,
please help us out.
(Chunghwa Cigarettes)
This is way too blatant.
This is yours, right?
Keep the cigarettes,
but return the money to me.
I'll get the money for you right now.
It would be so much easier
to just take the money.
It would save you a trip.
Then, the nature of this would change.
Director Chen,
count it. It's exactly 1,200 yuan.
Later, when I was
questioning the truck driver,
and the detention center director
asked me to bring the receipt to you,
I realized I had misunderstood you.
(Receipt: Received 1,200 yuan
from Chen Hongbing)
1,200?
Yes.
I assume
the family member
went to see Director Chen again.
Does he run into this often?
Occasionally.
Sometimes,
when the criminals' families run
out of options,
they all go to see Director Chen.
Why doesn't he
just return the money directly to them?
He will return it directly if he can.
But for some families,
if you return the money,
they will think
it's because they didn't give enough.
And they'll turn around
and buy even more expensive gifts.
When that happens,
Director Chen usually deposits the money
directly into the suspect's account.
Handling cases here
at the grassroots level
is indeed different
from how we do it in the city.
I've been learning as well.
You've worked hard
during this time, Director Chen.
We're veteran
police officers, aren't we?
It's only right
doing our duty.
I
don't like owing anyone favors.
You and your wife
have taken good care of me.
Even though I didn't want to,
I still owe you.
Don't worry about favors.
By the way,
I've been busy these past few days
and haven't had a chance to tell you.
I've already submitted
Gao Ying's paperwork.
I'll let you know
once the municipal PSB gets back to us.
Thank you.
(Elegant Magnolia Powder Cream)
Chief Liu,
what brings you here?
Director Chen.
What is this?
This is cosmetics I bought for your wife
the last time I went back to the city.
Please give it to Mrs. Chen for me.
Don't, Chief Liu.
Look at you.
Now that you're here,
you can't just leave.
Come inside.
This doesn't seem appropriate.
Come on in.
Ding Yue,
look who's here.
Chief Liu is here.
Na,
have some of these
scrambled eggs with tomatoes.
Give them a try.
I'm not particularly good at cooking.
I hope they're to your liking.
It's been a long time since I've had
this kind of home-cooked flavor.
It's delicious.
If you like it,
then come over often.
You can't eat the food at
the guesthouse every day, right?
Come often.
Thank you.
I'd rather not be a bother.
It's no trouble at all.
Here.
Thank you.
Thanks too.
Have some eggs.
Hongbing.
- Dad, why are you awake?
- Give me...
Give me a bath.
Scrub my back.
A bath?
Didn't I just wash you at noon?
When did we do that?
Alright.
I'll be right there.
You guys go ahead and eat.
Come on.
Dad.
Sit down.
You're really big on hygiene, aren't you?
Tell me about it.
It's fine.
The old man has moments
of clarity and confusion.
Eat more vegetables.
And this tofu.
It's all quite delicious.
Na,
there's something
I've been wanting to ask you.
This illness of yours,
it's been a while, right?
Do you know what it is yourself?
Illness?
I don't have any illness.
I saw the needle marks
from the IV on your arm.
They've already scarred.
With IV drips at this frequency,
it must be an immune system issue.
I saw it that day
when I was giving you the IV.
Mrs. Chen,
about this matter,
did you tell Director Chen?
Though we don't have
discipline like you police,
we don't discuss
patient matters with others.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
I didn't mean anything else by it.
I just wanted to remind you
that your health is what matters most.
Don't let your work
compromise your health.
Director Chen,
Mrs. Chen,
actually, there's something
I've been holding in for a long time.
I didn't know
if I should tell you.
What is it?
Tell us.
My illness
is untreatable now.
What illness is untreatable?
Yes, what is it?
Lymphoma.
It had already spread when it was found.
That day,
I thought I would die in the guesthouse.
But you came.
I felt that having family
is truly wonderful.
It's okay.
Chief Liu,
don't be sad.
Go back to the city
and recover properly.
Any progress on the case here,
I will report to you at any time.
Director Chen, don't try to persuade me.
This should be
the last case I take.
No matter what,
I have to see it through.
Also,
please keep this a secret for me.
Let me fully enjoy the joy of working.
Understood.
This way.
Last night,
in the wasteland outside Fengyang Town,
another body-burning homicide occurred.
According to the police investigation,
the suspect
was driving a red car.
Everyone,
if you spot a suspicious red vehicle,
please contact this station.
What's wrong?
Did something happen up ahead?
It's nothing.
You just finished dialysis.
Rest a bit more.
Hello.
Registration
and driver's license, please.
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
Chen Hui.
There seems to be someone outside.
Chen Hui!
Songge!
♪I always thought
once we see the full picture♪
♪We could understand
each other with empathy♪
♪I always thought
the path we never took♪
♪Must have had more beautiful scenery♪
♪I always thought
once we see the full picture♪
♪We could understand
each other with empathy♪
♪I always thought
the path we never took♪
♪Must have had more beautiful scenery♪
♪Keep moving forward
and don't look back♪
♪The shore is only reached
by the road ahead♪
♪Too much debt has accumulated♪
♪Lit night♪
♪Unfortunately, the breeze in town♪
♪Can no longer catch up to the children♪
♪Times have changed♪
♪Now, everything♪
♪Is no longer what it used to be♪