♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 29=
Right.
Now that we're in the capital,
it's do or die.
(Yuzun Pavilion)
Mr. He.
You're here.
Mr. Chu.
What a coincidence.
Is this a gift for someone?
Exactly.
I'm staying at the Xiao Mansion.
This is for Mr. Xiao
and his wife.
(This person)
(looks very familiar.)
(She resembles the woman
in the painting.)
Mr. Chu, who is this lady?
Well...
Who are you?
Are you close with Zilan?
I'm He Yan,
a friend of Mr. Chu.
Mr. Chu,
I'll take my leave.
See you.
(Ganming Pavilion)
Yuzun Pavilion, right?
Let's go.
(Yuzun Pavilion)
(It seems)
(Chu Zhao is interested)
(in He Yan.)
(I wonder)
(how Miss Xu will react)
(when she finds out?)
(Xu Mansion)
Miss Xu.
You seem
upset.
What's it to you?
Have you heard the story
about the female general of Jiyang?
Female general of Jiyang?
Never mind.
You showed such
refreshing honesty earlier.
Had you taken up sword and service,
history would
remember you as renowned
as that female general.
Haven't you heard, Miss Xu?
The female general He Yan
achieved remarkable feats
in the battle of Jiyang,
defending the city.
She is a role model for women.
By the way,
she's just returned to Yaojing.
He Yan?
Mr. He.
You're here.
What a coincidence, Mr. Chu.
He Yan
is actually a woman?
Correct.
She's a good female general.
I hear
that even Mr. Chu
holds her in high regard.
Though
whispers of her serving
in the army cross-dressed
have reached the common folk,
it remains unknown to His Majesty.
His Majesty even made her
Attendant Wu'an.
Who knows
what will happen
to He Yan
if His Majesty
discovers the truth?
Naturally,
it's a capital offense.
Hey!
Are you zoning out?
General Yan.
I am glad to see you.
Please.
Sit and drink with me.
You treat He Yan quite specially.
I came to see you,
yet you didn't even pour me liquor?
You have hands.
I do have hands.
But he doesn't?
It's chilly.
I'll fetch you a coat.
I'm just saying.
Why did he take it seriously?
Actually,
all these years,
he's only shown concerns
about He Rufei.
But now,
he cares about you too.
You seem
slightly better than He Rufei.
But don't go doing the things he did.
He cares about He Rufei?
You might not believe this.
Xiao Jue
painstakingly taught General Feihong
Qinglang Sword Style
day after day.
How is that possible?
Why wouldn't it be?
I saw it with my own eyes.
No, like this?
Xiao Jue,
you're secretly standing
outside He Rufei's room
just to teach a fool swordsmanship?
You secretly followed me
just to watch me
coach a fool?
T-That's not the same.
Have you lost your mind?
Why waste time on a fool
like him?
Are you even listening to me?
Why bother
with a fool?
I don't consider it a waste of time.
You coach him daily,
yet his progress
is barely noticeable.
He gets help from a top student,
yet he remains mediocre.
It's laughable.
I'll go tell him right now
that if he's got no talent,
he shouldn't waste your time.
Let's fight a duel.
I once tried so hard to force him
to accept my challenge.
Yet he always refused.
But he agreed
because I promised
to keep it a secret
from the ingrate He Rufei.
Can you believe it?
Xiao Jue must be blind.
Each one at Xianchang Academy
is better than He Rufei,
an ungrateful wretch.
So that's how these
Qinglang Sword Style techniques work.
Who kindly
left these notes to me?
(Feet still. Reverse sword spin.
Sweep waist, thrust left)
(Feet planted, turn left,
step right into bow stance)
There's more.
Once during archery class,
He Rufei forgot his thumb ring.
Xiao Jue
gave his own spare
(to He Rufei.)
Where's my thumb ring?
Size doesn't matter.
Better than nothing.
Are you even listening to me?
What took Xiao Jue
so long?
Whatever.
My wife is waiting for me.
I'm leaving.
So, that's how it was.
What is inside?
(You left a letter)
and a pouch,
and then disappeared.
What's that about?
What?
You left something else?
Nothing else.
Yan He couldn't wait
and left.
It's okay.
Put your cloak on.
All these days,
it's been like walking through darkness
alone.
No one noticed my existence.
No one cared about
my joys or sorrows.
No cheers,
and no apologies.
Happiness or grief,
beginnings or endings,
it was a story about a lonely person.
Until one day,
someone saw me.
(Back at Xianchang Academy,)
(the one secretly
teaching me swordsmanship)
was you.
(The one who lent me a thumb ring)
was also you.
Why were you so kind to me?
Back then,
(I was timid)
(and felt inferior.)
(Nobody respected me.)
To be honest,
at first, I did look down on you.
But you are so tenacious
and stubborn.
You never give up on yourself.
Perhaps our situations
are too similar.
At such a young age,
we chose
to shoulder the family's burdens.
My life
was also once low-point.
Sometimes,
I felt helpless.
That's why whenever I saw you
practicing alone
so hard,
I saw myself reflected in you.
I couldn't help but want
to be kind to you.
It felt like
compensating for my younger self.
Look.
Tonight's moon
is so beautiful.
Are you
returning this to me
because it looks ugly?
You noticed.
It looks terrible.
I wish to be like the bright moon,
guarding you forever.
(Rundu is in peril. I'm going to help.
I need your sword.)
♪Walking through the crowd,
without asking about the future♪
Every time Commander misunderstands me,
it breaks my heart.
Go on.
You and I met
in a former life.
I was once a female general.
I thought
you'd say "I will be."
The last secret.
I love the moon.
Yet the moon doesn't know.
♪Just to tread the snow you described♪
Do you still love the moon?
Yes.
♪It's hard to sever love or hatred♪
♪Before fate is confirmed♪
♪My love rests between your fingers♪
Now,
the moon belongs to you.
You're the first one
I taught swordsmanship to.
(You're the first one
I tended wounds to.)
(You're the first one I gave candy to.)
(You're the first one)
(I bought clothes for.)
You're the first girl
I tried to comfort.
(You're the first one)
(I covered for.)
Finally, I realize
that in my life,
the only person I love
is you.
♪Snow falls on windowsills,
moments fading away♪
♪Before fate is confirmed♪
♪My love for you burns fiercely♪
♪Lifelong devotion turns into a vow♪
♪That's my last wish♪
♪Awaiting the spread of moonlight♪
Since Xiao Jue and your sister
already suspect you,
they'll maintain high alert
during the return to the capital.
Our failure this time
was expected.
Chancellor.
What's our next move?
Perhaps
we strike first
before they meet His Majesty.
Our earlier failure
means we've lost the best chance.
You must stay calm now.
Currently,
their biggest obstacle
is a lack of evidence.
So,
you shouldn't act rashly,
avoiding giving them leverage.
I can't keep calm, Chancellor.
They're coming to the capital
to find evidence.
Are we just doing nothing?
There's a prerequisite
that the evidence exists.
Did you
leave any trace of what we did?
Chancellor.
He Yan and I
cannot coexist in this world.
Therefore,
since I worked with you,
I've held nothing back from you.
Tonight's Mid-Autumn banquet
marks the beginning.
I will
settle things clearly
with He Rufei.
Huaijin.
Are you ready?
I've been waiting
so long for this.
I guess
this must be
He Rufei, the renowned
General Feihong.
I am He Yan,
Attendant Wu'an.
General Feihong,
are you feeling unwell?
You should stay at Yuhua Temple
for your health.
Its location is excellent.
It's ideal for physical recuperation.
You're just second-rate.
I won't
stoop to your level.
Second-rate?
His Majesty made He Yan
Attendant Wu'an.
Are you
questioning His Majesty's judgment?
Take it one step at a time.
- Right?
- Sure.
That makes sense.
Huaijin.
Why does Mr. Yang seem
to hate you?
Back in Chonghuai,
I heard from Yang Mingzhi
about your conflict with Mr. Yang.
It puzzled me greatly back then.
I've long heard
that Mr. Yang, Minister of War,
is upright
and loyal to His Majesty.
How could he ally with Xu Jingfu?
Once in a morning meeting,
Mr. Yang's aggressive stance
incensed me.
But upon reflection,
I think he is
excessively upright.
He sees the world
in black and white.
So,
Xu Jingfu
used him
as a pawn against others.
Mr. Liu, cheers.
Cheers.
Let's drink.
Drink.
To you.
- Excellent.
Splendid.
The dance was superb.
Is Attendant Wu'an present?
I, He Yan,
pay respects, Your Majesty.
Rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Attendant Wu'an,
you raided enemies
at night,
burned their granaries,
and defeated Wutuo
in Rundu.
I've heard much about your feats.
You are
a capable young man.
Thank you.
The credit belongs to all.
The victory in Rundu
depended on civilians and soldiers.
With the help
of Commander Xiao and General Yan,
we won.
You're very humble.
Good!
Minister Xiao.
You trained a good soldier.
Thank you.
I simply employed standard drills
for military training.
His achievements stem
from exceptional dedication.
He has
worked so hard.
Attendant Wu'an,
I'm curious
about one thing.
Since you serve under Commander Xiao,
why didn't you impersonate him,
a man you know better,
instead of General He?
After all, General Fengyun
is as famous as
General Feihong.
Your Majesty.
If I pretend to be General Fengyun,
my face will
immediately give me away.
But General Feihong
always wore a mask in the past.
Few have seen his true appearance.
Thus, impersonating him
is naturally easier.
That's how I could
leverage General Feihong's reputation
to intimidate the Wutuo.
That sounds reasonable.
It seems
I ignored details.
Speaking of which,
you should thank General He.
Your Majesty.
General He comes from a noble family.
I don't dare to make a connection
with him.
Nevertheless, I must indeed
express my gratitude to General He.
Thank you, General He.
I am
very grateful to you.
Your Majesty.
I hold General He in high esteem.
Now that I've finally met him
at this Mid-Autumn banquet,
I wish to spar
with General He
to enliven the celebration for all.
May Your Majesty grant my request.
Challenge General Feihong?
He is so overconfident!
Exactly.
His Majesty just praised your humility,
and now you're getting cocky.
A bad general
makes a bad soldier.
Mr. Yang,
that's a little judgmental.
To match General Feihong's prowess,
I've practiced martial arts
relentlessly.
Your Majesty.
This Mid-Autumn Festival
is a time for peace and joy.
A fight game
seems inappropriate.
General He.
Attendant Wu'an
is awaiting His Majesty's reply.
Before His Majesty speaks,
why did you rush to decline?
Your Majesty.
I think
General He made a fair point.
A fight before Your Majesty
is indeed improper.
It's just to add to the fun.
When I
was Crown Prince,
I often sparred
with soldiers.
Both of you know what to do.
Don't hurt each other.
- As Your Majesty commands.
Use this sword.
The Qinglang Sword
is General Feihong's sword.
Why is Attendant Wu'an
holding it?
So strange.
Attendant Wu'an.
Why hesitate?
If you fear losing,
surrender now.
Bring it on, General He.
Incredible!
General Feihong is defeated?
How is this possible?
It's so...
Your Majesty.
I'm done.
Impressive.
He Rufei.
You wish me dead, right?
I'll take your life
like a vengeful ghost.
He Yan!
General He.
Stop shouting here.
You can't stand to lose?
Your Majesty, forgive me.
That's not true.
I...
Your Majesty.
People say
martial artists
are all proud.
General He's martial skills
are unmatched.
If he hadn't been injured
in the Huayuan Battle
or had recovered,
he never
would've lost.
General He is too young
to accept this outcome.
That's understandable.
Actually,
this outcome
means little.
So long as Your Majesty and officials
find enjoyment,
it would be great.
Attendant Wu'an.
At such a young age,
you show remarkable courage and wisdom,
making you
a good soldier.
- Congratulations, Your Majesty,
- on acquiring an exceptional soldier.
The Empress came with noblewomen
to propose a toast.
(Princess of Wei, Empress of Wei)
- I wish Your Majesty
- I wish Father
- happiness.
- May Wei lasting peace!
Rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
- We wish Your Majesty
- happiness.
- May Wei lasting peace!
Please sit.
(She's a good female general.)
(I hear that even Mr. Chu)
(holds her in high regard.)
Pingting.
Mind your manners before His Majesty.
Your Majesty,
I have something to report.
I bring charges against
He Yan of Yezhou Garrison.
She disguised as a man
to join the army.
She's been deceiving you.
Please punish her severely.
What?
Disguised as a man?
Is that true?
What? He Yan is female?
This is deception.
Exactly!
This is deception!
Yes.
How's this possible?
Who knows?
Impossible.
It's a capital offense.
It's insane.
Miss Xu,
before His Majesty,
mind your words.
Attendant Wu'an
couldn't possibly be female.
Your Majesty,
a body check will confirm
my honesty.
I just don't know
if she dares to do that.
Good idea.
Do a body check.
- Yes.
Minister Xiao.
In your opinion,
how should I handle this?
Your Majesty,
I'm sorry
for bothering you.
Actually,
I've long been aware of this.
What?
Your Majesty knew it?
So, that's true.
Yes.
Well...
(When I was young,)
I met a woman
by chance.
To be honest,
she has no talent
for martial arts.
Back then, I thought
she was rather foolishly persistent,
and she would give up
after encountering some setbacks.
But to my surprise,
she persisted day after day
and did it.
I've never seen
such unyielding determination in anyone.
She is like a steadfast tree
and as resilient as grass.
She commanded my attention.
Actually,
back then,
I didn't know how I felt about her.
I was a little too harsh on her,
giving her a strict teaching.
I guess
she must've hated me.
Well,
no wonder you remain solitary.
You frightened the girl away.
She didn't flee from my harshness.
However,
misfortune struck her family.
From then on,
we were separated by distance
and out of touch.
Surprisingly, we met again
in Yezhou.
She was in trouble
and helpless.
However,
she
remained indomitable
yet naive.
This reminded me vividly
of our childhood friendship.
Childhood friendship?
I don't think so.
You finally realized
you had feelings
for that girl, right?
You are right.
After our separation,
I came to realize
that my feelings for her
couldn't be forgotten.
Your Majesty.
I admired her exceptional abilities
and didn't want to part with her.
So, I let her disguise as a man
to stay at Yezhou Garrison.
Your Majesty.
I offer my two military merits
to beg your forgiveness
for my recklessness.
I implore your approval.
I granted the request
of Commander Xiao.
So, Attendant Wu'an
commits no act of deception.
Moreover,
I'm moved
by Commander Xiao's love.
He is fully pardoned.
- Your Majesty is wise.
Your Majesty is merciful
and forgives their deception.
Yet General Fengyun,
as military commander,
deceived us all
for personal reasons.
It may
disappoint the troops.
That makes sense.
If soldiers
start following
this example
and hide women in camp,
military order
will be ruined.
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪