(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(All characters, places,
and organizations are fictional.)
(Children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
No way! This can't be happening!
What's wrong, Mr. Ha?
(Update 2: "Momo's mother, Hyun Ran Hee,
Suspected in Apparent Suicide")
That's Geum Ba Ra for you.
She's first on scene and gets top intel.
She's our rookie, too.
What is going on?
The secret engagement story just blew up.
Gosh, someone's dying every day now.
The third update is out.
Hurry up!
Ma'am, it's dangerous.
Come on, what are you doing?
- Gosh, Chief!
- You're relentless. Seriously.
(Unpo Police Station)
Excuse me.
Do you have someone to help
around the house?
Who does the cleaning...
Was it just you and your mother
living here?
Shouldn't you have rushed her
to the hospital?
You didn't even perform CPR.
It was too late for CPR.
You just end up breaking their ribs
at that point.
- Should we move her?
- Yes.
Mom!
- We're going in.
- You can't enter.
We're close to her in both work and life.
- If we can't go in, who can?
- Let us go in.
We're practically family.
- Who's in charge here?
- The police!
Just give us one comment!
- Hey, let us through.
- Yes. sir.
- Is that confirmed, Chief?
- Look over here!
- Make way!
- Step back!
It's me.
Are we sure it's a suicide?
- Yes.
- Cause of death?
- Hypothermia, most likely.
- Hypothermia?
The bedroom's an absolute freezer.
The AC was...
This is not the time or place!
They're coming out!
Momo.
Hello.
You must be Momo's mother,
CEO Hyun Ran Hee.
Ba Ra.
- You actually came.
- Of course.
Your mother is here too.
Goodness.
Ms. Hyun.
I didn't expect to see you here.
Neither did I.
What brings you here?
This is Geum Ba Ra,
a reporter from Sungwoo Daily.
- Hello.
She's covering the exhibition today,
and my schedule just happened to be free.
Are you close with CEO Ju Yeong Ae?
No. My senior editor sent me to cover it.
Mom, do you have an exhibition coming up?
It's in the works.
- That's Momo, right?
- Yes.
She's so much prettier in person.
I'll be back.
Look at CEO Ju, schmoozing.
You can't just disappear on me
like last time.
Chairman Kang has arrived.
- Welcome.
- It's my pleasure.
Excuse me for a moment.
Hello.
This is my daughter.
Artist Paul Kim. He was based in Germany.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Hello.
Your pieces have already sold, you know.
Both of them.
She's a close reporter friend of mine
from Sungwoo Daily.
- Excuse me. Is Artist Paul Kim here?
- Yes.
- That's him.
- How's your work coming along?
It's been a little slow lately.
What do you do to relax?
Besides photography trips?
I just read books and whatnot.
Korea's changed a lot, hasn't it?
Have you been back much?
No.
She doesn't look like you.
An improvement on the original, right?
I've never met her,
but I'm told I look like my grandmother.
Excuse me, could I get a picture?
Thank you.
Give me a call next time you're in Seoul.
You must be busy, though.
It's fine as long as it's not last-minute.
This is Artist Paul Kim.
Hello. I'm Geum Ba Ra
from the Culture Desk at Sungwoo Daily.
- Hi. I don't have a card yet.
- Please.
Your work is your business card.
Would you mind telling me a little
about your piece?
Let me just get a picture first.
I'm not planning to run the story
right away.
You'll get fans after this photo gets out,
won't you?
What about the suicide note?
- The forensics team has it.
- What does it say?
(Emergency Medical Center)
- What happened?
- It appears to be a suicide.
Okay, right this way.
Ma'am, we're going to need you
to come down to the station.
- We'll confirm with handwriting analysis.
- Understood.
Check the gallery office, not the house,
for any documents handwritten by Ms. Hyun.
Got it.
Let me see the suicide note.
I won't write it in the article.
You've already gotten your scoop.
Go in my office.
Reporters will be
swarming in here any minute.
I can't imagine how you're feeling,
but we need to get your statement.
Can you walk us through what happened?
What time did you find her?
I don't know.
I didn't have anything scheduled today,
so I slept in a little.
And when I woke up,
it was quiet,
so I figured she had gone to the gallery.
How'd you know to call?
I literally just walked in.
James just told me.
Do you have plans for Christmas Eve?
You know I don't make any special plans.
I always have dinner with you
on Christmas Eve.
We're thicker than blood, I swear.
Does just sharing blood make you family?
Exactly.
Because plenty of siblings
are worse than strangers.
(Hospital Director, Shin Ju Shin)
You should do a talent donation this time.
What talent do I even have?
Perform at the Sponsor Appreciation Night
at Nua Children's Home.
My fingers are stiff now.
They'll loosen up if you practice.
It'd be great if James could come too.
(Auditorium)
Come on, let's go.
- Hello.
- We keep running into each other.
- It's not over, is it?
- Part two is about to start.
(Nua Children's Home
Sponsor Appreciation Night)
- Thank you.
- I'm a huge fan.
- Hello.
Are you enjoying the food?
(Nua General Hospital)
Do you come to this every year?
Yes.
The vibe here is so great with the music.
You're drinking quite a bit today.
It's Christmas Eve.
Next year, I'll keep my schedule clear,
come early, and have a meal with the kids.
You definitely should.
(Nua Children's Home
Sponsor Appreciation Night)
(Nua Children's Home)
- How'd the surgery go?
- It went well.
The Chairman is on a call
with Ambassador Yu Gu Jong.
All right. Is Momo here yet?
Yes, she's a big hit with our guests.
I'm so jealous.
(Nua Children's Home
Sponsor Appreciation Night)
You're here.
- Advisor.
- Where's your father?
- Advisor!
- What is it?
- What's going on?
- Advisor!
Are you adopting another one?
No.
- It's not been long since Oiji passed.
- Where are you?
Here.
I thought you'd be pulling an all-nighter
with Ju Shin.
Momo's sponsored by your company, right?
- Yes.
- Introduce me.
- Was Momo at the party too?
- Yes.
Forget about it.
She's getting engaged to Ju Shin soon.
Really?
Yes.
- Did you introduce them?
- Ju Shin is head over heels for her.
That's why Momo's here.
She'll be the foundation's first lady.
Go have a cold beer to cool off
instead of just water.
How are things between you and Eun Ah?
Of all people, Momo?
I'm on Team Geum Ba Ra.
Hello.
It's cold out here.
It's too hot inside.
I made a fool of myself the other day.
I didn't know you were Ju Shin's friend.
I got carried away hearing live music
for the first time in a while.
Do you have a side gig?
I'm not good enough to moonlight.
I'm so jealous of people
who can play an instrument.
- You could just learn.
- Then you can tutor me part-time.
Where's Ju Shin?
- The restroom.
- Is his stomach acting up again?
Yes.
And he only had juice on the way over.
I guess that's
how the skies keep things fair.
Ju Shin has a weak stomach,
but he's an A-plus in every other way.
I'm Ha Yong Joong, by the way.
With the Advisor collapsing that day,
Ju Shin never got to introduce us.
I'm Momo.
I looked you up. It's your real name.
Yes,
a lot of people assume it's a stage name.
So why did you look me up?
Curious about me as an actress?
Or as your friend's girlfriend?
Both, of course.
I hear you've been very busy.
I was away for a while,
so I have a lot to catch up on.
Everyone's been swamped.
Especially Ju Shin, of course.
Ju Shin...
never really showed much interest
in women before.
I even started to wonder
if he had a crush on me.
It's all set.
What do you mean?
You seem happy.
Do you have any jinxes, by any chance?
What kind of jinx?
The kind that makes you want to dance.
If only music were playing now...
I have the sudden urge to waltz right now.
With me?
Yes.
Spring is right around the corner,
and yet a blizzard hit us.
You know how to waltz?
I am an actress, after all.
I can sort of pull off the tango too.
I wish I'd learned it
for a day like today.
I heard your mother was
a double bass player.
She was.
Ju Shin...
didn't just say good things about me,
did he?
He said you were
his most troublesome friend.
Is my makeup too much?
No.
Why are you standing out here?
It's hot in this dress.
(Our deepest condolences
to the bereaved family)
(Family waiting room)
Push my meeting with Mr. Jo to tomorrow.
- The cross shoot is at 3 p.m.
- Send Manager Choi.
- Let's go pay our respects, Jin Ju.
- I've already been.
- When?
- Last night.
Momo.
Did I do the right thing?
Do I really have to let you go like this?
Do you think you'll be able to sleep?
Just talk to me like you talk to Momo.
If anyone heard you...
It's not like we'll be seeing each other
much longer anyway.
You can say you broke up naturally
by next year anyway.
Go.
I'm going to keep drinking
until I fall asleep.
I'm really starting to feel
like I'm becoming Momo.
She's not some stranger.
She's my own flesh and blood.
I am Momo, and Momo is me.
Puppies and wine...
are the deity's gift to humanity.
You're not having any?
I drove.
We can call for a ride.
When I look in the mirror,
it doesn't feel like Momo's dead.
It just feels like
I'm looking right at my daughter.
Hyun Ran Hee is the one who died.
They say there's more than meets the eye,
you should just accept what you see.
There's no need to overthink it.
It's too quiet.
He has such a noble brow.
So aristocratic.
Like fine white porcelain.
Leaving?
Loosen your tie before you go.
It looks so tight and suffocating.
Go abroad for a while.
It's me.
Why on earth?
(CEO James Ha)
- Hello?
- Hi, it's James.
Mr. Ha. Hello.
With Momo's mother away,
I'm sure you don't have an appetite.
I figured you'd be starving at home alone,
so I made some side dishes.
Sending them by a manager felt impersonal,
and I was worried about you.
I see.
Would it be alright if I dropped by?
They aren't dishes we have to eat today,
are they?
Of course not.
Are you on your way home?
Are you off work yet?
I'm about to.
Have a seat.
Do you have any food at home?
I'm not that interested in food.
Why not? Eating is extremely important.
That's no good.
Eat well in your youth to age well.
- Hippocrates said it best.
- "You are what you eat"?
Exactly.
Do you have a dog?
I lost her, the year before last.
Do you like dogs?
Of course.
Her name was Oiji?
They give out awards for this?
Yes.
She had been through a lot.
I think I taste some lemon.
That, and some other healthy stuff.
Stay for a quick dinner.
- No, I'm fine.
- It's no trouble. It's already made.
It's not from a package.
I slow-cooked it with premium beef.
You're so busy, but you made it yourself?
They say, "If you want it done right,
do it yourself."
I've heard that one.
Add salt if you need it.
Thank you for the meal.
- It's not bland at all.
- Good.
It's perfect. I actually prefer less salt.
That's the way to do it.
Wouldn't it be nice to live this way?
I'd treat her like a queen,
and she wouldn't have to lift a finger.
Gosh, look how she enjoys her food.
She didn't seem depressed at all.
Right. Maybe if her career
as Momo was failing...
- She was about to get married...
- I know.
She had a top-star daughter,
who was engaged to a catch
like Director Shin,
and her gallery was doing well.
Do you think having no worries
is a problem in itself?
How is Momo getting by?
By the way,
since you're Yong Joong's older brother,
you don't have to be so formal with me.
- You sure?
- Yes.
That makes sense,
since you're so close with Yong Joong.
Maybe she'll feel that way with me.
- Ha Yong Joong's car is now arriving.
- He's here for the side dishes.
It's all the same stuff, so take one each.
- One for me too?
- They're better if you make a big batch.
I'll drop Ba Ra off and take this to Momo.
And why would you do that?
- Does Ba Ra even have her car here?
- She can take a cab.
Right?
You're going to make a reporter
run errands for an actress?
Their jobs have nothing to do with it.
They were close friends.
Weren't you?
- Anyway.
- She's alone at home with no helper.
I can just ask her
to come down to the lobby.
Is Momo just some random person?
What if Ju Shin gets the wrong idea?
It could get awkward for Momo too.
It's just an errand for you.
What's the big deal?
I didn't ask you to. Leave me out of it.
Fine then.
I'll just eat it myself then. Forget it.
I think he's just worried about her.
That's my point.
Why is he so worried
about his best friend's fiancee?
Ju Shin will take care of her.
You think Ju Shin cooks and cleans?
You think he has time?
- If he had three bodies...
- And you?
Do you have time?
Imagine how hard it must be
for her right now.
We went through it too.
Have you forgotten?
Let's go see her tomorrow morning.
I can't just ignore this either.
It's too late tonight.
Her address.
You don't get it either, do you?
Sorry, all I have is water and coffee.
I'm thirsty.
That guy...
He's been doing better than I expected.
Being a bodyguard pays pretty well.
It's hazard pay.
Once I get the new place,
I'll sell this place...
and donate the money in An Hee's name.
You know I can help you out.
Am I treating you differently from An Hee?
I've faced so much discrimination,
I don't want to even hear that word.
Lawyer Tae Won Young said he knew you.
I signed a contract with his law firm,
and while we were talking
about that interview article...
I heard he got remarried.
Is he happy?
He's remarried?
- What did he say about me?
- Nothing really.
An associate was there.
Do you two have some kind of history?
Are you Ye Jeong's father?
Yes.
I'm here because of Ye Jeong.
I was on my way to the police station,
but I came here instead.
Ye Jeong!
Your father said
he was going to bed early.
Tell her to come downstairs.
Sit.
Let's talk about this inside.
- I'm home, Father.
- Alright.
Who are you?
My name is Geum Ba Ra.
I'm not in the same class
as Tae Ye Jeong, though.
Sit down, all of you.
Bring something out.
I'm fine.
I grew up at an orphanage...
with a girl from my class, Kim Jin Ju.
Do you know Nua Children's Home?
The one behind the cathedral?
Yes. Jin Ju and I have been roommates
our whole lives,
but Tae Ye Jeong constantly bullies her.
Today, she even hit her with two others.
- It's over and done with.
- How can it be over?
I ended it.
But you're the one
who started this up again.
- I got hit too!
- Quiet!
I saw the three of them
ganging up on Jin Ju,
so I had no choice but to hit them
a few times to defend her.
They started coming after me too.
What was I supposed to do?
Growing up in an orphanage
is already hard enough,
and it's a painful wound.
But they ridiculed us,
calling us brats with no parents.
But I endured it and put an end to it.
Did you know your daughter bullies kids
who are easy targets?
I didn't even...
That's not what a student does.
She does monstrous things
without a second thought.
Have you ever thought about what it's like
to be on the receiving end?
You're lying.
- Don't exaggerate.
- You think I'm exaggerating?
So...
Are you saying my Ye Jeong
did this to you?
Her "husband" did.
Hey!
It's just a stupid joke
among the kids at school.
I heard it clearly. Yoon Seong Tae.
He's a senior at our school,
and he said,
"You scratched my wife's face."
What...
Father.
He's just an older guy
who tends to overreact.
Is doing this to me "overreacting?"
So those guys you know just kidnapped me
as a group because they were bored?
And then did this to me?
- You provoked them!
- I don't know what you told them,
but they completely lost it.
Did you or did you not hear...
four senior boys screaming
that I scratched your face...
as they began to strip me and beat me?
You were smiling, encouraging them
to "teach me a real lesson."
Tae Ye Jeong hit me over the head
with a piece of lumber.
Come feel my head and see how bad it is.
You... You little...
Did you not know your daughter was running
around doing things like this?
Say something!
I'm sorry.
- Go to your room.
- No.
I'm not done talking yet.
I...
know how to fight.
For self-defense,
so I wouldn't just get beaten up.
If I hadn't held back with every ounce
of my strength today,
Tae Ye Jeong would be
in a full-body cast right now.
Big deal.
You always go around dropping
your dad's name, don't you?
Saying he's a lawyer
at a big firm in Seoul.
So who's going to sue you
after you beat them up?
I know.
Teachers walk on eggshells around you.
And you've got top thug Yoon Seong Tae
as your "husband."
He's not my husband, you witch!
Shut it.
To think she was born
just to bring shame to this family.
There are many other victims.
And they will all carry
those deep scars for life.
Okay, we understand.
We'll punish her severely
so she never does it again.
But it's the middle of the night,
and with his blood pressure...
The reason I came all this way is this.
I want you to hit her ten times,
right in front of me.
Or, I'll hit her myself, just as much
as Seong Tae's crew hit me today,
and I'll turn myself in to the police.
To be honest,
I don't really have much to live for.
Just like Ye Jeong taunted me
and hit me where it hurt,
my own parents abandoned me.
So why would I have any will to live
or attachment to my life?
I grew up never once getting
to say "Mom" or "Dad" like everyone else.
Can any of you even imagine
how that feels?
I only hit you back a few times
in self-defense.
You got so mad over a couple of hits
you sent your thug "husband" after me.
I don't know if he's really your man
or if it's just for show.
You shouldn't just say things like that...
You've done a fine job
raising your only daughter.
Try to imagine how the kids...
you tormented and beat up must feel.
They've likely imagined tearing you apart
a thousand times over in their minds.
Because that's what I was doing today.
I barely held myself back...
and came here to deal
with this rationally.
I'm sorry.
We understand, so please go.
- Something like today will never...
- You can't even hit her ten times?
We'll discuss it
and discipline her ourselves.
In front of me.
Only then,
I think I'll be able to live with this.
Go get me something.
Hurry up.
There's nothing suitable here.
I'll have something prepared by tomorrow.
- We have the golf club.
- Father!
I was wrong!
If saying you were wrong could erase
the scars and injuries I have,
I'd accept your apology.
You hit her ten times.
- Father!
- You hit her ten times,
and her father will get a beating from me.
You need to see this with your own eyes.
All because of this one girl!
Grandfather, I'll turn over a new leaf.
Starting today.
What exactly is your relationship
with that punk?
You're not even dry behind the ears.
Please, I swear.
He just always acts like he's flirting.
There's nothing going on between us.
He's just a bodyguard.
If my orphanage friend
hadn't been there today,
who knows what would've happened?
- They were trying to strip me...
- Hey! Get over here. Now.
Dad, I'm sorry! I was wrong!
- Honey.
- What a fine mess this family is in.
You feed her well,
dress her in nice clothes,
and you think just throwing money
at her studies is how you raise a child?
Darn it.
- Grandfather!
- Honey.
- Grandfather.
- Father.
No, honey, you have to stop him.
Maybe it was karma,
but two months later, Tae Ye Jeong died.
At their vacation home on Jeju Island,
on the beach right in front of the house.
Because I didn't have parents
and grew up in an orphanage,
I went through so much
and was always looked down on.
Sometimes I wonder
if the expressions I show people...
and the emotions I display...
are all just an act.
When I felt so worthless,
there were people
who genuinely cared for me.
There was An Hee,
and there was you.
An Hee took care of me
because we were in the same boat,
but you...
genuinely adored me when I was just a kid.
It was the first time
I had ever really felt it.
"Oh, so this is what it's like
to be adored."
It was only for a few months, but...
I've always missed that warmth.
Thinking of it helped me
get through the hard times.
So even if you...
like and love a wicked witch,
I feel like it's my place
to try to understand.
Maybe no one else has to,
but I do.
I'll always...
be by your side.
We'll never be apart again.
Forever?
Forever.
You don't have to force it.
I'm not.
My brother and I aren't related by blood,
but he's the only brother I have.
It's the same with you.
Just promise me one thing.
What?
When things get tough and you struggle,
don't try to bear it all on your own.
You've got me now.
I'll be content with just having you...
by my side or watching from afar.
My dear Ba Ra...
You've done so well for yourself.
The more I think about it,
the prouder I am of you,
and I'm so grateful.
Why'd An Hee have to die,
leaving us behind?
Imagine how great it would be
if he were with us now.
I have a favor to ask, too.
What is it?
Live a long, long life.
Promise me.
All right.
I have to grant any wish
my big girl asks of me.
Just don't ask for the moon.
Some things are just impossible.
If you find her,
tell her...
that her mom was so, so sorry.
You have to find her. No matter what.
You've been on a real roll lately.
It's been one Geum Ba Ra exclusive
after another.
(A sentence can change the world.
Relentless pursuit of truth)
Get in.
(A sentence can change the world.
Relentless pursuit of truth)
The other outlets are busy
just copying each other's stories,
and since you're so short-staffed,
it must be hard just to keep up.
You're doing a great job.
Not at all, sir.
I'm keeping an eye on you.
Thank you, sir.
Sorry, Yong Joong.
I just got an urgent assignment.
Don't apologize to me.
Okay?
Alright.
And you've picked up another cute habit.
At some point,
you dropped the formalities with me.
My gosh, what's gotten into me?
That's why I like it.
You think I'm a pushover, don't you?
No, that's not it.
Try that again.
No.
I'm the guy
you're most comfortable being with.
Get back to it.
Yes.
"Yes?"
Okay, Yong Joong.
You hang up first.
Here's your coffee.
Welcome.
Here...
Should I put this in the fridge for now?
Is there room?
I'll sort it out and put it away...
Have you been eating properly?
Don't you have anyone you can call?
My manager stops by every now and then...
What about Ju Shin?
How about staying somewhere else
for a little while?
We're...
all in the same boat.
Ju Shin, you,
and me.
Someone once said...
that if you don't have parents,
you're an orphan.
When did your parents pass away?
My dad passed away
when I was in second grade.
And my mom passed away
during my senior year of high school.
So I know how you feel
better than anyone, Momo.
I know how hard it must be
for you right now.
When my mother passed away,
I couldn't even really cry.
My brother cried a lot, though.
Isn't this the part
where he gives me a hug?
Did Ju Shin tell you about my brother?
James told me himself once.
That he was adopted in elementary school.
I heard James's birth mother
and your mother...
were in the same orchestra, right?
Yes.
It might sound like a cliche,
but it's true.
As time goes on,
the sadness does fade.
For now, all you can do is endure it.
There's no other way.
Thank you.
I bought the Laketop penthouse.
Would you like to stay there for a while?
What's the point of leaving it empty?
I was worried tenants would ruin it,
so it's empty.
The 18-million-dollar Laketop penthouse?
Goodbye.
Think about it and text me.
Okay.
Yes!
That was the most delicious breakfast
I've had in a long time.
Thank you.
- What's got you in such a good mood?
- It's Ms. Geum Ba Ra.
She said she loved my cooking.
You would've made a killing
in the restaurant business.
You dote on your brother,
so no wonder
he doesn't think about getting married.
He has everything he needs.
How many of our pieces got into
Sera Lauren magazine?
(Ha Yong Joong, CEO of WorldNet)
(Ha Yong Joong, Developer of
Record-Breaking Mega-Hit "Lost Knights")
(Ba Ra)
I know this must be really hard,
but people are curious.
So it'd be good to briefly announce
your future plans.
That should quiet down the media, too.
I can drop by for a bit,
or we could meet somewhere
you're comfortable.
Are you getting any sleep?
Only a little after I've completely
exhausted myself.
Are you cleaning up her things alone?
I'd like to help.
I'm okay.
Last year, on the day we were
supposed to meet,
I saw your mother at the airport,
and she was so cheerful.
Did you have any idea she was struggling?
Then why did you cut off all contact
for so long...
The moment I let my guard down,
I got burnt out.
I spent a few months in Lausanne, too.
Lausanne, in Switzerland?
I need you to run a story
on my retirement.
Wouldn't it be better to keep busy?
I don't have it in me.
Who would I even be doing it for...?
Your fans are going to be so disappointed.
Is your wedding with Director Shin
still on?
You don't have to talk about it
if you don't want to.
It's just so absurd.
Professor Shin, who was so healthy...
I mean, Ju Shin's father
passed away so suddenly,
and now my mom, too.
Does your head hurt?
Should I get you something for it?
No, I have some.
I'm not in a good state,
so if I'm not around much...
I understand. Take your time to heal.
Yong Joong stopped by, didn't he?
Are you that close? Are you dating?
He's an old friend from the orphanage.
We were best friends in high school.
I've told you this before.
My brain is completely fried.
I even forget to eat.
To be honest,
her condition was critical at first.
She only recovered because Director Shin
kept her on hyperbaric oxygen therapy.
How bad was it?
I never saw her myself.
I heard it from one of the executives.
Is she really going to retire?
Yes.
Has Director Choi told you differently?
(Ha Yong Joong: "Lost Knights" Creator)
(Actress Momo Suddenly Retires.
Agency Respects Her Wishes.)
Looks like Geum Ba Ra
landed another scoop.
- What is it?
- Momo announced her retirement.
My gosh!
(Actress Momo, 26, suddenly announced
her retirement from acting this afternoon)
(Nua General Hospital)
(Neurosurgery)
Could you please give this
to Director Shin?
Do you like the painting?
It's a Paul Kim, isn't it?
Take that painting down.
- Why? It's a nice piece.
- I'm giving it to Reporter Geum.
Hey.
You don't have feelings for Ba Ra, do you?
- You do?
- I've thought about it.
You know I have a thing for smart women.
Are you crazy?
Are you out of your mind? You're 50!
So what if I'm 50?
Age is just a number.
It's a very important number.
People think I'm in my late thirties.
You believe that flattery?
In ten years, you'll be 60.
- And Ba Ra's in her 30s.
- Her late 30s.
Snap out of it.
She's not the right person for you.
Don't you even think about it.
There are plenty of other smart women
out there.
Professor Lee Jin Hee, Dr. Shin...
Didn't you say they were both interested?
But I'm the one who has to be attracted.
That's greedy.
How could you go for Ba Ra?
She could be your daughter.
Look at actors in Hollywood.
It's the new trend.
Find a better trend to follow.
You're no Hollywood star.
Hey, I'm quite the catch.
James of Lim Company.
Everyone in the industry knows who I am.
Please stop. Don't embarrass yourself.
Fortune favors the bold.
- James.
- You just don't want to have...
to call her your sister-in-law, do you?
You've really got a problem.
That's rich. You fell head over heels
for your best friend's fiancee.
It's not like I knew who she was!
Either way, don't drag me into this mess.
How'd you feel if a woman 23 years older
than you threw herself at you?
It's different for men and women.
You'll get torn to shreds if you do that.
I don't care if they drag me
through the mud.
(True correction, bright future)
Before my mom passed away,
she told me I had an older sister.
It was like a deathbed confession.
Back when you two were in high school.
So you haven't found her yet?
It's not that simple.
In any case,
I've never met her,
but you're my sister's father,
and you used to be my mom's boyfriend.
You don't have to be so formal with me.
Did that...
cause any conflict?
No.
It's not my place
to say anything about the past.
I admit I was surprised.
My father was much older than she was,
so I had a vague inkling...
that there was a backstory.
If by some miracle we find her,
I'd like to get along as sisters,
not just because my mom wanted us to.
She's my only blood relative, after all.
So please, let me know.
You don't have to see me out.
(Investigator Park)
Hello?
I believe we've found your daughter.
Really?
(Doctor Shin)
Ladies first.
This is our first day as a couple.
- This is a bit of a weak celebration.
- It's more than enough.
So I'm your number one?
Don't tell me it's that Kim Jin Ju.
- You're friends with Geum Ba Ra?
- Yes.
Are both of you still single?
- A boyfriend.
- Right.
What if I only had eyes
for Director Shin Ju Shin?
Shin Ju Shin is someone
women would fall for.
- He's got it all.
- Hello, sir.
You should brace yourself.
Can I see her today?
Is it because I'm thinking
about Momo too much?
Sir.
I just wish I had someone
I could give my all to.
I gave you my heart
I gave you my tears
And I gave you my dreams
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)