[A new start! We will grow with you
at this new starting point]
Yu Lei's not here.
He should be back with Chen Ke.
Who said I was looking for Yu Lei?
Then you're here to...
For me?
No way.
Last time we played ball,
you said my ball was old and dirty.
So I went out and bought a new one.
I didn't expect that you'd also...
I already told you, it's not for you.
Don't get so close.
You stink.
What?
Me? I just took a shower.
How... How do I stink?
I even put on some cologne.
Smell.
Since when did the big ape start
caring about his hygiene?
Well... I wanted to change my image a bit.
What happened to your hair?
It's back to normal.
Oh, this?
My hair is naturally curly.
Straightening it is too much work.
So I just left it like this.
It's nice.
You look better... the way you were before.
[Episode 7: I Didn't Do Anything Wrong]
For this semester's final exams,
He Jin got the first-class scholarship
all to himself.
If Yu Lei and Chen Ke had been here,
he wouldn't have stood a chance.
By the way, the counselor said
the scholarship money
will be distributed on Monday.
Let's go out for a big meal then.
Sounds good.
Let's go to that place by the school gate.
Everyone's pretty busy
at the start of the semester.
Let's talk about it when we have time.
Right. No rush.
- Yeah. That's true.
- Chen Ke. You're back.
How's everything at home?
- It's fine.
- You're finally back.
We missed you like crazy.
Don't touch it. I'll get it.
Come on, come on, come on.
We've already tidied all this up for you.
- Your little notebook, your bedsheets...
- We didn't even throw out your notebook.
- Thanks.
- We even watered your plants.
You don't have to clean anything.
We took care of it all for you.
You guys...
Yu Lei. When did you get back?
You two... When did you get so close?
So...
Are you two now...
in "that" kind of relationship?
We...
Right now, not yet.
But we're planning on giving it a try.
Who said I wanted to give it a try with you?
Did you even ask me?
Then let me ask you right now...
Ouyang, will you?
Who told you to ask right now?
Then I'll ask again tomorrow.
No.
- The day after tomorrow, then.
- No.
Then when do you want me to ask?
I'll ask whenever you want.
Okay?
When did this happen?
Maybe it started when, every morning,
I started to find doing my hair annoying.
Things changed.
Curly hair suits you better anyway.
Tell me something I don't know.
Ouyang Han.
Seriously.
No matter who it is,
as long as you truly like them,
and that person can make you feel happy,
I'll be happy for you.
Besides, that guy Li Ming...
he only seems a little unreliable.
It just seems that way.
- He's actually a really good guy.
- Alright, alright, alright.
How did one break from school
turn you into such a busybody?
You should worry more about yourself.
How are things with you and Chen Ke?
You and Chen Ke...
have you made any progress?
What progress?
What's there to progress?
Chen Ke and I are just like blood Yu Leis.
I think you're the one
who's dense as a block of wood.
Your relationship with Chen Ke...
is it really that simple?
What's not simple about it?
Let me ask you this.
When he's happy, are you happy too?
When he's sad, are you sad too?
Every day, when you think about seeing him,
do you smile without even realizing it?
Every day, when you have to part ways,
do you hate to see him go?
When he's tired,
do you want to be someone he can lean on?
When you're feeling vulnerable,
is he the first person you want comfort from?
Do you want to kiss him?
Do you want to hold him?
Do you want to chase away everyone
who shows interest in him?
And never let him like anyone other than you?
He and I... W-We...
When he's happy,
you're even happier than he is.
When he's worried,
you're more anxious than he is.
When he's troubled,
you're the first one to frown.
If that's not love, then what is?
Yu Lei, you're in love with Chen Ke.
Have you really not realized it until now?
Yu Lei.
Yu...
What's wrong with you?
You're totally out of it.
I-It's nothing.
Who was that text from just now?
My mom.
She sent a text, saying...
On September 11th, 2001,
there was a terrorist attack
in the United States.
So far, 3,000 people have died,
and over 6,000 are injured.
How could so many people
be killed and injured?
Life is just so unpredictable.
Don't think about it too much.
At least the two of us are still okay. Right?
Yu Lei. Chen Ke.
The counselor asked for you two
to find some time this afternoon
to go see him in his office.
What does he want with us?
I think the results for
the make-up exam are out.
- Oh.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
[Finance]
Let's go.
This is yours, Yu Lei.
Here, Chen Ke.
And you were worried
about your makeup exam.
You did great, didn't you?
You're the one who's amazing.
I never see you studying.
How are your scores so high?
Yu Lei. Chen Ke.
You two have always had excellent grades.
I was never worried about you failing.
But, Chen Ke,
now that your family issues are all resolved,
this semester, you need to settle down
and put more focus on your studies.
Ma'am, don't worry.
Alright then.
Because this semester,
we're also paying close attention
to attendance.
Even for our electives,
if you frequently miss class,
it will affect your overall credits.
Ma'am, this semester,
Chen Ke and I took almost the same classes.
We went to every single class.
He wasn't absent.
That's not possible.
Several of his professors have reported to me
that Chen Ke has been skipping class.
Here. Take a look.
Chen Ke, look.
These classes are all marked as absences.
That's impossible.
I never signed up for these classes.
Miss, this isn't my schedule.
He's right, sir.
Chen Ke and I
registered for classes together.
I can vouch that he didn't pick these.
That can't be right.
Look, this is what the system shows.
It's right here.
And all the professors use this
to track your attendance.
Could it be a system glitch?
Or, maybe there's been
some kind of mistake?
Okay. Don't panic just yet.
I will report this to the administration.
Then, after I've verified the situation,
I'll let you know.
History of Ming and Qing Law, Latin,
Greek Literature...
What are these classes?
I have no recollection of them at all.
I know, right?
They're all so obscure.
They sound painfully difficult.
But we registered for our classes together.
How could this have happened?
It's impossible.
We both chose our classes
on the computers in the lab
and printed the schedules right away.
If it were really a system error,
then the ones affected
wouldn't just be me, right?
Do you think it's possible
it wasn't the system?
That someone secretly
logged into your account
and changed your schedule?
Who would log into my account?
Maybe it was a hacker?
I heard it's super easy
for them to steal accounts.
They have some kind of program for it.
If it were a hacker, why wouldn't they steal
something more valuable?
What do they gain by changing my schedule?
It's not like there's money in it.
That's true.
Why don't we go check the computer lab?
Maybe we can find some clues.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Ma'am. This is really important.
I'm begging you.
But according to the regulations,
you have to submit
a written application first.
There's a procedure.
It also needs to be signed off on
by the school's leadership.
This matter is not my call to make.
We just want to gather some evidence first.
Please, could you bend the rules for us?
The procedures and paperwork,
we'll complete them later. Is that okay?
I'm really sorry.
This matter, I really can't authorize.
Damn...
Ma'am, you have security cameras here.
Can we review the footage from that day?
We might find some evidence.
But, if you want to access
the security footage,
the police would have to get involved.
Even the school administration might not...
I'm begging you.
Please.
Ma'am, if your own child
were in a similar situation,
you'd want to help them get justice,
wouldn't you?
This incident happened several days ago.
I can't guarantee the recording
from that day still exists.
Thank you, ma'am.
Found it.
Ma'am, we've found the evidence.
Yu Lei.
Yu Lei!
- Where are you going?
- It has to be He Jin.
I'm going to make him pay.
Make him pay, how?
He's the one who burned you before, right?
This time he must be trying
to screw you over again.
Even if you can let it go of this matter,
I can't.
This time, I'm going to...
- No. You can't go.
- Why not?
With that scrawny body of his,
you think I can't take him on?
Of course you can.
But if you hit him,
you're the one who'll get in trouble.
Bro.
We can't just let He Jin get away with this.
That's true.
Then what do we do?
Just let him off the hook?
Since we have evidence,
how about...
Come here.
- What are you doing?
- He Jin. You're coming with me.
Are you crazy?
Let's go.
What are you guys doing?
Nothing much.
We just want to have a little chat.
What is there to talk about?
This is ridiculous.
He Jin.
My course schedule for this semester
was altered.
Do you know anything about that?
How would I know?
Yu Lei and I both clearly remember
that the last time we finalized our classes
this semester
was in the library's computer lab.
And, after we left,
you were the one
who sat down at my computer.
Why waste your breath on him?
He Jin.
You're the one who sabotaged Chen Ke,
aren't you?
When he didn't log out of the system,
you secretly changed his course selection.
Do you have any proof?
Don't make accusations without proof.
Sure, I went to the computer lab.
But I never touched the computer you used.
Besides, it's been several days.
Maybe you just remembered it wrongly.
You're just trying to pin the blame on me.
If you don't get out of my way,
I'm calling security.
He Jin.
Even now, you're still trying to deny it?
I don't know if you've noticed,
but the library's computer lab
has surveillance cameras.
What does that have to do with me?
I... I have a clear conscience.
A clear conscience?
Then do you dare come with us right now
and check the security footage?
You're trying to trick me.
Alright, Chen Ke.
He won't confess
until he's faced with hard evidence.
Once he sees himself committing
the act with his own eyes,
he'll come clean.
I get it now.
You're just trying to pick
a fight with me, aren't you?
Then hit me.
Go on, hit me!
That's enough.
He Jin.
I don't want to blow this out of proportion.
If you just admit your mistake,
and explain the situation to the counselor,
I'm sure they'll be lenient with you.
Stop with the fake sympathy!
Yeah. I did it all.
So what?
It's you people who look down on me,
one after another.
You hate that I'm from a small town.
You hate that I don't fit in.
You laugh at me behind my back.
What did I ever do wrong?
I'm clearly more diligent than any of you.
More self-disciplined.
So how did I become
the one with the problem?
He Jin.
I've never thought that way.
At Mingde University,
everyone here was once
the top student at their school.
No one here is better than anyone else.
And no one is weaker, either.
You can only earn others' respect
by acting with integrity.
You blame everyone else for everything.
Have you ever considered your own faults?
Chen Ke, stop wasting your breath on him.
Let's go straight to the counselor.
Let's go.
He Jin.
Your actions this time
were indeed out of line.
However, Chen Ke,
your previous class schedule
really can't be changed back.
How about this?
I'll talk to the professors
and explain the situation.
So your previous absences won't be counted.
He Jin.
After some discussion,
and considering your usual
academic performance
and grades have been excellent,
and also because
you've admitted your mistake,
the department will give you
a demerit on your record.
However, this demerit will only be
sent to your parents.
For now, it won't be publicly posted.
Counselor, can you not tell my family?
I... I was just trying to
play a prank on Chen Ke.
If my parents find out, they'll kill me.
That's not acceptable.
This punishment is already very lenient.
Also, you need to apologize
to Chen Ke in front of him.
Chen Ke.
I'm sorry.
Ke Ke.
Are you really planning
to move out of the dorms
and never go back?
Yeah.
If I keep living there,
I don't know how I'd face He Jin.
But you didn't do anything wrong.
He's the one who should
be moving out, not you.
No way. I can't just let this go.
I'm not letting it go.
I'm just tired.
So, what's your plan now?
Since the schedule can't be changed,
I'll just take all the classes.
I won't let him get what he wanted.
It's getting late.
Let's hurry up and pack.
Okay.
Come on. Don't think about
all that unhappy stuff.
Let's celebrate your new place first.
Thanks.
Eat up, Ke Ke.
I can't believe
you found a place so quickly this time.
That's why I say, Ke Ke,
you're just one of those people
who are blessed.
Things will definitely
get better and better for you.
Really?
Well, of course it is.
A-As long as we...
As long... As long as we...
Slow down.
Yu Lei.
Tell me, why?
Even though I haven't done anything wrong,
all this trouble always seems to find me.
Could it be...
that I'm really the problem?
No. That's not it, Ke Ke.
There's nothing wrong with you.
Don't worry.
Since you see me as a brother,
no matter what happens in the future,
I'll always be there for you.
I promise I'll take care of you
for the rest of my life.
Don't worry.
I can handle my own problems, myself.
You've already helped me more than enough.
Helping me for a lifetime,
that's too much to ask.
It's no trouble at all.
I do it because I want to.
Besides, didn't you say it yourself?
"Love is to always feel indebted."
I feel like I haven't done enough.
Even blood brothers
have to settle their debts.
A lifetime...
is just not realistic.
But...
I feel like we're more than just...
That's enough.
It's getting late.
You should head back to campus.
Okay.
I should have called out to him.
But I couldn't make a sound.
[Ke Ke, don't feel bad]
I should have kept writing in my diary.
But I couldn't write another word.
That final barrier...
Maybe I never should have tried to cross it.
Since I was doing just fine on my own before,
I guess I'll just stay that way.
Chen Ke.
You can do this.
So, in the stage of imperialism,
due to international monopolies
and the uneven economic
and political development of capitalism,
the world market further expanded
and developed into a unified,
all-encompassing world market.
Now, speaking of world currency,
let's talk about gold.
As I just mentioned, it can be used
as a general means of purchase.
- Here. Coffee.
- A general means of payment
to balance the deficit
in international payments.
So if you have gold and silver,
it's basically like having cash on hand.
- I see that now, many of our students...
- Hey, Yu Lei.
The topic the teacher was just talking
about hasn't finished.
And hoarding silver.
Actually, this is also a form of...
So, when you get home,
I want you all to review carefully.
Okay. That's all for today's class.
Class dismissed.
What was today's lecture even about?
I didn't understand a thing.
My hand is killing me.
Why don't I go to the next class for you?
I don't have any classes after this anyway.
You should hurry back and get some sleep.
Look how exhausted you are.
I'm fine. I can handle it.
Chen Ke, why are you trying so hard?
Someone messing with your schedule
isn't a big deal.
Last semester's final,
you didn't even show up,
and the professor still gave you a pass.
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you asking for it?
Alright, alright.
What rotten luck.
He's just joking.
Don't mind him.
Let's go, let's go.
He's always so arrogant.
Acting all superior.
He must have pissed off everyone in the dorm.
Otherwise, why would he suddenly move out
and rent a place on his own?
Just drop it.
Don't listen to them.
They're just jealous of you.
It's okay.
These classes you've chosen
are either obscure and difficult,
or they require a specialized foundation.
It's too hard for you to jump in midway.
Why don't you just drop them
for this semester
and re-enroll next semester?
If I do that,
then I'd really be letting
He Jin get his way.
But you still need to balance work and rest.
Let's go on an outing this weekend.
You should properly relax.
I've already got it all planned.
- We can go to that...
- No, thanks.
I have classes this weekend.
If you want to have fun,
you should go by yourself.
Then let's go to karaoke.
Or, we could check out a music store.
There's this new singer called Jay Chou.
His music is pretty good.
Or, we could go play some pool.
Bowling would be fun too.
Yu Lei.
I have too much on my mind lately.
My head's a mess.
And I don't have time to have fun.
Just leave me alone for now. Okay?
Okay.
Chen Ke.
Professor Meng.
Sorry to bother you again.
Not at all. Come, have a seat.
Lately, it seems like something's
been on your mind again.
About your situation,
I've heard all about it.
Going on like this must be
really hard on you.
I have a suggestion.
Take a look at this.
[Student Exchange Program]
Chen Ke, you...
- Sis.
- All you care about is Chen Ke.
You don't even want to see me anymore.
That's not true.
About Chen Ke's situation,
I've heard all about it.
I'm really sorry.
I've been so busy with my own things lately,
I wasn't able to help much.
It's fine.
It's all over now anyway.
Saves me the trouble of coming to you,
and having people say I'm pulling strings
or using connections.
I'm glad it's resolved.
And, from now on,
no one will have the chance
to say that about you again.
Sis, what do you mean?
I signed up for the school's
study abroad exchange program.
Starting next semester,
I won't be here anymore.
What?
You're going abroad?
I can't believe it.
Why are you leaving so soon?
What's with the sigh? I haven't left yet.
The paperwork still takes time.
So, when are you leaving?
Probably... in about two months.
I'll go over there first
to get used to the environment.
Chen Ke.
Senior. I heard you're going abroad soon.
I didn't know what gift to get you,
so I just bought you these flowers.
Thank you.
Chen Ke. Come.
Come sit over here.
Alright, everyone.
Even though I won't be here next semester,
this doesn't have to be
our last get-together. Right?
I just feel that while I'm still young,
I want to get out there and travel,
see things,
and broaden my horizons.
Who knows,
after I've seen and experienced it all,
I might find out that
this is the best place after all.
- Definitely.
- For sure.
But, when I first got my acceptance letter,
I was actually a little sad.
Because I really don't want to leave you all.
I haven't even left yet,
and I already miss you.
Don't think I'm being preachy,
but while we're still young,
and while we're still together,
we should cherish the good times.
Cherish the people around us.
Absolutely. Come on.
To cherishing the people around us.
- Let's drink to that.
- Let's all toast together.
- Together.
- Come on, come on.
Come on, let's drink.
- Here. Cheers!
- Cheers!
Cheers!
Bottoms up!
- Great booze.
- Bottoms up.
Come on, everyone.
Let's all take a group photo.
- Come on. Let's get a shot.
- Come on.
Everyone ready?
Three. Two. One.
Cheese!
Yu Lei.
Look at you.
You can barely walk straight.
And you still insisted on walking me home.
This is perfect, isn't it?
We can take a walk and sober up.
So... how have your classes been lately?
They're okay.
I've finally caught up.
That's good.
Back during winter break,
I heard my cousin say
she wanted to go abroad.
I just didn't expect
she'd be leaving so soon.
If I had known,
I would've spent more time with her.
You can't live your life with "what ifs".
If you'd spent a little less time
thinking about me,
maybe you could have
spent more time with your sister.
No. That's not it.
What are you talking about?
How are those two things the same?
But that's just how it is.
You can only focus your heart
on one thing at a time.
If you give more to one,
you'll naturally have less for the other.
No one has the energy
to focus on two things at once.
She's my cousin.
No matter what happens between us,
we'll always have our family bond.
But you're different.
You...
What's between you and me...
is a different kind of feeling.
Yu Lei, maybe I'll be the next one
to go abroad.
What?
You're going abroad too?
Chen Ke.
The way you're rushing to catch up on credits
is just too much for you.
So, I'd like to recommend you for the next
student exchange program.
That way, you can not only secure
your current credits,
but also broaden your horizons.
You'll also be able to focus
on your academic growth.
It's the best of both worlds.
Professor Meng, am I really good enough?
Of course you are.
I know your academic performance
better than anyone.
And you don't have to worry
about adjusting to the environment.
The university there
is our school's sister school.
It has a great academic atmosphere.
You'll be able to focus on your studies there
without any worries.
If I change to a new environment,
I'd probably have to start all over again.
What's wrong?
Are you scared?
I'm not scared.
It's just...
Is it that here,
there are ties you can't let go of?
What?
There's an opportunity like this?
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I'm going to apply too.
I want to go abroad with you.
I'm going abroad
because I agree with Professor Meng.
I want to further my studies overseas.
So what's your reason?
I... I...
Didn't my cousin say it?
We should see more of the world
while we're still young.
Besides, isn't this perfect?
The two of us can go together
and look out for each other.
Wait. What do you mean by that?
Don't you want us to go together?
I'm so grateful to have
met a friend like you.
But haven't you realized?
Ever since you met me,
you've run into nothing but trouble.
I think from now on,
we should give each other some space.
These past few days, studying by myself,
I've actually felt at peace.
And when you're alone,
don't you feel more relaxed too?
All this time being away from you,
I haven't been doing well at all.
Yu Lei, you don't understand.
My house is just up ahead.
You can leave me here.
You should go back.
No.
I won't let you.
I won't let you leave me.
Yu Lei, you're drunk.
We can talk tomorrow.
No, today.
Right now.
Don't you know that I...
I don't know what the future holds.
The only thing I'm sure of
is that I want to hold on to him
and never let go.
I've realized that I've been
in love with you for a long time.
The kind of "like" that's actually love.
I can't bear to let you go.
It seems we were destined to be together.
You two made my life hell.
So I'm going to make yours a living hell too!
Ke Ke... Ke Ke!