Is it out?
[IELTS Exam]
What score?
[Total score 6]
Bowen, I got a six.
A six?
Are you sure you didn't miss a zero?
No, it's six.
Even if I just guessed,
I could get over 10 points.
How could you only score a six?
You've disgraced Mom's status
as an English teacher.
Bowen—
Come over here.
Dad,
Mom,
I have failed you.
I failed to fulfill
the mission you gave me.
I let you down.
Bowen—
Shut up!
Have you forgotten
why Mom
named us Lang Bowen
and Lang Botu?
I haven't forgotten.
Say it.
Number one,
number two.
Louder!
Number one!
Number two!
Mom had such high
expectations for us.
Number one,
number two.
If we had a sister...
She would be named Number Three.
Right.
Translated, that would be Lang Bocui.
I'm a failure, not cut out for school,
and unworthy of the title "number one."
Did your genes mutate too?
A six.
Aren't you ashamed?
You're still laughing?
Get on your knees!
Kneel.
Mom,
I have good news.
I scored a six on my IELTS.
I can go abroad for grad school.
Who are you kidding?
Mom,
I didn't mean it that way.
He just made me so mad.
I'm telling you, Lang Botu.
You can fool me,
but if you lie to Mom,
believe it or not, I'll kick you to death.
Bowen,
how would I dare lie to Mom?
I really passed.
For the IELTS,
a perfect score is nine.
With a six,
I can go abroad for grad school.
You aren't fooling me?
I'm really not.
You scared me to death.
Can you be gentler?
Who designed this scoring system?
So messed up.
Mom, Dad,
Yangyang
can apply to foreign universities now.
Your spirits in heaven
can rest in peace.
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 11]
You should go.
He'll be back soon.
Then I...
I'm leaving then, Ying.
Hey,
why are you here?
I just got here.
Looking for me?
Need something?
Of course.
I want to get a drink with you.
If you wanted to drink,
you could've just called.
Why did you come all the way here?
I just wanted to come in person,
so I didn't call.
Look at how guilty you're acting.
Are you hiding
something from me?
Me?
I just had to come over.
Why?
We are bros.
Can't you just give it to me straight?
Kai,
I want to...
I'm giving this to you.
What happened?
I loaned out some money.
I'm collecting the debt these days.
The guy is a tough nut to crack.
If I come back in a couple of days,
you can give it back to me.
If I don't come back,
the car is yours.
Who are they?
I'll go with you.
It's too dangerous.
I'll do it myself.
Bro...
It's very dangerous!
He's so loyal.
I've always wanted to drive it.
Let's take it for a spin. Go!
There is a theory in economics
that a person will encounter at least
three major opportunities in life.
If you grasp just one,
you can turn your life around
and cross social classes.
Most people spend their whole lives
without grasping even one.
Why?
Because they are not prepared.
They don't realize
when an opportunity comes.
Looking back, they realize
that it slipped through their fingers.
Opportunities are always left for
those who are prepared.
Looking back at my past decades,
I've already missed
my first big opportunity.
I didn't do well
in the college entrance exam,
so I planned to study abroad
to improve my resume.
My family sold our house back then
and scraped together hundreds of thousands
to send me abroad.
If we had kept that house until now,
we would've received
demolition compensation
and be worth over ten million.
I wouldn't need to do this job.
But there's no point in regretting.
People have to look forward.
Now, the second big opportunity
of this lifetime,
Zhou Rong, this big fish, has swum over.
We must be fully prepared.
We absolutely cannot let this one
slip through our fingers again.
Chao,
it's not about slipping through
our fingers now.
If he really comes head-on,
we could stop him.
The problem now
is that he's ahead of us,
and we can't catch up.
What's the rush?
There's always a way.
We need to get a good car.
So annoying.
No manners.
What the hell?
Do you know how to drive?
Are you blind?
Bastards.
Get out of the car if you dare.
♪ Ha ha ha ha ♪
Chao,
this jerk is relentless.
♪ Ha ha ha ha ♪
I told you not to cause trouble.
We have a gun in the car.
If we cause a scene
♪ Ha ha ha ha ♪
and attract the cops,
we'll go straight to jail.
♪ The sacred light is reborn ♪
♪ The dream of every machine ♪
Stop the car!
Brake!
♪ Foolishness spreads in the revelry ♪
♪ This is humanity ♪
Chao,
it's totally our fault.
You sure know traffic rules well.
You two jerks,
get out of the car!
Are you crazy?
You stay in the car.
Don't get out.
Be good.
Get the hell out!
Sir, are you okay?
Here, Mr. Green Hat,
have a smoke and calm down.
Okay my ass!
Look at how you smashed my car.
Cut the crap. Pay up.
Pay up?
Sir, look,
you've been brake-checking us all the way.
Damn,
you have the nerve to say that?
I honked all the way for you to stop.
Are you deaf?
Besides,
if that jerk in your car
hadn't spit at me,
why would I cut you off?
Sir, let's keep things separate.
The rear-end is your fault
for cutting me off,
and the spitting is my buddy's fault.
The end result is that both cars
are damaged.
I suggest we each fix our own.
Cut the crap.
Pay up.
Go back.
It's just about money, right?
I only have
3,000 here. Take it all.
I have some small change too.
No.
I'll give it all to you, okay?
No,
you smashed my car like this,
and you're offering 3,000?
To fully repair this car,
it'll cost at least 30,000!
Sir, look at the car I'm driving.
Do I look like I have 30,000?
Fine.
I admit defeat.
I'm not trying to extort you.
Extorting you with this piece of junk
is pointless anyway.
How about this?
You call your insurance company,
so you won't have to
pay out of pocket.
To be honest with you,
our car doesn't have insurance.
Either you take the 3,000,
or you take full responsibility
and go to your insurance company.
I take full responsibility?
You hit my car
and want me to take full responsibility?
Is that what you mean?
Then how about I just give you my car?
Do you want it?
Yes.
[We are college students
who lost our money. Please help.]
[Bless you kind people.]
The market was better back in those days.
Setting up an endgame on the overpass
could earn me hundreds a day.
What's an endgame?
Have a heart.
Chess.
You don't understand that stuff anyway.
We don't look like college students,
do we?
What do you know?
[We are college students
who lost our money. Please help.]
Have some pity.
[Bless you kind people.]
That Professor Fu
from Jingda University's math department
is just like us.
That unlucky?
Ridiculous.
Is there any food at home?
There are some digestion pills.
Don't mention that.
Have a heart.
Give us eight bucks.
Is there
a junkyard nearby?
Give us eight bucks
and we'll take you there.
Then we...
Where you think you going?
What?
Honghong, Maomao or whatever.
Hong... Hongwei.
Hongwei.
What are you doing?
What?
Who are you?
He owes me money. I'm collecting debt.
Hey,
if he owes money, talk about the money.
Why are you getting physical?
So what?
How much does he owe you?
A hundred thousand.
A hundred thousand?
Wait.
You're asking people like us
for 100,000?
Are you broke out of your mind?
What is this?
[IOU]
You wrote this?
I wrote this.
-Don't have that much money.
No money?
Don't you have a junkyard?
Use that to pay the debt.
No,
that junkyard
-It's his.
-It’s mine.
Right.
Well,
how can you use my junkyard
to pay his debt?
Why not?
That's not reasonable.
Do I look like a reasonable person?
He's not a reasonable person.
Hey, you...
How about this?
You just strangle him,
and won't the debt be written off?
-Sir, don’t.
-Can you be reasonable?
How am I not reasonable?
If I strangle him,
wouldn't you still have to pay the debt?
Right, then wouldn't it still be...
Why should I pay the debt?
Why?
No, there's a knife.
No, no.
No need.
No need, sir.
No, no need to show it.
-No need to show it.
-Thank you.
I appreciate the thought.
Thanks for your trouble.
Well...
So...
There's an IOU.
The money was borrowed, right?
A hundred thousand...
Give me a week.
I'll pay you back 100,000 in a week.
Is a week okay?
Okay.
One week.
Is there any place nearby
that sells zipper oil?
Over there, up there.
Turn left.
Why?
You talked too fast.
You promised him a week.
Can you get 100,000
in a week?
Anyway, I don't have it.
What?
Do you think money grows on trees?
No, Tinggang!
Don't!
How dare you borrow 100,000?
Tinggang.
It's Li Penggai.
Li Penggai extorted me.
Li Penggai?
Yes.
Li Penggai said
as long as he got the 100,000,
he wouldn't give us a hard time.
He wouldn't give you a hard time!
What does it have to do with me?
I...
I just brought you in.
You just joined, right?
You...
Don't, don't.
I...
Where are we going to get 100,000?
If we can't, let's pull off a big heist!
How big?
If we can't, let's pull off
a medium heist!
Medium is fine.
How about here?
Is anyone here?
Since we got to Sanjiangkou,
this car has been with us.
Now that we're selling it,
I kind of miss it already.
You got infected by that corrupt official.
You're addicted to junk cars.
Not exactly.
We bought it for 25,000.
Is it appropriate to sell it for 30,000?
I'm thinking too small.
We'll sell it for 50,000.
Is anyone here?
Alright, stop yelling.
You know
we bought this junk car for 25,000.
But 20,000 went to fake documents.
The car is only worth 5,000.
So you mean we'll sell it
at the original price?
No.
We can't sell it by weight, right?
You just mentioned thinking small.
I reflected on it.
We are going to pull off a big heist now.
Can we haggle over
this petty cash?
What if this car
exposes our whereabouts
and alerts the police?
How can we do great things then?
Then what do we do?
We'll give the car away.
Give it away?
To whom?
There's no one here.
Because there is no one here,
no one will see us.
We'll just leave it here.
First time doing a good deed.
I'll leave a note for the lucky one.
Stop shaking!
If you break
my new car's suspension,
I'll kill you.
Can you rob houses?
Can you murder and commit arson?
Can you commit petty theft?
I can do that.
No, you can't!
You don't even dare to steal a bicycle.
For that 100,000,
we have to steal a car, got it?
Bro.
Don't call me bro.
There really is a car.
Even if there is a car, it's not yours.
Whose car is this?
Who parked their car here?
You can't park here!
Who parked here?
For...
free.
F-for free?
For free?
In your dreams.
No, look.
Impossible.
Look.
♪ The stars twinkle, the moon curves ♪
[For free]
Look.
I recognize these two words.
It's for free.
Isn't it for free?
♪ A gentle breeze
sways the willow branches ♪
The car door opens too.
Heaven blessed us?
And it comes with half a tank of gas.
Will this leave a scar?
It's a very small cut.
Don't worry, it won't.
Song Xing,
you are really something.
You acted recklessly
and got Li Qian injured.
If something really went wrong,
could you take the responsibility?
Stop scolding him.
Chief Zhang, Captain Wang.
There's nothing I can do either.
We can't control this matter.
If word gets out...
Yes, I know, I know.
Why are you here?
You should rest for a couple of days.
It's too stuffy in the dorm.
Please let me work.
No, you'd better not join for now.
If I let you work while injured again,
Director Gao will punish me again.
I'll punish him.
Li Qian, come here.
Come.
Stand here.
Get over here.
Do you know why the chief is angry?
Because I publicly pointed out
that he misread a word.
Cut the crap.
Would the chief be this petty?
I'm telling you, listen carefully.
It's because
the girl got hurt.
Song Xing, you're considered
a veteran, right?
Li Qian is just a rookie.
When things happen to you,
you're impulsive and reckless.
When things happen to Li Qian,
she's calm and collected.
You call yourself an investigator,
yet you got locked in an elevator.
If word gets out,
you'll become a laughingstock.
Right?
Li Qian here
outsmarted ruthless bandits.
If word gets out,
everyone will give her a thumbs up.
Don't you feel ashamed?
I was wrong.
You were wrong.
As for the future work of the task force,
don't participate in it for now.
Don't do this, I...
C-Chief.
I...
I urgently need a chance now
to prove myself.
If Captain Wang doesn't let me
participate in the investigation,
then won't I really become
the joke of the bureau?
You already are the personification
of a joke.
You...
Then what should I do?
You can make up for your mistakes
by taking care of the injured.
When Li Qian's injury heals,
we'll talk about your matter.
Let's start the meeting.
Okay.
Come on, meeting time.
Let me do it.
Are you really
taking care of me exclusively?
I'm sorry, Li Qian.
These days, I'm so unlucky
cold water gets stuck in my teeth.
Let's just wait for the hot water.
That crappy elevator
at Zheng Yongbing's place...
Did I blame you?
No.
I blame myself.
Blaming yourself is useless now.
We need to find a way
to get back to the task force.
That's why I'm here to take care of you.
Your injury needs to heal quickly
for us to have any hope.
Did you really not find anything
at Zheng Yongbing's place?
I found nothing.
There are photos of the scene.
Then did you check Ye Jian's
computer,
phone,
apps, WeChat,
and other electronics?
We've finished this part too.
Before Captain Ye left,
[Buy now] [Add to cart]
the last thing he opened on his computer
was Taobao.
[Price 19.90 yuan]
It's a watch.
Chief,
could this be
a breakthrough?
[Vintage square student
male waterproof digital watch]
Looks different.
Purchase link?
[Vintage square student
male waterproof digital watch]
Captain Ye browsed this watch?
Why would Captain Ye check Liu Bei?
[Vintage square student
male waterproof digital watch]
[Zheng Yongbing]
This is our only clue now.
[Liu Bei]
[Zheng Yongbing] [Liu Bei]
The most urgent task...
is to find him.
Chief Zhang,
this discovery is very timely,
but it doesn't seem to
relate to Captain Ye
and Chief Lu's case.
[Zheng Yongbing] [Liu Bei]
[Hu Jianren]
Chief Zhang,
any new discoveries?
Let me organize my thoughts.
Wait a moment.
[Hu Jianren]
[Complainant: car dealer,
sold a used car nearby]
[Lu Zheng car crash]
[Li Qian escorts Zhang Yi'ang home]
[Hu Jianren]
[Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau]
[Chairman of Rongcheng Group: Zhou Rong]
[Ping'an City jewelry shop robbery case]
[Hu Jianren]
Who?
Get out.
No, no, no.
Stand up and speak if you have any ideas.
Any ideas?
Anything to say?
Do you?
No.
If not,
be quiet. Don't make a sound.
Okay?
No one is allowed to
interrupt Chief Zhang's thinking.
Understand?
Yes.
Chief Zhang,
keep thinking.
It's okay.
This watch...
It was found in Zheng Yongbing's home.
He said Liu Bei left it.
Then is this watch the one...
Chief.
What are you two doing here?
It seems we are late.
Chief has already figured it out.
That's impossible.
We just found out about this.
Chief,
we found some clues.
What?
What? Tell me.
[Vintage square student
male waterproof digital watch]
No.
There's still a slight difference.
They don't look exactly the same.
[Vintage square student
male waterproof digital watch]
They're the same, right?
[Vintage square student
male waterproof digital watch]
This one is the same.
Ye was looking at this watch.
Chief Zhang,
you're a true detective.
Are you clairvoyant?
This watch is so expensive.
Should we investigate?
Chief Zhang,
checking the watch isn't dangerous.
Give me a chance
to redeem myself.
[Fenglinwan Hotel]
Why are we here?
The only luxury watch store in Sanjiangkou
is right inside.
Let's go.
I'm telling you,
those new girls,
don't...
Those are cops.
What are they doing here?
What?
Limited edition with a serial number...
This is the only one in Sanjiangkou.
I remember
a customer brought it in before.
Who was it?
Do you want an appraisal
or maintenance?
Is this watch real or fake?
That's an appraisal.
Two hundred yuan.
-We are...
-Let's do the appraisal.
We're undercover.
Mr. Lu!
What a coincidence.
Yes, yes.
Since you have already
followed us here,
come on in.
Mr. Lu.
Manager.
You two,
what a coincidence.
Shopping for watches?
Which one caught your eye?
We know the boss,
so we can get you a discount.
Mentioning Mr. Lu gets a discount?
That's great.
We're doing an appraisal.
This...
What about it?
This is a nice watch.
Where did you buy it?
Mr. Lu,
isn't this watch...
What?
Sir,
you just said
who brought this watch in?
Miss,
I'm sorry.
This is customer privacy,
I can't disclose it.
Song Xing,
take it out.
It's...
It's real.
I appraised it.
But
well...
the person who brought it in...
I really can't remember.
Those two are definitely hiding something.
Liu Bei was wearing the watch,
but why did it seem like Lu Yibo
recognized it?
It doesn't make sense.
Liu Bei is new to Sanjiangkou?
Right.
Captain Wang said
that's what Zheng Yongbing told him.
Why are you starting the car?
Aren't we going back to the station?
No.
Just because the manager
can't remember now
doesn't mean
he won't remember later.
How could this happen?
How could this be?
Didn't you say the watch
was already on a train
out of Sanjiangkou?
Yibo,
you don't trust me either?
Of course I trust you.
But that watch
couldn't have grown legs
and walked back, right?
I got it.
The police were following me.
Did you have that watch
serviced at the watch shop?
Yes.
Then I should give that manager
some hush money.
No.
That'll only make things worse.
The police will find out
about this sooner or later.
I'm done for.
The police will catch us soon.
Everything that's been happening lately
has been way too intense.
Danger and excitement
are your turn-ons.
Yibo,
you're getting worked up.
Is your blood pressure spiking?
Mr. Rong won't let us off either.
Yibo,
let's just do
what we need to do right now.
As for the future...
We'll talk about it later.
Do we even have a future?
I knew
you two would come back to me.
Do you remember
who brought it in for service?
I remember.
Who was it?
I don't want to say.
Then why did you get in the car?
I... well, I...
Well...
Cooperating with police investigations
is the duty of every citizen.
I didn't say I wouldn't cooperate.
But I work here.
I don't want to offend
the wrong people.
Understood.
Then how can we
make sure you don't offend anyone,
and we still get our answer?
Then you have to ask me.
Ask what?
Ask...
"Doesn't the shop have service records?"
Doesn't the shop have service records?
Yes.
Officers,
we do.
I searched through thousands of photos.
Only these three
have Ye in the background,
but they are all of the back of his head,
so they are very blurry.
It's fine if Ye is blurry
and unclear.
Is Lu Yibo unclear too?
There is one where Lu Yibo is quite clear.
This one.
Is there a
digital version?
Show me the digital version of this one.
Yes.
Chief.
We have a clue.
Did you find out whose watch it is?
It's Lu Yibo's.
How do you know?
Did you follow us?
Even the serial number is the same.
It's confirmed.
[Watch Servicing Record]
Song Xing did a good job this time.
Now it's time to go back to
Fenglinwan.
We'll toss
a pebble
into his little heart
and see what kind of ripples it creates.
What kind of ripples it creates.
Wang, let's go.
Let's go take a look.
Let's go.
[Municipal Bureau Chief Zhang Yi'ang]
Chief Zhang.
Mr. Lu,
are you at Fenglinwan?
In five minutes,
Captain Wang and I will be there.
What's the matter, Chief Zhang?
I just want to talk to you again.
Can we do it another day?
I lost something.
I have to go back and look for it.
Mr. Lu lost something.
Since you lost something,
you should come to us.
That's our job.
Or how about this?
You go to the Public Security Bureau,
explain everything clearly,
and we'll help you find it.
Take your pick.
Either works.
I'm here.
I'll wait for you.
Okay.
What happened? You lost something?
What did you lose?
Is this watch yours?
I lost it,
but it wasn't originally mine.
When did Lang Bowen
lose this watch to you?
About a year ago.
I don't remember clearly.
The information about this watch
is very important to us.
Think carefully before you speak.
I'll ask you this question again.
The night of Ye Jian's incident,
did he come to Fenglinwan?
Mr. Lu.
Let me remind you.
Without any evidence,
we wouldn't be
coming to you again and again.
I gave you a chance.
This is really your last chance.
Yes.
He came.
Why did Ye come to you?
He also asked about that watch.
Why didn't you tell us last time?
Later, Ye died.
I was afraid of getting into trouble.
[The World's Jokes]
Mr. Rong.
Wait.
[The World's Jokes]
Let me ask you a question.
A mushroom met an orange.
The mushroom told the orange to drop dead,
and the orange did.
Why?
I don't know.
Do you know why recently
I don't find jokes
funny anymore?
Is Lu Yibo causing trouble
again?
If he dares, I'll make him drop dead.
And you can take over Fenglinwan.
Mr. Rong,
I know something
that will cheer you up.
Zhu Yifei
will be in Sanjiangkou soon.
We can make the deal right away.
Get to it then.
Don't worry, Mr. Rong.
Zhu Yifei is
a big shot in the underworld.
He wouldn't do something as low as
selling fakes.
He's not a small fry.
[Zheng Yongbing]
I'll take this call first.
Hello?
Ren,
can you sell the God of Wealth statue
back to me at the original price?
Zheng Yongbing,
don't push your luck, okay?
Don't you know
how much I paid you
for that piece of junk?
Ren,
do you think I want to buy it back?
The investigators are onto me.
I have to return the stolen goods.
None of my business.
Why would the investigators
care about your petty crimes?
If I had known,
I would have melted it all down to sell,
instead of selling it to that woman
at Fenglinwan.
Wait a minute.
You're saying the police tracked you down
through Fenglinwan?
That's right.
Who's the woman?
Zhou Qi.
I sold the jewelry to her,
and she snitched on me.
Ren,
I'll add another 20,000, okay?
Ren?