(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Dear Lord, through your Son,
we pour the power of the Holy Spirit
into this water in abundance,
and may those who have died
with Jesus Christ
rise to a new life with him.
Your Son lives and reigns with you
forever and ever in the kingdom of heaven.
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit. Amen.
Now, God will share his own life
with this dear child.
Let us all take part
in this ceremony with joy.
Are the godparents,
who've offered to help guide this child
onto the right path of faith,
present at this ceremony?
I'm here!
Here I am, guys. The child's godmother.
Who's here?
Auntie and Uncle, sorry for being late.
Hello, Cousin. Hello, cousin's wife.
This woman is really the baby's godmother?
What's going on?
Yes, we picked her.
She's family, and she's…
she's the child's godmother.
In the name… of the Father,
the Son,
and the Holy Spirit,
I baptize Angela.
Amen.
Mu-hee, you must have gone crazy.
How dare you show up here!
Mu-hee's a part of your family.
You even said so in the article
and in front of the priest.
Well, then, you're showing us
how you're family?
You come with flowers for the baptism,
and everything's fine?
That's not it.
There's no world
in which I'm part of this family.
We've got no ties.
There's no Mu-hee here.
Um, what?
I'm Do Ra-mi.
Do Ra-mi?
You're filming a show, is that it?
I suppose you haven't seen the movie yet.
If this was a movie,
I wouldn't have arrived with flowers.
In the movie,
Do Ra-mi carries other things with her.
Oh, yeah? Like what?
A cadaver.
She delivers dead bodies to her enemies.
That's extremely terrifying.
I wonder…
whose dead bodies
would terrify you the most?
What scares you?
Mu-hee, tell us.
Do you remember how your parents died?
Should I say "I don't remember,"
like I did back then?
That's cool.
Well, I'll say I don't know.
Like I did then to piss you off.
Is that so?
We'll keep her in the dark, then.
It's better this way.
For your sake
and ours.
If that's how you want it,
you better not show up in her life again.
If you do whatever you please
and continue to show up
just because you want to hurt her,
her head could explode.
Boom!
All right, then.
She's not
just something you can shove
under the rug.
If she explodes, everybody dies.
So please,
receive the abundant grace from God
and go to heaven.
Amen.
Dance! Feel alive…
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
Hi there. I'm Do Ra-mi.
Do Ra-mi.
Do Ra-mi, your reputation precedes you.
Uh-uh. Different Do Ra-mi.
That creature is very frightening.
She's scary.
I am the version only you know.
The crazy bitch who's haunting Cha Mu-hee.
I see.
You must be that demon, I guess.
I should be scared of you, right?
You know what she said.
I heard too much about you already.
Although based on your clothes,
who would find you scary?
- Although, I wouldn't call you normal.
- You like it?
Looks good, huh?
I came from a photo shoot.
A photo shoot.
I heard you were there this morning,
and everything was fine.
Hey, how did you get in here?
I opened the door with the code.
I saw it when I came here
with that writer.
You're quite meticulous for a psycho.
One look at the code,
and you remembered it.
Cha Mu-hee's sneaky. That's who she is.
Creepy, huh?
Yeah.
I'm uncomfortable, thanks to you.
You can be frank.
I know so much about you already.
I've no desire to say mean things
to a person I just met.
But since you've said it's fine to,
I will.
I've had enough.
Whatever game you're playing right now,
I no longer want to take part in it.
So move along.
You're beyond boring. Get lost.
I don't like taking taxis.
Drive me home, okay?
Joo Ho-jin.
Hey, Ho-jin.
Hey, honey.
Are you angry?
Your pride's hurt 'cause I stood you up?
Aw, and I dumped you back in Canada.
What's wrong? Are you hurt now?
So cute.
When the driver comes,
we should go to my place together.
There's a nice bottle of wine.
We'll open it. Set the mood.
We'll listen to our song.
Yeah.
Sing.
Gets better each time I listen to it.
Your ride is on the way.
Once it gets here, I'll take off.
Don't make me leave.
You know I'll come back.
Hi, can I help you?
We're outside. Thank you.
Good.
I see you pulling up. Great.
Okay.
Cha Mu… Cha Mu-hee!
Come back here!
You can't…
Ah, shoot.
Please wait a sec. I'll get her.
Hey, Mu-hee!
She went back inside.
Please, wait. Cha Mu-hee.
Come on, stop this!
Your ride is waiting.
It's late. Go home already.
If you don't come out,
I'll report you for trespassing.
Hey, honey.
I scared you.
You go to sleep in this?
It's what you like to wear?
Oh, sexy.
That's my brother's.
It was in the laundry basket.
Why are you wearing it?
Give it back. Come on, now.
But I like it.
I wanted to wear it for the night.
Why? Why would you wanna sleep in that?
Should I sleep naked?
Hmm.
You have a dirty mind.
The taxi is here.
Go already.
You can just take that robe and get out.
Oh! I was so busy today. I'm too tired!
Oh, you're not staying here.
You're not gonna sleep here.
That's right. I'll shower
and then go to bed. Want that?
You won't do that.
- All right.
- Cha Mu-hee.
Cha Mu-hee isn't here tonight.
You see,
she wouldn't come to your house
after all that.
Hello? Yes, I'm sorry.
Please wait a moment.
She's on her way.
All right, then.
Okay, Ms. Do Ra-mi, let's have a talk.
Did she have you come to my house
to resolve things?
Because she can't say sorry
for what happened?
I didn't come to ask for forgiveness.
I'm here to make sure
you don't ever accept her apology.
No matter what.
For your sake, honey.
When you're in Italy,
don't let her persuade you.
This is my advice.
Your advice is of no use to me.
I won't be going to Italy, okay?
I'm looking for someone to replace me,
so I won't ever get involved
with Mu-hee again.
Yesterday was very upsetting,
but I understand that it wasn't her fault.
It's absurd,
but I won't be able to brush it off
and pretend you're not serious.
But I would never
get involved with a woman
who completely ignores
how other people feel,
depending on her mood.
Never. I can't stand those kinds of women.
Don't dump your emotions on others
and expect them to deal with it
because that's basically
psychological torture.
You're just a silly child
throwing a tantrum
'cause you wanted a toy so badly,
and you couldn't get it.
I just don't wanna be a part of that.
I'm gonna avoid you.
You said you think
before you speak. Is that right?
That means that you…
you despise Cha Mu-hee.
Yes, I do.
I don't ever wanna be with her.
I'll do my best to avoid her.
I'm not interested in being with her.
This is over, once and for all.
Okay.
So that's it. Don't change your mind.
Mm, time's up.
What do you mean "time's up"?
The timer.
It's for the pill I gave you.
Things could have gotten complicated
if Cha Mu-hee showed up.
You're Do Ra-mi. That's your story now?
Yeah, so if you run into Cha Mu-hee,
please don't tell her anything about this.
You're gonna keep insisting…
Good night.
And don't go back to her.
Oh.
Let's go back to
that child and a toy metaphor.
Just imagine that poor girl never had one.
Maybe she'd be confused because
she finally found something she wants.
Would you still consider that a tantrum?
She's really that pathetic.
That's why I'm here.
Are you awake?
Today's the day I'm moving in. Remember?
Ah, right.
You didn't answer your phone, so I used
the passcode you gave me to get in.
I didn't know you'd be here.
Were you drinking?
Is that why you slept on the couch?
Uh, no, I…
I brought my stuff inside for now.
It's not that much.
ZOLPIDEM, TRAZODONE, RAMELTEON
TAKE AT BEDTIME
It's for the pill I gave you.
She actually drugged me?
What's this?
Sleeping pills. Really?
Why'd she knock me out?
Things could have gotten
complicated if Cha Mu-hee showed up.
Mu-hee was here,
so why would it get complicated?
She was like
a different person last night.
Ho-jin?
- I'll put my stuff over there.
- Okay.
By the way…
…has Mu-hee
called herself Do Ra-mi lately?
Have you heard her joke around like that?
Yeah, she does that.
"You better watch out. I'm Do Ra-mi."
She's always saying that.
Oh, I see.
Everybody loves it
when she acts like Do Ra-mi.
She was a big hit at the photo shoot,
and they all said Do Ra-mi was killing it.
Mu-hee really loved it too.
Oh crap, the outfit!
Almost forgot about it.
Why? Because you need to return it?
She left set
wearing the outfit from the photo shoot.
Sounds like it's out of character for her
to leave a shoot
with an outfit from production.
Um, I guess.
She was tired and fell asleep right away.
She's been asleep until now.
She said that? Are you positive?
Is she better now?
I was on the phone with her earlier.
She's at Pilates right now.
Pilates?
You're doing so well today.
I've got a lot on my mind.
I need to focus on exercising.
Hey, about the replacement interpreter.
I have a friend. Her name's Yoko.
She's not completely fluent in Italian,
but she's available.
That's fine. Thanks for asking around.
It's all good.
But this isn't like you.
You're not the type to leave a job.
You're not irresponsible.
Or is it because of Do Ra-mi?
It's Mu-hee. Cha Mu-hee.
It's complicated. Please don't confuse it.
It's turned out well for her.
Playing Do Ra-mi
has turned her life around.
I read she was born rich too.
Her family's in education.
Maybe they knew your grandfather?
Why are you bringing him up?
They're connected.
Publishing and education.
I don't think so.
You're just trying too hard.
Anyway,
she was born to a rich family.
Who doesn't want that?
Just imagine that poor girl never had one.
But honestly,
why are you quitting?
- Did she dump you?
- Sure.
If I get dumped and rejected,
I should get really upset and get drunk.
Just quit my job on a whim.
Yeah.
Sounds great!
That's a healthy reaction, I guess.
Well, why not?
It might actually help to relax.
Drugging the guy who wants
to break up with you,
then going to your morning Pilates class
like nothing happened.
No way!
Man, she's worse than I thought.
Did Do Ra-mi really do that?
Hi there, I'm Do Ra-mi.
Yes, please contact Yoko quickly.
Tell her that she can make her plans
as soon as possible.
There won't be a camera on her
during the first part of our Italy trip,
so don't worry.
Thanks.
Uh, as for her accommodations,
we booked a detached villa in Italy,
like the one in Canada.
But this time,
Hiro will stay in the same place.
Oh.
I thought, because there have been
articles about Mu-hee's relatives,
so what if they mention her relatives
during the Italy part of the trip?
We could even do a video call
with her family and profile them.
I'm so sorry.
The family's not close to her at all.
I don't believe they'll want any of that.
Ah, is that so?
I guess we can't help it.
Hiro's team said he's a fool
for his niece, so he might be up for it.
He's odd.
But apparently, he's proud of his niece.
Oh wow!
We'll make sure to bring a nice gift
when we meet later today.
Excuse me?
You're meeting Hiro… today?
He's here in Seoul. You didn't know?
No, we didn't.
- You could come and join us.
- No, we can't.
He's here for personal reasons.
We won't bother him. No!
Uh, well, then.
Hiro's niece is five years old.
She loves blue.
Her favorite character
is Power Ranger Blue. Nothing pink, then.
She won't like that.
Pink, no. And blue? Hell yeah. Got it?
You got that? No pink, just blue.
Think of it as an FYI.
Blue. Okay.
Is Mu-hee still coming
for her interview today?
Yes, she'll be here very soon.
And where's Ms. Shin?
Ah, she'll be here soon. It's fine.
Apparently, she was working all night.
Ah.
PRODUCER SHIN JI-SUN
Come out. We need to talk.
Where are you?
I'm downstairs.
Come up to me. I'll be waiting.
I should end things
before we run into each other.
Yeah.
I did this to myself. I'm not gonna run.
Coming! Hold on!
Are you, um, the delivery girl?
Who are you?
I… was gonna see someone.
Uh…
Honey, you expecting someone? Come here.
What do you want?
Uh…
Well, nothing. Yeah.
Oh wow. He's a bastard.
I come up here to see her? Is that it?
I don't wanna cling to you.
The number
you're trying to reach is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
She's not picking up the phone.
What's the matter?
Hold on. Let's talk this out.
I swear, we never met!
You have to believe.
- Believe me, okay? I just--
- I don't believe you.
I don't know her, really.
Look into my eyes. It's the truth, okay?
- Hey! Let go of me. I'm done.
- No, don't walk away!
We just moved in.
We can't fight like this.
Really. We've been a couple
for over eight years!
Don't do that!
Let me in!
Yes. I'm gonna talk to the staff now.
I'll call you later.
Bye.
Great! Is this the outfit?
- Yes, I'm sorry. I was very out of it.
- Thanks for bringing it.
- I'm really very sorry.
- It's okay.
There's something in here.
- I don't know what this is.
- You don't?
Hmm. What is it?
"If someone was kind to me"?
It looks like a page torn out of a book.
Hello, Mr. Joo.
It's a verse.
You don't know this poem?
Uh, well, no.
I don't know it. I never read poetry.
Mm, really? You've never seen it?
No.
I never read any poetry.
But why was it in my pocket?
The person who wore it
before you probably forgot to wash it.
Just throw it out.
Let's get to the interview.
Yeah.
Uh, may I talk to you?
There's something I wanna tell you.
I'm sorry.
So, so very sorry about everything.
I'm here to make sure
you don't ever accept her apology.
Yong-u.
Yup?
They said we might see a festival
on our trip to Italy
because it's gonna take place
when we're there.
Sounds good.
We'll also get to visit vineyards
and old castles.
So I better go.
If I quit, I'll miss all of that.
And I'll never see him again
if I don't go.
Hey, Yong-u.
What if everything just, uh,
gets super hard in life,
and it all just makes you wanna
quit everything,
but then you close your eyes,
and you wake up,
and suddenly realize
someone fixed everything.
That sounds great. I'd be grateful.
Really?
Are you saying I should thank her
for all of this?
Are you talking about Do Ra-mi?
- What?
- Mu-hee, you fell into a coma.
And when you opened your eyes again,
you were a global star thanks to her.
Yeah, that's true.
Well, it's actually pretty cool, I think.
While you were just lying in bed,
Do Ra-mi has accomplished
a whole lot for you.
She did.
I wasn't in charge.
I can't remember.
Look, Mu-hee, just imagine
if that worked every time.
Just close your eyes.
When there's something
you don't want to do, you say,
"Do Ra-mi, go clean the bathroom now.
I don't wanna do it."
And she does it for you.
Is this real?
I can't do anything myself.
Maybe I should give up?
I closed my eyes,
and she's done everything while I was out.
Is it just like what happened back then?
Would it be okay for me to live like this?
Hi!
Welcome to Seoul.
Arigato.
They don't speak
each other's language at all.
How can they communicate without you?
They'll figure it out.
It's not for long.
Hiro has been learning English.
He'll be able to talk to Mu-hee.
I'm sure it's gonna be okay.
Oh!
I got this present for your niece.
How do I say a present?
Present. A child's present.
Thanks for the present.
I know she'll love it.
You speak English now?
I've been practicing.
That's amazing. Wow!
Now I feel guilty
I don't really know Japanese.
I should've practiced it too.
Slowly.
Takes me time.
I can say things slowly.
Did she get drunk? Was she rude?
Did she say something wrong?
I'm wondering the same thing.
He wanted to ask Mu-hee
about what happened on the plane.
What did you
tell me before?
I'm sorry.
It's here.
I can't remember. Sorry.
That day,
you were looking me straight in the eye.
I don't know what he's saying.
His vocabulary's still very limited.
If I knew what those words meant,
I'd understand why you did that.
What are you saying?
I'm sorry, I don't understand!
You… gave kiss.
Kiss!
K… kiss?
- Me?
- Yes.
What? No. I wouldn't. You're lying.
I know you're lying.
That's what you're doing.
I'm lying? You are lying to me!
You don't say that.
You didn't kiss me on the plane?
If you said I was drunk
and threw up on you,
I'd be okay, even if I don't remember.
But in no world would I…
I don't want to kiss you.
I don't understand you,
but I can tell you're denying it.
This is really frustrating.
Call Nanami over, please.
No need.
I think that tells me
everything I wanted to know.
I studied Korean,
thinking it might help me remember
what you said that day.
It didn't, so I came here to ask you.
But I guess
what I really wanted to confirm…
wasn't what you said that day…
but your feelings.
Whether you remember it or not,
it's clear you didn't do it
because you like me.
Maybe our language barrier isn't so bad.
If you understood me,
I could never be so honest with you.
Sorry.
Please, please eat.
It's on you!
Okay.
Did Do Ra-mi do all this?
What for?
Do I need to quit everything?
If I quit everything, what will you do?
So if I close my eyes, Do Ra-mi,
tell me, what are you gonna do?
KINDNESS, TO ME
Do that. You're good at it.
Plus, you're basically
the only one who knows
about the hateful troll in my head.
So… keep rooting for me like you do.
Pray I never lose to my Do Ra-mi.
Mu-hee, where are you now? Can we meet?
I'd like to talk to you in person
to confirm certain things.
This is urgent.
It's important that we meet.
You promised you wouldn't talk to Mu-hee.
Oh, honey.
Why would you do that? You can't change.
Do Ra-mi.
Ah.
I'm very busy right now.
No, wait, Do Ra-mi!
Drives me nuts.
Thank you for the meal.
If you decide to come to Japan,
it'll be my treat.
Why did I promise that?
You don't even understand.
Bye-bye.
How did it go with Hiro?
You can't really talk to each other.
You carry her passport on you?
Yours? We'll be going
to Italy in two days.
I want it.
I'll go ahead and take off to Italy.
Sure. What?
I'll see you there.
Wait, hey.
I wanna switch off my head
For a while…
ITALY
Can't you just dial it down?
I wanna shut down my POV for a while
Your shadow lingers too close
I can't take it now
Dance! Feel alive!
I would dive into the dark
I love to be alone, so leave me alone
Dance! Feel the vibe!
I might be a narcissist
I love to be alone
Just leave me alone
Dance alone, I'm dancing alone
Dance alone, don't ring the alarm
Dance alone, dance alone
PAPAGO♥
Oh jeez. He's calling me again.
You're calling again, honey. What is it?
Where are you?
You agreed to meet,
so tell me where you are.
Why? You'll come here if I tell you?
I will, but I can't find you.
Raise your hand, and maybe I can see you.
Oh.
Come, then.
There's something I need to confirm.
Are you the hateful troll
in Mu-hee's head?
Oh, that's me. Yeah.
I give constructive criticism, that's all.
It's for her own good, and yours too.
She will make your life difficult,
so avoid her.
I want to avoid her. Believe me, I do.
I don't even want to be here, believe me.
I'll never be happy to see you,
Do Ra-mi.
Mu-hee already went to Italy?
Good for her.
Shooting is different than travel for fun.
When was the last time
I went on a solo trip?
How's her meeting with Hiro?
Oh, yeah. The meeting.
They might have had a fight.
Hiro looked unhappy
when I saw him at the restaurant.
I'm here. You get a lot of editing done?
- We did.
- Yong-u brought us snacks.
He got your favorite macarons.
Thank you for these.
Did you look for the footage
that I mentioned?
- There are some copyright issues.
- How should we deal with that?
The cream inside is delicious.
I'm headed out for the evening.
- You're leaving?
- Yeah.
- Yong-u's taking off.
- Ah.
- Bye.
- See ya.
Thanks for coming.
You don't pick up your phone
when you're angry?
That's right.
I really don't wanna fight.
I only fight when I have to.
Even if I get hurt a little.
Hit me, go ahead. Come on now.
I'm not angry at you, Yong-u.
This is my fault.
I got into a fight with the wrong person,
so I'm mad at myself.
Think of it as bumping shoulders
with someone,
and they're walking by frantically
down the street to move on.
That's it. Let's put an end to this
with me saying sorry.
That means you're dumping me?
How can I do that
when we weren't even dating?
Friends who had fun.
A simple one-night stand.
I don't do one-night stands.
I would never sleep with someone casually,
then ghost her.
And I'm pretty sure
you're not that kind of person either.
I thought that it meant
we were dating now.
Are you telling me you're ending things?
Whoa.
I thought I made it clear
I didn't wanna fight.
And you're actually picking one now.
Then… let's be honest with each other.
You're a cheater,
but you don't have casual sex?
I'm a cheater?
You told me to just come up,
and I saw a woman in your apartment.
So sleeping with me while you're with her
makes you a cheater.
Was I a joke? That's why you date me,
even though you live with your girlfriend?
- How dare you!
- You went to my house that day?
I said I was downstairs.
You said to come to see you.
But I just moved.
I don't live there anymore.
Ah.
That's why you didn't answer
any of my calls, Ji-sun.
I was waiting here.
You were supposed to stay up and edit,
so I got you a coffee.
Uh…
You mind sharing that?
Ah!
I was so nervous. I thought we were done.
Well, then… we're still together?
Give me a moment.
I feel… like I got gut-punched.
I need a drink too. To come to my senses.
You spent 3,000 on wine,
a shopping spree, and a hotel suite?
You're spending too freely.
It's thanks to me she has it.
Bonjour.
You're speaking French.
It doesn't mean what you think.
She's the stupid one.
Well, you have something in common
with her, at least.
You told me you were Do Ra-mi,
so I hoped you were impressive
like the fictional girl.
I don't speak French.
So what?
This and this is everything I need.
What? You're a superhero
who defeats Do Ra-mi, right?
No way.
This is so great.
You've lost, honey.
I hesitated before coming here.
When I thought you were simply delusional,
it was okay.
And this time,
you didn't even ask for anything at all.
However, I regret coming here
since I heard you… call me "honey."
Don't be like this, honey!
I've been wondering.
How is a creature like you her alter ego?
That's easy.
I gave Cha Mu-hee her success.
That's what I thought too.
It's because of her fall
she's been having psychological issues.
And traveling so much
adds to all the stress.
- But that's not the whole story.
- What more is it, then?
Despite what was in that recent article,
you weren't a happy rich kid.
What would you know about that?
There's one more thing I found out,
although I didn't want to.
I saw someone on a hospital bed
in a large ward.
I saw that her family members
didn't care if she lived or died.
"How would someone, who's never had
anything she wanted, feel"?
You said that.
You could've emerged for many reasons,
but it may have to do with
that dark and sad past of hers.
A deep kind of pain.
No wonder you were kind.
It's because you took pity on her
when you saw all this.
So if I'm right,
will you share your version of the past?
You're right.
This girl's pathetic, so I had to emerge.
And if she's happy and fulfilled,
then you'll go away and leave her alone?
You have no idea.
I've been telling you,
happiness is not in her cards.
Why not?
Try being kind to me.
What?
If you're kind to me, I'll tell you.
- You've said not to be kind to you.
- Look.
One person wants to die
when they're treated kindly.
The other murders people
when someone treats them well.
What would kindness trigger, then?
I said don't get involved,
stop and avoid her, yet you're here.
Take responsibility, Ho-jin.
At least your timing is good.
Here, I was worrying
I had maxed my card out.
It's on you.
Thanks, honey. Bonjour.
Sit down. Do Ra-mi. Hey, wait, come back!
Thank you.
Excuse me. You left your bags.
The phone battery's almost dead.
You've got a charger?
- Tell me!
- I don't.
- Come on.
- No!
I need to charge up my phone.
Let's go. I'll ask someone for a charger.
- Come with me.
- That's so kind.
Honey, honey, honey, honey, honey.
You know, we're really vibing together.
It's casual and fun.
Uh…
Could we get a refund?
That woman
made a few impulsive purchases.
Certainly. To proceed with a refund,
I'll need the card she paid with.
Yes, yes.
Your credit card. Now.
Why? I need to pay to charge my phone?
They're taking advantage.
They charge for restrooms too?
- Here it is.
- Thanks.
Thank you.
- This is yours.
- Thank you.
Wait. Why is she taking those?
Stop it. You received a refund.
Are you dumb? I'll just buy it again.
No, you can't.
Your card's locked for three days.
It won't work. It's fully maxed out.
How's your battery now?
Hmm, there's not much power.
It'll die soon.
Soon, you'll have no credit card
and no mobile phone.
Shit.
Looks like
the South Korean production crew
will arrive after midnight.
Would you like to eat something
before we arrive at the hotel?
CHA MU-HEE
I'LL BE WAITING
You say you wanna
make me happy, but you got me pizza?
You wanted to sit somewhere
with a nice view.
There's no restaurant nearby,
so… I bought you this slice of pizza.
That's a restaurant. Or that one?
I have eyes. They're restaurants.
We could go to one of those.
Those are tourist traps.
Like the one
where you had me pay for your wine.
So expensive.
This is fine. Enjoy the pizza.
You could have gotten us a drink.
So, about what you said back then.
Once she's happy, you'll go away forever?
Most likely. But it won't be easy.
That's why you leave hateful comments.
So she can't ever be happy?
When she keeps fumbling in her life,
I have to hit her with a stick.
Even Italy, she wouldn't stop debating
if she should go.
I went ahead and did it.
So, to summarize, you make decisions
because you think Mu-hee
always takes too long before she acts?
Yeah.
If she finds out I met you,
she won't be able to deal with it.
Because you know her inner thoughts.
What'll you do, honey?
You've sorted out your feelings,
yet you're here.
Well, nothing's changed.
My feelings being sorted out have nothing
to do with you. They're about her.
I'm not going back on what I said.
So you've come all this way,
and it's just because of me?
Do you want me to go away?
All right.
To make it happen, there's a way.
What? Tell me.
If I drink a cup of nice, warm coffee,
she just might get so happy
that I'll go away.
If you put two sugars in that same coffee,
I could go away and disappear forever.
That's wild.
And also,
when that bell up there starts ringing,
she'll be happy just to hear it.
I'm sure.
Okay. I have no choice, I guess.
I will just listen
and do my very best right now.
Every time you hear me say
the most idiotic, dark, dirty stuff,
you must listen closely.
You'll be able to hear.
It's actually her mind talking.
That's right.
You are Cha Mu-hee as well.
Let's get to it.
I'll buy you a coffee with two sugars.
Look forward to this.
Let happiness come to you.
So if I close my eyes, Do Ra-mi,
tell me, what are you gonna do?
I ended up coming to Italy?
You really were waiting here.
Come to the clock square.
I will wait there.
I understood those words.
When that bell up there starts ringing,
she'll be happy just to hear it.
I'm sure.
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
This love is bittersweet
I wanna be yours, I wanna be yours
Close to me, close to me, close to me
I wanna be yours, I wanna be yours…
This love is bittersweet
Say it to me, say it to me…
I'll light it up
The way you walk to me…
This love is bittersweet…