♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my playful charm♪
♪Just to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for you♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 15=
=Liu Yexi dies, Ye Lang suspected=
What do I have to do
for you to believe me?
I brought this on myself.
It's all my fault.
Niannian.
Niannian. It's you.
- Wanna run?
- Let go!
You faked being unstable this long,
and now you can't keep it up?
I've wanted out of this home for long.
This place is a grave!
Everyone here is fake.
It's disgusting!
And you,
you brat!
Why didn't you
die with your mother?
What's the point of you living?
You're the last one
who gets to say that!
I won't kill you.
Trash like you
should rot in the Li family.
Let go of me!
Let go!
Ye Lang.
Do you know why Jiang Niannian left?
She saw through the Li family.
She thinks you're filthy.
Because you
and me,
and your father are all the same!
So fake!
So disgusting!
It's actually
all filthy tricks.
This place
is nothing but a grave!
Liu Yexi.
You've planned this for years
and schemed every step,
just so your son gets the Li family,
isn't it?
Other than poison,
what other dirty tricks do you have?
Use them all.
I'm waiting for you to end me.
Ye Lang.
You're the real madman!
Ma'am.
Ma'am took her own life!
I don't believe Mom would do that.
She hasn't even seen me get married.
Make arrangements ASAP.
Tell the public
it was a sudden illness.
Dad.
Master.
Last night,
I witnessed
Young Master and Ma'am
had a clash in the foyer.
Young Master even
grabbed Ma'am by the throat.
You...
saw it wrong.
There are indeed
finger marks on her neck.
Just like Liu said.
You...
Why?
She did hurt you before.
But why did you get her killed?
Mr. Li.
If this gets out of hand,
it becomes a criminal case.
Young Master may
have to go to the police station.
Ye Lang isn't going anywhere.
I've never seen a case
where one gets sent to the police
before the facts are even clear.
Niannian.
The priority is
to send the body
for an autopsy
not to send an innocent man in.
Ms. Jiang, you've misunderstood.
Young Master just needs
to give a voluntary statement.
If the police find out first
and come arrest him,
that would be worse.
We might need a lot for bail then.
If there's bail to be paid,
you won't need to cover it.
He is my husband.
I'll pay it.
♪I'm going nowhere♪
How much does she owe you?
I'll pay it.
Niannian.
You're back.
Don't get it wrong.
I just saw the news,
and you helped me before.
We're even now.
You gave me this card before.
I'm giving it back.
So,
you didn't forgive me...
I don't like
owing anyone anything.
(She's willing to spend on me,)
(it means she still cares.)
(Even if she only loves my money.)
(Loving my money)
(is loving me, isn't it?)
By the way,
I found this in Zhong Minghui's
secret email.
It should help you.
Could it be
Li Hong is actually
the son of Liu Yexi and Zhong Minghui?
Do his age match?
Besides,
we can't say it's Li Hong
from just one photo.
We need stronger proof.
A DNA test.
You're here.
I'd like to talk to you.
You want to ask
why I refused to look into Liu Yexi's death,
right?
She's dead.
It's over.
Everything ends there.
When my mother died,
you were the same way.
Like their deaths
meant nothing to you.
You're good at everything
except dealing with people.
You let emotions get in the way.
Just like your mother.
That's the one thing
that makes me hesitate
to hand our family over to you.
I just don't understand
why you're always so cold.
When my mother passed away,
you didn't shed a single tear.
Now Liu Yexi is dead,
and you're still the same!
Family interests always come first.
One day,
when you take over the Li family,
you'll understand.
I'm doing this
for your good.
You got her killed.
Are you ready to pay for it?
Do you love her that much?
This is the paternity test
for Li Hong and Li Zhongtian.
You're just some outsider's child.
Don't try framing Master Li Hong.
Do you dare look at it?
So you all knew.
I never meant to betray Master.
But Ma'am was so pitiful back then.
I wasn't even twenty.
I gave in to temptation.
Hong doesn't know.
He has nothing to do with it.
Please don't tell him.
He is innocent.
You think it's all your fault, right?
What do you mean?
Those decades of so-called family bonds
were all Liu Yexi's calculation.
(Test Results)
(Biological Paternity Confirmed)
(Not mine?)
Ever since
she told me she was pregnant,
I haven't had one good night's sleep.
I hated myself.
I regretted everything!
I swore
I would give Ma'am and my child
the best life possible.
I'd give everything!
That vile woman!
Young Master.
Thank you for telling me the truth.
In return,
I'll tell you one thing.
Do you know how Ye Mei died?
Liu Yexi
had me poison her medicine!
I regret
not poisoning you too!
You should never have lived this long!
Liu Yexi.
Liu Yexi, you vile woman.
You lied to me all these years!
I won't let you have it easy in hell!
Stop him!
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪