=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 39=
Xiaoxiao.
Thank heavens.
You're still alive.
I don't want you to die.
Got it.
In the end, I still died
for the one I love.
Farewell,
Yan Ke.
It's Miss He.
- Yes.
Miss He won the fight.
Blast it!
We won!
We made it out alive!
We won.
We won!
Xiaoxiao.
(It is Xu.)
Did you come to kill me?
North Chong has fallen.
The Cangshen you believed in
was never real.
Yan Ke, who gave you power,
has met annihilation as well.
Even the North soldiers
who trusted only you
were dead because of you.
You have nothing left now.
Nonsense.
I did not cause their deaths.
You killed them.
I'll avenge them on you.
I thought I was going to lose you.
No.
You will never lose me.
Xu.
Xiaoxiao.
I'm back.
The Chong people's privileges
in the 17 Prefectures are revoked.
All lands and houses they seized
must be returned
to Great Liang's people.
Within Liang's borders,
all people are born equal.
None shall serve another people.
People's will shall be loyal
to His Majesty,
(Decree)
as it should be.
This is hereby claimed.
Wonderful. Wonderful.
(Rice Shop)
The Chong foe!
Great Ancestor.
I have not failed your trust.
I've retaken all
of our lost lands.
I now return the military tally
and the marshal's seal
to His Majesty.
You've done an unprecedented feat.
That is high merit.
The people of Liang
will remember it.
You gave up military power so easily?
I never meant to hold an army.
Now that the 17 Prefectures
have been recovered,
I should return military power
to His Majesty.
How much time do I have left?
Just tell me.
When you stop dodging your medicine,
I will tell you.
(Liang)
Is he asleep?
Duan Xu is not doing well.
He...
If he really leaves,
what will you do?
I still have much to do.
Jiang Ai is watching the Void for me,
but her heart is not in it.
In time, she will return it to me.
Also, Chenying
absorbed the Spirits Lantern's power
and became a spirit.
His obsession is to protect.
If he is willing,
perhaps he can take over
my place soon.
I'm not talking
about the Sovereign.
I'm talking
about you.
I don't know.
Perhaps when that day comes,
I will know.
Right now, whenever I think
that Duan Xu may leave me,
I feel
as if time might vanish
into thin air.
I can see so many things
waiting for me to do,
yet I can't see myself.
(Zhaomu Pavilion)
Simu, you are back.
Who is this?
This is my brother, Chenying.
The Spirits Lantern made him a spirit.
He's still very weak.
Lady Jiang Ai, please watch over him.
Also,
please oversee
the Void for a while longer.
With Lady Jiang Ai here,
don't worry.
What obsession brought you here?
I want to protect Xu and Xiaoxiao.
I kept thinking they had not made peace,
and their wishes
have yet to come true.
I had to see them again.
And I had to
make their wishes come true.
Then
I really saw them again.
How lucky.
At such a young age,
you carry such heavy sorrow,
yet you count yourself lucky.
I'm not lucky.
Xu is gravely ill.
Xiaoxiao is hurting too.
But I can't help in the least.
Lady Jiang Ai,
if Xu is gone...
(Tomb of He Yicheng and Siwei)
Old man,
your grudge has been settled.
Are you pleased?
It's been over 400 years.
I am older than you two now.
From now on,
you may have one more neighbor.
After he passes,
I plan to lay him
to rest beside you two.
After you left, I swore
I'd never be left behind again,
and I'd be the one who leaves first.
(Tomb of He Yicheng and Siwei)
But I repeat my mistake again.
I gave him the right
to leave me
before I do.
One day,
I suppose it will break my heart.
And now,
I find myself thinking
that if he left me and vanished
from this world
50 years from now,
it wouldn't be
so impossible to bear.
But I've known him for only 7 years.
It's too short.
Truly, far too short.
But there is no helping it,
is there?
(Youzhou)
All is settled now.
Today, I shall drink
with all of you.
- Cheers.
I truly never imagined
that after such a brutal battle,
not only did we all survive,
but we also reclaimed
the 17 Prefectures.
My life is worth it.
Worth it indeed.
Han.
Qingsheng.
- Here.
- That we could reclaim
the 17 Prefectures
feels like a dream.
- I still remember
- Marshal Duan.
we entered Liangzhou.
Back then, you even suspected
I was a spy.
Now that I think of it,
he did look like a spy.
Come on.
Cheers.
Let's drink.
Marshal Duan,
I heard you returned
the marshal's seal.
If you don't want to be the Marshal,
give that seal to me.
I will take the post for you.
Would that not be just fine?
General Wu,
as I told you long ago,
if you chased office in Nandu,
you'd be done for.
Marshal Duan is right.
Right about what?
I was only joking.
I'd never be an official
in Nandu.
I won this land back
with my life.
I wouldn't rest easy
leaving it to others.
Han, say a few words.
General Wu is right.
I've grown used to the frontier.
I can't go anywhere else.
Come, come.
So you've all decided
to stay here?
That's right.
We'll stay to guard
the frontier.
I'll go
where Meng Wan goes.
Han and I
will stand with you two.
Xu, what about you?
The 17 Prefectures are back.
My wish is fulfilled.
Simu and I will wander the realm
and never return.
Xu,
are you truly leaving?
Though we part,
we still share the wind.
(Liang)
Your wishes have all come true.
What will you do now?
Simu,
I had a dream last night.
In that dream,
we lived a life of seclusion.
One cottage, two souls,
three meals, and four seasons.
Seeds in spring,
rain in summer,
chrysanthemums in autumn,
and snow in winter.
Year after year,
we lived a quiet, ordinary life.
♪With the east wind♪
♪In the season at its fullest♪
I want to return to our home
with you.
♪The old night♪
♪Borrow mortal warmth to ease the cold♪
All right.
♪Savoring wine and graceful dances♪
♪Let me love with all my heart
in youthful grace♪
♪With light, carefree words,
still shining bright♪
♪With you by my side♪
It's truly good to be home.
This is my home.
That was a gift from me,
along with myself.
What would you like to eat?
I'll take you to get some food.
Simu,
let's have fish.
♪If you'd let me know how to tell♪
I don't know how to cook fish.
You chose
such tricky ingredients.
Isn't it enough that I can?
We're having a full fish banquet.
♪Borrow mortal warmth to ease the cold♪
It doesn't seem willing.
What a slippery fish.
Simu,
help me scoop it up.
Let's give it a try.
♪In youthful grace♪
♪With light, carefree words♪
Simu,
I like being with you.
♪A pot of wine in fleeting dreams♪
♪A brief life dares seek eternity♪
♪Borrow one lovely dream;
let me savor this fleeting joy♪
Your Grace,
do you still like
my skull as you did
back then?
Yes.
I want to remember you,
your smile,
your scent,
your colors,
and this moment.
♪To what home shall I return♪
Great Ancestor...
Let's go.
Stop there.
Come here.
Great Ancestor,
spare my life.
I...
I have just recovered.
My eyes still have excessive heat,
so they're not so sharp.
I saw nothing at all.
I came to deliver medicine
to General Duan.
I brought all of these
from Starhaven Sect.
I am no longer a general.
Since you're here,
stay for a simple meal.
No, no.
I won't disturb you. Goodbye.
I'll cook today.
Don't you want a taste?
Great Ancestor,
you aren't treating him like a patient,
nor me like a person.
Then starve yourself.
Is it good?
I'll go check on him.
Ziji, sit down and eat.
It's not that bad.
It tastes fine to me.
What's wrong?
Look, look.
It's not that bad, huh?
I only threw up my food.
You're coughing up blood.
How is it?
Do you have any medicine?
- I have some.
- I'm fine.
Which kind do you want?
I'm fine.
However,
I do have one favor to ask.
What do you want?
Come here.
Come closer.
What?
Duan Shunxi.
Duan Shunxi,
I've never
wronged you.
Why must you make me
await my end
before Great Ancestor?
Everything in this world
will one day fade away.
Your Grace,
why force him to stay?
This is his fate.
None of your business.
As the Sovereign of the Void,
you can't stay in the Mortal World.
Go back soon.
Then how much longer will you stay
in this Mortal World,
Immortal?
Duan Shunxi,
you'll leave Great Ancestor.
Aren't you sad?
In all my life,
from first love to my dying day,
I have only loved one girl.
I count myself lucky.
Now,
I don't want my last days in sorrow.
Still,
perhaps when I die,
I'll cling to her and weep.
After I am gone,
will you grieve for me?
Will you hold me and weep too?
All these years,
whenever my death is mentioned,
you say nothing.
How absurd.
What are you running from?
Didn't your kind
set this brief fate
for the Hejia lineage,
Immortal?
You stayed by my side
and read mortals for years.
Now,
do you think your kind was wrong?
Immortals don't err.
Even mortals' right and wrong
are set by immortals.
Yes.
How very clever.
How could immortals be wrong?
Then why did you create
this order
in the first place?
To keep the world in balance
and secure happiness for most.
So,
you have been using
our kindness.
We have upheld
the happiness of the many.
Yet we have no choice
but to suffer for it.
You dress it up in noble words
while tormenting us.
Don't you see your arrogance?
That is
why I have come here.
If you still see no fault in yourself,
go back.
Ziji,
to speak plainly,
I am tired of this game.
(Ten years by your side)
(until this day.)
(Immortal,)
(will you save me?)
♪In silence, I gaze at you♪
♪My hand hangs and then falls♪
♪Let what stays unsaid pass♪
♪Why torture each other like this?♪
♪My wish might be♪
Ziji,
you grabbed me.
♪They fade like a dream♪
♪Daylight fades into ash♪
(It's been over a month
since your letter.)
(Are you and Miss He both well?)
(Somehow,)
(I often dream)
(of our childhood days in Daizhou.)
(Daizhou)
♪Collapse piece by piece♪
♪I hate that I hesitated♪
(Yet old days will fade like mist.)
(Erudite and Determined)
♪Leaving all behind♪
(I have found what I wish to do.)
(For now, all is well.)
(Though the moon may wax and wane,)
(I still wish that you and Miss He)
(can be as full as the moon)
(and live a happy life.)
(Your sister, Jingyuan, respectfully)
♪Let memories drift away♪
♪Alone, I gather them up♪
♪Like petals in the spring sun♪
♪Till the past falls still again♪
♪And turns to clear daylight♪
♪The wind returns with my dreams♪
Will you send Jingyuan a reply?
She's found what she wants to do
and started a new life.
I won't give her more to worry over.
Jingyuan mentioned
those days back in Daizhou.
I think
she cared for Xianye.
If the time they spent together
had been longer,
perhaps...
Maybe this is for the best.
She should soon forget
a brief, hazy memory.
How could she forget?
She will not.
Jingyuan wished us full as the moon.
Yet we're here,
and the full moon is not.
It's been so long since I
admired the moon with you.
The Mid-Autumn Festival
is too far away.
If you want to celebrate the festival,
we can do it anytime.
But if you want
to admire the moon...
Wait for a moment.
Simu.
The moonlight beneath the sun
is beautiful, right?
Do you like it?
I do.
I always do.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪