=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 38=
(Suburbs of Nanjing)
Your Majesty,
please punish me.
During the riot,
the late emperor was trapped.
I failed to return in time.
So, the two of you
fell into danger
without any help.
I...
I am guilty.
I've found out.
This isn't your fault.
Duan,
you're not guilty.
Xianye died for our nation.
How could I leave him in the wilderness?
But sadly,
all I can do is set up this tomb.
I once travelled from Nandu
to different cities.
But I've never been to the border.
Yet I know very well,
this world is very big,
beyond the Palace
and beyond the Capital.
The world
doesn't belong to the emperor,
but to the people all over it.
We are
gradually recovering the 17 Prefectures.
As a member of this nation,
I sincerely thank you.
Fang Ji and I had a promise.
I would retake the 17 Prefectures.
He would be a virtuous minister
to uphold this nation.
But so far,
I haven't fulfilled this promise.
Entrust me
with his last wish.
I'll govern the nation well.
I won't fail
the promise
the three of us made.
My...
My time is running out.
I'm going to die.
Xianye is dead.
You must look after yourself.
I hereby take an oath
upon Xianye's soul.
I'll devote my life
to recovering the 17 Prefectures.
My vow never changes.
Shunxi,
I trust no one but you
on border issues.
You and Fang Ji
can talk in private.
You always said I was insane.
But when you went insane,
you were even more fierce.
People always say
the Top Scholar is self-disciplined.
You were just pretending.
Don't worry.
His Majesty will be a good emperor.
He will bring our nation
into a prosperous age
we've been expecting.
Whether he's a friend
or he's the Emperor,
I believe this will never change.
You used to worry too much.
Now you've died before me.
You can stop worrying
and take some good rest.
And I...
I want to stay
with her for as long as I can.
(Duan Mansion)
I'm here
to bid farewell, Father.
I'm a bad son.
I can't serve you or Mother.
Please take care of yourselves.
Stop right there!
Father,
for our family's glory,
you sacrificed most of your life.
You and Mother both suffered.
I have someone I love
and something I want to do.
I will live for myself.
Duan Xu!
Stop!
Come back!
Come back here!
He...
Come back!
Duan Xu.
Come back.
Come back here.
When I was little,
I fell into a pit in the backyard.
It was very dark.
And the pit was deep.
I was really scared
and cried for help.
Then I saw my father
standing there and looking at me.
He said he wouldn't help me
or let anyone else help me.
He asked me to climb out.
If I had failed,
I would have died there.
I cried and begged him.
But he still left.
I tried many times
and fell over and over.
In the end,
I did climb out
all by myself.
I was thinking.
So, I could save myself
without begging for help.
Oh, I see.
So when you were abducted,
you didn't blame your father.
It's not quite like that.
After I came back from the Chong,
I heard that day,
my father stood near the pit
and guarded the hole.
He stood in the sun
for several hours.
He didn't leave
until I climbed out.
Even if Jingyuan and I
are his pawns in power games,
he loves us anyway.
Now it is time.
Marshal Duan is a military genius.
Now, we've taken
several cities
around Youzhou.
The last few battles...
Really exhilarating.
What are our casualties?
Guihe Army lost 20 percent.
Tabai Army and Chengjie Army lost
nearly 30,000 soldiers.
Bury them properly.
The next battle
will determine
the outcome.
(Youzhou)
Youzhou is the Chong's key.
They'll defend fully.
From tomorrow on,
we'll fight for survival.
We pledge our lives
to the capture of Youzhou!
- Capture!
- Capture Youzhou!
Captain Han is here.
Han.
I...
I'm late.
Lingqiu.
I shouldn't have left.
If I had been here,
Chenying wouldn't...
If we get a complete victory...
Tomorrow,
we'll follow the plan.
Yes.
Han,
I missed you so much.
The elixir you made
is remarkably effective.
I spared no effort to nurse him
and cast a blessed spell.
But Duan Xu...
He's been working all day
and draining himself.
I...
I'll just do the best I can.
How long has he got?
If he takes good rest,
perhaps,
he can live as long as I can.
If he could take good rest,
he wouldn't be Duan Xu.
If he keeps exhausting himself,
even if he has my blessed spell
and full recuperation,
he...
He has only two years left.
♪I go alone in the night without end♪
No.
Foxy has
a charmed life.
♪Wishful thoughts creep onto my brows♪
He'll always survive.
♪Through cycles of time, we get to meet♪
♪Snow on sunny days♪
♪Countless wayfarers roam the world♪
♪Luckily, I share a fate with you♪
♪I hold a lantern to draw the moon♪
♪Light up the night that haunts you♪
♪I have simple wishes, but I fear♪
♪The world can't hold them♪
♪You always stay with me♪
♪See the world I've never seen♪
♪However the years may wind♪
♪I wish I could live in your heart♪
Simu,
you think you can stop me
by sealing off the passage
between the Void and the Mortal World?
I'll turn the Mortal World
into my battlefield too.
(Liang)
Liang soldiers,
in today's battle,
we'll annihilate enemies
and reclaim our land!
Annihilate enemies! Reclaim our land!
Charge!
Kill! Kill!
Kill!
Your Grace!
Your Grace,
bad news.
On the battlefield,
many spirit soldiers appeared.
Liang troops couldn't resist
and suffered heavy casualties.
It's Yan Ke.
He actually created
so many spirit soldiers in this world
and even sent them to war.
Fengyi,
you go with me.
Liang soldiers,
how are you?
Are you all right?
Puppet spirits are tough to kill.
My sword can fight them.
But there are too many.
I can't kill them all.
(I must do something)
(to help Her Grace.)
Oh, my eyes.
Hold on there.
(As long as I sense the Glazed Pagoda,)
(I'll find Yan Ke.)
(Then I can help Her Grace.)
You said the spirits
would only fight my enemies.
Why are they fighting my troops too?
Why do you care
about such insignificant lives?
Now on this battlefield,
thousands of auras are mine to feast on.
Defeating He Simu won't be a problem.
When I become the Sovereign,
I'll give you as many troops
as you want.
You shameless fiend!
How dare you kill my people!
Don't think
you can rant before me
just because you have
the Lantern's power.
This method of cultivation...
I'll teach you only once.
Keep it in mind.
You're nothing but a puppet
I've made.
From now on,
the Spirits Lantern will serve me.
Glazed Pagoda?
You want to dissolve me?
But the Lantern won't allow it!
Yan Ke,
I'm going to take you on.
Your Grace.
Simu?
There you are.
Leave now or die.
Yes.
Traitor Yan Ke,
as the Right Hand,
you violated the Decrees,
disrupted the Void,
and plagued the Mortal World.
I'll take you back to the Void
and execute you.
Then give it a try.
Kill me here
or go save those mortals.
Make your choice.
Even now,
you're still playing
such a dirty trick.
You keep saying
you want to be the Sovereign.
But you hide all the time
and don't even dare
to fight me head-on.
Even Bai Sanxing surpasses you.
In my eyes,
you're just a mere rebel.
Today, I'll give you a chance.
Kill me
and you'll be the Sovereign.
Am I that despicable
in your eyes?
Stay where you are.
They won't disappear
until Great Ancestor
defeats Yan Ke
at the source.
They're killable now.
They're dead.
It's...
Liang soldiers,
I've refined your weapons.
Now you can also kill
these puppet spirits.
Prophet,
you should have used
this awesome technique long ago!
Soldiers!
Let's fight for our nation!
Kill!
Yan Ke,
you lost after all.
No.
I never lost.
In the past 300 years,
your trust,
reliance,
and closeness to me
were all fake.
He Simu,
you failed me!
Your arrogant father
treated me as a pawn.
He used me and abandoned me.
So did you.
Those I adored all failed me.
So I had to hold power
in my own hands.
What you didn't want to give me,
I would grab it myself.
All this should have been mine!
All you have is selfish desire.
All you strive for is vanity.
I gave you the power you wanted.
But your insatiable greed
was hard to satisfy.
That's why you thought
everyone failed you.
As for the Lantern...
In your eyes,
it's a supreme treasure.
But to me,
it's just like the throne.
A mere object.
Just because of evil spirits like you,
my father and my siblings
lost their lives!
Let go.
You can't control the Lantern.
You're the Sovereign.
If you vanish,
perhaps then,
all the evil spirits in this world
will disappear!
No!
Stop!
Simu.
No.
(I...)
(I can finally die.)
(It's not bad.)
(I no longer have to endure loneliness)
(or bear the pain)
(of being left behind by those I love.)
(Father.)
(Mother.)
(I'm coming to you.)
The Void is quaking.
He Simu's in trouble.
Let's secure this.
Spirits can't enter the Mortal World.
♪Falling down like snow♪
Simu is in trouble.
♪Joys and sorrows of the mortal world♪
♪Swept along by the daylight♪
♪The forms and hues of the mortal realm♪
♪Lingering for a fleeting moment♪
♪Was once touched by laughing tears♪
♪If I could live a simple life♪
♪For once♪
♪I'd be a guest in a sweet dream♪
That's He Simu's vital gate, isn't it?
♪Dawn and dusk rise and set♪
♪Longing to meet, yet parted by destiny♪
♪Let me wander through♪
♪Light and dark, without turning back♪
♪Wander to the other shore
with the lantern♪
♪Accompanied by eternity♪
♪As all things turn and flow♪
♪Whether I stay or go, I'm all alone♪
♪As stars shift and change places♪
♪A century is like a dream♪
♪Let me journey across them all♪
♪Without reincarnations♪
You little ant.
How dare you?
♪Moments may last♪
♪Love and hate will fade away♪
Leave! Leave!
Xu.
Simu is in trouble.
According to Prophet,
these spirit soldiers won't disappear
until Yan Ke is defeated!
Nothing shall happen to Miss He!
Xu, we can't kill
all these spirit soldiers on our own.
We'll take care of them.
You go help Miss He.
Go!
You must stay alive!
Yes!
- Yes!
Maizi,
take me to Simu.
All right.
(I'm all alone,)
(eternal and undying.)
(How nice.)
(I'm no longer lonely.)
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪