Visit Our Telegram Channel:
FILM SUB INDO
@filmsubindonueva
In 1939, the Nationalists won the Spanish Civil War.
Citizens of the Spanish Republic living in the Soviet Union became stateless.
They were apprentice pilots, sailors on their way,
war refugee children.
The Soviet Union accepted the Republicans, but did not allow them to leave.
They visited embassies. They try to escape.
In a climate of war and paranoia,
They were accused of treason, punished without trial…
and sent to a forced labor camp.
WINTER 1941
KAZAKHSTAN
SPASSK-99 WORK CAMP
Move! Come on!
Ladies to the left! Men to the right! Fast!
Come on!
-Keep forward! Come on! -Faster!
Don't get in the way! Keep moving!
Move! Keep going! Come on!
Move! Use your feet!
Ladies to the left! Men to the right!
Do it quickly!
Come on! Come on! Move faster!
Women to the left! Men to the right! I said hurry!
Come on! Faster!
Come on!
Straight ahead!
Come on! Faster!
Come in here! Enter!
Line up! Quick, do you hear?
Take off your clothes!
Take off your clothes. Back off. Take off your clothes.
Let go! Take off your clothes!
Things are on the table!
What are you holding there?
Let go!
Things are on the table!
Take off your clothes.
Do it now!
Don't make eye contact!
What don't you understand? Let go!
Put it on the table! Put it here!
Faster!
Let it all go!
Everything! Everything is on the table!
Come on!
Closer!
There! Come on!
Number 289, Telmo Kings.
Move! Come on! Go!
Number 297, José Muñoz.
There! Come on!
Number 295, Julio Hermida.
-Come on. Move. -Number 290, Eladio Junqueras.
Come on!
Move quickly. Come on.
Number 291, Melléin Palau.
What are you waiting for? Get moving!
Come on!
Welcome, Spaniards.
There is an empty bed in the back. Take your pick.
But most importantly, be quiet.
Captain?
Find a place.
Do you know what those five men did?
one of them is from Salamanca,
one of them is from Asturias,
one of them is from Andalusia,
one from Galicia, one from Catalonia,
What do they all have in common with a flock of sheep?
They all ended up in the same cage.
This is great, right?
Seriously, Barcelona people?
Oh Lord.
You should sleep now. Get some sleep.
Get up! Getting ready!
-Don't be lazy! Get up! -Everyone wake up!
-Fast! Get up! -Line up five by five! I said hurry!
Quickly!
What are you waiting for, an official invitation? Get up! Fast!
Come on!
Stop staring!
Move! Keep moving!
Come on! Down! Faster!
I said, move faster! Fast!
Line up outside! Fast!
Faster! Move!
Move faster!
Faster!
-Fast! -Come in here! Bath time! Run faster!
-Move faster! -Time to wash! Come on!
Yes! Get in there!
Come here! Fast! Come on!
Come on! Speed ​​up! Faster!
There!
There he is! Faster!
Faster!
-Line up! Fast! -Faster!
Get up there!
Faster!
Follow the others! Faster!
Get in there!
Faster! Don't crowd!
Why is it so slow? Faster!
Run! Faster!
Come on! Faster!
Come here! Follow the brigade leader!
Through this way. Come on.
Here he is. Please get in line.
Faster!
The mining work schedule is from 08.00 to 18.00.
The two-hour round trip is not included in the price.
Refusing to carry out obligations will result in punishment.
Violating the formation will be punished.
Each brigade is obliged to fulfill this quota.
You eat as much as you dig.
Each group must stay with their brigade leader.
Number 73!
Number 57!
Tobacco smuggling is grounds for punishment.
in the form of spending a week in a hole.
Ignore! Continue as before!
Leaving the line is considered an escape attempt!
-Wake up, damn it! Get up! -I told you to just ignore it!
Come on.
This is your workplace now.
Start getting used to it. Make yourself at home.
And as I said before...
The rules here are simple.
No quota means no food.
Be careful there.
A cart full...
from everyone.
Like I said.
Everyone understands?
Hey! Are you sleeping or what?
Now, listen to me.
Groups one and two went to Nikolay.
Groups three and four, follow me, for God's sake.
Understood?
You want to stand here forever?
Will you help?
Good grief. What kind of partner did I get from me.
Take the stones. Hold the stones.
-I'm working on it. -Citizens of Barcelona!
-I'm working on it. -Damn.
I just don't feel well.
Citizens of Barcelona!
Return! Back to work!
-Please let me go! Please! -Retreat!
-Please! -Retreat!
-Please let me go! -I told you, come back!
-Stop this! -Retreat! Fast!
Everything is alright! Everything went smoothly!
Thank You!
Calm!
-I can't breathe, Eladio. Eladio… -Calm down!
-I don't want to die here, Eladio. -It's all in your mind.
You can breathe.
-Eladio, I don't want to die here. Eladio… -You can breathe. You can.
Look at me. Look me in the eye, dammit!
I don't want to…
Take a breath.
Breathe. Come on.
Inhale.
Just let it out.
Breathe with me. With me.
Take a breath. Exhale.
Better?
Come on! Move faster!
Why are you standing there? Move!
Don't hinder others! Keep forward!
Fast! Faster!
Why are you just standing there? Move! Let's go!
Come on! Move quickly! Faster!
Move!
Move! Come on!
Come on! Quicken your steps! Don't slow down!
Come on! Faster!
Come with me.
Come on.
Help me get him out of that hole.
Here.
I'm Hans Müller.
What can I do for you, my friend?
Are you a trader?
Possible. Why?
I need paper and ink.
Three portions of half rations.
Wait.
How can I talk to the head of the camp?
You're serious?
Do you see that man behind?
He is the boss. Talk to him.
He was a translator and secretary to the head of the department.
If anyone could introduce you to him, it would be him.
Why are you talking to that German? Are you friends with Nazis now?
Faster. One by one.
In rows of two by two!
Faster!
Keep up the pace! Keep forward!
Do not stop.
Faster.
Spaniard!
Why are you standing there? Hurry up.
Come on! Put it here.
Okay.
Come on, Hermida.
Wedge.
-Hey. Julio. -Huh?
Are you still here or not? Give me the piece. Come on.
What's taking so long?
If this happens, we will all be doomed! Come on!
Yes. We are working on it.
-Head. -Mmm?
This is Telmo Reyes Aguirre, a captain of the Spanish Republic.
He wants to apply for a review of his trial.
And why are they reconsidering the final verdict regarding treason?
This system never makes mistakes.
Because there is no betrayal. And there is no trial.
Our only mistake was wanting to go home to our families.
To Spain?
You will definitely be executed on the spot.
The war had ended there.
For God's sake.
War never ends.
-We are looking for a way out. -So you visited the German embassy.
We visited many embassies.
This is an indication of betrayal.
With all due respect, Chairman,
You share Poland with them.
We just want to go back to our families.
The Soviet Union is your only family.
The desire to leave the Soviet Union was an act of betrayal. Is that clear?
Chairman,
The Spanish went beyond plans in the coal mines.
They brought in double the specified quota.
If you take the initiative to convey my request,
I will make sure to defend myself during the trial.
We just want a fair trial, folks.
How did you call me just now?
You are an enemy of the people, accused of treason under Article 58.
You are prohibited from speaking to me in that manner.
You are not my comrade in arms. Absolutely not.
Such insults can be severely punished.
You can go.
That's your son in the photo, right?
He had been called to the front lines.
Captain…
I speak Russian,
Because I am a senior captain of Kirovabad flight school.
The plane was a Tu-2.
This is a medium bomber aircraft.
If they entrust that to your son, you know you can be proud of him.
Thank You.
Wait a moment, Captain.
Nazarov has given me a guarantee. He will send my letters for review.
-Is it true? -Yes.
Seriously?
What do I care what Nazarov says?
I only care about what you say.
What do you think, Captain?
I promise you.
We're leaving here, citizens of Barcelona.
SPRING 1943
TWO YEARS LATER
-Move faster! -Come on, you bastards!
Faster!
Move!
That way!
That way! Straight ahead!
Come on!
Move!
Faster!
New faces arrive every day.
It seemed that Germany was losing the war.
Fascist bastard.
Dirt!
Look. Spanish flag.
-I don't believe it. -Yes. They are Spanish!
Jesus Christ.
Fascist bastards have arrived at the camp!
Long live Spain!
What life?
That's payback for you for acting smart.
Are there any Galicians here?
I! From Noia!
For God's sake.
Wall!
Who cares if they're Galician? They're fascist bastards, Hermida.
I don't understand you.
Damn, Eladio. I'm not sure the captain will like this.
I don't care about the captain.
What wouldn't I like?
Fascist, Captain. Trash from the Blue Division.
-One of them is from Noia. Even worse. -You're obsessed with Galicians.
Come on, kids! Enter into!
Come on! Move! -Faster!
That way! Straight ahead!
Move faster!
Come on! Move! Move!
Underwear is on the table!
Take off your Nazi clothes!
Do it now, I say! Let go!
Do it now! I said let go now!
What's hard to understand?
Quickly!
Take off your clothes!
Faster! Come on! Fast!
Can you be any slower?!
Faster!
I said faster!
Come on! Take it all off and put it on the table!
Quickly!
Let it all go!
Come on! I said hurry!
Things are on the table!
Faster! Keep going!
Take off your clothes!
Faster!
Let it all go!
Look for an empty bed.
And don't try to go out until dawn!
Visit Our Telegram Channel:
FILM SUB INDO
@filmsubindonueva
Everyone defecates in the same bucket. What is this, Lieutenant?
Communism.
What should we do?
We need to rest.
We'll arrange it tomorrow.
Find a place.
-Unlucky. -What are you doing, bastard?
-What the hell was that? -I'm trying…
-I'm sorry. I was… -Oh my! What an ugly tattoo.
-It's just… -I just… Don't!
Don't worry.
Don't look at them, Dad.
The kid is Spanish.
Maybe, but he's with the Urkas. They are murderers, Dad.
Stop staring at them, dammit.
If he was with them, then he had already chosen a side.
Every time you step forward into a new tunnel,
You take the pickaxe and tap the ceiling a few times.
As long as it doesn't sound hollow, you can continue.
-And if it sounds hollow? -If that's the case, then you're not ready.
The crop yield depends on the tunnel.
Some tunnels have a capacity of 20 tonnes per week, others 30 tonnes.
This one is number 60.
Pretty lucky, huh?
"Lucky," he said.
Nazi Germany, meet Dimitrov.
Spanish Nazis, come with me.
Come on. Hurry up. Let us go!
Stop looking at him.
Eat.
Number 321!
3-2-1, for God's sake.
-Come on! We're leaving, bastards! -Hey!
-Hey! -Move!
Faster, asshole! Why are you so slow?
In winter, you can't eat outside.
The soup is frozen.
I'm Telmo Reyes.
Captain of the Spanish Republican Army.
Which are your military manners?
Military manners?
This is a show of strength. Sad.
This is not a prisoner of war camp.
You're the enemy here.
You'd be better off if you just ate, slept, and didn't think too much.
Is that a threat?
This is a suggestion.
No offense intended, Captain,
But I don't usually take advice from a communist.
Move! Come on!
Get moving! Don't slow down!
Move! Move faster! Come on!
Come on! To the left!
Move! Keep going ahead! Come on!
Faster! Don't just stand there! Come on!
Move!
Come on! Move!
Come on! Faster!
Do not stop!
Move! Come on!
-Father! -Father!
-Catch him there. What happened? -Be careful.
Who did this to you, Dad?
Okay. Sit him here. Be careful.
Okay. Please sit. Watch your head.
Well, here it is.
Okay. Let me see.
Are you alright. Breathe. Okay?
Count to three.
One…
-It doesn't matter. Breathe. Calm. -It's finished.
You still do that?
Those letters won't save us from here, Captain.
Nobody blames you, okay? Nobody blames you.
-The law is on our side. -"Law."
Law is one thing, but justice is another thing entirely.
We've been here for two years, Telmo. Why don't you stop?
Do you know what Aristotle said?
"When humans are friends, they don't need justice."
That man named Aristotle would not last a day in this camp.
How long will you let my men suffer the consequences of your pessimistic complex?
We have endured humiliation in the mines, cuts in food rations,
but I refuse to let my men be attacked again,
especially not a priest.
-What is he talking about? -Don't know.
He must have tripped.
Control your pack, Reyes.
Didn't mean to offend,
But I don't usually take advice from a fascist.
This is not advice.
This is a threat.
Fucking Palau.
Don't forget your position, miner.
What?
-Come on. Just take it. -Don't lie to me.
-Take it all. -Come on. Just take it.
This is one of them.
And one more.
He learned to count.
Here's another one. And one more.
Here he is.
Here comes the number ten.
Come on. Turn up the volume.
Come on. Take it.
Number nine.
I don't have it.
Feel it.
-Ask for two more. -Don't lie to me.
Come on. Show us what you've been saving.
Wait. Let me.
-Ten. It's ten. -Shut up!
-A jack. Another Jack. -Ten more.
-Give me one more. -What?
Just take it, right now. Come on.
-Take it all. -Come on. Just take it.
And one more.
Do you understand what I mean? You understand what I mean, right?
No, look. It's very easy.
I need to make a deal with them. I need you to translate for me.
Do you understand me? Huh? Do you speak Spanish?
I know you speak Spanish. Do you understand me?
You and I with them...
Translate!
Agreement!
Now!
Come on! Please!
Application…
He wants to make a deal.
Like brandy. Queimada . Do you know what a queimada is?
-No, but I know what aguardiente is. - Queimada is like…
Where are you going?
Outside. We're done.
-Have you guys finished work? -Yeah, we're done.
Look at these brave Galicians.
My men have finished their shift.
Are you sure?
Okay. I will go with you.
I don't think so.
Go back inside.
Come on, champ.
-Go back inside. -Look at him.
Knights in shining armor.
What are you waiting for? What are you waiting for?
Back off, you bastards!
Come on! Let us go!
What are you waiting for?!
Get on your knees. Come on.
Very good.
Now, say it after me.
Arise, O workers, from your sleep!
Arise, O prisoner of poverty!
Because common sense now roars in rebellion.
And finally the age of hypocrisy ended
Take out your anger on me, Junqueras!
Leaving three corpses behind is not a good idea.
Don't bother, Lieutenant. These people only understand suffering.
You want to talk about pain? Huh?
May 14,
1937.
Llanes.
Franco's army enters the city.
They raped all the women.
Old woman and young girl.
My wife
and including my daughter.
My little daughter is only six years old.
Bastard!
You are married.
July 19, 1936.
Republican police killed the town's pastor and doctor.
The doctor in that town was my father.
One less.
Son of a bitch!
Calm down. Come down. Get down and don't move. Come down.
Damn.
You're the one who started the war.
Yes. And you lost it.
When will you realize that?
In this camp, the Republic won the war?
Sing a verse.
Just one, and I'll let you go.
Come on.
Just that.
Facing the sun with a new shirt--
You bastard bastard!
-Who do you think you are talking to? -The one you embroidered in red--
Come on. Sing it now.
Sing now! Sing it now, motherfuckers!
Sing your national anthem now!
Sing it now, you trash!
Sing it now, you fascist bastards!
Sing your national anthem now!
-Arise, O workers from your sleep! -Sing your national anthem now! Sing!
-Arise, O prisoner of poverty -Sing!
-Because common sense now roars in rebellion -Because common sense now roars in rebellion
-And finally the age of hypocrisy has come to an end -And finally the era of hypocrisy has come to an end
That's enough.
That's enough, Dimitrov.
NO.
Enough already.
My family…
originally from Leningrad.
This one stays here.
I'm not leaving without my lieutenant.
-Do what he says. -I won't leave you alone.
That's an order!
Do something, dammit! They will kill him!
-Shut up! Get out, Galicians! Go out! -They will kill him!
-You two get out! -We are all Spanish, damn it!
We are all Spanish!
Lie on the ground! Fast!
Do it faster!
Lie on the ground!
Remain silent!
Down! Face down!
Do not move!
-Submit! -Come on!
Come on, quickly!
Quicken your steps! What are you waiting for? Keep moving!
Come on! Move! Faster! I said faster!
Remain silent!
Do not move!
-Submit! -Come on!
My little daughter is only six years old.
Bastard!
My little girl is only six years old...
NO.
Please, I'm asking you.
Let go.
Leave him alone. He's protected.
Stand.
Chairman.
I'm Lieutenant Salgado. 250th Division, 2nd regiment, 1st battalion.
Since we arrived at this camp, we have been treated like ordinary prisoners.
and placed in the same barracks as murderers and rapists.
I want me and my men to be treated in accordance with the Geneva Conventions.
Germany was at war with the Soviet Union. You do not.
You came here to kill civilians for no reason,
thousands of kilometers from your home.
You guys are mercenaries. You guys are worse than rats.
Who caused these wounds to you?
It was a very noble act because it did not betray our fellow citizens.
Now is not the time to draw.
There is a lot of sadness in your pictures.
However, beauty also exists in this world.
If you know where to look.
Don't stop drawing, Lieutenant.
Are you friends with the killers now?
That man didn't kill your husband.
If not him, there must be someone who looks like him.
WINTER 1944
Lieut.
Forgive me.
-How are you? -I'm fine.
-We thought… -Welcome, Lieutenant.
-Thank you, Artigas. -We think--
I told you.
Manuel.
This is Pablito.
Pablo.
Father made a deal with the urkas.
Visit Our Telegram Channel:
FILM SUB INDO
@filmsubindonueva
Dad spoke out of fear.
I speak just in case. We could all end up dead.
But we won't be able to do it if we stay here, Dad?
Don't you remember what they did to you and the lieutenant?
Manuel is right. No one had ever managed to escape from a camp like this. Never.
Lieutenant, I don't mean to contradict you. The Italians tried, but they withdrew.
They didn't succeed.
If anyone escapes, the entire barracks will be punished.
Dad, do you know what this is? Does Dad know?
I keep this to remember who we really are.
We're soldiers, dammit. It is our duty to try.
How many kilometers do you think the nearest town is from here?
How many supplies do we need to avoid dying of hunger or thirst?
Which direction will you go?
Where do you think north, south, east and west are from here? Where?
There are hundreds of kilometers of barren land out there.
Yes, I know.
Afghanistan is here, for starters. Look.
And Russia is here.
Nobody said this was easy, okay?
However, this is our only chance to survive.
We hid in the truck.
We took a truck to Karaganda and from there, headed to Afghanistan.
Appropriate.
Well, we will need a compass.
And tobacco for the dogs.
Pablito stayed behind.
We could go on a suicide mission, but he's still a kid. I won't allow that.
When, Lieutenant?
When the snow stops falling.
Leaving before it melts is tantamount to suicide.
We'll do it in the spring.
I'm fed up with them.
Obey orders without question.
Resistance will be punished.
Stealing food will result in beatings and suspension of feeding.
Storing explosives is grounds for severe punishment.
Burglary or armed attack--
Don't move! Stay where you are.
What's this?
Chew
and eat it.
I told you to eat it.
Here he is. Enjoy your meal.
Pablito, continue the lesson.
Okay.
Valencia?
Logroño, Pamplona, ​​​​Santander, Murcia…
-Muller. -Burgos, León…
Sorry.
Photographic memory.
I read something once and it will always be etched in my memory.
How lucky.
Artigas. What…
It's okay, bro.
NO.
Do you know the kings and queens of Spain?
Kings and queens?
Yes.
-Alfonso. -Alfonso.
-XII. -XII.
-XII. Alfonso XII. -And who else?
Again?
Who else?
-Okay… -XIII.
Alfonso XIII.
Alfonso… XIV?
-Alfonso XV, XVI, XVII. -Stop it. He couldn't focus.
Take this seriously. Okay?
Seriously, Pablito, take this seriously. This will be useful for you.
Useful for what?
For something. When we get out of here, this will come in handy.
When I was 12 years old, I worked on a battery charger assembly line.
So?
-So? -Yes?
I once lived in an orphanage, in Urka places.
The kings did nothing for me. They won't do anything for you either.
-One day, you will come back. -Back to where?
-Well, home. -House? Where is my house, Dad?!
-Hey! -No, tell me.
Shut up!
Calm the sound!
They brainwashed him. Damn.
Eladio, calm down. It doesn't matter. He's an urka.
But he's a Communist, for God's sake.
The Republic did not pay for his education so he could become an altar server.
Do you think this is normal?
We have to do something.
I think you've done enough.
Number 321!
Come on, Dad.
I know you were the one who protected me from the urkas in the infirmary.
Oraz is a man of many words.
Has he ever delivered one of his speeches to you?
You don't know anything.
You studied medicine before the war, right?
For two years.
You need to work to restore your strength.
I know what you're doing, Reyes.
You want to prevent revenge against the Asturians.
I want to stop this before it gets worse.
You mean ceasefire?
Ceasefire.
I heard you're good at drawing.
I am willing.
Oraz is a man of many words.
-You can't go in there. -Shut up.
-I told you you can't. -Stop babbling!
Go away!
Urkas trades in the saliva of tuberculosis patients.
People will do anything to avoid working in the mines.
Let me pass first.
I think you already know Aisulu.
-Your new boss. -What do you mean, my boss?
First, bathe the sick person. Then help in the equipment storage room.
He will need your help.
At least until the new doctor arrives.
One of the urkas died in the line of duty, so in return they cut off his hand.
But you can always go back to the mine.
Her husband was executed by firing squad.
Well, I hope it's not in Leningrad.
Rise up, children of the Motherland
The day of glory has arrived
Tyranny is against us
The blood-stained flag was raised
What did he say?
That he--
What?
He is sick of the Italian national anthem, the French national anthem, and the Czech national anthem.
He wanted to hear the Spanish national anthem.
Unlucky.
I am a Phalangist
I will be a Phalangist until death or until victory.
And that is why I happily serve Spain.
I enlisted, went with the young men in battle--
If the priests and monks knew that they would be beaten
They would join the choir and sing.
Freedom, freedom, freedom!
-I am a Phalangist -Stop it!
I will be a Phalangist until death or until victory.
-If only the priests and monks knew-- -Freedom, freedom, freedom!
What did he say?
He only wanted one Spanish national anthem.
I feel it inside me
Sad emotions
I suffer, far from you
And my heart is broken
Never again
Will the sun bring me happiness?
In a Spanish garden, my love
Like a flower, I will always remain
If this is my scream of bitter sorrow
Reaching your feet into the wind.
Spain, return it to me with love.
Spain, my beloved
I feel it inside me
Sad emotions
I suffer, far from you
And my heart is broken
Never again
Will the sun bring me happiness?
In a Spanish garden, my love
Like a flower, I will always remain
If this is my scream of bitter sorrow
Reaching your feet into the wind.
Spain, return it to me with love.
Spain, my beloved
Concert?
Spring concert at camp.
In seven weeks.
There may be more talent in this camp than we thought, Chief.
Are you talking about Urka who plays the violin?
There are many others like him.
We will find them. We will make a work plan.
That will not distract us from the mine.
Forget about the mine.
We will double your food rations.
Bugosla Levandovski.
Number 319.
The candidates are released from the mine.
Good grief.
What used to be this place?
Did you know that these holes are like observation posts?
If you focus, you can see the Noia estuary.
You mean the Muros estuary, you smart ass.
Look. What do you see?
Good grief!
This is Cuco's boat!
Good grief. Cuco!
There are sardines.
Cuco! Work, you bastards! You just sit around!
Cuckoo! Say hello!
With--
What is that?
This is the domra, our traditional musical instrument.
But there's a piece missing, right?
No need for additional strings.
-Anything to avoid work. -Why?
"The people from Noia are like wooden bells."
"Those people from Muros are really crazy."
You!
Stop that, kid. Your little hands are not needed here. Come on.
No, it's needed, okay? Don't listen to him.
He did a good job.
Do you play a musical instrument?
Palau banged on a pin. Right?
-Come on. I don't have much time. -Don't let me hit you.
They are like little sardines. You fry it. It feels really good.
Oh, how delicious!
Dad, what are you thinking? You just keep quiet. Huh?
In the past he was always surrounded by women.
-Is it true? -There is no harm in talking. That's not a sin.
-What are you saying? -Dad is a true Casanova.
We'll do it during the concert.
Meanwhile the guards were busy serving guests.
-We're going home, guys. -Let us go.
Not mine anymore.
-Not mine anymore. -Not mine anymore.
Nurse!
A cart fell on him.
Hang in there, my brother. Hang in there. Here he is.
You'll be fine.
Don't just stare at him! Do something!
Listen to me.
-If something happens to him-- -He won't die.
He won't die.
He must live.
Go out! Everyone's out! Give us space!
He's my brother. If he dies, I will cut off your hands!
Alcohol. Bring alcohol.
Alcohol…
Hey, what are you doing?
That's not enough.
It doesn't matter.
Do you speak Kazakh?
And.
Oraz, he… married me.
"Oraz is teaching me."
He is teaching me. Oraz is teaching me.
Thank You.
Faster! Come on! Enter!
-Come on, come in! Come on! -Don't slow down!
-Faster! Do not stop! Come on! -Enter. Do not stop.
-Hurry up and move. -Come on!
-Enter! -Enter.
You can just watch and listen.
Be quiet for a moment.
You know Carballo, the guy from the garage?
Gosh, how could I not know him?
He is more powerful than the mayor. Jesus.
Then, you must also know Remedios, his cousin.
Treatment, yes.
Remedios… I danced a lot with her.
-Oh really? -At the Muros night market, yes.
How did you get to know Remedios so well?
-Okay… -I'll go.
-Maybe because of dancing with him. -Ah.
I know she is in a relationship with a man from Muros who is a smuggler.
Oh, I don't know about that.
-You don't? -People like to talk.
People do talk a lot.
Gentlemen, I just collected a debt.
-Who wants to taste? -I.
In German, we have a beautiful word to commemorate our homeland.
Longing for hometown.
- Homesick ? - Yes.
Thank You.
This word comes from heimat, which means place,
the city where you live,
and weh, which means pain.
So it means more or less painful nostalgia.
The word does not exist in any other language.
- Thank You . - Greetings.
Hey, German.
Call it whatever, but we call it homesickness.
You're right.
Longing for hometown. Longing for hometown.
Damn.
Come on.
But do you have a wife?
Are you waiting for me at home?
Then, how could I know?
I hope so.
I have the photo.
But I lost it in the war.
I don't know if I started...
Forget him?
Come with me.
-What? -Let's go.
The eyes are big. Yes. Big.
Actually it's small. Small and a bit slanted.
One…
OK.
Hey. Come on. Try it. Please. Try.
What's his hair like?
What's his hair like? What color is it?
-The color is black. Black. -Black.
Black, but closer to brown.
Because the color appears brighter in sunlight.
-But that… -He has…
So what does it look like? Wavy, straight?
Straight. It's straight. Yes, straight. And…
Straight and long.
And his face?
His face…
Her face is a bit round, you know?
The face is round.
It's like…
It tastes like chestnuts.
His chin is pointed like this.
He has a very small nose.
Small. Very cute.
And when he laughs,
You can see his dimples.
Like this, one on each side.
It looked like his mouth had brackets on each side.
He laughed. He laughed heartily.
Many.
He always laughs.
Visit Our Telegram Channel:
FILM SUB INDO
@filmsubindonueva
That's it.
There he is.
Are we friends now?
We are working there.
"Work."
Hermida.
Hey, listen. The problem is…
Did you hear that?
Ivan's family is already in Berlin.
The British and Americans are there now.
The Nazis had lost, so it was only a matter of time.
If I return to Spain, I know exactly what I will do first.
Eat a Spanish omelette.
How about you?
They say Franco is offering amnesty to anyone who wants to return.
Cleaning action.
He just wanted them to stop bothering him after the war was over.
I don't think anyone wants another war.
These are not good times for those who are full of hope.
These are not good times.
Here.
I have prepared a petition.
Signed in my own handwriting.
And did you know?
I'm sure this time...
No. I'm not just sure.
I'm absolutely sure…
that this time...
They will sign your case file.
Thank You.
Oh yes. By the way, news about that concert
has spread throughout the camp.
Your men have done a wonderful job.
Cheers.
Not just my men, sir.
But when you are released from this camp,
Those people will remain your enemies.
Have you forgotten it?
NO.
My men have noticed a few things.
Tobacco is gone. Kitchen utensils are missing.
Absence without valid reason.
You know, I'm quite curious.
about what really happened here.
I am not an informant.
Then who will you be loyal to?
A group of mercenaries,
Francoist,
fellow fascists, or, in the end…
to your own people?
Shit.
SPRING 1945
CONCERT DAY
Good evening, Comrade Marshal. I'm glad you made it too.
Relax.
Let's go inside. It's much warmer there. The concert will start soon.
Please. Come on in.
Awesome concert today.
Which, ng кстати, we have been preparing for several weeks.
Found some amazing people.
There will be a singing event today. Greta will appear on stage.
There is a domra performance today too.
There will be a violin. And domra.
Please sit. You will sit here.
Please sit.
There will be impressive singing performances. Well…
How about having a drink after a long journey to warm up? No? A little…
And you?
Very well.
Here he is.
And if you don't mind, I'll sit right here, near you.
Reyes.
What does Nazarov want?
He proposed to me. Just that.
What's this?
Why are you keeping my letters?
I just found out.
Nazarov said it the day you met him.
System…
never make a mistake.
Reyes.
Four years.
Four damn years.
Captain…
And Dad? Where is he?
He won't come.
Come on. Let us go.
Wait. Something is missing.
What do you mean, we--
Hurry up. Hermida, hurry up, damn it.
What is he doing here?
He will come with me.
-Do you know? -Is it important?
Let's go.
When does the shift change?
We will get to see the second part if we are lucky.
With those blue eyes
Soft as the sea
I got lost in their gazes
And I can't escape
The magic of their smiles
Will always take my breath away
When I saw their lips
My world started spinning
I've never liked opera. I don't understand at all.
Well, you're not a cultured person like me.
By the way, did you see that prisoner girl? I've heard better singing.
From here to Muros, my friend.
From here to Muros.
A directionless argument
Pride is vanity.
Words that hurt
Will this be the end?
Then came night.
We just held each other's hands
We kissed
And love shines once again.
With eyes as bright as the sea
I got lost in their gazes
And I can't escape
Artigas.
Rub tobacco on your body.
Take the truck.
Yes. I'm working on it.
Try this one.
I'm working on it.
Come here.
I'll take this truck.
Hey! Stop! Wait!
There is one body missing!
What is going on?
O!
I hope you enjoy the concert.
Did you hear how well the violin plays? And what about domra?
Domra is truly amazing, don't you think?
Let's take him to dinner.
Look, if you happen to be in Moscow,
Please come for dinner. We will be happy to welcome you.
Comrade Nazarov.
Fast.
ONE MONTH LATER
Get up.
Come on.
Are you alright? Let's go. Let's go.
Keep going.
Artigas screamed.
One of the Galicians did not survive. The others managed to escape.
Who?
I am sorry.
Germany has surrendered!
The war is over!
MAY 8, 1945 - END OF WAR
Come on! Shoot!
-Hey! Be careful! -Be careful! He's there!
Father!
Please try it!
Look!
Who wants it?
SUMMER 1947
Hey! Referee!
-Here! -Referee!
That's a violation!
Help!
Rotten!
-Referee! -Penalty!
Unlucky!
-Down! -I'm down.
-Help! -Come on. Get up.
I missed. The sun dazzled my eyes.
Damn, Dad. Now the sun is bothering you, isn't it?
Hey! Shut up! Come on, shoot!
Get it out of there!
Let's go!
-Palau! -Eladio!
-Dad, just steal it! -Damn!
Greta!
NO!
-Come on, shoot! -O'clock!
Target!
Palace!
Barcelona residents, what are you doing?
-Goal! Come on! -Let go.
Miners! Goal!
Look.
More and more women are leaving. This camp's days are numbered.
We will be next.
-Did they say where they are taking you? -Leningrad. Meet us.
-This. Use this. It's very cold outside. -Palau, he has to go.
Okay? This. Keep it warm.
What's his name then?
-Sorry, but they will leave without him. -Diego.
I love you, Diego.
-I love you both. -We love you.
-Yes, run! -Come on, Palau!
I'll score next time, I swear. Come on.
The Kazakhs had invited us to lunch at the kolkhoz.
for their help in cultivating the plants.
And?
Aisulu will also come along.
So make the best use of it.
I don't know how much longer they will allow us to leave the camp.
Which camp? There are only a few of us left here.
Don't go too far.
Artigas will cover the costs for you.
I owe you a debt of gratitude.
"One," he said.
Visit Our Telegram Channel:
FILM SUB INDO
@filmsubindonueva
What's wrong?
Your thoughts are far from here.
When we're out of here,
Come with me.
This is the land of the Kazakh nation. My land.
Flowers without roots will not last long.
I also have a piece of land waiting for me.
Save it.
I'll be back to get it.
The contents are meat. Can be lamb or veal.
And this is called baursaki. It's like a Spanish churro.
The main course has arrived!
Guys, sheep's head
Served for special, honorable and respected guests.
Thank You.
Raqmet.
Oh, raqmet .
Raqmet means "thank you" in Kazakh.
- Raqmet. - Thank You.
Let's eat.
It feels good.
Anara wanted to know who you were before you got here.
I work in a publication. It belonged to my father, but he was executed.
It's the only thing left of my family. Until they closed it.
I once worked as a cook in a hotel in Barcelona.
And I also like telling jokes. Yes.
Anara asked if you could tell us one example.
-Of course. -No!
-No, don't. -Do!
It would be best if he didn't.
-That's a bad idea. -Please do not.
So, there are kolkhozes, right? Like this one.
And, suddenly, that bastard Stalin appears, and…
I told you not to tell it.
I haven't told you the best part yet. You didn't let me finish my story.
-You have no sense of humor. Are you serious. -If they are cute…
Why did they imprison you?
You never told us.
Because think differently.
Whose side are you on?
None of them.
I don't have an ideology. I have principles.
We Kazakhs never imagined this,
that the world will come here,
at the gate of our house, but Allah willed it so.
We are also grateful for that. We thank Allah.
All praises be to Allah.
And to our God.
Whoever can get us out of here first.
Appropriate.
Enjoy. We have suffered enough. Please.
Seven years without eating.
Please try, Dad.
Seriously?
Don't bother me any more with this.
How do I tell my subordinates?
No one will help us. Neither Nazarov nor the Communist Party.
-What? -What about the Blue Division?
Franco did not want to admit that he had prisoners in the Soviet Union.
-Not now? -No. There are no prisoners of any kind.
And the party doesn't want to admit that they sent us here without a trial.
They say we are deserters.
Do they want us to rot here?
Ten, fifteen years? How much longer?
Impossible. We can't let that happen.
Calm.
Nazarov made us an offer.
Copyright belongs to the Soviet Union.
We join the revolution.
-What does it mean? -We become Russian citizens.
Exactly what we need. Should we also become communists?
There were no communists left in the Soviet Union.
Stalin had killed them all.
Well then, I can go because I'm Russian.
Your case is different.
You are here for a violent crime. And absolutely right. You are already a Russian citizen.
OK, so what does all this mean?
This means we will work in workshops and factories.
Then, we will be free.
But we will be Russian.
We can't go back to Spain.
What do you think about all this, Captain?
I promise I'll get you out of here.
That doesn't mean we're going to change prisons.
Your list is very long.
All prisoners, both Republican and Blue Division,
from here and other camps. Both men and women.
The risk is too high.
There will be a second payment when you arrive in Spain at this address.
"Clara St…" Is that your family?
Who cares who they are? They will pay dearly to save us.
Damn.
Good.
Can we trust those Nazis?
-Iván José González. -No one blames you, buddy.
Thank You.
-Take care of yourself well. -You too.
Roland Durban.
Eladio.
I am really, really sorry.
-Claude Gaspard. -Palau.
We will miss you.
Me, too.
Have a nice trip. Thank You.
-See you. -Young Busacca.
-May God be with you. -Good luck.
O! Barcelona resident.
Another.
How to say "paratrooper" in Russian?
André Monicelli.
"Parachute flutter."
What? Bad joke?
Very bad.
Take care of your family.
I will.
Goodbye.
Luciano Craspelli.
Look how quickly the fascists changed sides.
Melléin Palau.
Hey, soldier. Turn the shirt pocket inside out.
They were searching them.
If they find Müller's list, we're done.
What is he doing?
-What is he doing? -Hey! Back in line!
I told you, Captain. I told you.
-Line up! -And he still received the money.
-He gave them the list. -What is he holding there? Give it to me.
Let me see.
Those Nazi bastards won't get away with it.
-Junqueras, stop. -Müller!
Fascist bastards!
-Wait. -I will kill him! Let me go!
-Captain. -Let me go!
Let me go! Bastard! Let me go!
Let me go! Damn you!
-Oh my... -Wait.
Guard!
Eladio!
Junqueras.
Did you get shot?
OK, you're fine.
Remember, Lord, that we are but dust.
And man is like the grass and flowers of the field that wither.
And…
"With thundering music I come, with my cornet and drums...
I don't play marching songs just for the recognized winners."
"I play marching songs for the conquered and murdered people."
"Have you heard?"
that winning the day was a good thing?"
"I also said that falling is good."
"I hit and hit the dead."
"Goodbye to those who fail."
"And for those whose warships sank. And for those who themselves drowned."
"And countless unknown heroes
the same as
the greatest heroes known."
MADRID MINISTRY OF FOREIGN AFFAIRS
Please, sir. Just a moment.
-Again? No, not again. Impossible. -Excuse me. It's just...
What do you want? Can't you see I'm busy?
He returns. He's still there. He said he won't leave until you see him.
-What does he want? -I don't know.
Hey, no. You shouldn't be here. No!
OK, what do you want?
Do you know how to write?
-Yes. So what? -Then, note this down.
Esperanza Moreno.
Antonio Castillo.
Antonio Barba Penas.
Cesar Benítez Martinez.
Pablo Espinoza Gomez.
Abelino González.
Tomás Bernal Aroca.
Diego Salgado Jarque.
Manuel Fernández Collado.
Pablo Fernández Carrasco.
Eladio Taraño Junqueras.
Good grief.
Telmo Reyes Anguera.
Francisco de Asis Moreno Santos.
Father.
I am very happy.
You're going home.
Yes. We both deserve enough rest.
Is not it?
Despite everything that has happened, it has been a pleasure getting to know you.
bro.
See you later, Camp Leader.
I can already smell it.
What? Fabada?
Oh Lord.
What is fabada?
-You don't know what fabada is? -No.
Beans, bacon, chorizo… It's the best thing in the world, Pablín.
Antonio Barba Penas.
Adelino González.
Captain.
-Lieutenant. -Martin Marias.
I didn't expect you to stay.
I didn't expect you to leave.
Angel Turion.
David Obeso.
José de la Torre.
Thank You.
Have a nice trip. Take care of yourself well.
-Captain. -Domingo Correa Martinez.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Diego Salgado.
This is my home now.
-Take good care of everything, okay? -Thanks for everything, my friend.
Eladio Junqueras.
Now it's my turn.
In progress.
I'll keep you here, okay?
Pablito.
Take care of yourself.
-Pablo Fernandez. -Personal!
This kid isn't going anywhere. Remove his name from the list.
Hey! What are you doing?
-The boy… -Captain.
The boy was a Soviet citizen, like all the minors held in the camp.
-Captain, what happened? -Here are the documents. See for yourself.
Telmo.
I can't go back?
How legitimate is this?
It is legal enough to cancel the extradition.
-Telmo… -You bastard.
Hey! Boy!
-No! I'll do it. -Don't you dare let him get on the bus.
Yes.
-Pablito. -No. Leave me alone.
Leave me alone! I want to go back!
-Pablo! -Leave me alone, please!
Pablo.
Learn about the kings and queens of Spain. Okay?
What? What are you talking about?
Enter.
Come on. Pablito, hurry up.
Drive.
Can you explain what is going on here?
The bus will leave soon.
I'll drive to the next checkpoint,
Show me the documents there, and take the boy with me. Understand?
These documents?
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
Guard!
Get rid of him.
MADRID 1982
400 pesetas to be exact.
Is this your first visit to Spain?
They will have the power to be consulted.
regarding whether they want to be part of a military bloc.
Reject NATO! No military bases!
We don't want any military bloc.
Yankees are out!
Good afternoon, Lieutenant.
I'm Reyes.
Captain Telmo Reyes.
He…
He kept it all his life.
And he wants you to have it.
Captain.
Lieutenant.
Remember what Oraz used to say?
"No man is freer than he who has ever been imprisoned."
FOR MY MOTHER
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING
Ceasefire
Visit Our Telegram Channel:
FILM SUB INDO
@filmsubindonueva