(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 14]
How did they reply?
They told me
they are still considering it.
Nothing is certain.
We also sent people over to check.
They either said the boss was not there,
or they were vague.
I was thinking,
since the agreement
between us has expired,
I'll let the front office,
the rooms division,
and the finance department
settle the accounts
and take back the rooms this weekend.
Mr. Ji, please take the time to sign
these two documents.
Then I'll take my leave.
Okay.
[Senior]
[Xue Rui]
These folders
contain all the hotel's revenue bills.
For how to compile
and categorize them,
just follow last year's template.
Review my ass!
Listen carefully:
get the general manager's signature first!
Isn't the general manager's
signature here?
[Fund Review Form] [GM Signature: Ji Feng]
Here we need Mr. Wei's signature!
Don't you understand?
You don't even know
who you are working for.
Director Xue.
Director Xue,
is the occupancy rate
calculated incorrectly?
[Housekeeping Department
Occupancy Rate Report]
It's 10 percentage points
lower than last week.
[Total Rooms] [Occupied Rooms]
It was 58% last Friday.
[Occupancy Rate Line Chart]
After the weekend,
it
suddenly dropped to 48%.
Take a look.
[Resignation Report]
[Application: Xue Rui]
[Ji Feng]
♪ Life is full of ♪
♪ Countless crossroads ♪
♪ Chase joy too hard, and it slips away ♪
[Delivery List]
♪ All those confusions ♪
[HSKP Department] [Project] [Balance]
[May 31, Sales Department Banquet]
♪ No answers, no reasons ♪
[Sales Commission: 12,000 Not Recorded]
♪ Throwing ourselves
into the tide of the unknown ♪
♪ Knowing when to advance or retreat,
yet still asleep ♪
♪ Rushing to ripen before our time ♪
♪ Sighing at partings,
who meets whom at which crossing ♪
♪ Busy and restless ♪
♪ No turning back, no stopping ♪
♪ Our path—do you see it now ♪
♪ Just lift your head, oh ♪
♪ Don't look back ♪
♪ I've already learned ♪
♪ If it's not mine, I won't force it ♪
♪ No matter how you force it ♪
♪ It'll only turn into a long,
endless wait ♪
♪ Waiting to make peace with myself ♪
♪ And waiting to meet someone again ♪
♪ Wave goodbye ♪
♪ Just lift your head, oh ♪
Tail number 2867.
To the high-speed rail station.
♪ Don't look back ♪
♪ I've already learned ♪
♪ If it's not mine, I won't force it ♪
You don't need to go.
I came back myself.
♪ No matter how you force it ♪
Sir, I'm not taking the ride.
-It's okay.
-You can still open the order;
♪ It'll only turn into a long,
endless wait ♪
I'll pay online.
Okay.
By going back on my word,
♪ Waiting to make peace with myself ♪
I've completely offended everyone
at Yiting Siji.
You have to take care of me.
♪ And waiting to meet someone again ♪
I will.
I'll take care of your future.
♪ Wave goodbye ♪
Don't brag.
Also,
I canceled my lease.
I'm homeless now.
I'll arrange the rest.
First, go to HR and get onboarded.
Why in such a hurry?
I'm afraid you'll run away again.
Let's go.
Okay.
I got it.
Mr. Wei,
add a desk to Mr. Ji's office.
[Qian][Wei]
Sorry to put you through this.
Be my assistant for now.
Once I figure out the management team,
I'll send you back to
the finance department.
That's nothing.
Come,
come over and take a look.
I'll walk you through the situation.
Wei Siyuan's "iron triangle."
[Huang] [Qian] [Wei] [Feng]
Qian Xun from the sales department,
Huang Chengmin
from the finance department,
[Huang] [Qian] [Wei] [Feng]
and Feng Kaixin from the HSKP Department,
are all relatives.
Is it firm?
Yes.
Xiang,
come, say hi to mom.
One is the cousin
of Wei Siyuan's father-in-law,
Be careful.
another is his brother-in-law,
and this one is his wife's
younger brother.
They have total control over
Purong Hotel's finances.
Xiang.
Touch any one of them,
and you're up against all four.
Take it easy!
Baby.
[Yunji Equestrian Club]
Thank you.
Come on.
Go, go, go.
Come on, kids, get your milk.
Come, come, come.
Cheers.
-Cheers!
[Yunji Equestrian Club]
Bottoms up.
Of the two major clients
Purong Hotel lost,
one is Shijing Tech,
and the other is Zhanpeng Industry.
They have very good personal relationships
with Qian Xun.
Qian,
your business is our business.
Good, good, good.
Mr. Zheng, come.
If you want to
renew the contract next year,
Mr. Qian, it just takes one word from you.
Good, good.
Thanks for your help.
Come on!
Here's to our successful cooperation.
Putting it all together,
if you audit the accounts,
they'll delete clients.
That's basically telling you
the cost of messing with Feng Kaixin.
Yes.
I told you not to take on this mess.
Just let Kuanli
buy out this whole nest of vipers.
Let's not dwell on the past.
Since you chose to fight back,
we need to know our enemy.
I know Feng Kaixin.
He's just a good-for-nothing.
He only survives
because Wei Siyuan protects him.
[Huang] [Qian] [Wei] [Feng]
But Huang Chengmin is much more cunning.
You can tell from his accounts
that he
keeps a low profile,
and he's the sneaky type.
The head of the "iron triangle"
is Qian Xun.
In Purong Hotel, Wei Siyuan
makes the most illicit money.
Besides Wei Siyuan, he's probably
the one taking kickbacks.
So by doing this,
you're messing with his interests.
Watch out, he might
sabotage your performance.
After all, he's in charge of
the sales department.
The economic lifeline of the whole hotel
is in his hands.
I thought of that too.
So I don't plan to rely on him
for the first deal.
Then what are you going to do?
Here.
[Inbox]
Libo Group.
[Libo Group APAC Chief Brand Officer]
For the first deal,
I have to handle it personally.
[Marcos Yang Visits Purong Hotel]
That way, we can make sure
nothing goes wrong—
and it also sends them a message.
You focus on bringing in revenue,
I'll help cut costs.
You start auditing.
We'll hit from both sides.
I've caused you three a lot of trouble.
I am here
to sincerely apologize.
Let me toast you.
Bottoms up!
Alright.
Your business is our business.
Don't treat us like strangers.
You guys,
don't just stick together.
The new general manager is young
and unfamiliar with the place.
You should take the initiative
to look after him.
Look after him?
Sure.
I'll "take good care" of him.
I promise
I'll kick him out
in less than three months.
I know that guy Ji's background.
Didn't he just study abroad
for a few years?
[General Manager's Office]
[Inventory Ledger]
[Notice on Receiving Libo Group]
[APAC CBO Marcos Yang]
[Send]
[Customer information of Purong Hotel]
[Sending emails]
[Sending successfully]
[Purong Directors Group Chat]
Directors,
please check the client information
in the email.
Prepare to receive Libo Group's
APAC CBO
Marcos Yang.
[Okay.]
Kaixin,
reply quickly.
No.
I won't reply.
[Ji Feng]
Feng is only fierce in words.
Kaixin is considered to
be controlled by him this time.
I'm so mad!
I...
I'm angry.
He actually bossed me around!
Who does he think he is?
Don't go too far.
Me, going too far?
When guests check into the hotel,
the HSKP Department definitely
needs me to arrange things.
But he
didn't even ask,
and directly named Xu Miyu to take charge.
Does he treat me,
the Director of the HSKP Department,
he...
as a vase?
You're not a vase,
but a wine bottle.
You...
Brother, say a few words for me.
Xu Miyu is the forewoman
of the executive floor.
VIPs staying on the executive floor
are naturally handled by Xu Miyu.
What are you so upset about?
Me?
Of course I'm upset!
Who doesn't know that woman
is Mr. Ji's favorite?
She gets all the spotlight?
It's gone too far.
The spotlight
depends on how you let her take it.
If you want her to shine,
you let her shine the right way.
If you want her
to stumble,
that's also an option.
Right, Mr. Wei?
What do you mean?
Between Xu Miyu and Ji Feng,
isn't there still you?
You can just make some arrangements
in the middle,
and set a trap for Xu Miyu.
Will Ji Feng deal with it or not?
If he doesn't handle it,
he loses public support.
If he does handle it,
he's already short-staffed—
he loses another person either way.
Brilliant.
You two are the brilliant ones.
Come on.
Stop drinking.
A toast to you two.
Bottoms up!
Drink less.
Think it over carefully.
Do some real work.
Kaixin.
Ms. Xu,
the executive floor
has been quite peaceful lately.
How is it?
Are you getting used to the work?
I'm trying to adapt.
Director,
I'll keep working hard.
Good.
Very good.
Right now,
I have a good opportunity
for you to perform.
It's like this.
Next, our hotel
will be hosting an important VIP client.
Mr. Ji
assigned this task to our HSKP Department.
Now I give it to you.
You should know
this is a rare opportunity
to prove yourself.
In our HSKP Department,
many forewomen
want to show their faces.
I have faith in you.
This
is the customer's profile.
You must study it carefully
when you get back.
Prepare well,
and strive to make new contributions.
Okay, Director.
[Customer Information of Purong Hotel]
What's wrong?
You look like you're not very willing.
No.
Thank you for your favor, Director.
Our executive floor
will definitely provide
good reception service.
Good.
Ms. Xu,
I have high hopes for you.
Please make sure I won't
lose face in front of Mr. Ji.
Okay.
I will do my best.
Come on.
Go back and prepare well.
I'll be going now.
[Purong Hotel]
Mr. Qian,
here are the client profiles
you asked me to print.
Please take a look.
[Director's Office]
Keep them with you for now.
But the notice says
this client is coming tomorrow.
How should we arrange this?
Well,
ask everyone in the group chat.
Give these materials to
whoever is willing to go.
Okay.
Notice: Colleagues, please check that
the client's information is in the email.
Please actively participate
in the preparations for
hosting Libo Group's
APAC CBO,
Marcos Yang.
Thank you for your cooperation—
from sales department.
What I sent you
is the renewal contract drafted by Purong.
Check it for any issues first.
I'll talk to Mr. Wei.
I'll let you know when I have news.
Honey,
don't be in a hurry to sign the contract.
What's wrong?
Purong Hotel is in a total mess right now.
Don't get involved.
Changing ownership
is next year's business.
Besides,
Mr. Wei is not an outsider.
Let's just sign this year's contract.
That's not how it works.
Whether Wei Siyuan's position
is secure or not,
it's hard to say.
Anyway, just listen to me.
Sign it a couple of days later, okay?
Okay?
Okay.
I'll listen to you, honey.
What is it?
I have something good to show you.
What good thing?
[Yueting Real Estate:
Build A Home With Ingenuity]
Where we live now
is convenient and affordable.
Isn't it good enough?
Look closely,
this is a school district house.
The Experimental Primary School,
the Normal University
Affiliated Primary School,
and several private primary schools
are all nearby.
I just passed by
when I met a client today,
and saw many people rushing to buy it.
Look at this floor plan.
[The highlight of the household]
Every room faces south.
Where else can you
find a floor plan like this?
After the child is born,
whether a nanny or our mom comes to help,
don't they need a nice place to stay?
Right, that makes sense.
But the problem
is the child hasn't been born yet.
It's too early for school.
Now to go to primary school,
you need 5 years of school district house
qualification in advance.
You still think it's too early?
You silly dad.
Let's wait until I'm done with
this busy period.
No.
We have to go house hunting this weekend.
Otherwise, this floor plan
will be sold out.
Honey,
I've been really busy at work lately.
Which is more important,
the baby or the company?
The baby is more important.
Let's go take a look this weekend.
[Health condition]
[Psychology health attention]
Mr. Ji.
How are you doing with the materials?
Almost done.
I'll review them twice more.
Mr. Yang
is Spanish-Chinese.
He has a deep affection
for Chinese culture.
He travels around the world all year round
and has stayed in various luxury hotels.
This time he comes to Shanghai
and chooses our Purong Hotel.
He has high expectations
for this stay.
Details are your strong suit.
I'll leave this to you.
I understand, Mr. Ji.
[Receptionist]
Okay.
You're the only one here today?
I'm on the night shift.
Find someone
to cover your shift and get some rest.
I don't want you
to look sleep-deprived tomorrow
when receiving VIPs.
Okay.
[Receptionist]
Mr. Ji,
don't worry.
Tomorrow, the executive floor
will definitely
use our fullest enthusiasm,
overcome all difficulties,
and help you win this big client.
Okay.
[Purong Hotel]
Hello, Mr. Ji.
Hello.
Morning, Mr. Ji.
Good morning, Mr. Ji.
I'm Lu Zhenzhen from the sales department.
Do you remember me?
My mother-in-law
just had her 60th birthday last month.
Of course.
Welcome to Purong Hotel.
I just transferred to
the sales department.
Please take care of me, Mr. Ji.
Hello, Ms. Xu.
Mr. Ji,
I won't let
any personal feelings interfere with
my work.
Oh my god.
The wife and the mistress
are in the same frame.
Are they going to fight?
Marcos,
I'm great to see you in Shanghai.
Long time no see.
Hello, I am Zhen,
the sales representative
from Purong Hotel.
After the long journey,
would you prefer to take a rest
or grab something to eat first?
I'll rest first.
Welcome, Mr. Marcos.
I'll take you to your room.
This way, please.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Good morning, Mr. Yang.
I'm the director of the rooms.
My name is Feng Kaixin.
Hello, Mr. Feng.
Mr. Yang, your Chinese is so good.
Great.
Mr. Yang, please come in.
Excuse me.
Marcos,
after such a long flight,
you must be hungry.
You can go to the restaurant
for some food.
No need to be so complicated.
I'll just grab a bite here.
There are ready-made sandwiches
in the Executive Lounge.
Cold food is bad for the stomach.
Marcos has a weak stomach.
The Executive Lounge can make hot food.
How long will it take?
Anytime.
Serve the dishes immediately.
Master Yue,
did anyone else give you
the guest's dietary restrictions?
No.
Okay, thank you.
Your business banquet
is actually very suitable
to be held at Purong Hotel.
I think your hotel
is indeed quite tasteful.
It's just that the other company
has already
booked a restaurant in advance.
It's okay. There will be
other opportunities in the future.
It's a pity.
There will be opportunities anytime.
Ms. Xu.
This salad is a bit too much.
I'll portion it out for you.
Thank you.
Swap out the egg and mayonnaise,
and replace them with
Japanese roasted sesame dressing
and chicken breast.
Halve the portion.
Make it fast.
Okay.
Thank you.
I don't mean to look down on you.
At this level, you're still managing to
get by as a forewoman
on the executive floor?
We'd hate to disturb you.
Have a good rest.
Ms. Xu,
your explanation?
I am sorry, Mr. Ji.
The person you should
apologize to is Marcos.
But on my documents...
Ms. Xu,
I told you again and again yesterday
and emphasized
the importance of this task.
How could you still make
such an amateur mistake?
I handed such an important client to you.
It is clearly written in the documents
that Marcos is allergic to pollen
and eggs.
You didn't even look at
such important information.
Do you have any sense of
responsibility for your work?
You brought shame to our executive floor,
no,
the entire HSKP Department.
Mr. Feng, the documents
you gave me clearly...
You're still explaining, huh?
Look at you,
still trying to pass the buck to me.
If it weren't for me
and Mr. Ji taking charge
on the spot today,
who knows how much loss the hotel
would have suffered?
Look at your working attitude
and level.
Do you still deserve to be
an executive floor forewoman?
Ms. Xu,
can you handle it well?
I can.
I'll trust you one more time.
Just let it go?
Ms. Xu,
Mr. Ji wants to see you in his office.
I was just heading there.
[Receptionist]
Come in.
Mr. Ji,
I've read this document over ten times,
and I've memorized it.
It really doesn't mention
Marcos' food allergies.
Here.
[Allergies: allergic to pollen and eggs.]
[Professional Background]
Wait,
this is not my file.
I highlighted my copy of the materials
with a marker.
[Health status] [Mental health concerns]
Look.
Fortunately, I have a photo.
It was marked with a highlighter.
[Health status]
Not bad.
You reacted quickly.
I know this was not your fault.
I called you here
to give you a new one.
Then just now...
You were eager to prove yourself,
and I wanted to see what you could do.
Mr. Ji.
All right.
That's the end of this matter.
It's safer if you use my version.
For all future reception work,
you report directly to me.
Understood?
Understood.
Thank you, Mr. Ji.
Mr. Marcos,
I know that Libo Group
is known globally for its long-termism.
The acquisition of Taisheng Metropolis
seven years ago
is unsurpassed among
global construction companies.
Has your hotel cooperated with Libo?
Of course.
Our hotel hosted the annual meeting
of Libo Group's
branch in Shanghai, China last year.
We are also negotiating
with Libo Group's partner,
Shenjiang Industry,
on some projects.
Sorry,
I'm late.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
How is it?
Are you used to the food?
This meat is not bad.
It's especially tender
when I bite into it.
I really like it.
This is our hotel's signature dish.
The veal shank is very delicious.
It was carefully prepared for you
by a chef in our kitchen who specializes
in Mediterranean cuisine.
So thoughtful.
Braised prawns.
Try it.
The flavor is quite rich.
How was it made?
It
is made by our...
This cuisine
mainly depends on the sauce.
In most places, the sauce
is made by mixing store-bought ketchup.
But in our kitchen, the sauce is made
by simmering wild mushroom broth together
with fresh tomatoes,
so it has a very seasonal flavor.
So did you arrange
these dishes?
I learned that you prefer Chinese cuisine,
and you also like
various kinds of seafood.
So for tonight's menu,
most of it is Chinese-style seafood.
Thank you.
I'm glad you like it.
I love it.
And thank you too.
You are all like my family.
You know me very well.
Right, Kenny?
Of course.
The service staff you trained
have never disappointed me.
You're flattering us.
Don't be.
Come.
Cheers.
It's really great.
As long as you like it.
[Receipt]
[Shang PIN JIN HUO JI LU BIAO]
Who is it?
Xue Rui!
Xue...
Mr. Xue?
[Shang PIN JIN HUO JI LU BIAO] [Receipt]
Wait a moment!
Coming.
Mr. Chen.
Why is your door locked?
What are you hiding?
Mr. Xue, why are you here?
It's a bit chaotic.
It will
ruin
your suit.
Are you treating me like a stranger?
It's a work uniform.
Did you forget?
We used to come here
at the end of every month
to settle accounts.
Right.
You were in charge of
the purchasing accounts back then.
This place is great.
This is the granary of Purong Hotel.
It is a treasured place.
I want to live here every day.
How is it going?
Are you busy?
Business is okay.
We have a few tables for lunch.
But,
they are all regular customers.
No new ones.
How much revenue do you make during lunch?
Brother Chen,
can you let me see your purchase orders?
I'm afraid not.
Chef Jia is not here.
I can't make the call.
Come on.
You are the manager
of the purchasing department.
You can't even make this call?
What purchasing department manager?
I'm just a grocery shopper.
Okay.
I won't make things difficult for you.
Look,
when Chef Jia comes back,
ask him to prepare the purchase order
and hand it in to me today.
No.
This won't do.
Brother,
let me be honest with you.
The new boss
has been looking at
the Chinese restaurant's bills lately.
They are really rushing me.
Do me a favor.
After Chef Jia comes back,
have him prepare it and hand it over to me
so I can report back
and get through this.
I see.
All right.
I will definitely tell him.
Okay, thanks.
I'll let you get back to work.
It's nothing.
The cup.
Thank you.
Okay, take care.
Bye.
How did it go?
I'm already this old,
and I still have to
play spy games with you.
Good thing I have strong nerves.
I said everything you told me to say.
But your goal
definitely isn't
just the purchase order, right?
You know me best, Rui.
Are you still not going to
tell me your plan?
Here.
[Personnel Registration
Form of Purong Hotel]
Jia Shikun
claims to be a disciple
of Huaiyang cuisine master Gu Shanghong.
[Name: Jia Shikun]
Relying on his signature dish—
salted pork rib soup with bamboo shoots—
said to be a top specialty in Shanghai,
he has been secretly taking advantage of
the hotel for years,
and no one has dared to touch him.
To solve the problem
of our Chinese restaurant,
he must be eliminated.
I know about Jia Shikun's problem.
But if you touch him,
the board won't agree.
So I want him to leave by himself.
How are you so sure
he'll leave on his own?
He's hot-tempered
and cares most about his reputation.
Even Wei Siyuan
takes a detour when he sees him.
A newly appointed manager,
recklessly trying to use him as an example
and making him hand over
the account books...
Do you think he'll be furious
and try to assert dominance over me?
That's all your guess.
I asked a headhunter I know.
There are quite a few hotels
trying to recruit him this month,
including Kuanli Hotel.
I'm just giving him a little push.
Be quick about it!
Chef!
You're finally here.
I've been looking for you everywhere.
You cut it so big?
You want to choke someone?
Recut it!
What is it? Speak.
Speak.
The higher-ups are investigating.
The higher-ups?
Yes.
Is it the guy surnamed Ji?
The new boss is taking office
and throwing his weight around my turf?
They're forcing us
to hand in the list today.
Why don't we just fool them a bit
and let it go?
If you want to play,
go play with him.
I won't.
Chef, don't be like this.
Don't talk to me, I quit.
Listen to me.
You suppress this matter first.
We will always have a way out later.
Take what?
What do we do?
-What should I tell him?
-Calm down.
I'll talk to him.
I will tell him.
Don't be in a rush to leave.
Well..
Right, just...
Good for you.
You did so much on your own,
and didn't tell me anything.
If I had told you,
Rui, would you still have
such excellent acting skills
in the purchasing department?
Do you have a suitable chef?
I have someone I'd like to try hiring.
At Duan Aoxiang's banquet,
[Personnel Registration
Form of Purong Hotel]
I saw her creativity.
She graduated
from Le Cordon Bleu in France.
[Name: Li Qiaoqi]
She has ideas and she's capable.
And I heard she has a particularly
good relationship with you.
Yes.
I know her quite well.
She's straightforward
and a doer.
She can definitely be trusted.
Once Jia Shikun leaves,
he will definitely
take his kitchen staff with him.
As long as we give her more time
and trust her,
she can slowly build her own team.
In that case,
we...
Come in.
Mr. Ji, Director Lu is...
Mr. Ji,
at 6:30 tonight,
Mr. Marcos' business banquet
will be changed to
the small banquet hall in our hotel.
[Banquet Hall Application]
A total of five tables.
Please sign it.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
It took me a whole day
to finally convince Mr. Marcos
to move the banquet to our hotel.
[Banquet Hall Application]
[General Manager's Approval: Approved]
There will be many big shots tonight.
Top executives from
the construction, mining,
[Banquet invitation request department:
Sales Department]
[General Manager: Ji Feng]
and real estate industries will be here.
This is a very rare
promotional opportunity for us.
You are in charge of this banquet.
Report to me if anything comes up.
Rui.
Director Lu picked a great time to come.
Jia Shikun might not have left today.
With such a good chance to set me up,
how many people do you think
are left in the kitchen?
What should we do then?
Should we ask HR?
Didn't you say we should
let Li Qiaoqi have a try?
Now is the chance.
Let's see if she can seize
the opportunity.
She can do it.
[Dinner menu] [Cold dishes] [Hot dishes]
[Staple food][Soup]
How long does it take
to cook a five-table dinner?
It's not a matter of time.
You saw it too.
Chef Jia took more than
half of the kitchen staff away.
I need manpower.
How many do you need?
I want three Sous Chefs,
and a dessert chef.
I can't give you three.
I'll give you one first,
and I'll transfer the rest
to you from other departments.
Okay.
Mr. Ji, Mr. Xue.
What is it?
I just went to see
Manager Chen from procurement
to get him to sign the guests'
dietary restrictions list.
I happened to see him
locking the door and leaving,
so I came to ask what happened.