(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Are you available, sir?
Yes, sir. Good evening.
Please let me get that.
- Whoa, you have a lot. Oh, careful.
- Yes.
You must've been on a long trip
for quite a bit of time.
- I'll grab that.
- I've been away for three months.
The weather's gotten a lot warmer.
Oh, it's so hot these days.
I guess it's expected this time of year.
Leave it.
A famous guy has just arrived.
Sir, over there.
He looks like a celebrity.
I gave a ride to someone well-known.
You know Lee Jung-jae?
The guy who starred in Crooks?
Ah, yes.
His son's a handsome guy.
Lee Jung-jae was going on
about him being a singer or an actor.
Yet when looking at his face,
his son's just not handsome enough.
He doesn't have it.
Ah.
Have you been around a celebrity
in real life, sir?
Now you're wondering what role I played.
I get it. It was a small part.
A person with no luck,
who's never had love or success.
Let's bet for real?
I win the bet, you follow me.
LOTS OF NEW EXPERIENCES
ON SET FOR THE QUIET WOMAN!
Oh.
She's shooting a new movie.
CAN'T WAIT FOR YOU ALL TO SEE IT
CHEESE CATS I MET ON THE STREET
She shared that picture
without asking for permission.
"Papago."
"I'm thankful to him."
9,999 FOLLOWERS
Okay, then.
FOLLOWING
10,000 FOLLOWERS
10,000?
Did I make that happen?
This is Papago.
As per the terms of our bet,
I'm following you.
Sorry for leaving you like that.
Good luck with filming.
I hope you get your big break
and your festival begins.
Wow, there must be a celebration.
They're setting off fireworks.
Yes, they are.
It is a celebration.
DO RA-MI, CHA MU-HEE
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
I wanna switch off my head
For a while…
No, no, whoa. No way!
What the…
Let me sink in my quiet melancholy
Sometimes it's fine
To lean into the lonely
Perfect light, perfect stage
Oh, please, turn on the lights for me
I'll be dancing alone
Dance! Feel alive!
I would dive into the dark
I love to be alone
So leave me alone
Dance! Feel the vibe!
I might be a narcissist
I love to be alone
Just leave me alone
Somebody to love
Somebody to hurt
I'm exhausted by all of them
Where should I go?
Well, don't give a "uh"
Lately, I don't overthink for myself…
Like adolescence
It's getting tough
So I gave up on this early
Just leave me alone
The Netflix original film The Quiet Woman
became an overnight sensation
as soon as it dropped.
The main character
Do Ra-mi's wild, crazy dance
went viral with over 100 million views,
spawning tributes all across the world.
But the actress who played the part
was so dedicated to her role
that she became unconscious
in the final days of filming.
Now fans all across the world
are praying for her recovery.
Do Ra-mi! Do Ra-mi!
My guest tonight went from unknown actress
to the scream queen
of modern horror films.
Now she's become an icon of hope
after making a splendid comeback
after overcoming a major injury.
- Okay.
- Please welcome to the All Night Show
the star of the South Korean film
The Quiet Woman.
Cha Mu-hee!
Feels like a miracle walking in.
Welcome to the show.
- Thank you.
- Wait.
Welcome.
Please give Do Ra-mi
a big round of applause.
Please give her a big round of applause.
Cha Mu-hee, please introduce
yourself to the audience.
Uh, please
introduce yourself to the audience.
Ah, hello. I work as an actress
from South Korea.
I'm Cha Mu-hee.
Nice to meet you.
I just wanna say
that was really great. They loved you.
- Merry Christmas.
- Happy New Year!
- You too!
Mu-hee, you were so cool out there.
Amazing! Awesome! What's wrong?
Take this ring off.
I need to go to the bathroom,
but I can't go with all this jewelry
worth over 100,000 bucks.
What about the outfit? It's Chanel.
Oh, you're right!
Oh shoot! Oh no! I sat down in this.
Mu-hee, you need to get used to this.
"Chanel?" You're Do Ra-mi.
You wear the shit out of this!
That's the attitude.
I guess.
Is this life even real?
What are you saying?
These last few weeks have felt unreal.
Is this real, Yong-u?
Or did I die in another world?
And then I woke up, and now I'm in heaven!
Wow, you're super happy now.
Are you happy?
Yes, I'm happy!
The sun's out, and I love it.
If this isn't really real,
then I'd rather just die now.
This is real.
You're Do Ra-mi, the movie star!
You go ahead
and pee with that ring on, queen.
Oh, Mu-hee, before you change,
you need to take a selfie.
Your fans are waiting for you, girl.
- Okay.
- And get some rest.
I have over ten million followers now.
Before my accident, I just had 10,000.
Ms. Cha Mu-hee?
Is something wrong?
Are you feeling all right?
Ah, yes.
I'm okay. Just fine.
I was nervous, so I got a little dizzy,
and then I got a bit flustered.
Hello, I'm home.
Welcome back, Mr. Joo.
Mr. Kim brought guests again.
Again?
This place is full of old books,
paintings, and antiques.
So many old things.
- I think of it as a museum.
- Impressive.
Oh, yes, there's so much here.
It's great. It's so amazing here.
He published my first novel,
but we were more than workmates.
We were friends too.
And back when he was alive,
this house was like my second home,
you know?
- Yes, please look around. Don't be shy.
- Yes.
Ho-jin! Come over here.
He's the grandson.
The son of his daughter.
- Ah.
- Watch what you say.
He speaks every language.
Ah, hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Say hello.
They're professors
from a Taiwanese university.
They're going to check out the books
and stay for a few days.
See, I told you he'd let us stay here.
Ah, I'll take care of them.
Don't worry and don't mind them.
- Mr. Kim.
- Oh, just give me a moment.
Let me show them something
really valuable, okay?
Could we have a word?
You've been using my house regularly
for your guests without asking me?
You leave it empty
while traveling around the world.
It's better to have people here
than to shut it up like this.
Your grandfather
always liked having people over,
and you don't need to attend to them.
As the current homeowner,
I just don't like having
so many strangers around.
Well, wow, no.
When your grandfather passed away,
I thought he would leave the house
to his grandchild.
I also thought
he would leave me all these books.
Instead, he left it to his only child,
your mother,
who doesn't have
any interest in this stuff.
Since you're here,
will you give my mother a call
and have her take these books
and other things that fill up this house?
She needs to take it all.
How can she
when she's not even in the country?
We can send it
in a shipping crate by boat.
If you do that, I'll make a report
to the Korean Heritage Service
for taking valuable assets
out of the country.
Then what do you expect me to do?
This place can't be on the market
with all of this stuff.
I can't keep living
in this huge house alone.
That's why I keep inviting guests over,
so you're not alone.
Goodness gracious, you're needy.
Please listen,
and pass on this message to her. Okay?
You can tell her to come here
before the end of the year
and deal with this stuff.
Oh, well, your mother will have to
return to Seoul for that to happen.
Whoa! I found it!
Oh!
This is it.
How about getting engaged?
What?
Well, she came back
for your grandfather's funeral.
- She'll show up for her son's wedding.
- Can't exactly get married alone.
True.
You need a lady to do that.
Oh. Hey, are you dating a celebrity?
What are you saying?
A girl at the publishing house in Japan
asked if you knew the famous Do Ra-mi.
She wondered if you came to Japan
with her or something.
There's this photo, and it could be you.
Here, take a look.
I have no idea.
This is it.
- Uh…
- Okay, stay still. Let me see.
Ah…
Ah, the resemblance is uncanny.
Spill the beans.
Just a meaningless picture.
We weren't traveling anywhere together.
This post means nothing.
Keep that from my face.
So, tell me again. The person in, uh,
Do Ra-mi's Instagram post is not you?
No. I already told you it isn't.
I got a call from Shunji, who's in Japan.
He asked,
"Are Do Ra-mi and Ho-jin dating?"
"Did they come to Japan together?"
I've never dated Do Ra-mi.
We've never gone anywhere together.
We don't know each other.
Ah!
I already told my family back home
that Do Ra-mi is my friend's friend.
Don't tell anyone that.
I'm not dating her.
There's nothing
that's friendly with her, okay?
- I don't know.
- Stop laughing.
- But I don't buy it.
- He's really a terrible liar.
What are you looking at?
Hey, does this…
this guy look like anyone you know?
You just see a profile.
Mm… Hmm.
Has the same height and build.
Strangers wouldn't be able to tell.
But everyone who knows you
would say it's totally you.
People who know could tell?
Hey, come gather around!
Let's count down the new year. Yeah!
Let's turn on the TV.
Actress Cha Mu-hee is also in attendance
at this year's
midnight bell-ringing ceremony…
Do Ra-mi's part of
the bell-ringing ceremony?
Yes, of course. Do Ra-mi is
the talk of the town these days.
So Cha Mu-hee is the name
of the actress who plays Do Ra-mi?
Let's count down for our dreams
to come true in the new year.
Nine, eight,
seven, six,
five, four,
three, two, one!
Happy New Year!
I'm gonna get fit this year!
Good!
Let's do a glamorous shot
with an elegant vibe.
Okay.
Mu-hee. The pictures we took today
will be on the cover of Vogue.
It will be published
in five Asian countries.
And Vogue Singapore
will send a journalist.
She'll interview you another time.
Uh, if she's Singaporean,
will the interview be in Mandarin?
I don't have much experience
speaking Chinese.
Don't worry. She speaks Mandarin,
but we hired an interpreter.
- Ah.
- It'll be great.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
"Are you feeling better now,
Ms. Cha Mu-hee?"
Ms. Cha Mu-hee?
Oh, sorry.
- Please, could you say it again?
- "It's so nice to see you."
"We were worried about you.
How are you doing?"
Good. I recovered,
and my health is fine now.
Oh wow.
It's a real pleasure to see you too.
Could you say that to her?
"Thanks for asking.
I'm feeling much better now."
"It's a pleasure to meet you too."
That's great to hear.
Your fans in Singapore were giving you
so much love and support.
Would you like to say hi to them?
Ah…
I've never been there, but I'd love to go.
I've watched a few YouTube videos
about it.
It does seem like such a lovely place.
I hope to spend time there soon.
You really should. Please do.
We welcome you anytime.
But talking about traveling,
your fans are really curious
about this issue.
Who is the gentleman in one
of your Instagram photos from Japan?
You even hashtagged "thankful" to him.
There's a picture
from your trip to Japan on Instagram.
Who's the man
you mention you're thankful to?
The fans can't sleep without knowing.
Oh.
Yes, I see. That man? He's…
Well, he's someone I quickly met
who was helping with giving me directions.
He knows Japanese and other languages,
so he's just a guy who was kind.
Oh, I see.
Well, he was pretty handsome,
so I guess some of your fans
might have expected something
more romantic between you two?
There's hope the relationship
is romantic and is leading somewhere.
It's the fans' wish.
They want a romantic connection.
Well, he's someone
who I happened to have run into.
He was just some guy.
It really meant nothing.
But, well, sometimes,
it can be a nice fantasy.
The thought of traveling
and encountering a stranger.
Someone who's charming and helpful.
It can give me
a hint of the butterflies, yes.
Thanks for asking.
Hey, Mr. Joo.
Oh, well, where's Ms. Cha Mu-hee?
I need time to speak with her.
Oh, she asked for you to join her.
She's waiting in the parking lot.
Let's go this way.
I can wait here.
I only have a few words to say.
It'll take a minute.
We have to go to the next item
on her schedule.
- You can talk to her on the way there.
- No, wait, Yong-u, uh, it won't take long.
- Hey, watch your head.
- Ah.
- Uh, here.
- I'll talk to her another time.
Hop in, Mr. Joo. She's right here.
All right, go ahead.
- We don't have much time. Go on.
- Uh…
Sorry. I haven't had a chance to eat yet.
Well, have you had lunch?
Uh, I'll eat later. Thanks.
So please go ahead and eat.
I've eaten enough already.
Oh. Well, then,
all I see is a small salad.
Is that enough to sustain you?
The daily schedule's very full,
so I quickly eat in the car.
If I eat a lot when I'm working,
I get bloated.
I had no idea we'd see each other again.
I was totally shocked to see you
when I turned around.
Sorry for startling you.
I really wanted to speak to you.
Trying to book this gig was difficult.
So I asked a fellow interpreter
for a favor.
The job today was actually assigned
to another translator?
However, you wanted to see me?
Yes.
Why though?
Uh, well, you see, um…
There's something
I really need to ask you, Mu-hee.
I, uh…
We're here!
My next gig is right next door.
Since we have a lot of stuff,
we had to drive over.
Oh, let me tell you why
I came to see you today.
Sure.
The day we met in Kamakura, can you, uh…
- Let's go. We're really late.
- Ms. Cha Mu-hee has arrived.
Sorry, that other interview went over,
so I need to go.
Could you wait? It'll take two hours.
Would that be okay for you
to hang around for a while?
I'm so sorry.
Can you give us one more minute?
Seriously? You're 40 minutes late.
- Ah, okay. I'll stand by.
- Gosh, I'm really sorry.
Yes, we'll head right up
to the green room.
It's a talk show hosted by Jun Hyun-moo.
You can watch from the set.
I'll let Yong-u know.
- Nice to meet you.
- Good to see you.
Ah.
She'll come out from there.
You can just stay here and watch.
Ah, sure. Thanks.
Uh, yes, hello?
Oh, that day? Uh, excuse me for a moment.
Okay.
I don't think that day will work.
Sorry. Yeah.
Yong-u, are you there?
Yong-u, were you able
to bring Mr. Joo Ho-jin in?
Yong-u? Hello? Huh?
He seems to have disappeared again.
Mu-hee, who was that guy
in the van with you?
Was he the interpreter from the interview
you did before this one?
Yes, but I met him in Japan. Very briefly.
When I heard his voice from behind,
I got startled,
and my heart started racing.
Mm-hmm. That makes sense. I saw your face.
I thought you had
quite a funny expression, if I may say so!
I keep having memories of us together.
I even thought about trying to find him.
We had an odd connection,
and meeting today like this
makes me giddy.
Do you think this job is just
an excuse, and he just came to see you?
I can't believe that.
Mm, he's very good-looking,
and he has a nice voice.
Did you notice his eyes
and his smile? OMG!
He had dimples when he said,
"Ms. Cha Mu-hee." Am I right?
He's really smart and has good manners.
Tell me more.
What exactly happened
between you two in Japan?
The short answer is nothing.
You said there's a connection.
He wouldn't have bothered otherwise.
You can tell us the truth. We need to know
if there was some action or not?
Hey, why's your face so red?
It got flushed all of a sudden.
- It's hot in here. That's all.
- Your cheeks are on fire!
She woke up from a coma
to find out she's become a global star.
Our guest for today is top actress
Ms. Cha Mu-hee,
better known as Do Ra-mi.
Welcome. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
You're in high demand.
It's almost impossible to book you.
- Thanks for joining me today.
- Thank you for having me.
Of course.
You became a global sensation overnight.
It must have been shocking.
Do you get recognized everywhere now?
No, not at all. It's not what you'd think.
I don't get recognized when I'm out.
What makes me the character
requires a lot of makeup.
- Do Ra-mi has a very dramatic look, so…
- Oh, uh-huh.
Then you should walk around
with white powder on your face.
You really should.
You know, lots of people
would recognize you, then.
Here's a discussion
we really have to have.
You were filming when you had a fall
during the last day of the movie, right?
What happened?
On the last day of filming,
I performed a scene
when the stunt wire got disconnected,
and I fell.
It was an accident,
but I was in a coma for about six months.
Oh dear.
It felt like that entire time
I was sleeping.
I had closed my eyes.
And when I woke up,
it was as if I had a long dream.
Now, many things are different.
- So much has changed.
- What a story.
Excuse me.
Uh, hi there.
Do you know where Cha Mu-hee is?
Well, since the shoot's over now,
I guess she already left.
She left already?
- Ms. Cha Mu-hee?
- Let's get out of here.
I'm sorry I kept you waiting.
It must've been boring.
No, it was actually fun.
I had no idea so many people work on set.
There's even more for movies.
Just in case, is it okay for you
to walk around like this?
Uh, no one really recognizes
Cha Mu-hee yet.
If I say "Do Ra-mi," they'll know.
Are you cold? That coat isn't warm, is it?
It's a new collection
that hasn't hit the stores yet.
They sent it to me in advance
so I'd wear it, even if I freeze to death.
Ah, marketing.
You're a walking mannequin.
Well, I'll take that. It's all so new.
You've had a long day.
We'll wrap this up quickly so you can go.
Sure, although
I would love to eat something.
Can we go and grab some good food?
Grab food to eat together?
We were on our way to have a yummy meal,
but we never got around to it.
I wanna have dinner with you
to make up for it.
All right, then.
It was wrong of me to leave that way.
I'll pay tonight, since I left.
There's a restaurant that's close.
The walk over there will be cold,
so put that on.
Okay, thank you.
Since we have a special guest tonight,
I would like to share this bottle of wine
from my homeland of Italy.
- It's on the house.
- That's not necessary.
We won't be drinking.
We're not planning on staying long.
Thank you for the gesture.
It's up to you.
- Enjoy your dinner.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Are you a lightweight? What's wrong?
No, not at all. I can hold my liquor.
I just don't wanna drink
'cause I don't wanna waste my time.
Yours or mine. You had a busy day,
so we won't be staying long.
Ah.
Oh, you mentioned
that you had something to say, right?
What is it?
Yes, you uploaded the photo
you took in Japan on Instagram, right?
Uh…
Oh. Yes.
You saw the post on Instagram, then?
You need to delete
that picture you uploaded.
What?
The lady from Vogue brought it up,
and everybody saw it.
That's why I… want you to take it down.
Ah, you…
Wait. So,
you took on the translating job today
just so you could tell me
to delete that photo on Instagram?
Yes.
I had no way of meeting you otherwise.
Uh, okay.
You could've asked me right away
when we saw each other
after the first interview.
Oh, I wanted to do that.
You were extremely busy.
I hadn't realized
this was regarding a photo
featured on a social media platform.
I didn't think you'd try to find me
due to Instagram.
Sorry for seeking you out.
However, I never
gave you my permission to post it.
Why would you think that it would be okay
to put it out there?
It didn't even show your full face.
That journalist didn't recognize you,
even though you sat behind me.
Everyone who knows me can tell it's me.
There have been misunderstandings.
Where's my friend?
So many ridiculous misunderstandings.
Delete it right now
so we can get this over with.
I heard you!
I'll delete it for the effort
you went through to find me.
But are you sure you can handle it?
Why is that?
Look.
This one has a million likes
and 60,000 comments, you see.
Now, if I go on and remove it,
questions will naturally come up,
and people will be curious.
You said you hardly use those sites.
Then you don't understand
how social media works.
Deleting and unfollowing
have huge implications.
Delete a post? "They broke up."
People will think
something happened with us.
So, for example, they would think
that the man who dumped you
after your big break was me?
You said people who know you
already think it's you.
It'll cause more unease for you.
You might go down
as the man deleted by Do Ra-mi…
Hang on. Let's not be hasty.
Let me give it more thought.
Could you change the date
that this was shared on?
Can that be, uh…
Can that be done?
Can you do that?
Dumb question.
No one can do that.
But you want it removed due to the date?
Yes. This post was made
without thought or concern.
I don't want anyone to know I was there.
Especially not her.
She must not find out, Mu-hee.
Oh, so that person
who you went to the island for,
she doesn't know you were there?
You didn't meet her that day?
You left me to see her.
I made a point to not go to her.
Wait. You didn't go to see her
when you had a chance?
I guess not.
I guess I'll never change.
And that meal.
That yummy meal was wasted.
Cha Mu-hee, you've changed in many ways.
But I was happy to see you.
It seems like you're in the middle
of your festival, like you wanted.
Thanks a lot.
Well, as you know, we missed out
on that special meal back then,
so you can pay for tonight.
Thanks. This meal was really good.
My van's coming to pick me up.
Do you want a ride?
No, I live in the area.
I prefer to walk any chance I get.
Okay, good night, then.
I just want my scarf.
You won't be cold in the van anyway.
I'm walking home.
Ah!
Did you do the translator gig today
just to see me?
It looks like that photo
might have been an excuse?
Because now I got my big break,
you wanted to say hi,
and were curious to see
what life's like now and how things are?
Ah. You could think of it that way.
It's a bit tiring,
getting famous and stuff.
I got two calls the other day.
It was a childhood friend
I didn't even know,
and the landlady of an apartment
I used to rent years ago.
Isn't that strange?
I did wonder about you,
even though we only ran
into each other once.
Yeah, I get it.
So go ahead and decide what you wanna do
about that photo, and let me know.
Oh, you don't have my number, don't you?
Would you… like to?
I'll contact your manager
and leave you a message.
Hey, please pick up when I call you.
I've called and texted, but you're just
impossible to get a hold of.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'll put your contact info in my phone.
I don't usually pick up calls
from unknown numbers.
You have my business card.
Pick up my calls.
- Sure.
- I'll think about the Instagram post.
Then I'll let your manager know. Okay?
I'll be going, then.
Bye, and best of luck.
Okay, bye.
So how do you know each other?
Oh, he came by the hospital.
Wait. He visited me when I was in a coma?
Yeah.
- Uh, maybe twice or three times?
- Oh, when?
When you were in the room
with seven other people.
I shared a room with seven people?
I thought they put me
in a private one in a nice ward.
Well, actually,
before you blew up as Do Ra-mi,
you were in the standard ward.
Not the best, but not terrible.
The insurance covered your hospital
and caregiver fees,
but the studio and the agency argued
over who was in charge
if you never woke up,
and they threatened to sue each other.
It was a big mess.
I was gonna quit if you hadn't woken up.
The translator gave me his business card,
but I didn't save his number.
Here you go.
There it is.
He knew I was in the hospital, Yong-u?
A bunch of news articles came out
about what happened.
He must have seen them.
But honestly,
public interest faded very quickly,
and no one wrote a follow-up.
I figured he was curious about you
since there was no way to tell
if you were going to make it.
Some people are like that.
I assumed you guys were close.
No, not at all.
I had only met him once before.
I'm glad. It's nice to see you.
I wondered about you, too,
even though we only met once.
Yes. Okay. Let me take a look,
and I'll call you back. Bye.
Now, where did I put that?
If she removes it, it'll create interest?
I'll be the man who got ditched.
The thought of traveling
and meeting a stranger,
someone who's charming and helpful,
it can give me
a hint of the butterflies, yes.
Thanks for coming along and helping me.
- This trip wouldn't be as fun without you.
- Oh, sure.
Yeah, likewise.
This is a lucky charm,
said to connect those who belong together.
If you and I are meant for each other,
we'll meet again someday.
Okay, I'm almost there.
All right, will do. Who is she again,
the one you want me to meet?
Ji-sun!
Thanks!
- Whoa. You look so pretty today.
- I do? Great.
Oh, hey, Ho-jin. Here.
Hi.
Ho-jin.
If I save his number,
Instagram will put him
on my suggested friends list.
If I look through all of the comments…
I could just track and find her.
Who do you wanna find?
Just this girl
whose birthday is on April 8th.
I wanna see how great and amazing
she must be to land such a…
…awesome, kind guy
who's wrapped around her finger now.
Why though?
Did that girl scam Mr. Joo
and take his money or something?
Mr. Joo?
Ah, well,
I address certain people officially,
just to be a bit more professional.
It's just to show respect.
You call me Mu-hee, not Ms. Cha? Why?
Because you and I are close.
Oh, speaking of, he just texted me.
He wants you to delete it.
- There's nothing more? That's all he said?
- Yep.
Please let Ms. Cha Mu-hee know
I prefer to have the photo deleted.
So then, once I delete it, it's over.
Good. She deleted it.
MR. JOO HO-JIN
Did she get worse after
she was transferred to a different room?
I'm worried.
I saw that Ms. Cha Mu-hee
was transferred to another room.
Is she better now?
Why did he have to be so nice to me?
Now I can't forget him.
Shoot, and now
I even memorized his number.
And now, I can't forget it.
Hello?
Oh, yes, hello?
This is Cha Mu-hee calling.
Oh, hello.
I wanted to let you know
that the photo has been deleted.
- It's now off the socials.
- Yes, I saw it.
Ah!
Good. You saw it.
Well, glad you did.
That was quick.
So, uh…
The reason why I also made this call
was to try and…
Well, I just found out, um,
you visited when I was unconscious.
I thought I should call you
to say thank you for that.
I just found her, Mu-hee!
The girl whose birthday is on April 8th.
I went through the comments on his posts,
and I found her.
No way. It's Producer Shin Ji-seon.
She's famous.
You know Producer Shin Ji-seon, right?
Oh, sorry.
Oh, Mr. Joo Ho-jin.
Uh, you didn't happen
to hear that, did you?
You went and looked her up?
You must think I'm a
stalker and a psycho
because I looked her up,
and I wanted to clarify that.
I wanna explain myself,
so I had us drive here.
Thank you for agreeing to see me.
How did you go about finding her?
Well, I, uh…
It's kind of easy to do on the socials.
You know, 'cause everyone leaks
sensitive info online.
We found her when we went through
all the comments
that her friends left her on Insta.
You found her
by going through the social network
of someone you don't even know?
I can't believe you're so curious.
Oh, but…
Well, if you put it that way, I'm…
Yes, it was odd and pretty intrusive.
So, I'm sorry.
Now that you know who she is,
do you wanna know more?
Oh. Uh…
Well, I'd rather not.
I feel embarrassed,
and I wanna go back inside.
So I'd like to stop doing this
if that's okay, Ho-jin,
and go into this cozy car
that's waiting for me.
Thank you.
I also can't guarantee
that I won't be checking out
that girl's Insta account anymore.
I'm a bit nosy. I can't help it.
You're right, okay?
Whatever, Mu-hee.
I shared that story with you,
even though you're… a total stranger.
Everybody's somewhat curious, I guess,
so… you should go.
You were also curious
to find out how I was doing,
even though I'm a stranger to you.
You wanted to know if I was okay
while I was in the hospital, I heard.
So that's why I…
I…
That's why I'm so grateful to you.
So,
I did actually call earlier
to let you know I appreciate
how much you worried while I was sick.
Yet, here I am apologizing
because I was being nosy.
You should head in.
Yeah, as for her Instagram,
I won't… I'll promise
not to check it that much, okay?
I don't believe you.
I know how obsessed you are
with Instagram.
You have zero self-control.
What do you want me to do about it?
Delete my account?
You would do that
with ten million followers?
Well, uh, tell me everything right now,
and I promise I won't stalk her.
And don't ask any questions.
I will not share anything
out here with you,
like why I'm so curious about you
and any of your past girlfriends.
Fine. Let's go talk inside.
We'll satisfy your curiosity,
which you possess
for reasons you can't explain.
At least we'll have heat.
In case you're wondering why I live here,
I'll just tell you now.
This is my house.
I inherited this house
from my grandfather.
Ah.
This is such a huge home.
Don't bother asking how large this is
or how much it's worth.
I wouldn't ask those kinds of questions
because, by looking at this place,
I can tell it's fancy.
Ah, this is nice and hot.
Do you like drinking coffee?
I'll be shooting a coffee ad soon.
Would you like to have some sent to you?
- I get it for free.
- No.
I'll see it and buy it myself. Thanks.
Sure.
Well, do you have
any nieces or nephews or kids?
Kids have become obsessed with Do Ra-mi.
Want signed posters?
I don't have any nieces or nephews.
Ah, you don't have
any kids in your life. Okay.
That's too bad.
I also have Do Ra-mi merch and stuff.
- Do your parents like Do Ra-mi?
- Cha Mu-hee.
I say whatever comes
since this is awkward.
I don't know what to say.
Now that I'm inside,
my feelings are all over, I guess.
You said the thought of meeting someone
on a trip gives you butterflies, right?
I was on a trip when I first met her.
Was it the same place,
that island we went to?
We promised to see each other again,
but we didn't,
and I thought that was the end of things,
but I ran into her again.
She was the… girlfriend of someone close.
Oh. I…
Well, does she still not know
that you have romantic feelings
for her after all?
I hope she doesn't.
I've buried them deep inside.
Oh, but what if
you had gone to see her
on that island for her birthday?
Would… you… have told her
and everything would've changed?
It's a pretty pathetic "what if" scenario.
But I might have.
Then, Mr. Joo Ho-jin…
if on that day
we'd gone for that dinner together
instead of being separated by the train…
would things between us have,
well, uh,
changed too, you think?
The time I met you, I didn't just happen
to accidentally drop by that island.
When that woman asked me
for the island as a present, I have…
I've made it there that day every year.
She's never found out,
and I didn't plan to tell her my feelings.
On that day, though,
I planned to let my feelings go.
Just one day.
So that's why you asked
to have it deleted, I guess.
It showed the date.
To you, it's just a photo
that's like a nice souvenir,
but to me, it's…
it reveals a secret
that no one must find out about.
If we had spent the entire day together
and I hadn't rushed off
to see if I could find her…
I don't think it would have changed
anything between us at all.
It'd be the same.
Ah.
I see.
I went down a rabbit hole on Insta
and stumbled on a tearjerker of a movie
that
I'm not part of.
Cha Mu-hee.
Don't be worried. These aren't tears.
I have a runny nose.
Ah, your nose is running.
It runs when I'm outside in the cold
and then go inside where it's hot.
Ah, I see.
- It's just my nose.
- I understand.
- Why won't it stop?
- Here.
Stupid and silly. That's all.
Nothing to look at.
Ah.
Here. For your trash.
It's okay. I don't wanna leave behind
this snotty piece of tissue.
I want you to know this because
I want to avoid any misunderstandings.
The reason I said all that stuff about
curiosity and the train tracks and all
is so I could make sure you're not,
you know…
Know what, Mu-hee?
I was just a bit curious
whether you had feelings for me.
Maybe I was just concerned.
That's it, really.
Concerned?
I was in an awkward spot.
What if you use that
to coerce me into going out with you?
It's a realistic concern.
I'm a star now.
Well, as you know,
I just became a huge star,
so I can't exactly date or get involved
in a relationship right now. You know?
Ah, I see.
So the way you put it,
I have to understand
that I wish things were different with us.
Okay.
I will never…
ask you
to go out on a date with me.
Even if someone tries to coerce me.
Also, I'll apologize.
If I made you worried
by appearing out of nowhere,
I'm sorry.
We'll promise
to never see each other again.
Does that help reassure you?
About what I said,
I, uh… I'd like to explain.
It's like my runny nose.
I didn't want that. It's…
The things I said meant nothing.
It spilled out 'cause I was uncomfortable.
I'm sorry.
There's no point in apologizing
to someone you'll never meet or see again.
We've told each other
our secrets as strangers.
Let's leave it at that and call it a day.
We don't owe each other anything.
So that's it, I suppose. It's over now.
Um…
So, I guess this is goodbye forever.
All right.
I'll get going.
So long.
Take care, Ho-jin.
I won't ask to walk you out,
but I can still root for you.
Your anticipated festival
has finally arrived.
Congratulations.
I'll be watching from a distance
and cheering you on.
Thank you very much.
Ah, it's started raining.
I guess this is goodbye forever.
It's all right.
Once I close my eyes and open them again,
it'll pass, and I'll be okay.
The globally renowned actors
who delivered outstanding
and passionate performances this year
are about to grace the red carpet
of the Tokyo International Film Festival!
Just now,
Cha Mu-hee, who caused a global sensation
with her role as Do Ra-mi
in the movie The Quiet Woman,
has arrived on the red carpet.
Wake up.
I'll help you.
Let's walk together.
Before the conference begins tomorrow,
there will be a brief meeting
for the professors.
Please interpret at that meeting too.
Sure. I'll meet you in the lobby
tomorrow morning.
Thanks for your hard work today.
Good night.
Cha Mu-hee?
What are you doing here?
Are you okay?
Something's wrong, and I don't know what.
I, uh… Well, I'm going crazy.
My festival is over…
and there's nothing I can do about it.
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?