(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
The grand prize of the National
Children's Essay Competition
went to one of our own.
Please welcome Jeon Yi-gyeong
to the podium
with a warm round of applause.
WITH PASSION HOTTER THAN THE SUN
WE ALL COME TOGETHER
I don't have a dad.
Other families have a dad
but my family is just my mom and me.
But compared to all the dads
my mom is stronger.
We live in a big house.
There's a huge chandelier
in the living room
and Mom always wears
shoes that clack.
If there are no flowers in the house
my mom doesn't go out.
Mom always buys lilies or hydrangeas.
My mom told me
a house is one's face.
It shouldn't be messy.
Mom is so cool.
You could become a writer, Yi-gyeong.
You're a better writer than I am.
If you read every day like I do
you can write better.
Why did you say you don't have a dad?
It's not something to be proud about.
She won an award. Be nice.
Writing is just a hobby.
Don't even dream
of becoming a writer.
You won't get anywhere doing that.
Are you ready?
Smile.
One, two, three.
Let's take one more.
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR AWARD
NATIONAL CHILDREN'S ESSAY COMPETITION
I DON'T HAVE A DAD
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
EPISODE 6
Kidnapping, a vegetative patient,
and murder?
This poor family.
Should they do an exorcism?
EVIDENCE 3
- Is that the weapon?
- Yes.
- Bo-ram.
- Yes?
Stand over here.
Someone was in here.
She came in and got whacked.
She fell on the spot.
Then they hit her one more time.
Where's the building owner?
He's waiting outside.
Let's talk to him.
We meet yet again.
Yes.
From what I heard,
you found her this morning.
- Yes.
- What time was that?
Was it between 7 a.m. and 7:30 a.m.?
Do you have any idea
why Madam Jeon was here?
Not really.
I'm just asking
a few simple questions.
You don't have to worry too much.
If necessary,
we'll investigate at the office.
By any chance, are we the suspects?
Right now, everyone's a suspect.
Oh, yes. That makes sense.
The investigation
will clear everything up.
You have surveillance cameras, right?
- Yes.
- Could I have a look?
Sure.
Is this all you have?
Yes.
Why?
We've been using security cameras
since last night.
We didn't use them before
because we had some issues.
You didn't use them before
but you turned them on last night?
Yes, isn't that fortunate?
We caught the culprit on camera.
Is that the only way in and out?
Yes.
Isn't he the café owner?
I heard he hadn't been around
for a few days.
Yes, that's right.
The part-timer was on his own.
What?
Don't you find it strange?
What's so strange?
Everything that's happening
inside this building.
I wouldn't know.
Mom!
- Yi-gyeong, wait.
- Let go of me!
Yi-gyeong.
Mom!
- Let go of me!
- Yi-gyeong.
Get a hold of yourself.
Seon.
My mom...
What is my mom doing here?
Why is my mom down here?
Yi-gyeong.
Oh, my gosh. Yi-gyeong.
Wake up.
Oh, dear.
Yi-gyeong?
Yi-gyeong, are you all right?
Seon.
Why...
You don't remember?
You passed out.
Su-jong is handling
the funeral arrangements.
There's no rush.
Get some rest.
Seon.
The storage unit.
The storage unit?
The one in your basement.
Oh, that room?
What about it?
Was that always there?
It used to be a cold storage unit.
The freezer system broke down,
so now it's just a storage room.
We keep odd bits and pieces there.
Why do you ask?
Can you help me sit up?
Yes, of course.
Let me help you up.
Ms. Jeon Yi-gyeong.
You need complete rest.
I'm fine.
No, please. Hear me out first.
Did you know?
About my mom?
No, not about that.
About the pregnancy.
What?
Who's pregnant?
We ran a routine blood test
when you came in unconscious.
Are you sure?
We notified our OB-GYN.
A doctor will come to see you.
- Bye, then.
- Thank you.
OUR DEEPEST CONDOLENCES
IN MEMORY OF THE LIFE YOU GAVE
TO BETTER SEJEONG-RO
Yi-gyeong.
You must eat something.
For the baby's sake.
What's wrong?
It's so sour.
Mr. Kim.
I just can't believe it.
How did Mrs. Jeon end up...
She was fine just a few days ago.
It's all so sudden.
Hello.
Yi-gyeong, you have a visitor.
- Your mother...
- I met your mother
before she passed.
I pray she rests in peace
in a better place.
- This way...
- Okay.
POLICY DEPUTY NAM SANG-HO
- Deputy Nam.
- Hi.
Hello.
You can sit over there.
Oh, gosh. We haven't met in a while.
Let me pour you a drink.
You hang out with the likes of him?
You're being a little harsh.
Did you think about it, Mr. Gi?
Yes, I'll follow your lead.
Good, you made the right choice.
Do you know that old man well?
There's a baduk clubhouse
in my building.
He's the owner, a tenant of mine.
We meet every day.
Then you must also know
about his building.
- Hanmaeum Building.
- Yes.
Do you think you could buy it?
Bring me the deed to that building
and I'll give you
an extra ten-percent share.
That would be ten billion won.
If you were to get dividends
on top of that
the total could be larger.
Let's eat.
Oh, dear.
- Did you eat something?
- Yes.
The food here's pretty good.
Funeral hall food isn't usually good.
And the killer?
Well, considering the circumstances
we're pretty sure it's Oh Dong-ki,
the first-floor café owner.
We issued a warrant,
so he'll get caught soon.
And previously
wasn't there something you said
about the place I was locked up
when I got kidnapped?
Like what?
- Coffee grounds.
- What?
We found coffee grounds
on her clothes.
Yes, that makes sense.
Does that mean
the café owner is the kidnapper?
Are the two cases connected?
What a jerk.
Where are you going?
Are you Deputy Nam Sang-ho?
That's right.
I asked you to come give a statement,
but you never responded.
Oh, that was you.
Hang on. Where did you say
you were stationed?
I'm Koh Ju-ran, a detective
at Yongdaemun's Violent Crimes Unit.
You know the late Jung Chang-su,
don't you?
Jung Chang-su?
I found your business card
on Jung Chang-su's dead body.
Almost everyone in the neighborhood
has my business card.
They're as common
as a flyer people hand out.
Don't you have one, Mr. Gi?
- I have it right here.
- Ju-ran.
Come with me.
I do apologize.
- She's a bit too eager.
- Okay.
That's totally fine.
Darn you.
- Su-jong.
- Yes?
- Do you need anything?
- No, we're good.
Okay, I'll bring you some food.
She's a brazen one.
Are Gen Z kids these days
all that rude?
Anyway, Mr. Gi.
Bring me the old man's building.
Do you understand?
Yes.
- I should go.
- Oh, really?
No, don't follow me out.
Goodbye, sir.
- Take care.
- Thank you.
Bye, sir.
You said you didn't know him.
What do you mean?
Deputy Nam.
Do you know Deputy Nam Sang-ho?
No.
Who's he?
LET'S GO TO...
LET'S GO TO OUR BUILDING
RIGHT NOW? AREN'T WE NEEDED HERE?
THE POLICE SUSPECT OH DONG-KI
WHAT IF THEY SEARCH THE RESTROOM?
OKAY
Yi-gyeong asked
about the cold storage?
Yes.
That was the last one.
What exactly did she say?
Did she seem to suspect me or...
Or what?
She may be suspicious of Oh Dong-ki.
I don't know about that.
It didn't sound like that
but she seemed to have
noticed something.
Let's stop and think.
We know for sure
that Oh Dong-ki killed her mom.
Yes.
But what if he's caught?
He'll tell all he knows about us.
- He would.
- Naturally.
Then we can't let him get caught.
- He can't get caught now.
- No.
Should we smuggle Oh Dong-ki
out of the country or something?
- My goodness.
- Hang on.
What number is this?
Pick up and see.
Hello?
It's your fault.
Oh, Dong-ki, hello.
Who is it?
It's me, your landlord.
Did anyone follow you?
No.
Oh, right.
You're not wearing a wire, are you?
We don't have that kind of thing.
We'd also get into serious trouble
if we told the police.
Come in.
The room smells a bit.
Can I open the window?
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, sorry.
Just open the window.
Why act like you're sending a signal?
What signal?
Why are you in black?
We were at the funeral hall.
The woman you attacked died.
You're blaming me?
You asked and I answered.
Whatever. Where's the money?
- Well...
- So...
Police were everywhere
so we couldn't get the cash.
That's your problem!
Bring me money
before I spill the beans!
Keep it down, Mr. Oh.
Listen.
Give us a little more time.
- How much time?
- A week.
Let's just all go down together.
Let's crash and burn.
Okay, fine.
I'll get the cash
as soon as possible, okay?
It's two billion won.
You said one billion.
Look at what you did to my hand.
I deserve double.
Did you get your hand looked at?
It will fester if you don't.
Mr. Oh.
By the way
do you have a plan
once you get the cash?
That's my business.
Are you confident
you won't get caught?
Are you scared that
I'll get caught and start talking?
We trust you.
You remember the video, right?
We're a team.
That's just crap.
Don't you try to screw me over.
Let's pay him off. Set a date.
- What are you doing?
- What?
What's on your mind?
You're thinking about something else.
Well...
The man I sat across from
at Madam Jeon's funeral.
Deputy Nam.
What about him?
The redevelopment project.
From what Deputy Nam told me
if we can buy Mr. Kim's property
we'll get a windfall for real.
What about Oh Dong-ki, then?
What are you even talking about?
I agreed to join the redevelopment
investment company
that Deputy Nam's a part of.
It's 100% guaranteed.
There's no risk
and the rate of return
is over 1,000%.
So instead of paying Oh Dong-ki
you'll buy another property?
Are you insane?
Will paying off Dong-ki
solve all our problems?
What if he takes the cash
only to blackmail us?
He threatened to talk
if we don't pay him.
Will you bury him or something?
Is that what you want?
That's why
I'm trying to discuss it with you.
This is an opportunity
too good to miss.
It's a crisis, not an opportunity.
It could end up ruining our family.
You say you do it for us
but you only think of yourself.
What about Da-rae?
Give up on that deal.
The money we have right now
isn't exactly clean.
Let's live within our means.
Do you think it's worth
staking out this place?
Will Oh Dong-ki come back?
He might have hidden some cash.
Don't you think it's weird?
Forget about Madam Jeon for now.
What was Oh Dong-ki
doing in the basement?
That is weird.
So I did some thinking.
Oh Dong-ki was locked up
in the cold storage.
When the door opened,
he attacked blindly just to get out.
Who locked him up?
His landlord.
You think so as well?
I didn't get it at first
when you suspected Mr. Gi.
Things keep happening around him.
Why do you think Mr. Gi
locked up his tenant?
I don't know.
That's what I can't figure out.
Do you remember the guy we saw
at Madam Jeon's funeral?
Deputy Nam.
Deputy Nam? Who's that?
What happened?
You said his death
was ruled an accident.
They found my business card
on Jung Chang-su's dead body.
Okay?
Do you think all you have to do
is kill someone?
Why don't you go around
announcing what you did?
I apologize.
Does it feel good or bad
to get chewed out
after all that hard work?
But you see
there's always a reason.
You're just not that bright.
All that effort and you're not even
a permanent employee.
When will you earn enough?
Should I make a call
to Real Capital's head office?
To say the kids they sent
are useless?
We won't make the same mistake again.
Couldn't you have done
a better job the first time?
Go see a doctor.
- Thank you.
- You're bleeding.
Take it.
- I apologize.
- You can go.
Do you want me to just kill him now?
Where's the fun in that?
Sorry, I'll see you tomorrow.
You look so relaxed.
Don't you want a shot?
Hwal-sung.
What do you think?
Do you want me to give up as well?
Talk to me.
If only you hadn't made that offer
I wouldn't have come this far.
What now? What should I do?
Why did you cross the line with Seon?
You betrayed your friend
and your wife.
Was that fun?
Do you know Yi-gyeong's pregnant?
Yi-gyeong's pregnant.
You punk.
You're not even human.
What are you, then?
Hwal-sung.
Are you all right?
Tell me.
What kind of human are you?
What do you mean? Are you okay?
Should I tell you?
Seon told me something
when we shared a bed.
She said...
you have no self-confidence.
Because you were born dirt poor.
Give it all up and turn yourself in.
That's the least you can do
to cause those around you less pain.
How can you say that to me?
Hey, you.
Shut that hole of yours.
Why? Are you also going to kill me?
Can you even do it?
Know your place.
You're a big loser.
Look at this punk.
Is that all you've got?
Wait, what?
What are you doing here?
Why did you make the choice?
How did you know I was here?
Do you know what happens
when mice get stressed?
Lock up a mouse in a glass box
and deliver periodic shocks.
It'll sting.
The shock was minor, but over time
it was diagnosed with cancer
due to stress.
What do you mean? What stress?
Now, lock up two mice
in the same glass box
and apply the same amount
of electric shock.
What do you think happened?
Talk to me. Take a guess.
How would I know?
They began to fight one another.
Do you know what's funny?
They grew healthier
as they continued fighting.
Their coat became shinier
and they had a bigger appetite.
Even though it stung
and they got stressed out.
Isn't that interesting?
What part of this
is supposed to be interesting?
"The pain that cannot kill me
only makes me stronger."
Don't you know?
We must be destined to cross paths.
See you around.
What the heck was that?
HANMAEUM BUILDING
Hee-ju.
Oh, my. Sir!
Hello.
I can prepare
the contract right away.
You should sell your building.
Forget it.
Wait, sir.
I'm sorry.
His mind is set on not selling.
LAST WILL
Your mother
left all her assets to you.
This was
the last business
she had been working on.
SEJEONG-RO GLOBAL REDEVELOPMENT
With the change
in the redevelopment zone...
That's enough.
And this.
I'm not so sure what it is.
But your mother said
it was her most cherished item.
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR AWARD
NATIONAL CHILDREN'S ESSAY COMPETITION
I DON'T HAVE A DAD
I don't have a dad.
Other families have a dad
but my family is just my mom and me.
I want to grow up and become a mom.
A mom just like my own.
Why don't we call it a day?
No, we can continue.
I'm fine.
Come on in.
Have a seat.
You're good at finding people, right?
It's my expertise.
Find him.
Who?
Right, that café owner?
Yes.
Things will move much faster
if you bring official documents
with his personal information.
I'll give you a call.
Once I find him,
should I hand him over to the police?
Oh, we do anything
as long as we're paid.
WITH SINCERITY, NOT BURDEN
KINDNESS EVEN TO THOSE IN DEBT
LOAN HEAVEN
What's this?
What? Su-jong.
Wake up!
- What's up?
- Yi-gyeong is calling.
Pick it up.
Hey, Yi-gyeong.
Hello, Seon.
I'm sorry to bother you this late.
You don't have to apologize.
Anyway, what's going on?
It's not a big deal
but I felt bad that the incident
happened at your building.
I was too busy at the funeral
to say that to you.
Don't say that.
You were the one
who suffered the most.
We're sorry for what happened.
Yi-gyeong?
Seon.
Can you help me?
I'm having trouble summarizing this.
What is Yi-gyeong saying?
She hired someone
to find Oh Dong-ki herself.
What's she going to do
after finding him?
Do I have to spell it out for you?
She asked for the document
from our contract with him.
We should hand it over, right?
Are you listening?
- Seon.
- Yes?
Do you also think
I'm a loser?
What are you suddenly talking about?
(What's going on, you two?)
Why aren't you asleep?
(What are you two still doing up?)
Da-rae, Dad and Mom
have too many things on our minds.
(What's bothering you?)
It's tough to say.
You'll know when you're older.
(Right, Yi-gyeong called.)
(She wants to go shopping with me
on the weekend.)
Seon.
Can you trust me just this once?
What do you want to do?
You don't have to worry about it.
I'll make sure
it goes well this time.
I won't seriously break the law.
But why do I feel so anxious?
Seon.
I really want to change.
I will make it happen
and I just need a bit of your help.
You're not someone
who'll change that easily.
What about the money?
Is it ready?
APRIL 3RD
BUGWANG SKY ROAD
Hey.
Let me make this clear again.
If you try to pull any tricks,
I'm going to spill everything.
Seon, I brought the file.
Yes, leave it on the dining table.
Okay, what are you making?
It looks so milky.
That soup is as good as medicine.
The living must go on.
- Have a taste.
- Okay.
It's hot.
Wow, this is so rich.
- It's delicious.
- Is it okay?
All right.
Thank you, Seon.
You didn't have to do this.
You need to eat well
in times like these.
My mom also loved gomtang.
It's good.
Did you bring that thing
I asked you for?
Yes.
Right here.
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD
OH DONG-KI
BUSINESS NAME: CAFÉ JINSIM
NAME: OH DONG-KI
LOAN HEAVEN
AM I GETTING THE DOCUMENTS TODAY?
So, Yi-gyeong.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm not alone anymore.
I'll consider my baby
as the last present from my mom.
I'm going to start over.
If you need help with anything,
just let me know.
Okay.
Anyway, I have a question.
It's about Hanmaeum Building.
SE-YOON BUILDING
UNDER INVESTIGATION
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Hey, Hee-ju.
Hello, Mr. Gi.
I got a call from Hanmaeum Building.
He wants to see you tomorrow.
How did that happen?
I'll explain it to you
when we meet tomorrow.
Please have the contract ready.
Bye.
I'm staying for the night.
May I have Room 605?
It's 50,000 won.
Here.
Hey.
Ju-ran!
SEON
HE JUST LEFT
BELLUNA MOTEL
COME TO BELLUNA MOTEL ON GYEONGWON-RO
VCU YOON BO-RAM
I'M ON MY WAY
I'm the police.
I'm investigating at the moment.
A man wearing a black cap
just went inside, right?
Can you tell me which room he's in?
Room 606.
And let me have the master key.
CAUTION: STAIRCASE
Hey, come to Room 606.
OH DONG-KI
This was Oh Dong-ki's room.
Ju-ran.
I see lots of odd stuff here
like syringes.
APRIL 3RD, 11:30 P.M.
BUGWANG SKY ROAD PARKING LOT
- Bo-ram.
- Yes?
Look at this.
What time is it now?
It's right now.
Sir, to Bugwang Sky Road.
Can you drive quickly?
LOAN HEAVEN
Hello?
You're looking for Oh Dong-ki, right?
WELCOME
PARKING LOT ENTRANCE
Darn it. Why won't he show up?
You don't have a tail, do you?
Then we'll all go down.
I don't.
Let's put an end to this.
Where's the money?
And it's time to stop joking around.
Open it.
Right here? Me?
Yes, right here.
Darn it.
What are you doing, man?
That was easy.
Seriously, man.
Thanks so much
for keeping your promise to the end.
Sure.
Darn it.
These are fake, you bastard!
How dare you deceive me?
LOAN HEAVEN
What's going on?
What is it?
Boys.
I'm sorry,
but why are you doing this to me?
Don't you think we're too late?
Wait!
Just come here!
What the heck is that?
Stop them.
Get him!
Freeze!
Bo-ram.
Do not come near me!
If you do, this punk is going to die!
Drop the gun.
Who do you think you are?
Lower the gun.
I'll shoot if you don't.
I said, lower the gun.
Drop the gun!
Lower the gun, or I will shoot.
What are you doing? Get your gun!
Hello?
Oh Dong-ki died.
He died?
The police fired at him.
The police?
Yes.
I brought two billion won in cash.
Yi-gyeong said
good things about your family.
I see.
Material wealth
does not equal happiness.
Yes, sir.
I just need enough
to look after my family.
Don't you already have that much?
This is my limit.
Your building is the last one, sir.
Do you have the courage to stop?
What do you mean?
Not giving up is one kind of courage
but knowing when to quit is another.
You should remember this
for Da-rae's sake.
Yes, sir.
SELLER: KIM CHUN-GIL
Okay.
BUYER: GI SU-JONG
Keep an eye on Yi-gyeong for me.
She's a special kid to me.
Yes, sir.
Should we head out?
Congratulations!
This is insane! It's 30 billion won!
It's all thanks to you, Hee-ju.
I'll get a bonus, right?
Of course. Let's talk outside.
Da-rae.
You can pick out something better.
It's too expensive.
It's all right.
It's okay.
Excuse me.
Yes?
We'll take this one.
- Yes, I'll be right back.
- Thank you.
(Thank you.)
(Don't mention it.)
- Should we continue?
- Sure.
I got a call from the detective.
The tenant in your building
was the one who kidnapped me.
(Mom, I need to go to the restroom.)
Okay, you should go.
Why do you think he did that?
For money?
I don't know. Well...
These days,
money can make people betray friends
and even kill their family.
All for just 3 billion won?
Don't you find those people pathetic?
Don't betray me, Seon.
I can just give you
three billion won.
Goodness.
It must be your morning sickness.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
You should get
the morning sickness shot.
It even gives you extra nutrition.
Do you know a good place?
I'll hook you up
with a clinic I know.
Go there and ask for Nurse Joo.
She'll put in extra care
since you're my friend.
You're the only one
who looks out for me, Seon.
YEON HWA-JIN INTERNAL MEDICINE
NURSE JOO
Do you like it?
FOR LEASE
CONTACT M&amp;A REALTORS
DEPUTY NAM SANG-HO
Great work.
I knew I had an eye for people.
I'll do even better in the future.
That was an unexpected turn.
Hey.
Are you happy?
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
Take over Pyeongbukgwan.
I want to check
if this is the same drug
they used when I was kidnapped.
What were you two whispering about?
My life is miserable enough as it is.
Stop messing with me.
Aren't you glad I'm awake?
I need your signature
regarding the inheritance.
Are you going to divorce him?
What's wrong with you?
If you do, let's start over together.
If I convince Pyeongbukgwan,
I'm taking half the shares.
Do you have any last words?
The final words you wish
to leave to your family.
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Jennifer Lim