( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(Lee Na Young)
(Jung Eun Chae)
(Lee Chung Ah)
(Honour)
(Supported by the Culture Ministry
and Korea's Creative Content Agency)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were
filmed under production guidelines.)
Ms. Hong Yeon Hee.
I've been waiting for you.
Ra Young.
Where's Ms. Hong Yeon Hee?
You came because of the text?
"Help me."
I'm the one who sent that.
What have you done?
"Okay. I'm sorry."
"I won't do it again."
Okay. I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
That's what you said, Ra
Young. You said it yourself.
That night...
It was a night just like this.
Now I remember it all so vividly.
That night.
The sound of the crickets,
the sound of the wind.
And you...
- Think this nonsense will work?
- Let me go!
Is that why you brazenly
dragged my wife into your scheme?
It's just like back then.
No matter what happens here,
there's no one to help you.
And
you
won't be able to say a word anyway.
You were the same way back then.
Because you were scared?
You kept quiet to cover for your
friends who cracked my head?
No, that wasn't it, Ra Young.
Could you really have reported them?
Did you have the courage
to stand up in court?
Afraid the whole world would
find out what happened to you.
Afraid they would forever
see you as nothing but a victim.
That's what you were afraid of, wasn't it?
You're still afraid, aren't you?
That's not true.
- I'm not...
- What?
Go on. Say it.
Say it, and I'll let you go.
What happened to you that night?
Say it yourself.
Shut it.
Why?
It's not like you're telling the whole world.
After all, I already know everything.
That terrified look on
your face, just like now,
your look of utter despair,
how helpless and pathetic you were.
I saw it all.
You can't do it?
Then why start something you can't finish,
pulling a stunt like this, Ra Young?
You'll never escape
that night. You know why?
Because I can crush you
like this whenever I want!
What's the situation with the Magan Hotel?
Yes, sir. It's been handled.
It's unlikely she'll regain consciousness.
Are you out of your mind?
Leaving just one text,
and going in there alone?
What were you thinking?
Nothing happened.
How are you feeling? Are you okay?
Yes, I've found Ra Young.
How's the victim?
They're saying it was an
overdose. She's in critical condition.
She had cardiac arrest en route.
They said we have to wait and see.
All right. I'll stay and watch over things.
Did you find our guy?
Looks like he slipped
out through a private gate.
There's no CCTV. It seems
he didn't come in that way.
(Episode 8)
So, what do you want to do?
Well, anything that'll cheer us up.
Something to blow off all
this frustration and stress.
Let's go.
This is seriously the
most fun I've ever had.
I had a feeling we'd click.
This is the first time I've
ever been out this late.
And I've never worn
clothes like these before.
So, are you feeling a little better?
Yes.
But it kind of feels like I'm
doing something I shouldn't be.
That's what makes it
fun. It's a thrill, you know?
Hold still.
But is your face really okay?
Yes, it's fine now.
That must have hurt so much.
Who did that to you?
Whoever it was, I'll have
to make them regret it.
Close your eyes.
They'll probably come to regret it bitterly.
Hello?
Sang A?
This is Yoon Ra Young, the
attorney. You remember me, right?
Where are you? Are you still out?
Why? What is it?
Your mom's been hurt.
Don't tell anyone. Just take
a taxi right now. Immediately!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I have to go right now.
I'll call you later.
Don't let anyone know you're here.
And make sure you tell Sang A that too.
I'll keep her out of school for a while.
I'll have someone from my team posted here.
You'll have to stay with them.
It's the only way you are safe.
And here.
Take it.
Thank you.
Promise me.
That you'll bring that jerk down for good.
I will.
I promise.
I overheard you earlier.
About the DNA sample you asked for.
I never would've given it to Park Je Yeol.
Not if I'd known
what Park Je Yeol did to you.
I know.
- Sang A.
- Mom.
What happened to your face?
Did Dad do this?
- I'm okay.
- You call this okay?
If only I hadn't gone out...
It's not your fault.
I'm sorry, Sang A. This will
never happen again. I promise you.
The number you have dialled
is not available. After the beep...
Sang A, it's Dad.
Are you with your mom
right now, by any chance?
I don't know what your mom
told you, but none of it is true.
You know how your mom
is, Sang A. She's not well.
When she gets like this, we're
the ones who have to help her.
You know what I'm saying, right?
(Yoon Ra Young)
It's me.
She's with her mom, and they're safe.
I'll file for a protective
order. For the child too.
I wouldn't try to contact or
approach them if I were you.
How dare you run off with my daughter?
But you know, Ra Young...
You know that's completely useless.
You think the world's
changed a lot, don't you?
But you and I both know it hasn't.
And you haven't changed either.
You know what I mean, don't you?
The one thing I know
is that I'm going to watch you crumble
with my very own eyes.
(Sehan Hospital)
You're here.
How are you feeling?
I feel a bit better than yesterday,
so they moved me here.
Forget the victim for a
second. I'm worried about you.
You know you shouldn't
be pushing yourself like this.
When I think about what
happened to Yoo Jeong,
I can't rest easy.
I'll stay here, so why
don't you get some sleep?
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who did wrong,
but you can't even
bring yourself to hate me.
Right now, just focus on your condition.
I'm going to do my best to do the same.
(Shin Jae)
(Patient Registration and Billing)
Yes, how can I help you?
I'm from the Mujin Police Station.
What room is Lee Da Eun in?
The one who transferred yesterday.
One moment, please.
It says here she's been
transferred to the ICU.
- The ICU?
- Yes.
Okay.
(Intensive Care Unit)
Darn it.
- Seung Jin!
- Hey, Seon Kyu.
What are you doing here?
What do you think?
The captain kept talking about
you running around alone, so I came.
So, the victim is in serious condition?
How bad is it?
It's not looking good.
Is that so?
So what exactly happened?
What's this about a sex trade
app? Break it down for me.
I'll tell you on the way.
Go to the apartment. Stay on high alert.
Yes, ma'am.
This is better, right?
We can't let them get us again.
I did exactly what you said
with the thing you gave me.
The evidence implicating Park Je Yeol
- should all still be on here.
- It's probably password-protected.
I'll start by trying to crack the password.
(Connect alert,
Unauthorized access detected)
(Administration)
(Deleting app)
(Deleted)
Any progress?
You're a feisty one.
What's happening? Is
it being deleted again?
Don't worry. I was prepared for this.
They got me once, but
they won't get me twice.
No matter how they try to
delete it, the data here is safe now.
So don't you worry.
But we do have one problem.
There's a limit on the
number of password attempts.
If we fail too many attempts,
the encryption key gets wiped.
And then we can't decrypt
the data, even if it's still there.
- How many tries do we have left?
- Three more.
This method is too risky, so
I'll try to find another way in.
How am I supposed to take this?
This is a faithful execution
of our contractual obligations.
This suspension of services
without any prior notice?
The security and safety of our members
supersedes all other terms of the contract.
That was the core of
our agreement, after all.
And that's the very reason
you chose to partner with me.
This sounds like a
rather precarious situation.
We're not at a green light,
but it's not a red light either.
Rest assured, and please be patient.
And why should we keep trusting you?
LnJ will never be able to talk.
Because they'll be completely
sunk before they can.
I give you my word.
We'll watch a little while longer.
We'll see if this yellow light turns green,
or red.
No way. Trolls probably just
used the photo maliciously.
But anyone can see that's
a picture of our attorneys.
Morning, everyone.
What's with the long faces?
Did something happen?
Attorney Hwang. You haven't seen it yet?
Seen what?
This...
("Unsolved Murder
Attempt from 20 Years Ago")
("Perpetrator, A Famous Lawyer")
(The unsolved attempted murder
of a KU law student 20 years ago, )
(perpetrator revealed to be
a famous celebrity attorney)
Hello. Hi, everyone.
Hello.
Yes, hello.
(Park Je Yeol)
I gave you plenty of chances.
Now let's see you fall apart.
Into a million pieces, in
front of the entire country.
What should we do?
("Kim Jae Won's Quest," Juvenile gang rape)
We're out of time.
Let's get ready. We're on in ten seconds.
You're here.
Park Je Yeol... He beat us to the punch.
What do you mean?
He exposed us. Our story.
("Unsolved Murder
Attempt from 20 Years Ago")
Our names and photos are
all over the online forums,
and the public is already turning on us.
What do we do?
(Perps of the 2005 murder attempt, )
(are Attorney Yoon Ra Young and...)
Are you asking us to consider
the Juvenile Act's original purpose?
Revision? Rehabilitation?
Preventing stigmatization?
You're aware that since
that law was enacted in 1958,
its age limit was never revised, correct?
Because of a law that reflects
the circumstances of 70 years ago,
the victim will now live 70
years in unending agony.
While the perpetrator
faces no criminal liability,
and is free to live out those
70 years back in society.
Right. The Assembly's discussing
- a bill to lower the age.
- But I have to ask.
Are you in a position to
say that, Attorney Yoon?
Because there are interesting
rumours going around right now.
In 2005.
The attempted murder case of a
Hankuk University male student.
I'm talking about the assailants.
Since this hasn't been confirmed,
we have no comment at this time.
The attorneys are out, so
they are unable to comment.
We'll release an official statement.
How can you write about something
that hasn't been fact-checked?
An official statement
will be released later
I'm not sure what you mean...
And why are you bringing this up now?
("Kim Jae Won's Quest")
You're the assailant, Attorney Yoon.
- Oh, my.
- It was really her?
You, Attorney Yoon, and
your colleagues at LnJ.
The victim was a student in
your department, wasn't he?
Three of you women
ganged up on a classmate.
It took him a full 16 weeks to recover.
His doctor said any later
and he would've died.
And to this day, he
suffers from severe trauma.
How dare you, after all
the lies about that crime,
after facing no legal consequences for it,
become a lawyer with a straight face
and talk about "Protected
Juveniles" and "victims"?
How can you act so
righteous, Attorney Yoon?
- She has a point.
- That's what I'm saying.
That's...
What happened back then...
At the time, I...
You won't be able
to say a word anyway.
You were the same way back then.
Because you were scared?
- I...
- Afraid the whole world
would find out what happened to you.
Afraid they would forever
see you as nothing but a victim.
That's what you were afraid of, wasn't it?
I...
That incident...
The reason I couldn't speak about it...
You'll never escape
that night. You know why?
Because I can crush you
like this whenever I want!
Because I was a victim of sexual assault.
("Kim Jae Won's Quest")
When a friend who came to save
you is dying right before your eyes,
and if you don't defend yourself,
and you know you'll be
killed right then and there,
what would you do? What
if you were me, Attorney?
The perpetrator was
my boyfriend at the time.
He sexually assaulted me and beat me.
And he did the same to my
friends who came to save me.
You should've let the court
decide if it was self-defence.
But what did you do instead?
You hid the truth for 20 years.
Did you ever ask the victim to forgive you?
Aren't you being so shameless,
showing no remorse or regret?
No.
I regret it immensely.
I should've told the world sooner.
I should've been braver, not afraid.
So you're admitting it?
That you committed a heinous
crime and hid it all this time?
Because if I had, I could have saved them.
Reporter Lee Jun Hyeok,
killed investigating a sex ring,
Jo Yoo Jeong, framed
for murder and then killed,
and even now, at this very moment,
all the victims being exploited
by that prostitution ring.
- What is she talking about?
- What's she saying?
Wait, prostitution?
What is this all of a sudden?
Are you changing the subject?
There's a secret prostitution
app that caters to the elite.
The app is called Connect In.
And an active prosecutor
is involved in running it.
Right. I want to thank our
guests for joining us today.
Unfortunately, that's all the
time we have for today's show.
Solicitation of murder,
procuring prostitution,
and running a criminal enterprise.
The prosecutor facing these charges
is the man who sexually
assaulted me 20 years ago.
A prosecutor at the
Mujin Prosecutor's Office,
Park Je Yeol.
Wait, a sex offender?
The operators, administrators,
and even the users of Connect In
I call for a swift
investigation into all of them.
Any attempt to cover up
this truth will not be tolerated.
Everyone watching this broadcast right now,
you are all witnesses to this case.
("Kim Jae Won's Quest")
She exposed Connect.
What do we do now?
If she doesn't have proof,
this will blow up in her face.
(Do Jun)
Do Jun.
I think you should come to the apartment.
How much longer do you think it'll be?
I don't know. We only have one shot left.
(System, Password attempts remaining: 1)
("Kim Jae Won's Quest")
You didn't think I had it in me, did you?
Just like 20 years ago.
You thought I'd just run away, didn't you?
Do you have any idea what you've just done?
I know perfectly well.
You were right. You broke me.
But that doesn't mean you beat me.
I think I've changed.
I wonder if the world has too.
("Kim Jae Won's Quest")
(System, Password attempts remaining: 1)
The illegal prostitution app?
So we just have to get in, right?
We only have one attempt left.
Let me take a look.
Yes, sure.
(System, Password attempts remaining: 1)
(Decryption pipeline)
So? Think you can crack it?
Yes. It's not like I have a choice.
(Decryption pipeline)
Even for Baek Tae Joo,
this is going to be tough.
It looks like the server is
blocking access to the app entirely.
If we fail just one more time,
it'll really be game over.
The usual way won't work.
We need another solution, fast.
I think I'm in.
What? No way...
(Authentication complete,
Password unlocked)
- Where is Lee Da Eun?
- In that room.
Da Eun?
My name is Hwang
Hyeon Jin. I'm an attorney.
Can you hear me?
No, that's impossible.
I've been stuck on this for days.
No, I'm telling you, with
conventional methods,
it's impossible to get in.
Exactly. That's why
I modified the attempt counter
and the device block check routines,
then repackaged it to
bypass the authentication.
You did all that just now?
How did you even test that?
- Mind if I take a look?
- Yes, of course. Go ahead.
So, did that help?
I don't really do regrets.
Rather than dwelling on the past,
I'd rather take a single step forward.
But I think I would've regretted it
if I hadn't taken your hand.
See? I told you.
That we'd make a great team.
You're back?
I told them.
I told them everything.
It took me way too long, but
I finally did it.
Did you put up a good fight?
This is for
the 21-year-old you.
You've been through so much
to get here.
What are people saying?
So now,
what's going to happen?
Whatever the outcome,
we'll face it together.
You know that, right?
Today, let's not look anything up,
and try not to think about it.
(Incoming call)
Yes, hello?
(We're rooting for you, Attorney.)
What is all this?
Look.
Attorney, it's me, Han Yu
Jin. You remember me, right?
I was only able to take the stand
because you stood by
me and gave me courage.
Now I'm returning that courage to you.
All of this
is from our clients?
Looks like broadcast viewers sent them too.
I've gotten more than my
fair share of funeral wreaths,
but this is a first for us.
I did some digging on my way over,
and all the talk about us
online has completely vanished.
Everyone's going crazy over
Connect and Park Je Yeol.
The stage is perfectly set.
Then it's time to bring out the guillotine.
(The people's police:
Here to serve and protect)
The evidence is ready.
You can't trust the cops.
Or anyone. You know that.
Come alone, and be discreet.
Got it. I'm on my way.
Hey.
Where are you off to?
Hello?
The admin account access logs
and server logs were also there.
We also found financial details
and orders to procure victims.
This is more than enough
evidence to put Park Je Yeol away.
Solicitation of murder,
solicitation of statutory rape,
money laundering, and
running a criminal enterprise.
He won't be seeing the light
of day for a very long time.
What about the users? Was
their information on there too?
Not for now. It's encrypted.
But once we secure the server,
they say we can trace everyone.
That must be him.
Hello.
I told you to come alone.
Come on, you know.
You know you can trust him.
Hyeon Jin, how have you been?
Are you holding up okay?
Come in.
Thanks.
The evidence?
Right here.
When will the investigation start?
We need to lock him up fast,
- so he can't do anything more.
- Now that we've broken the story,
the police will have to act quickly.
Everybody freeze.
What do you think you're doing?
Have you lost your mind?
You know, right? These
are live rounds. Okay?
Let's do this the easy
way. And no one gets hurt.
Seon Kyu, bring that to me. Come on.
You're sure you won't
regret this, aren't you?
Darn it.
I really don't want to do this either.
But what choice do I have?
This is how it turned out.
Give it to me. Now.
Hurry up!
What do you think you're doing?
Shoot me! Go on, shoot!
Shoot me, or I'll kill you. Shoot!
You jerk...
From the very beginning, you...
(Firearm use permit confirmation,
Name: Kim Seung Jin)
You're arrested for destroying
evidence and aggravated threat.
You have the right to remain
silent, and the right to an attorney.
When you asked me to come with
you, was this your plan all along?
I was hoping it wouldn't come to this.
Seung Jin. You jerk.
Gosh. It's Team Leader Jang. Hold on.
Even when I saw your burner phone,
even when you pulled that stunt
at Lee Seon Hwa's crime scene,
I wanted to believe you.
That I was wrong about you.
- Here he comes!
- He's coming!
Are you being booked for
running the Connect In app?
Police were also
involved in running the app.
Who are the high-ranking officials
who used the prostitution app?
Do you have any comments?
Did you sexually assault
someone 20 years ago?
Prosecutor Park.
I didn't think you were coming in today.
Why? Did I file for a day off?
What's on my schedule today?
What time is the interrogation
for the Mujin-dong case suspect?
- About that...
- You haven't cleared your desk yet?
Isn't anyone going to clean up in here?
Gosh, the stench is so bad
you can smell it from outside.
I knew you were getting reckless.
It seems your final stop...
(Prosecutors' office)
Was here all along.
This is your stop.
The Minister's orders.
Darn it.
Let's get a move on.
(Prosecutor Park Je Yeol)
(Suspension Notice Chief
Prosecutor Park Je Yeol)
(Minister of Justice)
(Minister Oh Yoon)
The number you have dialled
is not available. After the beep...
Sir. We can still get out of this.
The only evidence they have is
the data they pulled from my phone.
If we challenge it as illegally obtained,
it will be ruled inadmissible.
But what if the girls come
forward to testify as victims?
They saw our faces.
The only one they have is
that girl from the Magan Hotel.
And even then, she was drugged
when she was matched with us,
so she won't remember a thing.
You see how quiet the
others are, don't you?
Who's going to step up and talk?
The entire country would
find out what was done to them.
They're probably hiding
somewhere, quiet as mice.
Yes. We also figured
we wouldn't be implicated.
You know how these things go.
People will make some noise for a while,
but they forget all about it
if it doesn't concern them.
If you could just help
us get through this...
No, I think you're misunderstanding me.
You can't dodge the arrow. Nor should you.
What are you...
The arrow's already been fired.
Someone has to take the hit.
I trust you're not foolish enough
to make an enemy of all of us.
It's a shame you're
taking the fall, not LnJ.
What happened to your face?
Are you okay?
It's nothing.
Are you okay, Attorney?
I mean, after the broadcast.
I saw it too.
You weren't surprised?
I didn't mean to expose Connect like that.
It was bound to happen eventually.
And
you heard, didn't you?
Everything else I said on there.
To be honest, it's still
agonizing, and I'm terrified.
If the nation were reading the
diary I planned to take to my grave,
this is what it would feel like.
But you know, Min Seo...
For the past few days, I've
been sleeping so soundly.
For the 1st time in 20 years.
I now realise it's because
I fought for myself.
I was the one who was
hurt. I was the victim.
I deserved respect, to be cared
for and to receive an apology.
But for 20 years, I just abandoned
that wounded part of myself.
All because I was afraid
of what people would think.
So what's your point?
Why are you telling me all this?
I just wanted to tell you, Min Seo.
That even though it's hard and I'm scared,
I feel like I can finally move
on to the next chapter of my life.
What's the point of any of that?
Does that make what
happened to me just go away?
It's the same for you, isn't it, Attorney?
Can you clear all this away and
go sleep in your room right now?
No, you can't. You're too scared
someone might be outside your door.
From there, you have a
clear view of the whole house.
And can you live without
all these extra locks?
Can you leave the house
without your stun gun?
No. I bet you can't, Attorney.
I'm the same way. I'll
have to live like this forever.
Scared, in agony, wanting to
die, and plagued by nightmares.
But at least, we can stop it.
So that others like me won't
suffer nightmares forever.
Unless I can make them suffer
exactly what they did to me...
No...
Unless I can make them suffer even more,
none of it means anything to me.
Thank you for the meal.
Prosecutor Park, tied to the scandal
for running the sex app Connect In,
has appeared at the Mujin
District Prosecutor's Office.
When asked by reporters if
he admits to the allegations,
- Darn.
- He offered no comment and
- entered the office stone-faced.
- The nerve of that guy...
Look at him, waltzing in
with his head held high.
Better get used to it. You'll
be seeing a lot more of that.
How's Da Eun doing?
She's doing much better.
But she can't seem to
remember any of the details.
I was hoping we could
get a lead on the users.
- Yes.
- There's a call for you, Attorney.
Put them through, please.
Attorney Yoon Ra Young, LnJ
Law Firm. How may I help you?
Hello?
I'm calling because I saw you on TV.
I'm
a victim of Connect.
Hello? Are you still there?
Yes. I'm listening. Please, go on.
Attorney Yoon Ra Young?
You've come to the right place.
I know how difficult it must
have been for you to come here.
Thank you for being so brave.
Actually, that time
when you were on TV talking about Connect,
I really struggled with
what to do back then too.
But I was just too scared.
But I realised if I don't do anything,
those people will just keep
doing those horrible things.
I have to stop someone else
from going through the same thing.
That's why I'm here.
Do you happen to remember any of the users?
A face, a name, anything like that.
Those men
were very careful to hide their identities.
I didn't recognise
anyone just by their face,
but I might recognise
them if I saw a picture.
The app's been deleted,
so all I have left is my memory...
Is that enough to make them pay?
Su Eun, your testimony is
powerful evidence on its own.
But to secure a conviction
when other evidence is scarce,
we need consistent testimony
from other victims as well.
So, are there others who have reached out?
A few other victims said they
would come forward, actually.
But no one's shown up yet?
Su Eun.
How long were you
standing outside our office?
About five minutes.
That's common here.
Most people have a hard
time coming in for the first time.
It's only a few steps,
but crossing that threshold
can sometimes take all
the courage a person has.
It's cold out.
Let's wait a little longer. They
might just need more time.
Okay.
Looks like raising all
that hell was worth it.
Come on in.
Attorney, I'm here because
I saw the broadcast.
Me too.
Everyone, thank you so much for coming.
Please, have a seat over here.
Let me make you all a promise.
To protect every one of you,
we will do everything in our power.
(Honour)
A scandal that will shake
the nation to its core.
You think they'll even bat an eye at this?
The green hoodie. Apparently,
they're Han Min Seo's.
Issue an APB. Now!
Do you really think you can
handle making an enemy of us?
I'm not the one who raised the stakes.
I've always been a firm believer
that justice will prevail, ma'am.
- My mom is the one making a move.
- What in the world did they want?
Where are you right now?
- If you want to know, come find me.
- What is this?
- We're with the Joint Task Force.
- You can't come in here.