Make love...
is an action of affirmation to show true love among two people.
I really don't want to go to Penang.
I think I will miss you so much.
Please wait for me,
I will come back and make love to you every night.
The Lord will come home in two days.
Do you remember Tone, Soi's son, who used to work here?
Did you get to meet him?
I hired him to be Shen's personal driver.
You're Lord Sampanpanich's wife and you need something to show, okay?
But your husband is home now, it will get better, right?
But since he got back
he hasn't been the same.
This is Shen, my wife.
Nice to meet you, ma'am.
This is Tone. He will be your personal driver.
What are you doing? Don't do that.
Make love...
You are the one who taught me this.
- When you came back…
- Listen to me!
It's my right.
And we will not talk about this anymore.
Come on, kids.
Soi, where is Tone?
He's sweeping leaves at the back of the house, sir.
- Tone.
- Mr. Perm.
You're back.
How was your trip? Was it fun?
So much fun. Here, I got something for you.
Wow!
Look so yummy.
Thank you, sir.
This one is so good, you should try.
You're right, it's good.
You always bring me gifts from your trip.
It's because you're my friend.
Take a good care of him.
I've raised him for years.
I love him so much.
What about me? Do you love me?
Why did you ask me that?
About last night,
did you really expect me not to ask you anything?
Well, I'm sorry about last night.
Listen, if you want anything,
just let me know. I'll get it for you.
Do you think that what I really want
are things, money and gold?
I really want your love.
Do you think that I don't love you?
I love you in my own way.
You will need to attend a ballroom dance class this afternoon.
There will be a dance party at my boss' palace next month, Prince Pin.
I will take you there.
Okay.
Where do you want me to take the lesson?
Tone knows the address, he will take you this afternoon.
You need a dance partner for the class
so you should dance with him.
I'm busy lately.
Is it okay that Mr. Perm wanted me to be your dance partner?
Well, he needed to work, didn't he?
This is how it has to be.
How are you legs?
Are they still hurt from Khunying's punishment?
Did you put some ointments on?
I'm fine.
I can tolerate wounds on my legs.
Well done. Excellent.
Everyone,
we have new students joining our class today.
They are Shen and Tone.
Shen and Tone,
this is Mr. Suthee, our dance instructor.
You all should take a break
and allow me to give our new students some dance lessons.
Let's start with the beginning lesson.
Can you step closer?
Please take one more step
towards each other, getting closer.
The male needs to show both of his palms up.
Then the female needs to put her palms down on his.
Shen, please hold his hands.
Please do it.
That's it, holding hands like that.
Then the male will start the first step with his left leg.
It will be four steps which are
left-right-left-touch.
The female will need to walk backwards, following these steps
right-left-right-touch.
Then you will repeat the steps back and forth.
Got it? Let's try it first.
I'll start counting to four.
One…two…three. Go!
Step, step, step, touch and four.
Step, step, step and touch.
You need to be more natural.
Don't be too stiff, relax your muscles.
Look into each other's eyes, make eye contact.
You need to look at your partner.
I'll start counting again.
One…two…three, hold hands. Let's do it again.
One…two…three…four. Step.
One…two…three…touch and four. Go!
One…two…three…touch and four.
What were you thinking?
Why did you let your wife take a dance lesson with a driver?
How did you know about this?
Rayrai's friend also took the same class.
Jintana stopped by and hung out with me this afternoon.
Shen needed to take dance classes for prepare for social events.
I was busy
so I asked Tone to be her dance partner. What's wrong with that?
You let your wife hold hands with one of our servants
and you thought that was normal?
Have you ever loved your wife at all?
If she was my wife, I wouldn't let her do that for sure.
Good thing that she wasn't your wife.
I trust both Shen and Tone
so I let them dance together.
What about the others' opinion? What would they think?
Have you ever thought about that?
It could ruin our family's reputation.
Mom, in western culture,
people who are dance partners
don't mean that they are doing some nasty things.
Can you be a little bit more civilized like the rest of the world?
Did you just call me barbaric?
Well, slamming a table during dinner time
doesn't consider as civilized either.
Tone, be honest with me.
Did Mr. Perm really let you take a dance lesson with his wife?
That's right, auntie.
This is strange.
Normally, husbands will be possessive of his wife over thing like this.
In Mr. Perm's case,
he is more open-minded than the ocean.
Mr. Perm said that he trusted his wife and Tone.
Why are you still questioning about this?
- What?
- Yeah.
One more thing,
Mr. Perm loves his wife so much.
You never loved someone, you wouldn't understand.
What? How did you know? Huh?
Tone.
I saw it that when two people were dancing,
they were getting so close like this.
Did you and Ms. Shen get so close like that too?
Shin, can you stop with your disgusting questions?
We were not that close, there is plenty of space between us.
Yeah…right. Plenty of space, huh?
You said it as if there was a huge space between the two of you.
When you danced with Ms. Shen,
did you feel anything?
Shin, you a--hole.
I told you to stop asking me disgusting questions.
This could taint Ms. Shen's reputation.
Fine, whatever you say.
Mr. Perm has always trusted you since you were a kid.
- That was so loud.
- You deserved it.
Tone, you see her?
She is Ms. Daeng, Chaokhun Direk's daughter.
That's right. Can you give her this necklace?
And tell her that it is from me.
You like her, why don't you give it to her yourself?
I'm shy, that's why. Come on, give it to her
before her dad takes her home.
Ms. Daeng,
Mr. Perm asked me to give you the necklace.
It's cute. Please say thank you for me.
Wait.
Can you put it on for me? I can't do it by myself.
Mr. Perm only asked me to give you the necklace.
He didn't tell me to put it on you.
Can you keep me company?
My dad is working and it's taking too long.
I'm sorry.
I can't do more than he asked me to.
Excuse me.
How was it?
She said thank you.
Excellent.
I can trust you with this kind of task.
Don't tell anyone
- that I stole my mom's necklace.
- What?
Honey?
Should we take a dance lesson on weekend?
So I could learn it with you.
What's wrong with learning with Tone?
It seemed inappropriate like what your mom said.
I'm busy.
Just take a lesson with Tone, it should be fine.
Don't skip a class, you need to know how to dance.
There will be good dancers attending the party at Prince Pin's palace.
I will find a seamstress to make you a dress.
Honey?
What now?
Rehearse the dance.
Please rehearse the dance with me.
You need to do it yourself, I already know how to dance.
How was it yesterday? Did you start to know how to dance?
Sure, I did.
Hello, Jintana and Santi.
How are you?
Are you Jintana, Rayrai's friend?
I…that's right.
Rayrai just mentioned you yesterday.
Nice to finally meet you.
Sure.
Since you've known how to move your feet,
he needs to put his hand on your waist.
What did you say?
Put his hand on your waist.
Can't we just hold hands?
It's just a dance lesson, we're not at a party.
We need to rehearse it like we are actually in a party.
If you don't know how to put your hands,
your moves won't look nice.
Let's just try.
Excuse me.
Don't touch me there! I'm ticklish.
I'm sorry.
Then you need to
slowly put your hand on his shoulder like this.
And both of you hold these hands like this.
That's right.
You can't even dance properly by yourself.
Won't you step on people's feet at the party?
I am rehearsing my moves.
I will get better on that day.
It is more than just dancing at the dance party,
but it is a way to socialize for aristocrats.
A clumsy Chinese girl like you,
people will laugh at you at the party for sure.
Aristocrats like to laugh at other people?
Did you talk back to me?
So I would know how to behave.
Ms. Rayrai?
Breakfast is ready.
Ms. Rayrai. Are you okay?
How is she?
Is everything okay?
Are you going to tell them or should I?
Mom, you're about to have a grandchild.
What? Your wife is pregnant?
She is 3-month pregnant.
But it is her first pregnancy so it didn't show much.
Shin, get the orange.
She is pregnant so she must crave something sour.
- Thank you so much.
- No problem.
Excuse me, I need to go and see her.
Sure.
Come on, follow me.
May I?
Perm,
aren't you happy for me?
It is my first child
and the first niece or nephew of this house.
Sure, I'm happy for you.
Excuse me, doctor.
- Okay.
- Chan, give him a ride back.
Right...
I heard that you were back from your official duty in Penang, didn't you?
That's right. I've been back for a while.
My friend is an English doctor,
he also practices in Penang.
His name is Dr. Trevor Smith.
Have you seen him?
I'm not sick, why would I need to go and see him?
I see.
Well, there must be so many Thai government officers working there.
He sent me a letter and told me that
one of his patients was Thai government officer.
I thought that it was you.
It wasn't me.
Did he tell you about the treatment given to them?
He didn't tell me.
It would violate his code of conduct.
We just talked about this and that, nothing in details.
I'm glad that you're healthy.
See you later.
Honey?
Honey!
Should we go and see Rayrai upstairs?
No, but you should go.
Okay.
- Tone.
- Yes, ma'am?
I need something to drink.
Sure.
Thank you.
Ms. Shen, here.
Thanks.
So, are you beginning to like dancing?
What did you say?
You wanted me to teach you English, so I asked
Are you beginning to like dancing?
Yes.
Little.
A little bit.
Bit
The shoulders' length is 14 inches.
The arms' length is 23 inches.
I guess 'fine feathers make fine birds'
can't be applied with everyone.
What do you think of this gown?
Not bad. Is it fit you well?
It's a little tight on my hips,
I need to get it altered.
Why don't you put on your outfit?
We can see if they will go well together.
No need to, I'm too lazy to try it on.
It's not good?
You can order another one.
It's fine.
It tastes good.
Are you okay?
Talk to me.
What?
I said 'Talk...'
to me…'
Talk to me.
You can tell me.
I just feel like
it's hard to have
everything so perfect all the time.
What do you mean by 'everything?'
Everything in this world.
Including people.
Are you talking about Mr. Perm?
I don't know what's going on between both of you,
but I can say that
Mr. Perm loves you so much.
He can do everything in his power to make you happy.
He can't do everything.
If that so, is there anything I can do on his behalf?
You can let me know.
I will do it for you.
There is something you can't do on his behalf.
Let's eat, we have a dancing class to attend.
- Here's some water, ma'am.
- Thanks.
It was such exhausted like crazy today.
But it's crazy fun too.
Ms. Shen.
Should we visit the rice field before going back?
We can rest for a while.
I don't think so.
I'm afraid my husband will be worried about me when he gets home.
But he has a meeting today.
He should be home late.
It's so windy out here.
So much cooler than the weather at home.
What type of dance do you like?
Well, I like…
I like…wal.
Waltz.
What did you say?
Waltz?
Waltz.
What about you?
I like it fast like
swing or guaracha.
Why do you like 'waltz'?
I like 'waltz….'
That's right.
because….
I feel free when I dance.
I feel like I am a bird.
I can fly.
I can fly to any places.
Like that.
I wish I could fly.
Are you okay?
Ms. Shen.
I think you should rest in the cottage.
Easy and slowly.
Be careful.
Please wait a second.
This oil can help with muscle tension.
May I?
Is it hurt?
Just a little bit.
I'm sorry.
Did you carry this type of oil in the car?
That's right, ma'am.
I see that we dance every day,
and we could need it when we have problems with our muscles.
The oil can help releasing muscle tension.
Is it still hurt?
I'm fine.
You said that you was fine
but it was the same tone as when you were hurt.
Where did you learn about the massage?
My mom has muscle problem.
I used to give her massage all the time.
Are you tired?
You can take a nap if you want.
You didn't rest today. I'll prepare you a bed.
There, I'm done.
I should continue my massage.
Are you up?
Yeah.
What did you do? Why did your hair get all wet?
I was sweaty.
I walked to the back of the house and I saw a big jar.
So I took a shower.
I feel so refreshing now.
You should be more careful next time.
How were your feet?
Much better now. Let's go home.
Follow me this way.
Please wait here.
- I will get Ms. Shen for you.
- Okay.
No need to.
Khunying?
Is her gown finished?
That's right. I altered the hips for her.
She will be the most beautiful lady in the party for sure.
- Shin, get the gown.
- Yes, ma'am.
Thank you so much.
I will give it to Shen myself. You can leave now.
It's alright. You can go.
Okay.
Unwrap the gown for me.
Yes, ma'am.
It's beautiful.
But I think it can be even more beautiful than this.
Are you almost done? What took you so long?
Almost done.
This is for you. So you would look more like a lady.
- What is this?
- Just open it.
Is this for me?
You can wear it to the party and blend in with the others.
Come in.
Your gown is here, ma'am.
The seamstress delivered it since morning but Khunying received it for you.
I will put it on.
It will go well with the pearl set you just gave me.
Who received it for her?
Shen! Shen!
Plaikaew said that…
Mother!
What happens, Shen?
I think there is an animal running around in the house.
Look at this.
It bit my gown and it is ruined.
If any of you sees it, you need to hit it hard.
So it won't destroy your belongings or bite anyone.
- Hey!
- Mom!
Look at your wife! She can't talk to me like that.
Mom, she didn't mention anyone.
You're right.
But your gown was ruined already.
I don't think you can attend the party tonight.
Yes, I can.
I still have my gowns in the closet.
What gown?
You have the nice gowns to represent Pipatratsada family as an in-law?
You can see it yourself.
Shen!
Get changed, now!
Your dress is too scandal, like you're going to join a Chinese opera.
I won't let you wear this dress when you're accompanying my son.
This is so embarrassing.
What can we do, Mom?
Her western style gown was completely ruined.
I think she also looks good in this dress.
And you don't have to be embarrassed for me.
I am the one taking her to the party, not you.
Let's go.
Hey!
Mom! Why did you do that?
To protect the family's reputation,
I can be more violent than this.
Don't mind her, let's go.
Perm! Come back here.
Perm!
- To Nimman Palace.
- Got it, sir.
Keep smiling.
He is Prince Pinpreeda, the owner of this palace.
He is the head of commerce ministry, where I work.
We are so grateful for him,
he has taken care of our family, including my father and me.
A lady who is sitting next to him
is his youngest daughter, Khunying Anongnuch.
I will introduce you to him.
Hello, Perm.
Good evening, sir.
Don't be too formal, have a seat.
Is this your wife?
That's right, her name is Shen.
I'd like to introduce her to you, Your Highness.
Shen?
You are good-looking and your dress is pretty.
You picked the right one, well done.
Nuch, you should say hi to her.
You two are the same age, I think.
You shouldn't spend time talking to an old folk like me. Go there.
Find something for your wife to eat and hang out with people your age.
It will be dancing session later.
You can't miss it.
I won't, Your Highness.
You should get to know other people.
You will need to attend the social events all the time.
Got it, honey.
- Perm.
- Hi, Noppon.
Sombat, how long have you been here?
I finished two glasses already.
Why did you just get here?
I was busy helping Shen get ready.
Where are your wives? Are they here?
They're here. They're hanging out in the room over there.
Why don't you bring your wife to meet them?
I will be right back.
Did you see the Chinese girl who accompanied Mr. Perm?
I did.
I thought you invited a dancer from Yaowarat to entertain us.
Hey, they're here.
Hello, ladies.
(In unison) Hello, Perm.
I'd like to introduce your new friend.
This is Shen, she is my wife.
Can you hang out with all of you?
I will be hanging out with the guys.
See you on a dance floor.
Too bad, we have no seat left for you.
Why don't you find a chair?
Or you can sit on the floor.
Come on, Nuch.
I will get a chair for you.
Come here.
Excuse me.
What are your names?
I only know Anongnuch.
Call me by my full name.
M.R. Anongnuch.
I'm sorry.
I'm Sriprapai.
I'm Ornsalao.
Amarapa.
Saraithip.
Chittamas.
Wallapa.
Let's test your skill in Thai.
Can you memorize all of our six names?
Sriprapai, Ornsalao, Amarapa,
Saraithip, Chittamas and Wallapa.
Are you alright?
I am alright. I can drink more.
- Slow down.
- This is our second glass.
Don't forget that we still need to dance.
- How many glasses will we finish.
- I will wait. You go first.
Right, I can't wait.
It is time.
I think you all have already had fun drinking already.
It's time to enjoy the dance floor.
If it's getting late,
I don't think you all could be able to dance.
I still can dance, can't you?
Perm,
can you dance with my daughter on my behalf?
I'm too stiff, I can't dance with her.
Can you take care of her?
With my pleasure, Your Highness.
I feel bad for her.
Her husband didn't even want to dance with her.
She is with her husband but she is left alone.
Honey,
when will you dance with me?
Can't you see that I am dancing with Nuch?
M.R. Anongnuch.
Can I have my husband back?
Hey!
How could you say that to her?
Where are your manners?
You should wait for me outside.
Get out, go.
I'm sorry for her, please don't mind her.
Ms. Shen,
why are you sitting here all by yourself?
What happened?
Talk to me.
I was just bored of this stupid party.
I think you should take me home.
What about Mr. Perm?
He is having fun with his peers inside.
He must have forgotten about me.
Can you take me home?
And you can come back to give him a ride later.
- But I…
- My husband said that
you need to listen to me, didn't he?
You're right.
Ms. Shen.
This is your favorite dance. It's waltz.
Why don't you get back inside and dance for a song?
Mr. Perm could be waiting for you.
We can just dance here.
I am just a driver.
But I want you to know that
I will always be here right by your side.
What happened to you?
I should have invited this unlucky woman into our house.