(Support Admin Watch on www.kissasia.co, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(Previously)
There's one rule of mine you should know.
I don't…
do “seconds.”
but I think it was too fast.
Who told you… that I like him?
Jimmy did.
Did you tell P'Toh that I like Fah?
Something felt off back at the resort.
You started this game, Teh.
Can you drop the…
“no seconds” rule?
But I'm a man of my word.
But every rule…
has an exception.
I want them to have a partner.
May I?
Please don't hurt me.
I would never.
You're too precious...
And yet...
so tempting to break.
Then… break me. I'm yours.
I'll be gentle with you.
"Love Alert"
(Episode 4)
You're cute.
What's that sound?
Just a message.
Who's texting you this early?
It's Jimmy.
Can't we cuddle a bit longer?
I need to step out for a bit.
And I'll give you more than just a hug.
Bastard!
What the hell did you do to my brother?!
Are the photos not clear enough?
Or do you want the full video?
God damn you!
It's good that you're mad, Teh.
Now you know how I felt
when you were screwing Fah next to me.
You stabbed me in the back.
You knew I like Fah, but you still did it.
But this has nothing to do with P'Toh.
I've made it his business now.
Stay away from Fah,
and I'll leave your brother alone.
Even if I leave him,
You'll never have a chance with him anyway.
End it or not?
I won't let you hurt my brother!
I'll stay away from Fah.
You'd better keep your word.
Otherwise, I'll keep using your brother…
until I'm bored.
Then I'll throw him back to you.
My brother is a human being!
How can you be such a cold-blooded...
Son of a bitch!
Stay away from Fah,
and I'll leave your brother alone.
You'd better keep your word.
Otherwise, I'll keep using your brother…
until I'm bored.
Then I'll throw him back to you.
P'Toh, what's that burning smell?
Well, I…
wanted the egg to be crispy.
Can I have mine like that too?
Please?
P'Toh,
what's your secret?
I've never had a fried egg this good.
There's no secret.
I just… want the person
eating it to be happy.
That's why it turned out well.
I see.
You see what?
You wanted me to be happy.
That's why it's so good.
Now that you know.
I hope you'll do the same for me.
Or at least…
please don't hurt me.
Why say that?
Was I too rough on you last night?
You were my first.
P'Toh,
do you know how important a “first” is?
How?
You can have as many people as you want,
But you only ever… have one “first.”
And I'm so glad …
that it was me.
I guess I'm not your first, right?
I don't really care about that.
Because I'd…
rather be your “only one.”
P'Toh,
thanks for everything. For the fried egg…
and for youself.
Anyway, I have to head to class.
Get it over with. I'm gonna be late.
Punch me! Do it if you have the balls!
You bastard!
You're even worse.
I hope this is the last time
I see you near my brother.
I expect the same from you…
Stay away from Fah.
Fine,
I can do it.
Keep your end of the deal too,
or I'll beat you up.
Oh.
If you don't want your brother
suicidal from a broken heart,
you'd better not be all talk.
See you later, “bestie.”
How long have you been standing there?
Oh, Teh. You're home.
Why are you looking at me like that?
P'Toh…
I'm telling you again.
Jimmy's a player who's
incapable of loving anyone.
Why do you keep bringing it up?
I wanna keep reminding you,
so you don't fall for him.
I'm just worried about you.
You've got this, Toh.
Stay strong.
You can make him love you for real.
Then break me. I'm yours.
Fah!
Teh.
It's about our date tonight.
I already booked movie tickets,
but drinks are on you. Deal?
I can't… I have to study.
Oh. What about another day?
But you're paying for tickets and drinks.
Name a day.
I don't know… Maybe after exams.
And when is that?
The professor hasn't announced the dates.
You should invite someone else.
You really want to watch this movie, right?
Do it before it out of theathers.
- But...
- I need to go to class.
Let's talk later.
Fah.
Oh, Jimmy. What's up?
I… accidentally bought
an extra movie ticket.
Everyone's talking about it.
Want to go with me?
I want to see that one.
But… you should find someone else.
Thanks anyway.
Why? You don't want to go with me?
Nope.
I already have someone specific in mind.
Besides, you're a hot shot.
You'll find a date in no time.
You only want Teh, don't you?
Hello?
Mr. Jimmy! Saensee's been hit by a car!
What?!
Jimmy, what happened? Tell me.
Saensee, my cat, he's been hit.
How… is he now?
I don't know. A vet is examining him.
P'Toh, what am I going
to do if he doesn't make it?
P'Toh,
I'm so sorry…
I didn't know who else
to call, so I called you.
It's okay.
Take a deep breath.
Sit down.
Will Saensee be okay?
Take it easy.
Don't worry so much, Jimmy.
The vet said Saensee's going to be fine.
He wasn't hit by the car.
He was just in shock.
He's in good hands tonight. Don't worry.
I know.
I can't help being worried.
We normally cuddle on the bed.
It's just me and him.
Let Saensee cuddle
with the vet for tonight.
If anything happens, the vet's right there.
If Saensee is ready to come home,
I'll go with you and pick him up. Deal?
Thank you so much, P'Toh.
I don't know how to thank you.
I would've been a mess if you weren't…
here by my side.
Don't mention it.
Just let me know if you need anything.
We're not exactly strangers.
Thank you so much.
Mmm, smells so good.
Which one? The cabonara or me?
Both the chef and the meal.
I'm all sweaty. Stop sniffing me.
I don't smell any sweat. You smell nice.
You're teasing me again.
You're just so fun to tease.
I thank you for…
being here with me.
I'll plate this.
Put it on the plates for me.
I need to take this call.
Yes, Teh?
Where are you?
Why aren't you home yet?
Oh, I'm… out with my friend…
Someone who just got back from the US.
What's up?
I'm just worried.
It's already late. When
are you coming back?
Come on, I'm a grown-up.
Let me have some space.
How can I? You'll run into bad people.
By the way…
has Jimmy contacted you?
Ah…
No.
Why?
Nothing.
That's it.
Just get home soon.
Got it, young master.
(Get well soon, Saensee.)
I didn't know I was living in the US.
You heard that?
I thought I was being quiet.
Well…
I lied because I didn't want Teh to worry.
You said you were out with your “friend”…
Stay the night.
So I can hug you in Saensee's stead.
But I...
Please.
- But I...
- Please.
Just one night.
Jim, I must...
P'Toh,
Stay with me.
Jimmy?
When did you get in here?
Just now.
Let me help you wash up.
(Plaifah: You up?)
(Plaifah: I thought you said
you wanted to pursue me?)
(If you've changed your
mind, just be direct about it.)
It's not like I want to quit.
(Read)
What's with him?
He didn't reply.
Did he…
have a fight with P'Toh?
Who's calling?
Oh,
it's Fah.
You're not going to answer him?
He probably called me to ask where I am.
I'm afraid if I keep
lying, Teh will catch on.
He didn't pick up.
You're cute.
You're that scared of your brother.
It's your fault.
You're making me a liar.
Is a lie for your peace of mind…
wrong?
And…
have you ever lied to me?
What would I even have to lie about?
I don't know.
I was… just wondering.
I hope…
you won't hurt me.
Don't be cruel to me.
Hello there! I'm all better now!
Strong and healthy as ever!
Glad to see you're okay, Saensee.
Feeling great and ready to go!
Stay healthy, okay?
There you go, into the bag you go.
Hello?
Got it. I'll be there.
P'Toh,
I have to rush to uni.
Can you take Saensee back to the condo?
Of course.
Stay with mama for now.
Daddy will be home soon.
See you later.
P'Toh didn't come home last night.
Where did you take him?
Saensee got hit by a car and
was admitted. How should I know?
Bull.
Believe what you want.
I need to go check on Saensee now.
Are you sure you're
staying away from P'Toh?
Yeah.
What about you?
Stay away from Fah?
I've stayed away from him.
How's… Saensee?
A vet said it was just shock
and had to stay overnight for observation.
Good.
I'm glad it's nothing serious.
There you are. I've been looking for you.
Are you free, Jimmy?
Come with me for a bit?
Sure thing.
P'Toh…
Has Jimmy contacted you?
Ah…
No.
Why?
(Get well soon, Saensee.)
You're not on my level, Teh.
(Next Episode)
Are you here to spy on me now?
I couldn't get a hold of you.
Don't call me. And don't come
here again for a while.
Are you spacing out?
Don't tell me you miss Jimmy.
Are you in love with Jimmy?
There's really nothing between us, I swear.
It's fine if you don't
want to tell me the truth.