(This drama is a work of fiction.)
(All characters, organizations,
and events in this drama are fictitious.)
(This drama complied
with production guidelines...)
(for filming child actors and animals.)
I don't need anything else.
Just tell me
whether you killed my mom and dad.
Myo Jin!
Do you miss your parents?
Do you need to see blood
before you'll be satisfied?
If you want revenge,
get your head on straight first.
You have a secret too.
I'm sorry. I was selfish.
Your revenge...
No matter what it takes,
get your memories back.
The things I said to you,
no matter how terrible the accident was,
they're not something you can just forget.
(Kidnapping)
Unbelievable.
Hey, hand me that.
This stuff works instantly.
Young Gu, buy this by the box.
Yes, boss.
You can't reach her?
What are you saying?
This is strange.
She's usually home by now.
Since when has her phone been off?
Well, that's...
So you haven't even tried
calling her until now?
Not until I called you?
I'll call her right now.
You're supposed to be
looking after Myo Jin.
Where the hell has your head been?
A person is missing,
and you don't know anything?
This has never happened
to me before either.
Then from now on, make her report
where she is and what she's doing.
She goes wherever she wants
and doesn't answer my calls either.
Why are you only blaming me?
But today isn't a hospital day.
So if she went out anyway,
you should've followed her,
or at least known where she was going.
And if not that,
you should've set a time
for her to come home.
Fine. I get it.
I'll go out right now
and look around town.
Happy?
This is so simple.
What has she been doing until now?
I guess her housekeeper days are over,
because Ryu Jun Ho's going to fire her.
Boss.
That guy over there...
What? Is that the bastard from earlier?
What's that?
Hey, Young Gu.
What's that bastard holding in his hand?
Boss.
It's a hammer.
- What?
- Mr. An, long time no see.
Why are you here?
What?
Are you the boss?
Damn it. Young Gu, go!
Like you said, I didn't kill him.
There's a woman passed out in the car.
What should I do?
Did you do that?
No, boss.
She was like that from the start.
You want to date someone, don't you?
No, sir. She's not my type.
If you've got nothing to do,
load this up, you punk.
Yes, boss.
(Joan Partners Architecture Office)
What brings you here, ma'am?
The CEO.
Sir.
You have a visitor.
What did I tell you to do
when I'm working?
I'm sorry.
Something urgent came up,
so I had to intrude.
Director An?
I thought you were here because
there was an issue with the construction.
You startled me.
The gallery construction is going well,
and you can expect
a more than satisfactory result.
It seems I interrupted your work.
I'm sorry.
My personality can be a bit...
I make mistakes like this sometimes.
Not at all.
I came because I wanted
to ask your advice.
It's about a friend in the same industry.
He has a bit of a problem.
For you to come
all the way here in person,
you must be quite close.
Yes.
We've known each other since college,
so it's been a long time.
He's very reserved,
so I'm worried about him.
Ask me anything.
This friend has
an important presentation...
coming up for a project.
And during preparations,
he got some help from higher-ups.
Quietly.
But the other side found out.
Well, he hasn't told me much,
so I'm not sure,
but it seems like
he's taken some damage too.
He's a close friend,
and he seems to be struggling a lot.
It's hard...
to watch.
I was wondering how I could help,
and I thought I should ask
a respected senior...
in the industry.
It's not a good example,
but the reality is that things like this
often happen in the industry's shadows.
I'm sure you feel awful
because he's your friend,
but it's better not to get involved
in matters like this.
Even if you step in,
it's rare that anything meaningful
comes of it.
Is that so?
Of course.
Your friend made the first risky move.
I don't see any need for you to step in...
and clean it up, Director An.
Frankly, it isn't possible.
The other side...
won't just stupidly sit there
and take it either.
But there's something
my friend doesn't know.
The other side is using
some serious shortcuts too.
He's cozying up
to a four-term assemblyman,
playing golf with him on sunny days,
and even taking on construction
for his daughter's office building.
He's putting in a lot of effort.
With money and favors, quite passionately.
I think I know...
who this friend of yours is.
Mr. Cho.
At this point, would it be better
for everyone to quietly do their own job,
or would it be better to go all out
and have a nasty fight?
I honestly have no idea.
Which would you recommend?
I have an appointment.
I'll be leaving now.
Right.
Please halt the gallery construction.
I'll wire the costs incurred so far
this afternoon.
(Jigu Electronics)
I got all the money,
and I did as much work as she paid for.
Everyone has...
their own life, right?
So stop having pointless thoughts.
Come on.
Right?
Who am I...
to stick my nose into someone else's life?
Well, I'm sure
they'll figure it out themselves.
Don't do it.
It's hot.
Lee Sang Ho.
If I've drawn my gun,
I have to shoot something,
even if it's a rotten pumpkin.
Extortion, threats, fraud,
taking money by force,
and even assaulting a former cop.
Does it make sense
to just leave a guy who did that alone?
(Gi Cheol)
(There's no such thing
as a good rich bastard.)
(Do you think threatening
a corporate chairman is easy?)
(Ham Myo Jin?)
Sir, you trust me, right?
Please don't do this. Think it over.
Now, we just need to get rid...
of that leech, Ham Myo Jin,
who's clinging to Ryu Jun Ho,
before that bitch sucks everything dry.
I'm warning you.
Leave that girl alone.
Ham Myo Jin...
has another agenda too?
(No recording file found)
You scared me.
That startled me.
Are you awake now?
What happened to me?
You don't remember?
You suddenly
disappeared yesterday, Ms. Ham.
It was chaos.
Where were you wandering around
on your own,
without even telling me?
Well...
Luckily, your phone had location tracking,
so Jun Ho barely managed to find you.
Thank goodness that was there.
I'm sorry.
Why did you go
to such a dangerous neighborhood?
It's a redevelopment area,
so it's deserted,
and everyone has already moved away.
I don't remember anything.
Do you really not know...
what you did there?
No.
Then,
I wonder if anyone saw you.
I heard there are still
a few people who haven't moved out.
Jun Ho said so.
Wherever you go, you should contact me,
or at least leave a text.
Jun Ho told me to pack my things
and leave immediately,
but I begged him and barely got past it.
I'm really sorry.
I'm partly at fault too. I left you alone.
Where is Jun Ho now?
Call him.
If he hears you're awake,
he'll come flying over
no matter where he is.
Yes.
Anyway, get some rest.
You need to eat something.
I'll bring something.
Pick up.
- The customer is currently unavailable...
- Damn it.
(Idiot Woo Sik)
Damn it.
Seriously?
Is this bastard
missing a few screws or what?
- The customer is currently unavailable...
- Damn it.
Are you awake, you kidnapper?
You were next anyway.
Wait.
If I did anything wrong to you two...
Hey, if you don't know, how would I?
We don't have time.
Boss.
This bastard...
was getting beaten too much
to understand the situation.
Yes?
Do you know how many Chinese customers...
came to the store today and left?
Those rich Chinese people.
You kicked away a pile of money
that walked in on its own,
and you still call yourself a businessman?
You damn idiot.
I'm truly sorry. I deserve to die.
Please, just spare my life.
Bastards who sell people...
all say the same thing.
So forget it the moment you hear it.
What?
Was it nice
scamming those innocent people?
A useless piece of trash like you...
beat up my brother and stole his money?
Hand over every penny you have...
and leave quietly.
Where did you spend
all the money you made?
You secretly ate it all
behind your partner's back.
Did it fill your belly?
I have something to tell you.
I only did what I was told.
Someone else took all the money.
My bankbook and seal were taken too.
I have nothing.
Bullshit.
Just kill him.
It's true.
I barely make a living running a tiny bar,
but somehow I got mixed up in this,
so that vicious boss takes
every penny I earn.
Your boss must be happy, being rich.
Right?
Even now, my boss is stuck
to some mentally ill woman...
because that woman's husband
is a construction tycoon.
My boss and that husband
are working together...
to get rid of that woman right now.
A rich bastard is trying to kill his wife?
- Yes.
- And your boss is helping him?
My boss is no ordinary villain.
My boss will probably score big from this
and run off overseas.
Then I won't get my money either.
Where is your boss?
You're saying that weasel-like bastard
has Hae Sik's money?
Yes, that's right.
If we meet your boss,
we can get the money right away?
Of course.
If you come with me,
I'll get those two bastards...
to pay your brother's money,
interest, damages,
all of it.
I'll prove what I'm saying
by calling right now.
If even a little bit of it isn't true,
you can do whatever you want
with my money and my body.
I'll even write it in blood.
Do it.
We don't have time.
Whether they answer or not,
you get one call.
You go find a plastic bag.
Yes.
We're going to ruin all our clothes
because of the blood.
Where is it?
Ri A.
What do you think you're doing right now?
Were you hiding somewhere
reflecting for days?
At least you know you should be ashamed.
Hey, enough.
I can't work with you anymore,
so bring back all the money
you took from me.
You must've been pretty shocked.
That's what you get
for not doing as told...
and doing whatever you want.
Shut up and bring me my money.
Money?
You're talking about money?
Because you didn't listen to me,
you haven't even done
one thing right so far.
While I'm asking nicely,
give me back my bankbook and seal.
Bring back all the money
you stole from me, you thieving bitch!
Stop talking bullshit, Woo Sik.
Let me explain it to you again.
You ran away because of gambling debts,
and you only survived because of me.
Hey.
I clearly told you to run.
You ruined everything yourself,
and now you're asking for money?
Your bankbook?
You want your seal back?
What a brilliant move it was
to keep them in my hands.
Your boss is a woman?
Yes.
The history of metal is,
in effect, the history of humankind.
That is an undeniable fact.
Humanity's brilliant achievements...
were possible because metal existed.
Even in this small phone,
there is aluminum, cobalt,
tin, and palladium.
An astonishing number of metals...
are part of our everyday lives.
For this museum,
I want to invite in metal, the outsider.
Metal was once treated as nothing more...
than a structural support for buildings.
The countless people from Korea and abroad
who visit this museum...
have their own cultures and languages.
They are outsiders.
Just as music is a language
that unites the world,
metal has long been
a common language of humankind.
We thought they were different,
but they are not.
The meeting of metal and music...
will create new solidarity and fusion...
with the outsiders who visit this museum.
That is what I firmly believe.
My theme...
is "Strange Yet Familiar."
A museum is not a new space.
People think they know museums well,
even if they are not familiar.
So even without going there,
they believe they know
what will be there...
and what kind of experience awaits.
They see it as a place they can predict.
That place, neither new nor moving,
why do people still visit it?
A space like that called a museum.
Why must we build one again now?
I felt I needed to consider the reason.
Memory!
The memory people will encounter here!
People come here...
to encounter that memory
they want to keep for a lifetime.
In this museum,
the more brightly the memory of every
piece of content they encounter shines,
the more people will return.
That is why a museum must give people...
a good memory they will never forget.
The theme of my work...
is "A Place for Memory."
May I ask you a question?
Is there a memory as powerful
as the one you just described...
that you also carry?
One you'd want to include in this museum.
I'm fine,
so please tell me.
It's not good.
It's terminal pancreatic cancer.
It has already spread
throughout your body,
so surgery would be meaningless.
Is there a reason...
you didn't come to the hospital
until your body got this bad?
I was just busy.
How much time do I have?
Three months at most.
Realistically, it'll be less than that.
I'm sorry to say this,
but to the people you can tell,
it's best to tell them in advance.
With your body in this condition,
we don't know what might happen or when.
So doing that will help you.
Please don't drink alcohol.
You should at least ease the pain
in the time you have left.
You'll need more painkillers.
I'll prescribe them for you.
Since you're giving them anyway,
give me the strong ones.
Plenty of them.
Since I won't be coming to see you again.
(Personal Information - Ryu Jun Ho)
(2022 Founded Mono Architecture)
A scholarship student
in Brown's architecture department,
with a minor in economics.
He came to Korea
and founded Mono Architecture.
Young Architect Award.
He won it two years in a row.
His life is a straight path to success.
He must have nothing to envy.
Sir.
Don't you think this feels
a little too dramatic?
That Ryu Jun Ho left the country...
right before the villa accident?
He was in Germany
on the day of the accident.
There are even immigration records.
What better alibi could there be?
But the chief says we should ignore that.
The chief does have a point.
If those two set their minds to it,
what couldn't they scheme up?
And the woman has ironclad memory loss.
They're untouchable.
Forget that.
Ryu Jun Ho and Ham Myo Jin.
In the middle of all this,
I'm more curious
why those two are living together.
Business partners?
A love story against the world?
They must know staying together
will only make the police more suspicious.
They know that perfectly well.
I don't understand why they're doing this.
Then why are we going
to meet Ryu Jun Ho now?
We have to find out...
whether it's business...
or a love story.
You have arrived at your destination.
Is this it?
That bastard.
I guess he really is loaded.
I know you must be busy.
Thank you for making time.
If I can help, I should.
For the investigation,
I may have to ask you
some uncomfortable questions.
Please understand.
I'll try.
Sir, what do you think
about Ms. Ham's accident,
in terms of the place and time?
Do you think it's something
that could reasonably happen?
I'm curious too...
why Myo Jin was there at that hour.
But we haven't talked about that yet.
She lost her memory in that accident,
and she's receiving treatment.
So I'm worried...
it might give her...
an even greater shock.
Does that mean you'll wait
for her treatment to progress...
before asking her?
The best way...
would be for it to come out
in the police investigation.
That would be the right way, yes.
I'll also need to ask...
a few questions about the villa accident.
You were engaged
to the late Ms. Choi Hee Su quite early.
Hee Su wanted it.
When we first visited your home,
why didn't you mention your relationship
with the late Ms. Choi?
It's something that could
easily cause misunderstandings.
Are you asking
about my private life right now?
That day,
weren't you there
to investigate Myo Jin's accident?
That's true,
but this is a question
I have to ask again now.
Is that so?
Who knows?
If you, detective,
had conducted...
a calmer and more considerate
interview that day,
perhaps...
Hee Su's story might have come up too.
The truth is,
it does bother us quite a bit.
The late Ms. Choi...
and you were in a common-law relationship,
and now, you're living...
with Ms. Ham, who was Ms. Choi's friend.
You may see it that way, detective,
but...
we respected one another's choices...
and sincerely supported each other.
I hope...
you won't look at the three of us
through such a strange lens.
The day of the villa explosion
was a special day, wasn't it?
It was Hee Su's birthday.
And yet you went to Germany.
Coincidentally, the day before
the birthday when the accident happened.
I had no choice
because of a conference schedule.
Even so, how could you...
Detective.
At this point,
I believe I've answered...
enough of the uncomfortable questions
you mentioned.
Didn't you come today...
about Myo Jin's accident investigation?
I'm sorry.
I have an urgent schedule,
so I should get going.
If there's more to discuss,
let's set another date.
Thank you for taking your valuable time.
Please understand
if we bother you a few more times.
It seems you still have
a lot of questions.
Actually,
unlike Chairman Choi Young Ho,
who died in the fire,
Ms. Choi...
was murdered
with a stab wound to the neck.
The villa accident...
was a murder case disguised as a fire.
Murder?
Yes.
That's right.
Are you certain?
Judging by the pattern
of the wound and its depth,
there's a strong possibility
it was a revenge killing.
The National Forensic Service...
is fully reexamining
the materials from the accident scene,
so...
we'll likely identify the suspect soon.
How can someone change that much?
He's completely different
from when we first saw him.
He sees right through us...
like he already knew when we would come...
and what we would ask.
Still, when he heard
Choi Hee Su had been murdered,
he lost it.
I don't think he expected that...
because even his face changed color.
Seeing him today,
I realized he was acting in front of us
when we first saw him.
Isn't that right?
Ham Myo Jin and Ryu Jun Ho.
Maybe both of them were.
Ri A sent this,
saying you absolutely had to see it.
Headquarters...
has contracted with the audit team
of the top company in Korea.
Since it's the vice chairman's order,
we're definitely the target.
This competition.
Do I...
really need it?
It's ridiculous, isn't it?
That I'm thinking like this now.
I believe it's an opportunity
worth staking everything you have on,
and a once-in-a-lifetime chance, sir.
Once this museum is completed,
you'll rise to the top of the industry.
As an architect,
yes, I suppose.
Definitely.
(Wang Gi Cheol)
(Don't let your guard down.)
(They're far smarter than you or me.)
(Approached Choi Hee Su's fiancé
Name, Ryu Jun Ho)
(Chairman Choi Young Ho
funded Ryu Jun Ho's business.)
(Company name, Mono Architecture)
(Using Choi Hee Su and Ryu Jun Ho
to track Chairman Choi's whereabouts)
(Neither of them has noticed.)
(Atibam)
(Atibam Tablet Lorazepam)
(Neuropsychiatric drug)
(Indicated for treating
patients with schizophrenia)
(Clazapam)
(Clazapam Clozapine,
neuropsychiatric drug)
(Panic disorder prevention,
reduced onset of depression)
From now on, I plan to keep
only basic medication treatment...
because despite the test results,
your condition is already
no different from a normal person's.
I'm sure of it.
There's something so huge
behind the Choi Hee Su case...
that everything else can't compare.
That bastard Lee Jong Su...
knows how to stir up Wang Gi Cheol...
and the leverage to extort money
from Chairman Choi.
I need to catch that bastard
who beat the hell out of me,
break him down
and dig out the whole story.
This is the last time.
Just once, and I'll never do it again.
I mean it.
Just once.
(Central Municipal Hospital)
What brings you here?
It isn't visiting hours right now.
Police.
I'm here because there's
something urgent I need to confirm.
Do I need to show you this?
May I see...
patient Lee Jong Su?
Even if you're police, by regulation,
visits without prior notice
aren't allowed.
I'm sorry, but please come back tomorrow.
I see.
There's nothing I can do, then.
Then could you at least
connect me to the officer...
on duty outside his room?
I'll just relay instructions and leave.
Yes.
This is the duty room.
Please connect me to the officer assigned...
to patient Lee Jong Su in Room 8111.
Yes.
Please wait a moment.
You'll be connected shortly.
Thank you.
May I use the restroom?
Great job you guys are doing.
You bastards are slacking off.
You've got it easy, don't you?
Here you are...
What?
Lee Jong Su.
Stop right there.
Damn it, that bastard.
Stop right there!
Is that bastard really a patient?
Stop right there.
Come on.
Got you, you bastard.
You bit me.
You son of a bitch.
Come on.
Should I wait? What do I do?
Damn it.
You there, sir.
Where are you coming from?
Is something going on?
Sir.
Catch him!
Why are you doing this?
Why are you running away?
That man over there is trying to...
You punk.
You're dead today.
There he is. That's him.
You bastard.
Stop right there.
You.
Lee Jong Su.
Stop right there.
What's the reason?
Why are you using Wang Gi Cheol...
to threaten Chairman Choi, Ham Myo Jin,
and Ryu Jun Ho?
If you don't want to eat
prison food for life,
talk right now.
Bullshit.
You're not a cop, are you?
You son of a bitch.
What?
Why are you grabbing me?
I'm not the one you should catch. He is.
I'm telling you, arrest him, not me.
He's the one
who impersonated a police officer.
Arrest him immediately.
He said he would kill me.
Please save me.
Don't worry. You're safe now.
Hey, you idiots.
Can't you see he's putting on a show?
I said he's the one you should arrest.
You must be insane.
Go say that at the police station.
I'll explain everything.
Arrest that guy first, all right?
Arrest me and that guy together.
- Who do you think you're ordering around?
- Let's go to the station together.
- Put him in the car.
- Yes, sir.
It's not me you should arrest.
- Hey, let go!
- Go.
I feel good every time...
because...
you're different from the others.
You seem to have a lot on your mind.
It couldn't have been easy
to come here like this.
After today,
I won't be reachable for a while.
It's because of
the solution I have in mind,
so please understand.
Will you be all right?
They're not easy people,
so things could get ugly.
I have a request.
Yes?
Don't stop...
until I ask you to.
What if...
someone dies?
Then there's nothing we can do.
I told Jun Ho...
that you woke up
and that you're resting now.
Sharp-tongued Ryu Jun Ho said...
that if you don't take your meds properly,
no, that if your condition gets
even slightly worse from now on,
I have to pack my bags immediately.
I'm sorry for putting you
in a difficult position.
It's honestly annoying.
You're probably
the only one in Korea, Ms. Ham.
What do you mean?
Who can make cold-blooded Ryu Jun Ho
smile, be gentle,
and actually care about someone.
Here, take this.
I have to report back.
This isn't what I used to take.
I don't really know.
Jun Ho said the hospital changed
your medication.
He said he went alone
because he thought it'd be hard for you.
Hurry up and take it.
I definitely gave it to you.
I'm telling you, that's not it.
My gut has never been wrong.
Yeah, that's true.
I told you clearly...
that Ham Myo Jin is back to normal.
But isn't it terrifying
that she's pretending she isn't?
Look, you frustrating CEO Ryu Jun Ho.
She must have some scheme.
That's why she's doing it.
You saw that text
and you can still say that?
Hand her over to the police right now.
Use personal protection
or whatever excuse. Just get rid of her.
What kind of trouble are you asking for...
sticking with that woman?
I'm telling you, I saw it.
Go straight up that way and you'll see it.
A gray two-story house
with a parking lot on the first floor.
What does that boss look like?
(Ri A)
Here.
She's not my type either.
Why are you talking to a photo like that?
Do you know her?
No, sir.
What do we do now?
Have you already forgotten
what we came to do?
I'll be back.
What about her male partner?
What was his name again?
Ryu Jun Ho.
Ryu Jun Ho?
Bring him too.
Why do we need that guy?
If we only bring the woman boss,
and she says he has all the money,
what then?
Understood.
Are you going alone?
Are you coming too, boss?
Should I?
Use that bastard to lure them out
and bring them quietly.
Me?
What are you doing?
Okay.
Hey.
This isn't our neighborhood.
Don't make noise.
I don't do anything
you tell me not to, boss.
Use nice words
and bring that boss of yours out first.
If you try anything funny,
I might kill all of you.
It's her.
She's my type.
If we had time, we could've had
something mutually beneficial.
Consider yourself lucky
and stop selling people.
But...
What?
You little...
Damn it.
Hey.
Did you think...
you'd be safe without killing me?
You annoying bastard.
Why won't you answer your phone?
Are you looking for your lackeys?
Damn it.
You bastard.
Come here.
Get lost.
You bastard.
Let go.
Let go!
Let go of me.
You're dead. Let go!
That dumb bastard.
Why are you running away?
- Let go.
- You're dead.
(Copying)
(Complete)
She's definitely hiding something.
Please listen to me and call the police.
That woman should be...
rotting in a psychiatric hospital
or prison, not in this house.
Wait a second.
After locking me up in this backwater,
aren't you even sorry?
I've spent way more time
with Ham Myo Jin...
than with the man
who's supposed to be my future husband.
(REVERSE)
Are you sure no one saw anything?
Actually...
Anyway, what are you going to do now?
It's my turn to move now.
People like you and me...
are cruel and shameless.
Do you even intend to treat Ms. Ham?
I'll be the judge of Myo Jin.
Did I kill Hee Su?
Have you forgotten...
that I told you not to cross the line?
I'm going to kill...
every last one of them.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)