[If you don't turn yourself in,
your limbs will rot and you'll die]
[All characters and events are fictional,
and any resemblance is coincidental]
[Scenes with children and animals were filmed
safely under professional supervision]
[Law and Order, Positive Change]
You're back. What about your paper?
[With a dream, you can start again]
Thanks to you, it went well.
Did you solve the riddle I gave you?
[Murder: 12+2, Rape: 19, Attempted: 15]
12 plus 2.
That makes 14 murders in total.
Are you saying there are
five more unknown murders?
I knew you'd figure it out, Professor.
I'll admit to all acts related to
the nine cases already known.
And I'll honestly confess the rest as well.
But
only if you tell me something, Professor.
Tell you about what?
About you, Professor.
You said you lost everything.
Tell me exactly what you lost.
For each answer,
one hidden murder.
Fair enough, isn't it?
[Murder: 12+2, Rape: 19, Attempted: 15]
If you're not willing to talk,
I'll take my secret to the grave.
Alright, let's do that.
Now, it's getting interesting.
Start with your side of the story.
What exactly did you lose?
I lost my friend.
You've done a great job.
I knew you'd pull it off, Prosecutor Cha.
[Episode 6]
It's all thanks to you, sir.
Now that we've identified the suspect,
catching him will be easy.
Now I can finally get some peace of mind.
What are you staring at so intently?
Do you see this date?
[December 13, 1987]
That's the day Choi In Sook went missing.
- What?
- When Choi In Sook was murdered,
Ki Beom was with me.
Then why is Park Ae Sook's purse
in the bookstore?
If it was not Lee Ki Beom...
Could it be
Lee Ki Beom's brother?
Hey, what do you mean?
Are you saying
he might not be the real killer?
When Choi In Sook was murdered,
Ki Beom was with me.
[Wedding Reception
December 13, 1987]
Just give me more time.
Look, I've got a press conference
in 10 minutes.
I was about to announce
we've identified the suspect.
Why rush a press conference
like this all of a sudden?
You're the one who wanted to rush this case.
When did I say that?
Anyway, cover this up.
If not... oh, right.
Hasn't your stab wound split open yet?
Should I open it up again for you?
Hey, hey!
Wow, you're really
repaying kindness like this?
Anyway, cover it up!
Just be vague about it, okay?
You're good at that. I'm off!
Cover what up?
Just cover that up!
Hey, Tae Joo!
So what are you going to announce today?
Have you found the serial killer?
We have identified
a prime suspect in the seven murder cases
that have occurred in Kangseng
over the past two years, but...
- "But"?
Is he a prime suspect or not?
Father!
[Bang Kyung Moon Clinic]
Drop by sometime.
This old man gets lonely.
I know you're even busier than I am.
There must be a patient named Lee Ki Hwan.
Let me see the list.
- Just a moment.
- Isn't that Detective Kang?
- Detective?
- Yeah.
The detective in charge of
the serial murders.
Please introduce me to him.
Huh?
[Dr. Jo Yun Seok
from Korea Atomic Energy Research Institute]
I'm Jo Yun Seok.
Please have a seat.
Why is someone from the nuclear
research institute looking for me?
I was hoping to explain some
scientific methods that could help
narrow down the suspects.
Is there such a method?
It's a method called 'radioisotope analysis.'
What can you do with that?
Just like our fingerprints are all different,
the elemental composition of human hair
also varies from person to person.
So you're saying
you can irradiate the suspect's
and the killer's hair,
and based on the elements released,
determine if they're the same person?
Yes, based on the results, we might infer
their occupation or living environment.
Have you ever identified
a suspect using this method?
No.
Has it ever been accepted
as evidence in court?
Well, not yet.
Everything has a first time, doesn't it?
- A first time...
- Today,
the Kangseng Branch
of the Muwon District Prosecutors' Office
announced they have identified
a serial killer behind seven murders of women
over the past two years.
The suspect is a man in his 20s,
surnamed Lee, who lives in Kangseng
and runs a bookstore.
The murder of a middle school girl
on the 22nd
has also been confirmed as his doing.
Looks like you don't need my proposal.
The crime scene is
- That darn lunatic.
- around Jangseong village.
He targeted women who were
usually alone on their way home,
abducted them,
restrained their hands and feet
to prevent resistance,
sexually assaulted them,
and then brutally murdered them.
As the suspect
continues to kill,
the interval between crimes has decreased,
and bodies were also
found around the village...
Mother, please stay strong...
Take it away!
What should I do?
We have clearly classified this case
as a serial murder case,
and will conduct a thorough investigation
to determine the full facts,
ensure such incidents do not happen again,
and remain fully committed
to justice and accountability.
The prosecution has placed the suspect,
Mr. Lee, on a public wanted list
and stated they will do their utmost
to apprehend him quickly.
Thus, attention is now focused on
whether this will bring an end
to the serial murder case
that has left Kangseng in fear
over the past two years.
This has been Reporter Kim Ji Hun from KBS.
It's ginger tea.
The aroma is nice.
What brings you here?
You must be busy with election preparation.
Let's finalize your marriage arrangement
with Chairman Kim soon.
That can wait until after the election.
How do you know
how the election will turn out?
We need to set a date in advance,
so there's no backing out.
So you found the serial killer?
Yes.
You've worked hard.
Father.
Cha Si Young, you...
Detective Kang!
How rude of you! I have a guest here.
I don't have time
to take a number and wait, sir.
Could I borrow Prosecutor Cha?
Alright, I understand.
Let's talk later, okay?
If official business is urgent,
this old man should step aside.
No, Father, you don't have to do that.
- Just a moment...
- You don't need to come out.
Wait.
Have we met somewhere before?
I don't think so.
I must be mistaken.
I'll call you.
Wait, Father...
[An Upright Republic of Korea]
Hey!
What's up with the press conference?
I told you we need to investigate further.
I thought about it too.
The date on that photo of Lee Ki Beom.
It's the date of Choi In Sook's
disappearance, not her death.
The body was too decomposed
to determine the exact time of death.
- What are you saying...
- And also,
like her mother said,
Choi In Sook might have run away.
There are many possibilities.
What's your excuse for this right now?
Why are you being
so unreasonable all of a sudden?
Who's being unreasonable right now?
Is it because of Sun Young?
What do you mean by that?
Sun Young is pregnant
with Lee Ki Beom's child, right?
Jeez... I knew it.
Back at Lee Ki Beom's place,
I wondered if it might be morning sickness.
What is Sun Young going to do now?
Why are you even bringing her up now?
Hey.
You want to save him because he's the father
of your future niece or nephew, don't you?
What are you even talking about?
If not him, then is there
another suspect besides Lee Ki Beom?
That's...
It's certain the suspect is
someone around Lee Ki Beom.
So I'll widen the investigation...
Bring me the real killer!
Bring me evidence and convince me, you punk!
That's the order of things, Tae Joo!
You darn commie punk!
[Capital 1-2]
Spill it quick, you punk!
Let's end this today.
I've treated you nicely all this time.
Let's start again.
Darn it, it's driving me crazy.
I told you to bring him in, not beat him up!
I'm sorry, Prosecutor Cha.
Take that out of his mouth.
Yes, sir!
So, your bookstore has a lot of things?
You heard, right?
What was found in your bookstore?
Communist books were found,
and a victim's purse too.
It's like a treasure trove, huh?
I didn't do anything.
What did you say?
Say that again.
It wasn't me.
He might be telling the truth.
Maybe it's not him!
No,
that can't be.
Look at his eyes!
Do they look like the eyes of a liar?
Jeez, this guy isn't the serial killer.
He's just a commie!
Then who is the suspect, Mr. Cha?
It must be his brother! The bookstore
belongs to his brother, right?
That makes sense.
Good grief, how did your mother
raise her children like this?
One's a serial killer,
and the other's a commie.
In that case, your mother's
the root of it all, you know.
Giving birth to monsters like you...
Shut up! Stop talking nonsense!
Calm down and keep this in mind.
This is how the world
will see your mother from now on.
What are you waiting for?
Why aren't you bringing in his brother?
- Yes, sir!
No, not my brother!
My brother isn't that kind of person!
Then who is it?
Tell me who it is.
Promise me,
if I confess,
you won't touch my family.
This punk is threatening a prosecutor, huh?
Promise me!
You punk.
In return, there's something
you have to promise me too.
[Korea Atomic Energy Research Institute]
Oh, hello.
Welcome.
Sorry,
but to be honest, I didn't come here
because I trust your test.
I came here
simply because I'm at a loss,
hoping I might get lucky and find something.
Yes, I understand what you mean.
This is the suspect's hair.
Please analyze it.
If you look here,
[Radioactive Isotope Analysis Report]
compared to average, titanium, sodium,
and chlorine are significantly higher.
Is there a special reason for that?
High titanium levels would mean
the person has been exposed
to a titanium-rich environment.
He could be a worker in a factory
that handles alloys or welding.
What about sodium and chlorine?
Those are the main components of sweat.
He's likely someone who sweats a lot.
So you're saying the killer could be
a factory worker
who's constantly
drenched in sweat, is that it?
Probably.
[Occupation: factory worker]
Go stay at your parents' for a while.
But will you and your mother be okay?
You know how stubborn my mother is.
She's not the type to
leave Ki Beom alone and go somewhere.
Please take care of her.
Don't worry about us, Ki Hwan.
[Murderer, get out]
[Korean Novel]
[Kangseng Bookstore]
Tae Joo!
Where have you been?
Hurry up and clean this up.
Oh, okay.
I don't know how they found out,
but both the house and bookstore are a mess.
How is your mother doing?
She's been laid up in bed
from the shock, of course.
I told her to stay at a relative's,
but she won't listen.
Lee Ki Hwan isn't type B.
He is type AB.
[Lee Ki Hwan, Type AB]
Ki Hwan, actually...
What is it?
Oh my, you should be careful.
It's just a small cut.
It's not small at all. Jeez.
Hold still. It's bleeding a lot.
- No, I'm fine.
- Press on it.
What are you doing?
What's with that blood?
What is this?
Ji Won, hey!
Ji Won, I'll explain everything.
What were you going to do
with Ki Hwan's blood?
Are you trying to check
his blood type or something?
- This is a misunderstanding.
- Misunderstanding?
Ki Beom wasn't enough, and now it's Ki Hwan?
What's the evidence this time? What is it?
Did you find evidence in the bookstore?
The purse?
Is that it?
You're suspecting me because of that?
Purse? What purse?
Tae Joo, is that true?
So you
really came for that,
to find out my blood type?
You could have just asked. I can tell you.
I'm type AB.
If you don't believe me,
take this and get it tested.
Enough, man.
Yeah, honestly,
I suspected you.
But not anymore, though.
I'm sorry, I'm really...
- Are you okay?
Are you alright?
- Let me see.
- Jeez.
Let me see, hurry.
How did the victim's belonging get here?
Unless someone deliberately placed it here.
I don't know where things went wrong, either.
We need to catch the real killer,
so Ki Beom can clear his name.
That's the situation now.
That punk is definitely close to Ki Beom.
Has Ki Beom been hanging out
with shady people?
Like someone with a criminal record...
No. They are all people
he's known since childhood.
He could be a worker in a factory
that handles alloys or welding.
Any friend working at a factory?
Yeah, there is one.
Why the factory?
Where is it?
Ilwon Industries.
[Testing Facility]
Excuse me, is there a guy named Jung Soo?
Over there.
[Ilwon Industries]
Here it is.
Yes, thank you.
[Lee Jung Soo, Type O]
Type O...
They're here!
What was your motive?
Is it true you chased down and murdered
a schoolgirl who visited the bookstore?
Please move aside.
Are you the real killer
in the serial murder case?
Answer me!
Just say one thing.
He is not saying anything.
Did you get anything?
- No, no...
- Jeez.
How does it feel? Relieving, isn't it?
That's what confession is like.
Detective Kang, good timing.
Lee Ki Beom just confessed to everything.
[Security Interview Room]
What?
Already?
This little rat finally realized
he couldn't escape
and spilled everything right away.
I need to talk to him for a moment.
No way, man.
Just a minute is enough.
Detective Do,
let's step outside for a smoke.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, wait a second.
Ki Beom.
What happened?
It's exactly as you heard.
Was it really you?
Answer me!
Yes.
What?
Why would someone who's been
hiding so desperately
suddenly confess so easily?
In return, there's something
you have to promise me too.
Don't bring up being detained
or anything like that.
I heard evidence was found
at the bookstore, right?
If I kept denying it, my brother
would inevitably be suspected.
How could I
do that to my family?
You care so much about your family,
but you killed victims so brutally?
They all had precious families too.
But they aren't my family.
So you...
So you tried to kill Sun Young too? Huh?
Are you really the Ki Beom I knew?
Darn it!
Tae Joo.
What happened?
What did Ki Beom say?
Ki Beom has confessed.
Did you hit him?
- What?
- You beat a false confession out of him!
Ki Beom was brought in today.
He confessed as soon as he arrived.
That punk... Ki Beom is the killer!
No! It's not true!
He admitted it himself!
He said he did it himself!
You, me, all of us, we've all
been fooled by him this whole time!
Get a grip!
No...
Don't cry. Why are you crying?
No.
- Sun Young.
- No...
I'll find a hospital.
Just get an abortion first.
It's okay.
- Give me a cigarette, please.
- Okay.
[Kangseng Serial Killer Arrested,
Mr. Lee, 20s, Bookstore Owner]
They caught the suspect even before
a special investigation team was formed?
The newly assigned officers are in chaos.
[Prosecutor Cha, second son of Candidate Cha]
They're asking if they should still come.
What is this, all show and no substance?
Hold off the assignments for those
who haven't been dispatched yet,
and form the team as planned with the rest.
What? What are you planning to do?
It'll only take a moment.
I have something important I need to say.
It's no use asking me, Ms. Kang.
What's going on?
I... I have a favor to ask.
[Security Interview Room]
Sun Young.
You have 5 minutes.
I'll be outside.
Thank you.
Ki Beom.
What happened?
I asked the prosecutor in charge.
Sun Young...
Don't get involved with him.
Don't even ask him for favors like this.
Is that what matters right now?
Why did you admit something you didn't do?
That wasn't you!
How can you smile at a time like this?
You still believe me now?
Even when I say I'm a murderer,
you still trust me?
Ki Beom.
We're having a child.
What?
I don't know why you're lying, but...
if you think of our unborn child,
if you're not ashamed before our child,
fight until the end.
Fight
and make sure to come back.
Please stay by our side.
Okay?
Ki Beom.
I'll wait for you.
Sun Young...
Aren't you writing the article?
What?
Excuse me for a moment.
So? What did you do next?
After I followed her,
I threatened her
with a knife.
And then?
I said
I would kill her if she didn't come with me.
Right.
The voice is similar, but I'm not sure.
"The voice is similar"?
That's enough.
Alright, you can take this back now.
Even so, you've had a hard time
coming all this way.
Huh?
This isn't mine.
It must have gotten mixed in by mistake.
Please throw that away.
Excuse me, Ms. Park Ae Sook?
Who are you?
Well...
I'm Seo Ji Won, a reporter
from Kangseng Daily.
Do any of these people look familiar?
I don't recognize any of them.
Who are they?
Let's say they are people who frequented
the bookstore where your purse was found.
Wasn't the suspect already caught?
Doesn't it feel strange?
Your ID was inside the purse.
If I were the culprit,
I think I'd leave that purse
in front of your house, as a warning.
But why did the culprit
leave it at the bookstore?
I tend to be suspicious,
so please understand.
Actually,
I just found this
inside the purse.
[Pig Café]
It's not mine.
[2nd Floor Information]
Dad!
I'm sorry!
Whenever my kid sees an adult man,
he thinks it's his dad.
Hae Jun, let's go.
What are you waiting for? Let's go.
Is Lee Ki Beom's statement almost done?
Yes, would you like to see it?
Why would I?
Did Lee Ki Beom really give this statement?
Yes, why?
It's all information we already know.
And some of it doesn't even match.
What do you mean it doesn't match?
It says he was already wearing a handkerchief
when he abducted Kim Mi Yeon, right?
It doesn't match.
According to Kim Mi Yeon, the suspect
only had his hat pulled low at that time.
He put on the handkerchief afterward,
before attacking Ji Won.
Could he have been confused? Or maybe...
What are you talking about, Ki Beom?
I won't just write down
whatever you tell me anymore.
You punk!
You haven't been beaten lately,
so life feels easy, huh?
Get up!
This is why someone like you
needs to be beaten every day, you punk!
- What are you doing?
- Detective Kang!
Move aside.
Ki Beom!
Darn it.
Are you alright?
Look at me.
- Ki Beom, are you okay?
- Tae Joo.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
What is this?
This...
These aren't fresh wounds
from just yesterday or today.
When did you get these?
You were lying about
losing Lee Ki Beom from the start, right?
You were secretly imprisoning
and interrogating him all along, right?
What does that matter now?
We caught the suspect.
Illegal arrest!
Unlawful confinement and assault!
Any confession obtained that way is invalid!
If Prosecutor Cha finds out
everything you've done...
So that punk ordered it, huh?
What a double celebration this is.
Prosecutor Cha caught a serial killer,
and your approval ratings have risen.
Exactly,
I'm benefiting from this guy too.
When I heard he had been stabbed,
my heart just sank.
Anyway, you really don't hesitate
to do dangerous things.
If anything like this happens again,
I won't let Hee Jin marry you.
Understood.
Oh my, Dad.
I really admire that side of Si Young.
Oh my, you...
Have you no shame,
right in front of Candidate Cha?
No, it's fine.
Hee Jin is such a sweet girl.
Thank you, Father.
"Father"?
That sounds nice.
It would've been nice
if your wife could have joined us.
She's a bit unwell,
but I'm sure she'll be back on her feet soon.
Keeping talent like this only in Kangseng
would be a national loss, don't you think?
Everyone has their purpose, I guess.
Where there's a will, there's a way.
Oh, how about holding the wedding
right after the election?
That would be good.
Please eat.
Once this case is over,
prepare to move up to Seoul.
Pardon?
You just get ready quietly.
Chairman Kim will handle the rest.
The wedding will be held in Seoul anyway,
so he'll naturally hurry it along.
There's no better occasion
to greet people than family events.
And Chairman Kim isn't the type
to miss such opportunities.
Go home.
Aren't you coming in?
Jun Young is probably waiting.
I'm heading to the office.
That guy.
He has good eyes.
He's ambitious and gutsy, but fearless.
If needed, bring him to Seoul and use him.
What are you doing?
My little sister is sick.
Please give us a ride.
- What?
- He's really...
- Go home now! Hurry!
- Just to the hospital.
Please give us a ride just this once.
Aren't you afraid of me?
I'm more afraid of something
happening to my sister.
Your eyes are really...
Your sister has a good older brother.
Father smiled.
Father...
smiled.
Follow me.
Wow, this place is still
exactly the same as before.
Are we the only ones who've changed?
We...
Darn you!
What? Feeling nostalgic?
Want to go back to the old days and fight?
Hey, you punk!
You punk! You deserve a beating.
Darn it!
What are you doing, you punk!
Jeez, stop it! You lunatic!
This is driving me crazy, seriously.
I'd forgotten for a moment
what kind of punk you are.
Honestly,
no matter what kind of punk you were,
I thought I could overlook everything
because you saved Sun Young.
But no.
You're still the same darn punk
you've always been.
You're no different, you punk!
That look in your eyes, huh?
That darn look!
You don't even know your place, you punk!
You can't even tell where you belong
and where you don't.
You don't even know about hierarchy!
How dare you beat a prosecutor!
What, is being a prosecutor
some kind of privilege?
So being a prosecutor gives you
the right to detain and beat people?
Oh, that is what this is about?
Because of Lee Ki Beom!
You're making such a big fuss over just him?
- "Just him"?
- You even admitted that you were wrong!
Well, no matter the means,
this time I'm right.
How come you never learn?
After what happened with Lee Seong Jin,
you still don't get it?
Threatening people, you punk,
assaulting them,
and making them nod out of fear!
Darn it!
Forcing confessions to avoid beating!
How much truth do you think there is
in a forced confession like that?
Release Lee Ki Beom.
Clean up your own mess
while I'm still giving you the chance.
I can't do that.
Fine!
Then I'll do it my way.
You just wait.
I have
learned a lot about you.
Do whatever you want, you punk!
You're late, huh?
You are still up.
Father went straight to Seoul for work.
I'll be staying here for a while.
Do I need to leave?
I thought you felt uncomfortable
in this house.
Good night.
Fine! Then I'll do it my way.
You just wait.
I have
learned a lot about you.
How ridiculous.
What could you possibly do?
[Kangseng Police Station]
Alright.
Good night.
My goodness, looks like
things got pretty intense.
At least you didn't embarrass the police.
Pardon?
Darn it!
So what do you want?
Lee Ki Beom is not the real killer.
He was illegally confined and beaten,
leading to a false confession.
- Any evidence?
- There are signs
of long-term assault on Lee Ki Beom's body.
Come on, not that.
If he's the real killer,
illegal detention and assault aren't issues.
Do you have proof he's not the real killer?
He has a solid alibi
for at least one of the murder dates.
Because he was with me.
Could that one case be a copycat crime?
No.
Because there clearly is a pattern
unique to the killer
that hasn't been revealed to the public.
Okay.
Then your task is clear.
I'll prove the injustices
Lee Ki Beom has suffered
and catch the real killer.
What do you need from me, then?
Please allow Lee Ki Beom
to receive hospital treatment.
Fine.
[Pig Café]
You don't seem like the type to work here.
Not young, either.
What?
Didn't you come
because you heard we were hiring girls?
[Ssanghwa Tea, Honey Tea, Coffee]
I'm not here for a job, but to find someone.
[Seo Ji Won, Kangseng Daily]
Someone? Who?
Anyone who might recognize this purse.
We usually require at least
one coffee order per girl here.
You want one?
Yes, please give me one.
I don't know.
- Two?
- Not coffee.
Do you have ssanghwa tea?
One ssanghwa tea here!
So have you ever seen this purse?
This is the one that man gave me.
Go to the hospital and get treatment first.
Thanks,
Tae Joo.
The killer is someone close to you.
Friend or neighbor,
he's definitely in your circle.
Blood type B, with hands
as delicate as a woman's.
I don't know.
No one comes to mind.
Can't you even remember
where you lost your handkerchief?
I'm sorry.
It's nothing to apologize for,
so don't bow your head.
I'm sorry
for letting you go through
something like that.
That's not
something you should
be apologizing for, either.
Then do you happen to know
where the bathhouse you were held at is?
No. They covered my eyes.
Those darn punks.
We need someone who can testify
that you were illegally detained.
There is.
Someone who will testify.
I was making a delivery, and he
suddenly jumped out. It was a mess.
You can't just suddenly jump out like that!
This is too much.
It's not like you did it on purpose.
I'm sorry about that day.
He must've felt sorry,
so he came by and left it as a gift.
But...
[ID Card, Park Ae Sook]
There was a woman's ID inside.
Do you think I'm some beggar?
How could you give me some secondhand junk?
Take it back!
So I returned it.
Who was that person?
Some guy
[Pig Café]
who works at the farm equipment repair shop.
Im Seok Man.
Seok Man saw me being taken away.
Excuse me, are you Mr. Im Seok Man?
I'm Reporter Seo Ji Won from Kangseng Daily.
I have a few questions to ask you.
Do you have a moment? It won't take long.
Oh, dear.
Oh, are you here for repair?
Is there someone named Im Seok Man here?
Try that store over there.
Okay.
Oh, Seok Man is quite popular.
A young lady came looking for him earlier.
A young lady?
Yeah, she was really pretty.
[Seo Ji Won]
Ouch!
Ji Won!
Hey, Seo Ji Won!
What are you doing, you little punk?
Seo Ji Won, why are you here?
Are you hurt anywhere?
No, it's nothing. It's nothing.
I'm fine, I'm fine. Let go, quickly.
Kang Tae Joo, why do you always
throw punches as soon as you see someone?
- You...
- Hey!
Seok Man was helping me remove the shards.
Come on, there's one more here.
Here, here.
It's almost done.
It's sharp. Please don't touch it.
Oh, this...
Ji Won, don't you recognize me?
I'm Ki Beom's friend.
You're Ki Beom's friend?
You've paid for our drinks a few times.
Oh? Oh yeah, right.
Good to see you!
Ji Won, blood...
Thank you.
So what brings you here, Reporter Seo?
Well...
Probably the same reason
as you, Detective Kang.
- The purse!
- The witness?
The purse?
What witness?
I found this purse.
I didn't know there was an ID inside.
I thought someone had thrown it away.
Then you are the one
who left the purse in the bookstore?
I thought if I left it there,
the owner would be able to find it.
Why would you do that?
You should have just put it back yourself.
I was worried I'd be mistaken for a thief.
This is driving me crazy.
Wait, if this is all true, doesn't that mean
Ki Beom can clear his name?
Right, if this guy just testifies.
You'll testify, right?
Of course I will. It's all because of me.
Right, of course.
Let's go, right away!
Right... right now?
Why? Is that a problem?
Can I finish what I was working on first?
The boss told me to finish it today.
- How long will it take?
- 10 minutes, no...
I can finish it in 5 minutes.
Go ahead then.
- I'll be right back.
- Alright.
This is really good news.
Ki Hwan and Sun Young
can finally breathe easier.
You're right.
Jeez, that kid.
He witnessed Ki Beom
being illegally detained...
He was limping, like he was injured.
I swear it's true!
Hey, Tae Joo! Where are you going?
High titanium levels would mean
the person has been exposed
to a titanium-rich environment.
He could be a worker in a factory
that handles alloys or welding.
What about sodium and chlorine?
Those are the main components of sweat.
He's likely someone who sweats a lot.
The killer could be a factory worker
who's constantly drenched in sweat,
is that it?
Probably.
There you are.
It's all done.
As a police officer, it was my negligence.
I should have realized sooner
that Ki Beom wasn't the real killer.
Right.
Only Ki Beom, who was innocent,
ended up suffering.
Mr. Lee Yong Woo,
don't you feel sorry for Ki Beom?
Why would I?
After all, Mr. Lee Yong Woo, he suffered
because of your crimes, didn't he?
It's not like I was the one
who put him in jail.
You think so?
Then is Ki Beom the friend you said you lost?
I'll tell you that slowly.
By the way, Professor,
could you speak more casually?
You were pretty casual with me back then.
Is it because we haven't seen
each other in decades?
You know me, right?
Are you messing with me?
What are you really up to?
The special investigation team
has found another major suspect.
The suspect is Im Seok Man, right?
I need to check it out.
Im Seok Man is type B.
He's acquainted with Lee Ki Beom?
If he's the real killer,
isn't that good for you too?
I can't lose a friend like that again.
So he was at the scene
of Lee Joo Hee's murder as well?
Seok Man, what are you doing here
at this hour?
I messed everything up.
I...