(Uilhan Brewery)
(1. Malting, 2. Malt milling, 3. Mash tun, 4. Hopping)
(Kim Se Jeong)
(Highly passionate, highly sensitive)
(Lee Jong Won)
(Shin Do Hyun)
(Baek Sung Chul)
(Uilhan Brewery)
(Naro Beer)
(Brewing Love)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Scenes with child actors and animals were filmed...)
(under production guidelines along with experts.)
Beer must be gulped.
Pour me a full glass.
Pour me one.
Do whatever it takes to find it.
No new product is without a flaw.
If we miss out now,
we'll never be able to stop the release.
How...
What do we evaluate?
It's the taste.
It boils down to whether this beer tastes good.
Taste is never absolute.
Why not? Because our tongue is so very sneaky.
The first sip might taste great,
but the second and third, not so much.
That's what we must target.
I like the story.
Select a beer that suits your taste.
Three lines so you can pick the flavour and strength you like.
But now we must think.
Why did large companies only release one line per product?
Wouldn't there be a reason no one did this before?
If all three were to sell equally well,
that would be great.
But that's a delusion.
Do you have to sour the mood like that?
We haven't released the products yet.
It's our job to consider the worst-case scenario.
Isn't that what we're here to do?
You're right. Go on.
If we release multiple products at the same time,
one is bound to sell better than another.
What doesn't sell will become dead stock.
Wouldn't wholesalers only want to buy what sells well?
Who would buy what will become dead stock?
If wholesalers start buying only what sells well,
only that product will reach the shelves.
That means the consumers will only be exposed to...
one of the three products.
How is that different from releasing just one product?
Now do the math.
(Assessment Submission)
What do you think about the new product?
I like it.
All three are of decent quality...
and I think they'll sell well.
I really like the 11 percent one.
I'm not sure about the other two.
They might end up in the warehouse.
Won't that be a headache for your Sales Team?
It would. I feel the headache come on already.
This new release has so many problems.
I don't like it much.
(Economic Assessment)
(Efficiency to cost: 2 out of 5)
I knew it.
I too thought it didn't go down smoothly enough.
It's tasty, but it lacks body.
That's crucial for a beer.
(Taste Assessment)
(Aftertaste and body)
(Taste and aroma)
I got sick after the second glass.
That evil gossip is at it again.
It's too light.
Taste it again.
Seriously.
It's not good enough to release.
(Uilhan Brewery Collaboration Taste Test)
What's the matter with it?
This can't be.
This just can't be.
It can't be.
(Brewing Love)
(Episode 10)
You should've...
done a better job.
If you make something perfect, no one can find fault with it.
You know that anything mediocre...
gets shot right down like your product did today.
The chairman wants to taste the beer tomorrow.
What will he say?
I don't even want to think about it.
The chairman might like it.
I'll stick with what we made.
The chairman will decide.
Goodbye.
We're done for.
Darn it.
Too bad the taste test flopped.
You already decided it's a flop.
It's not over yet.
The chairman will taste the product tomorrow.
Today's assessment was dismal.
The chairman would never like it.
How come you say the exact same thing as my director?
What else could he or would he say?
If you think you've flopped,
it's best to cut the loss and quit.
If you push ahead and end up in the red,
who will take the blame?
Cheer up.
I won't give up yet.
That's not my style.
It's not?
Styles change.
You're still so very confident.
Aren't you too full of yourself?
I'm not full of myself.
I believe in my team's hard work...
and the taste of our beer.
Bye, sir.
Are you all right?
You look like you got chewed out.
Well done, Yong Ju.
It's not over yet. Let's stay strong.
Yes. We won't know until tomorrow.
Let's keep going.
Shall we...
get a drink?
We worked so hard.
Right. We gave up going on dates...
to help develop the beer.
- Who cares about dates? - I care!
Isn't zero points a bit too harsh?
Our Together tastes so good.
Why did it score so poorly?
It feels like it's my fault.
I wasn't a good enough leader.
You never failed to give it your all.
I know that too well.
Together tastes really good.
I can guarantee that.
You're upset.
Both the directors.
They said we'd flopped and that we were done for.
Do you know what the marketing director said?
What did he say?
"You should've done a better job."
How dare he say that?
I got him to approve every single step.
Shouldn't he have done a better job tasting the samples?
He gasped and cheered when he tasted it before,
but now...
I'm dead upset and hurt.
My Yong Ju's upset and hurt.
Together's so good.
I know. You're right.
It's okay.
(Jisang Liquor)
Sir. We held a taste test for the main staff yesterday.
Please refer to the scores.
I'm sorry to say...
the marks aren't that great.
Forget those scores.
What you think is more important, sir.
Brewmaster Yoon Min Ju's new beer.
Aren't you excited about it?
That will do. I'll taste it for myself.
The assessment...
is disastrous.
This means we shouldn't release it.
I'm so nervous.
Honey, hold my hand.
We're at work.
Guys. Will you hold my hand?
- I hope it's going well. - I hope it's going well.
It'll go well.
It will.
Tell me.
Does this beer taste good or not?
It's a yes or no.
Is that a hard question?
Is it too hard to answer?
What does your intuition tell you?
- It's tasty. - It's fantastic.
I think so too.
Then it's only right to go ahead.
Chairman. You're kidding, right?
You saw the scores from the internal assessment.
Yes.
I can't completely ignore the internal assessment.
Let's do this, then.
We did an internal assessment.
Let's do an external assessment.
That's only fair.
- An external assessment? - Yes.
I'll enter it in the international blind beer contest.
If we win, you will release the product immediately.
How's that?
I like that.
A win at the international blind beer contest.
That title is better than any marketing campaign.
Good.
If any of these three win that contest,
we'll release it.
Mr. Yoon. Do you think you can do it?
Of course.
My beer never fails.
And one more thing.
If we win, I'd like full authority until the release...
of the new product.
Yes!
I look forward to it.
You're all here.
- How did it go? - How did it go?
- How did it go? - What did they say?
Calm down, guys. The result is...
- half and half. - Half and half?
We didn't get the clearance to release the beer,
but we still have a shot.
If we win the blind beer-tasting contest.
How can we do that.
That's as good as a no.
- I should type up my resignation. - What was that?
TF Team. Don't you believe in Together?
Right. After all we went through to make it.
- I believe in it. - We'll win.
I'm confident we'll win!
Then to boost our morale,
how about a team dinner?
I thought you hated team dinners.
I love that you suggested it first.
Well...
Sorry but we...
have plans.
What are you doing in front of the others?
We all know you're dating.
They're dating?
You're seriously clueless too.
We have eyes, you know.
I never let it show.
It's obvious even at a glance.
Was I the only one who didn't know?
Come with me. When did you figure it out?
- I could tell right away. - "Right away?"
- Are you really dating? - Well...
- I should go. - Me too.
Wait.
Don't you two have plans?
- We do? - We do?
It looked like you two needed to talk.
Forget it if not.
- Do you have something to say? - What?
I don't.
Do you?
What did Mr. Yoon want us to talk about?
Fried chicken tastes best by the river.
Here.
Leave it.
Why do Koreans love fried chicken so much?
From elementary to high school,
kids never stop talking about it.
"Dad brought fried chicken on the way home."
"Soccer's on today,"
"so I'll ask Mom to order chicken."
"There are two drumsticks..."
"and Mom gave both to my brother."
Even on sports day at school,
they sit around to share a box.
Do you know that...
this is the most shared food among families?
You never had it with your family?
- No. - Not once?
Not once.
I'll do it. I'll be your family.
Ms. Beautiful Bang.
I'll buy you chicken after work,
eat it with you when soccer's on,
and give you both drumsticks.
Like today, let's sit...
by the river and eat it with beer.
Let's do...
everything together.
Look over there.
They're taking wedding photos.
That must be the trend these days.
That has nothing to do with us.
I guess not.
Can I ask you something?
Marriage is your life goal.
Should you give up on it that easily for me?
You could...
meet someone much better.
You're an essential part of my marriage.
I don't know when, but you've become an essential part.
It could've been...
when you lowered the screen on your truck,
when you told me to blow out the birthday candle,
or when you called me "Ms. Beautiful Bang."
I don't know when it was,
but I guess I liked all those moments.
Let me ask you something too.
I keep thinking...
there's another reason you can't get married.
I want to know what that is.
But you won't tell me, will you?
We can never have a full conversation.
Can I go?
I want to...
tell you everything.
I want to come clean to you,
and that's bad.
(Chae Yong Ju, Head of Marketing)
No. Forget it.
(YNWA Swimming Center)
- How do we look? - So beautiful.
This is your final chance to surrender.
- Surrender! - You're surrounded!
Don't shoot me, please. Don't shoot.
Don't shoot.
- Spare me. - You'll be okay. Get down.
No.
Don't shoot.
How did my dear Min Ju know I was here?
Look right here. It says, "If you can't..."
"contact me by midnight, consider me dead and find me here."
I couldn't ignore it when you even sent me the address.
I had to cancel my date to come here, you punk.
My gosh. This guy called me "you punk."
How touching.
How can you joke around right now?
But I was quite serious today.
Remember what you said?
That there would come a day...
I could properly face it.
I almost died facing it.
I thought I was going to die, okay?
Goodness. So why the swimming pool of all places?
Is it because we were in the lows together?
The water calms me down.
It knows every part of me.
People die when they can't breathe.
I can't breathe.
At times, I forget how to breathe.
It's funny, isn't it?
It's not funny.
You're just desperate.
I don't know that past of yours that makes it hard to breathe.
And I won't ask until you tell me about it first.
But don't you like Ms. Bang to the point...
you want to fight against that past?
You know everything.
You seriously do.
- Did you win that fight? - I lost.
And without mercy at that.
I tried to fight it head-on.
Now, I'm too scared to fight it again.
I'm giving up.
It won't do.
A guy who can't breathe getting married is absurd.
I can't become a husband.
I don't even know when I'll get better.
Just imagine me passing out in front of Ms. Beautiful Bang.
No way.
I can't do it.
I'm a man who can't protect his woman.
Seriously.
Chan Hwi. There are no male and female roles in love.
Being handsome, ugly, rich, or poor has nothing to do with love.
Isn't it love when nothing else matters?
When everything is incomprehensible.
Not being able to understand with your head is love.
Isn't that why we say we fell in love?
Don't make me cry.
I must want to marry Ms. Beautiful Bang.
What now?
What? It's Chae Yong Ju.
What brought you here in the morning?
Must I have a reason to come to my boyfriend's house?
No. You're always welcome here.
Because of Oh Chan Hwi, we couldn't have our date yesterday.
Let's have a proper one today.
- All right. - I'm hungry.
- Are you hungry? - Yes.
That's bad. I can't let you starve. Come this way.
(Dried seaweed for gimbap)
How did you know I like gimbap?
What do I not know about Ms. Chae?
Watch from your seat...
how good I am at making gimbap, Ms. Chae.
Yes, sir.
Tasty dried seaweed...
is key in gimbap.
Is that so, chef?
- Yes. - I see.
Don't eat the ingredients.
- How about two rows of ham? - Yes.
Aren't the gimbap ends you get while watching them...
- being made the best? - They are.
Here. Open up.
My granny...
used to feed me gimbap on picnic days.
Is that so? Then I'll feed it to you from now on.
- Have one. - Okay.
Goodness. It's good.
("The Empath's Survival Guide")
Here.
Thanks.
Why do you not ask me about my past?
People were always curious.
How tough life was.
What made me suffer so much.
Isn't such a life normal?
Stuff like that.
To me,
the present is important.
The memories we'll make from now on are much more important.
Neither you nor I can know everything about each other's past.
How lonely it was. How miserable it was.
How can we understand it all?
Simply because we're lovers,
we don't need to know about the pain we barely forgot.
As I used to work in the Special Task Force,
there is loads of confidential information.
What kind of training I went through.
Where our military camp was.
Actually, most of it is confidential.
I can't tell you any of it.
Just like those.
I think everyone lives...
with at least one piece of confidential information.
I won't dare to ask or guess...
about the times...
you've endured.
I will...
only look at Yoon Min Ju before me.
The one who hasn't given up...
and has stubbornly come this far...
after walking through the thorny path.
Right here.
I will only look at Yoon Min Ju right here.
Let's do that, okay?
Okay.
Let's do that.
Shall we get going now?
To where?
A place you'll love.
You helped me find a lot of things I like until now.
It's my turn now to help you.
Gosh, but all I need is you to be by my side.
No. I can't let myself be indebted.
Come on. There's no owing each other when it comes to love.
That's not true. I owe you tons.
Let's go. Get up.
Let's go.
I'd like two as well.
- I want four. - Wait, okay? Give him a break.
- I want four, please. - Good grief.
- Hold back a little. - Can you finish them all?
- I totally can. - What is wrong with her?
This is the rumoured must-eat place.
- I know. - It sure is delicious.
Gosh, it looks good.
- Ms. Beautiful Bang. - What are you doing here?
I was waiting for you.
Everyone. I need to get permission from a certain someone. Let me ask.
What?
Can I do business here?
These customers want my toast so much.
They're dying to buy one.
- His toasts are rumoured to be good. - I want to try one.
I heard the service was great.
I don't really mind.
I must be a hit in this town, too.
Wait just a bit, okay?
(Hwi's Toast)
Let's go.
- Where? - Didn't you want to know?
Know why I avoid marriage.
I did. Let's go.
Let me make it clear right now. Nothing good will come out of it.
It's not my problem if you regret it.
Okay. I'm fine with everything.
Oh Chan Hwi!
Enough!
What is it? Did I scare you?
I guess I'm no longer cool.
It's too early to get frightened.
What if I told you I even shot a person to death?
Stop joking around.
I'm not.
Let's go grab a bite.
Didn't you say I was going to love it?
Yes. Don't you love this place?
Gosh, I thought it was a lovey-dovey date.
We're here!
Min Ju. Why do you always run late?
- Min Ho? - You're hopeless.
You were taking so long to let us try the new beer...
that we started to think you went to pick the hops.
What took you so long?
Everyone was waiting for you.
I didn't know you came.
Okay. Now that everyone is here, let's get the party started.
- Let's party! - Come on now!
- Help us out over here. - Okay, let's go.
- Look at all these beers. - This way, please.
It seems he likes to stay seated.
I'm guessing he keeps his distance from his son.
He's not easy to get along with, is he?
Goodness. No, stay seated.
- Gosh. - Oh, dear.
She's right. You made a long trip coming here.
It's fate that we've met today.
Let's have some fun chit-chat.
Together, okay?
Tell us first...
why you are keeping a distance from your son.
Is keeping a distance this family's tradition or something?
I'm just curious, all right?
I'd appreciate it if you could give me some space.
No way.
Life never goes according to your will.
Try the beer your son has made.
- Goodness. - Nice.
Let's have fun.
All right. Cheers!
- Cheers! - Cheers!
Even if I look at them from all angles, they don't look alike.
I take after my mom.
- Right? - Yes.
CEO Yoon's family is alive and well.
But why did they never visit?
Is this the first time trying your son's beer?
What?
Well, we never had the chance to try it.
He never brought any over.
Who threw a glass at me...
when I wanted to make beer?
And who left home...
because of a simple disapproval?
We'd have to speak the same language to live together.
Goodness, as if you ever wanted a proper conversation.
It's not like you tried either.
- You... - Come now.
Stop it. Today's supposed to be a happy day.
That's what it's like between Dad and Min Ju.
There's no need to walk on eggshells.
Yes, it's okay. This is the usual.
Please dig in.
- She has the heart of an angel. - I know, right?
Hallelujah.
At this rate, I'll have to wait until my 60th birthday to eat.
The mourner's house would be a better place to eat.
- I'm hungry. - Hush.
This won't do. All right.
Everyone has to chug it down this time. Raise your glasses.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
- Chug it down! - Cheers!
Thank you.
Guess how long it takes for a person...
shot in the head with a rifle to die.
Thirty seconds?
Ten seconds?
Five seconds?
"I've pulled the trigger."
"There goes the bullet." When those thoughts crossed my mind,
they were already dead...
in split seconds.
But it's much faster than that.
The speed of a rifle bullet is about Mach three.
That's fast to the point...
where you're already dead...
before you realize you've been shot in the head...
and feel the pain.
Why have you been mentioning those since earlier?
I killed them.
People.
I'm serious.
I...
wanted to become a soldier since I was seven.
Shooting guns looked so cool to me.
And I became a soldier like it was natural.
I requested a dispatch because it looked cool.
My salary was also doubled.
At first,
I loved how life was better than in Korea.
But little did I expect...
our country's ship...
to get hijacked back then.
Three men have been taken hostage.
(Barber shop)
(Watch your head)
Hands on your back! Get down!
(Deck office)
Align your aim and fire immediately to take them out instantly.
Our nation's hero.
Why are you spaced out?
It gets better after a good sleep.
Not wanting to be labelled as weak,
I endured for five years.
I thought I'd forget if I endured it.
But...
from one day on,
I couldn't breathe.
Do you know what it means to have killed someone?
In the middle of a delicious meal,
I would have dry heaves.
Goodness.
I can still smell the blood from back then.
Are you all right?
Please open the door.
- Chan Hwi. - Chan Hwi.
- Are you okay? - My family walks on eggshells.
When I can't eat,
neither can my family.
When I can't breathe,
That's why I left home.
So that my family...
can eat properly...
and take a breather.
Can...
you do that?
Can you...
live such a life with me?
And forever at that.
I'll head inside.
No, not again.
Please.
Oh Chan Hwi!
I'll try.
I'll try to eat well...
and remember to breathe.
I'll try my best, and throw in the towel...
when it gets too much for me.
So don't run away from me if that's what you're afraid of.
I won't let you leave me.
- Here. - I won't go.
Come on. Take this.
What is it?
You can't come inside until you drink it all.
Forget it.
Okay, fine.
- Come on. - I can't believe you.
Why are you out here alone?
I was getting some fresh air.
I can't come inside until I empty the cooler.
Yong Ju's orders.
To both me and you,
she is someone precious.
Don't you agree?
If you had thought so,
you should've been at her grandmother's funeral.
She was in so much pain.
I expected no less...
since you attended Mom's funeral...
as a soldier and not as her husband.
That's what I still can't understand.
I was at her grandmother's funeral.
I made it to the door.
Why didn't you come in?
Ever since I lost your mother,
I haven't been able to attend funerals.
For some reason, I can't set foot inside them.
They scare me.
(Condolences)
My military uniform and boots are like my armour.
Having them on was the only way for me to remain stable and sane.
It was your way...
of not crumbling.
Your great-grandfather, your grandfather,
and even your uncle. We're a family of soldiers.
I was forced to be a man in the traditional sense.
Never did I come across a man like you...
who was sensitive to every small emotion.
Even though I wanted to be close to you,
I didn't know how to do it.
Your mother was the only one who understood you,
so I leaned on her instead.
Who knew she'd leave us so soon?
I didn't know what to do.
You should've told me.
Unbelievable.
You're like a mind reader when it comes to other people,
but not when it comes to your father.
You're right.
I never even tried to understand you.
That's right. A son...
didn't even bring his father his own beer.
How is it?
It's decent enough.
How can we have a conversation when your answers are always short?
To be honest, it felt good.
Hearing that you're the reason...
the village people have a stable life...
made me so proud.
Then, come back to visit.
Sure.
Gosh, when will we drink all this?
We're mosquito food out here.
There are eight cans,
so we'll have four each.
Seriously?
Our livers aren't in the same condition.
Not when I'm significantly older.
Okay, let's do this.
We'll see what happens. Here.
You did great.
- Goodness. - Gosh. Hey.
We're back.
Come have a seat here.
Goodness.
Nicely done.
This is so unfair.
What on earth?
What's with the dialect?
Were you one of us?
You know,
I've been trying to get on his good side...
and had to live my life...
walking on eggshells around him.
- What are you doing? - Let go of me.
What came over me...
that had me fall for a man who is so much older than me?
That's enough!
Mr. Yoon Chang Seok!
Would it kill you to be a fraction of what he's like?
Goodness.
Min Ju...
only has eyes for Yong Ju.
Those eyes...
were meant to look at her.
Mr. Yoon, here's what you'll do.
Once a week,
you'll have him teach you how to be sweet.
- Nicely put. - Keep going.
Classes on how to be sweet.
Goodness, my baby.
Mom, come sleep with me.
It's scary to sleep here.
Goodness. Today, you'll sleep with your father.
- Just us two? - Just us two?
That's right.
You know that your father is a high-ranking military officer.
He'll defeat any ghosts that come your way.
Now, go to bed.
Cheers.
- Goodness. - Sisters.
- Sure. - There you go.
- Here. - My goodness.
Do you want a hug?
Why am I being comforted by the sight of those two?
Thanks, Yong Ju.
See? I told you you'd love it.
Will the beer competition soon take place?
We'll fill out an application and send our beer.
Then comes the evaluation and awards.
Goodness. I should get started on the label design.
What? But we don't know if the beer will be launched.
Come on.
How can a beer you made not win an award?
It will be smooth sailing until the launch...
because I'll be that prepared.
Trust me.
Sure.
It's a precious beer we made together,
so I'll make sure it's a hit.
That being said, you'll properly see me do my work.
I've been eyeing you from the moment we met.
- Is that so? - Continuously.
Let's go.
(Uilhan Brewery)
(Sealed, Fragile)
I'm here for the delivery.
Hello.
Please have it delivered safely.
- Hello. - Hi.
Thank you.
C13, C14, and C15. All there.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(2024 International Blind Brew Cup)
Judges, for this procedure of tasting, to your tables.
Over here.
- Welcome. - Hi.
Everyone, we thank the contestants for being here...
for the award ceremony...
of the 2024 International Blind Brew Cup...
that is being held in Korea.
The award ceremony will now commence.
First of all, I'll announce the winner for the bronze.
Taking home the bronze is People's Lager...
produced by Brew House Crib.
First winner of the bronze award.
It's People's Lager produced by Brew House Crib.
What's taking Yoon Min Ju so long? Unbelievable.
What if the beer wins an award?
Am I supposed to accept it instead?
He'll be here. He said so.
Don't get ahead of yourselves.
It's not like you have a chance at winning.
How can you be that sure?
These must be swapped out...
before they're entered into the competition.
(Sealed, Fragile)
This is me righting a wrong.
It's for the company's sake.
My actions will save the company millions.
It scored zero points on the internal evaluation,
so it winning an award...
seems weirder to me.
A score of zero.
Lastly, all that's left is the winner of the gold award.
Let me announce it right away.
The 2024 International Blind Brew Cup, lager division.
The gold award goes to...
Guests, I apologize for the delay in the announcement.
It's a first which is why there was a brief misunderstanding.
The winner of the gold award is quite special this year.
Multiple beers submitted by one brewmaster...
have been awarded the gold award.
Let me announce the winner.
Brewmaster Yoon Min Ju of Uilhan Brewery.
The winning beers are Together 5, Together 9, and Together 11.
Congratulations.
And the gold award winner is Uilhan Brewery.
Brewmaster Min Ju Yoon's...
Together 5, Together 9, and Together 11.
Congratulations.
No way.
Min Ju's so cool.
Are you kidding? He continues to amaze me.
I can't believe his beer actually won gold.
I was stewing over there thinking you weren't coming.
What's the matter? I was right on time.
Unbelievable.
This is how far you should go.
If you continue on this path, you'll only be ruining yourself.
What are you talking about?
As if you don't know.
You do.
(Sealed, Fragile)
I'm here for the delivery.
Hello.
You must be new. We meet for the first time.
Why are you this tense?
Why can't you hold my gaze?
I'm sorry, but I'm cancelling your service.
I'll still pay you your fee.
What is it? Do you have to take this particular cooler?
You know what's in here.
I see. You're planning on swapping the beer.
Of course. That'll be hard to do...
once they've been submitted.
You can't afford to lose out on this window of opportunity.
(Uilhan Brewery)
You know Director Yeom Jang Gun at Jisang Liquor.
You do. There's no way of fooling me.
Would you like to do as I say or talk to the police?
The choice is yours.
From this moment on, the TF Team has full authority...
regarding the release of Together.
You're done getting in the way.
Nicely done.
Unbelievable.
My gosh, of course.
Do as you wish, Mr. Yoon.
Let's launch the product.
Chae Yong Ju, get on it.
- Yes! - Nice!
Gosh, you did great.
Nice!
We did it!
Hello, sir. The first batch is being transported today.
I was thinking about stopping by the factory to...
What did you just say?
Why can't the beer be transported today?
What on earth are you saying?
I'll come to you. I'll be right there.
(Jisang Liquor)
Min Ju.
Why are you here?
The first batch of products can't leave the factory today.
- It can't happen. - Hold on.
Were you the one who stepped on the brakes?
What are you saying?
They must leave the factory today...
to be sent to direct-only stores across the country.
What if we can't meet the launch deadline?
Push the deadline back.
I also have authority over the launch of Together.
Yoon Min Ju, what's going on?
This is our beer.
We made it together.
This batch of beer...
will be dumped, Ms. Chae.
(We thank Son Jong Hak for his special appearance.)
(Brewing Love)
There's a subtle difference to the taste.
Was there an issue with quality control?
I can't have it released in this state.
It's more important to keep our promise.
It tasting perfect is more important.
We'll see who hits rock bottom first.
Are you kidding me?
Find out who's responsible.
It was an inside job.
I found it.
What are you trying to say?
You know what.
I don't. I don't know a darn thing.