I'm John.
Come on, John.
You don't want to be late on your first day.
I miss you.
Don't bite your nails. You are 18 years old.
People will think you're nervous.
I'm nervous.
I hate this uniform.
Why can't I wear pants like boys?
Because you are a beautiful girl.
I love you. Have a nice day.
Take care.
Hey! No!
Wait!
He loved me... He loved me
Hey, you!
Hey!
Come here.
Yes.
Hello. I'm John.
Can you turn around?
Yes, turn around. Completely rotated.
Like this?
- That's okay.
-I like that.
You will come with us.
I will not allow you to be taken advantage of by a group of poseurs.
Yes, I'm talking about you.
What is your name?
Speaking Italian is not recommended
Inside the school campus.
But you were just...
- What?
Where do we go?
To school.
Welcome to Saint Mary's International School
In the heart of Milan.
A hotbed for all the rich students and nepotism.
Children of huge wealth.
Are you rich?
You don't have to be. You are beautiful.
Okay.
By the way, I'm John. I don't think I knew your name.
I didn't tell you about it.
Ignore Emilia. She's in a good mood today.
- I'm Blaise.
- That is, it burns intensely.
So, John, tell us about you.
I recently moved here with my mother from London...
"Drama King" on the left. Don't look.
"John"!
What did you say?
Stay away from James Hunter.
Who? You mean this fighter?
Yes.
- I don't like it.
- That's better.
- Let me guess. "John White"?
- Yes.
Professor Beckett.
Welcome to Literature, Humanities Level 1 class.
Have a seat.
Are you okay?
You have booked…
Never mind. "Woe."
I'm Will. Are you John?
I speak a primitive language.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were coming.
This is my seat. Get up.
Where to?
This is not my problem.
Are you always so rude?
This is my nice way.
James Hunter, you're not just late
But my class was also disrupted.
Leave Miss White alone.
Either sit in another seat or leave.
Okay, idiots. You know the instructions.
Only pencils are allowed.
You have 30 minutes to complete the test.
And John, we're studying Othello.
I don't expect you to give any answer.
“I know, Iago.
Your honesty and love make this matter less severe.”
This is amazing.
“You might have doubts about the burning of stars
Or the movement of the sun.
You may suspect that the truth is a lie.
But never doubt my love.”
- The British know Shakespeare well.
- Indeed.
This is so generous of you.
The era of chivalry is over.
You are my competition.
-Is she your competitor now?
-I don't know this yet.
Is that all?
Temporarily.
Is this poisoned?
I don't rule out that I did that.
“Separation has a delicious bitterness,
So I'll wish you a good night until…"
Damn!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
No, I was pointing with my hand when...
You mean it's my fault you can't hold a cup?
It was an accident. You don't have to be rude.
I will show you the meaning of rudeness.
I'm not allowed to enter here.
Hello. Nice to meet you. Hello.
I'm John.
Hello.
Leave me.
I'm so sorry. I saw your dick.
Get out.
Yes. Nice to meet you.
Well, you enjoyed insulting me...
This is my first day here,
I don't want to be caught
Inside the boys' changing room.
- What are you doing?
- What?
Is Snow White so shy?
Can't you look at my abs?
Or are you afraid of falling in love with me at first sight?
Fall in love with you at first sight? You?
This is very funny. You disgust me.
I swear if you keep doing this I will kick you.
I want it clean and ironed by Monday.
Do you think I'm your maid?
I won't do that.
Maybe a cold shower will change your mind.
Really, a cold shower?
Okay! Okay, I'll do it.
Don't eat too much starch.
It didn't take long.
I'm already a girl
Most popular in school.
I was severely insulted.
Why? Because you got caught
In the boys' locker room?
What is the reason for all this anger?
Does James do drugs?
That wouldn't surprise me.
Well, enjoy your weekend.
If you need me, I'll wash James' clothes.
You won't waste your first weekend
At James's laundry.
What are you doing?
Call my number. We're going out this evening.
Send to your address
Blaise and I will come pick you up.
We will not accept rejection.
Seriously, you're the best friend.
I know.
- Goodbye.
See you soon! See you later.
This must be a joke.
No, I understand that.
We can do that another time.
When will he come back?
That won't work, right?
Wait a minute because my daughter is back.
One moment please.
Hello. It was supposed
We meet a client tomorrow afternoon,
But Jordan's son's babysitter is sick.
Who is Jordan?
- Who do I work for?
- Tell him that I will babysit his son.
You have school.
Yes, tomorrow is Saturday.
You are right. This is great.
"Jordan." Hi, I apologize for that.
June said she could help us
Tomorrow afternoon.
She always did this in our city.
Okay, great.
I will talk to her and I will call you back.
Goodbye.
You saved me.
I bet he'll give you a tempting reward.
I'm happy to help.
Would you really be happy to help? What is the return?
There will be a party this evening.
It's our first night here together.
Actually it's our second night,
I would like to go very badly.
How was your day?
Is that all?
I won't pay you to tell me how your day was.
You are a bad girl. Do you know that?
You like to stir up trouble, don't you?
Shouldn't someone do that?
Weren't you caught at all?
- No.
- Not at all?
Absolutely.
Hello.
What?
How are things going?
We're done!
- Well done, Blaise.
- Thank you.
This is from the period of my mother's liberation after her separation.
I am sure its size will suit you.
- I don't want to seem unruly.
- Yes.
Come on.
Remove the dressing gown.
And here we begin.
It's nice.
It's very short.
This is the point.
It's okay.
Very octogenarian.
You look like a doll. Go.
That's a lot of fruit.
Next.
- This is it!
- This is what is required.
Yes.
Yes!
What's up?
I feel like my breasts are going to pop out.
Is this a bad thing?
- Yes, this is a bad thing.
- For your sake.
What is this place?
It has everything that comes to mind.
In her face!
The fight is over!
The winner is Alessandra!
Waiter!
Thank you!
- Let's get drunk!
I limit myself from drinking.
Come on!
- To you both!
Guys, would you like to gamble?
Thank you. You look cute when you do that.
Thank you.
What is this?
It is a QR code that opens an application
Allows betting on fights.
I'm going to go hype up the crowd, okay?
Enjoy your time.
Goodbye!
"Woe!"
"John."
Wow...you look beautiful.
Thank you!
How was your first day?
Yes, it was good. Until you met your best friend.
You mean "James"?
Okay
Yes, I heard about the shower room incident.
He was just teasing you.
It's very funny, believe me.
I love him.
Believe me, you will love it too.
No, I don't know about that.
Here we are.
Let's get ready to fight!
Guys, are you ready or not?
Let's shout loudly!
Tonight you will see an amazing fighter.
Luigi from Rome!
It's scary.
-And now the champion defending his title.
-You don't realize what's happening.
"James Hunter"!
Here he is the hero! Yes, James! "Hunter!"
"Hunter!"
"James Hunter"! Come on, let the fighting begin!
You can do it, my friend! Punch him and walk away.
Kick it! Come on!
For your sake! This is what I'm talking about.
- Well done!
- That was easy, man!
Very cool!
"Hunter!"
Here's to James!
Success requires diligence
Sacrifice and love of what you do.
Aside from the 10,000 euros I made.
- To you!
To you!
To Austin, the best coach in the country!
Will is his best friend and boxing training partner
At all.
-I love you, my friend.
-Me too.
To you.
I'm so proud of you, boy.
Would you like to say hello?
Nope. you go. I will wait.
-Are you sure?
- Yes.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
I beat him in the first round.
I mean, is there anyone who can stop you?
It's just the beginning.
Do you know, Willy?
With more effort,
You can enter this ring.
Tonight we celebrate James.
What is Snow White doing here?
She is with me.
- Really?
- Yes.
Treat her nicely, my friend.
I like it.
It's not "Aryan."
I'll be fine.
Okay.
I liked your kick to him. This was like…
It was like...
I knew that.
Sorry.
Can I help you?
I was looking for a recycling bin.
No, I don't mind.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Is this because of Jackson?
He doesn't know he's gay.
It's time to reveal my superpower.
Yes!
- Is he looking?
- As if he was enchanted.
-Can I tell you a secret?
- Sure.
I hate dancing.
What? Why?
Because when I dance, I feel like I look like an idiot.
-You say "clumsy"?
- Yes.
I'll go to the bar. Do you want something?
A cup of water would be good.
Okay.
How are the happy couple?
He's so cute.
Yes.
- What?
- Nothing.
He's cute.
Who is this?
- It's Ari.
-His ex-girlfriend.
She left him and broke his heart.
But don't worry about it. It's become an old story.
- Follow me, Blaise.
- Goodbye!
Are you having a good time?
I was.
Good.
- It's time to say goodbye.
- You're leaving, fine.
Not me.
But you.
What? Are you going to fire me?
You are quick to understand.
- What's your problem?
-You are my problem.
Listen, you clearly have a strange obsession with me.
Yes, I'm obsessed with getting rid of you,
And keep you away from Will.
Why? Why does that matter to you?
Who are you to decide who I date?
Why do you assume I care about who you date?
You can fuck me
Every guy in school, Snow White.
Except for Will.
-Does Will know about this?
- No.
And he won't know.
"Woe."
Don't let her in.
How can I return to my home?
You can keep the rest.
How dare you!
Fuck you.
My shoes... I hate you!
"Will: What happened, John?"
"(John): I apologize for that, I'll make an appointment to come back."
"(Will): Can we meet tomorrow?"
"Just you and me.
Without James...
I promise"
"I'll meet you at noon at Bosco Vertical."
"Sweet dreams"
"(John): Bye."
He's so cute.
What a narcissist.
Wow, it's exciting.
Wow.
Are you having a good time?
Don't.
Does the pillow have a name?
What time is it?
Almost ten o'clock.
Coffee?
Here she is!
You are the best mother ever.
I don't know about that, but...
I feel sleepy.
No, don't go back to sleep.
I'd like to know how your first day was.
How are your classes?
From your new friend who lent you
A £3,000 dress?
And why do you have a pile of boy clothes?
Moreover,
From the mysterious gentleman on the pillow
Who do you kiss passionately?
Good night.
You little brat! You have to tell me everything!
everything!
- Okay.
For your information, his birthday is next Tuesday.
Isn't this supposed to get easier?
But it doesn't happen.
Okay. I better get back to work.
Big cup, small cup.
Mom, August hit me!
It bothers me.
Hi, I'm August White and I'm so cool.
All the ladies love me.
You are extremely annoying.
Your future is bright, brother.
- This is Guy Aulente.
- “Gao”… “Gao Lenti.”
- "Guy Aulente."
- “Gaolin”… “Guy Aulenti.”
Yes, something like that.
And have you lived in Gay Aulente your whole life?
Yes.
But you moved a lot?
After "Milan"... it becomes 7 cities.
- No, wait, but 8.
- 8 cities?
- Yes.
- New schools entered all of them?
I traveled for a mixed martial arts tournament,
But I am a lover, not a fighter.
What are your hobbies?
I love reading suspense stories
And watch true crime shows.
I think the darkness motivates me.
Do you write too?
No, I write in my diary.
But it's a way to express myself.
Sometimes I write about my mood.
- She doesn't seem like a moody person to me.
- Good.
I deceived you.
"(James)"
"James Hunter."
Give me a moment, I promise.
Hello, can I call you later?
I'm out with my mom, yeah.
I will inform her of your greetings.
I'm done.
Are you okay?
I'm curious why you told him I'm your mother.
It's not worth getting into an argument with him.
He's been my best friend since we were kids and...
Your close friend?
Well, he's a terrible person.
It makes a bad first impression.
The first, the second... and the third.
Yes, they are all bad impressions.
When we met in elementary school,
I was afraid of James.
I was shy and strange.
He was afraid of no one, and I wanted to be like him.
Why?
You don't know how many times James pushed me.
To lose my temper.
He does it with everyone,
But then he makes them love him.
Trust me, that will never happen.
Did you like that?
- Damn.
- What's wrong?
I'm supposed to babysit this son...
- I will call you.
- Okay.
- Thank you for the tour.
- Yes.
And on the qiblah.
I'm sorry I'm late.
- It's okay.
- Okay.
I'm John, hello sir...
"Jordan."
This is Jasper.
Hello, Jasper.
Thank you, Jasper.
I'm supposed to be back in about two hours.
- Message me if you need me.
- Okay.
Enjoy your time.
Okay, Jasper, what would you like to do?
Would you like to play?
Mixed martial arts, yes!
"Jasper!"
Seriously…
Jasper, please!
"Jasper!"
What nonsense?
"Jasper"…
Damn.
"Jasper"?
"Jasper."
"Jasper!"
Where did this boy go?
"Jasper"?
Is this another prank?
Okay.
No!
What are you doing here?
I live here, you idiot!
Jasper lives here. This is Jasper's house.
Yes, he is my brother.
This is the worst that could happen.
Wow!
Haven't you ever seen a man's genitals before?
I definitely saw.
You can look now.
Thank you.
Wow!
Snow White, you remember the Lord's name
In vain again.
And all because of a naked boy.
You must be experiencing severe depression.
I am not repressed.
Rather, I feel disgusted. Get dressed.
Your orders are orders.
I killed the rabbit.
Would you like to try?
Would I like to pretend to shoot?
On helpless animals?
They are animal shaped balloons.
Yes, it doesn't matter. My answer is no.
I don't think you should teach your brother that.
If I don't teach him, how will he learn?
What do you prefer, Snow White?
To teach him to knit?
Good.
I was wondering when you were going to come in
Sexism in debate.
They have arrived.
"Jasper!"
He's so cute.
Thank you.
We are concerned about finding a private school that suits him.
- Won't he go to Saint Mary's?
- No.
He has a slight degree of autism,
So this may not be the most suitable option for him.
Where is his mother now?
Did I say something wrong?
No, not at all.
I had a nervous breakdown more than a year ago,
She is currently in a rehabilitation center.
I'm so sorry.
No, please.
We have been separated for years.
I got married again, but...
Not a good man.
What do you think you are doing?
Excuse me?
What gives you the right to talk about my mother?
In front of strangers?
You don't know anything about her. I am not a perfect father.
This is my son.
- "Edward."
- "James"!
My name is James.
And I prefer Hunter.
- Where are you going?
- I'll go out.
Can you be more specific?
I'm going to a party.
Is this the same party you were talking about?
What party?
James can pick you up, John.
Yes, that won't happen.
Sorry.
What's wrong with this boy?
You have no respect...
Who knows? Can we leave?
Now you're going to come in and apologize. Is this clear?
Can I take you to the concert?
I won't leave for an hour,
But I will be happy to accompany you.
Great.
Electronic cigarettes?
Of course you do.
What? Does smoking bother Snow White?
Not smoking.
You're the one who annoys me.
I don't know why you're angry with me.
I didn't choose to come.
Can you stop talking?
Believe me, I'll be happy never to talk to you again.
I get it.
She likes quiet girls
So that they do not challenge your narcissistic personality.
You're still talking.
What is this?
Its name is a motorcycle.
I know what a motorcycle is. I won't ride it with you.
Is the little princess afraid of the bike?
Bike?
Nope.
Are you the one who will drive it? Yes, definitely.
- I will drive.
-You won't.
I won't teach you.
Yes, Pietro.
Well, I'll destroy him in round two.
I will arrive in 20 minutes.
You!
- Goodbye!
- What are you doing, John?
Get off the bike.
- Get off the bike!
- See you later!
Hey! Stop!
Not bad for such a weak engine.
-Are you serious?
- Don't get me started.
Really?
- Hello.
What was that?
Are you dating?
Oh my, no.
Really? Because you both look like that.
That was nothing.
This doesn't seem like anything.
I came from his house.
So, it's worse.
- No, I was sitting...
- Yes.
It's a long story.
Would you like to respond? Maybe the call is yours.
"(James)"
Stop. For your sake.
Hey, shouldn't we stand in line?
Guests are not allowed inside.
Don't direct your words at me.
What do you inject?
Vitamins.
- They don't look like vitamins.
- Sorry.
Who are you?
She's not a special person.
Great.
Where are you going, beautiful?
Sorry, I speak little Italian.
Hey, seductress.
- Why the rush?
- "Pietro"!
Get your hands off me!
What's your problem?
Do not interfere in what does not concern you.
Help!
No, stop!
Jackson, stop them!
What the hell are you doing?
What are you doing? Leave it!
He attacked Will. What did you expect me to do?
To wait
Until you get in the ring for the damn fight
Which has now been cancelled!
Do you know how much I bet on it?
I did it for Will.
I didn't ask for your help.
I was about to get hit hard.
Someone had to defend her.
What did you say?
So, are you the cause of all this?
Can you do me a favor and get out of my face?
Then Jackson intervened. It was crazy.
I can't believe I missed out on all this fun.
- Hello.
Welcome
How is everyone?
Not the best night.
James is drunk, and I'm going to need help
In dealing with him.
James drunk?
Can you please?
- Okay. now?
- Now.
The other direction. The other way, my friend.
Yes.
Let's put it on the back.
Where did you get the truck?
My father is the school principal.
I didn't know...
- What a shame!
- What a shame.
This is disgusting.
Return it intact.
Intact.
This is funny.
"Saint Mary's International School - Milan"
Don't let him have this.
Where's my drink?
You won't throw up, right?
Do you know where my jacket is?
I will bring it.
I will be right back.
"White."
Come here.
What?
It's a secret.
Come closer.
Have you always been this beautiful?
- I didn't finish.
-You're drunk.
Besides, only God knows what they're injecting you with.
Tell me the truth.
-How much do you want to fuck me?
- Fuck you.
Slow down, Snow White.
Is there anything else?
Sometimes you look at me that way.
Which way?
This way.
The one you're looking at now.
Give me that bottle, Hunter.
-Give it to me!
- No, I won't.
Give it back to me!
Stop!
-Someone is sensitive to tickling.
- I'm not!
Really? So what is this?
Stop! If you tickle me again I'll bite your finger.
I dare you.
"John."
What's going on here?
Nothing.
Nothing. I was checking if he was still breathing.
You want to stay back?
Or will you sit with me in the front?
I would like to be with you.
Would you like me to walk inside with you?
I'll be fine.
Okay, good night.
Good night.
Did I do something wrong?
I don't know. Did you?
Listen, I'm sorry about what upset you,
But I don't read minds.
Either you talk to me, or we end things now.
The whole night fell on me like a thunderbolt
Since I showed up with James on his bike.
I told you that I was babysitting his brother.
Yeah, and then it happened in the hallway
- When Pietro harassed you.
- So what?
I wanted to protect you, but instead,
I looked like a complete loser
He needs James to save him.
I can fight my own battles.
I don't always need James.
Battles?
What do you think of me then?
A damsel in distress who needs someone to save her?
- John, that's not what I meant.
- That's exactly what I meant.
And about James,
He's unconscious in the back of your truck.
Listen, John, I don't want to argue with you.
I'm sorry. You've ruined everything.
Yes.
What?
Fuck all that.
Wait. Maybe…
- Maybe it's better to...
- Yes. Okay.
Watch your head. Are you okay?
Okay.
This is very fast.
Faster?
Nope.
Are you okay?
Damn…
I haven't done that in a long time.
I reached my peak early.
Damn.
After five minutes I can start again.
start what?
No, I didn't mean...
I don't think we've reached that point yet.
Do you mean to have sex?
- Isn't it?
- Yes.
- Not for me at least.
- Sure.
- Maybe I should drive him home.
- Yes.
Thank you for coming...
On a wonderful evening.
- What a shame.
- Would you like me to walk inside with you?
No, I'll be fine.
Damn! How did you do that?
Damn it, what an idiot I am.
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
I was waiting for you. I must have fallen asleep.
How was your evening?
Almost no special events.
I apologize about Jordan's older son.
I shouldn't have put you in this position.
It's okay.
According to Jordan, he's completely lost.
Do me a favor and stay away from him.
I have a bad feeling about him.
There is nothing to worry about.
By the way, I have to go to Paris.
Monday.
Will you be okay alone?
- Yes, I'll be fine. I promise you.
certainly. Thank you.
Thank you.
-I love you.
-Me too.
- Good night, my love.
- Good night.
I'll see you in the morning.
My dear diary,
James Hunter continues to act mean.
What's wrong if Will orgasms early?
Will is perfect for me.
So, my diary,
Can you please tell me
Because I'm so attracted to this bastard?
What's wrong with me?
I can convince myself
To love Will and hate James.
I just need willpower.
I have to be strong. Ali…
"(James): Are you home?"
"John: You know I'm home."
"Are you okay?"
"John: What do you want, James?"
"(James): It's your turn, send me your picture?"
"(John): Impossible!"
"James: Please"
"(James): I write with one hand."
"(John): And where is the other one?"
"(James): Guess..."
"Give me a clue"
Wow.
"(John): This is not your picture."
Fuck.
"(James): You must be angry,
"All this excitement without letting it out."
"(John): I will survive"
"James: I can help you, just tonight."
"John: You deserve a slap, good night."
"(James): I have experience and I can know
"The needs of polite girls"
"(John): So, expert,
What do you want me to do?"
"James: Put on your headphones, Snow White.
I will call you"
Put your hand down...
And take off your pants.
Start moving your hand.
Hurry.
And now stronger.
"(James)"
Let me hear you now.
higher.
Yes.
"(John): You did this."
You're welcome.
Good night.
"(John): Erase this!"
On my dead body.
Wow, this was amazing.
Don't say a word.
Are you in a bad mood today?
We shouldn't have done that.
- He did what?
-You know exactly what I'm talking about.
Nope. I lost consciousness.
- Good.
- Then I saw the picture
Which you sent me after your orgasm,
- And I got all the memories back.
-Give me that picture!
Nope.
No!
- No.
- Come on!
For your information, I pretended to.
I pretended?
This is the truth.
There is one truth, Snow White.
You reached your ecstasy while thinking about me.
Yes. You think you're very charming, don't you?
I think you are proud of yourself
For stealing your best friend's girl.
Did you steal?
Is this what you think I'm doing?
Listen to me, Snow White, and listen carefully.
Everything I do, I do for Will.
What makes you think it wasn't a test?
To see if you deserve it?
Is this all we had? Test?
A test I failed.
The last thing he needs is a girl messing with his head.
Can I help you?
Sorry. You can't enter.
What do you think you are doing?
That's nice.
If you touch me I'll scream.
Well, I'll definitely touch you.
I'm sure you'll scream.
Where will you touch me?
Here.
And…
This is interesting.
Is that all you have?
This is just the beginning.
I love school.
When will Taylor, Bobbi, and Tiffany return?
From their trip?
Soon.
I have a chance to get my money back.
We will return to work.
- When?
- After school.
The problem is that we can't use the club.
So we'll go to the backup place.
Okay, I'll spread the word.
Hey James...
There is no room for other failures.
The fighting is back.
In the spare place.
I'll take care of it.
Let's go. Hurry up!
Hurry up, man. Come on.
We will settle in this room.
What is this place?
I think it was a World War II bunker.
Landmine!
How funny.
Wow. You should have seen your face.
I will be right back.
Okay.
This looks different.
Is it the same drug?
No, that's better.
Trust me.
I've always done that.
I know.
What is the value of betting on the fight?
More than 6000.
Hello, what are you doing?
Nothing.
Okay, let's do this.
What a coincidence.
Shall we go?
Come on, my friend. As usual.
You'll wish you were dead.
I will excel at humiliating you!
Do you hear me? You're just an asshole.
Are you ready?
Are you ready? Start fighting!
Hey, stop. That's enough!
James, that's enough.
Who is the vile defeated now?
My hero, James Hunter!
Great, my friend. Great.
What's up?
- I'm fine.
- I'm not fine.
This is an allergic reaction to steroids.
Let me guess, is your body itchy?
Do you feel nauseous?
I feel…
-Are you a doctor?
- Shut up.
You weigh about 80.
- What? Is this good?
- No.
Take, drink this. You need mineral salts.
How do you know all this information about this matter?
My brother was on steroids.
I didn't know you had a brother.
It was mine.
Not a topic I like to talk about.
You!
- How many times...?
-He's having an allergic reaction
About what you injected him with.
What did you inject him with? “Trenbolone Acetate”?
“Testosterone Cypionate”?
- I don't know.
-You don't know.
- How stupid are you?
- What did you say?
- Repeat that.
- Austin, calm down.
She can't talk to me like that.
Let's be alone for a bit.
I'm not going anywhere.
Get out.
Right away.
Okay.
I'll go get the car.
I don't like this man.
I think this feeling is mutual.
You are lucky because you are a girl.
Do you think this is my fault?
He should apologise.
And you have to thank me.
What? This is not funny.
These masculine ideas are all complete nonsense.
What is this?
It's celebration.
Have you seen "John"?
No, I haven't seen her since the fight.
Goodbye.
Hello!
"Anonymous: Don't trust them!"
"Don't trust them!"
Hello!
"Woe!" Let's dance.
Come on!
I'll catch up with you shortly.
-Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Okay. Have you seen "John"?
Nope.
Where did you go?
Okay.
Anyway, see you on the dance floor.
"Vodka (Semyonov)"
Fuck all that.
Do you realize what you are doing?
I've done this a lot before.
95.
It would have fallen further
If you weren't touching me like this.
I can stop.
I don't want you to stop.
"Ari!"
"Ari."
Are you okay?
I'm in better shape.
Don't drink, right?
What do you think?
I don't know.
You taste great.
- "Will."
-You are delicious chocolate.
"Woe!"
What's up, Will?
Nobody wants me!
Nobody!
"Woe!"
You don't have to stay with me.
Do you want me to leave?
Nope.
This is wrong.
What's wrong with you?
What's up with you?
My friend!
We have a problem.
Everyone get out!
Did you hear? Get out of the way.
The party is over.
The offer is over!
Come on go!
Are you okay, Will?
Go away!
I'll follow you on his bike.
Let's take him home so he'll be safe.
Okay. Don't worry.
I ride my bike to your house.
I'll come get it after I drop him off.
Will he be okay?
I will explain to you later.
I'm with you.
You are fine.
Miss White.
You scared me.
What are you doing here?
I need to talk to you about James.
Tell me what he told you about me.
Nothing.
You are his coach.
I am also his stepfather.
James is a very important person to me.
And the last thing I want
It is for a beautiful, spoiled woman to intervene among us.
Okay.
Now I can see why boys are so infatuated with you.
You are so beautiful.
Can I come in?
I don't think this... my mother...
Your mother?
I rang the bell and no one opened.
So, we are completely alone.
What a shame.
I made you sad.
Keep this a secret between us.
Okay?
Maybe I'll come back later.
Goodbye, Miss White.
Hello, I'm April. Please leave a message...
Damn.
The police are coming. You have to leave.
Can I get my bike key back?
"Hunter."
Are you okay? Did something I said make you angry?
Would you like it sugared, Hunter?
What do you do with that?
If I were to be your bodyguard
I have to wear the appropriate outfit.
You don't have to stay.
I can defend myself.
Don't be stupid.
I'll sleep on the couch.
Just don't try to lure me
In my sexy new outfit.
Are you going to tell me what happened with Will tonight?
I don't think so.
Will you tell me who threatened you?
No one threatened me.
Tell me what happened.
You really care about him, don't you?
I care about many things.
Tell me what happened to him tonight.
He's just going through tough times.
We all go through difficult circumstances.
What are you protecting?
From himself.
Do you know Ari?
Yes.
Well, they were in a relationship.
It was a serious relationship.
Then things got worse.
Will became obsessed with control and possession and...
Ari ended her relationship with him.
He got into a spiral.
What do you mean by "vortex"?
He's fine now.
He should just walk away
About the things that complicate his life.
Things like me.
Something like this.
-Does he know you're doing that?
- Absolutely not.
Everything I do, I do for Will.
For "Will"?
Isn't it for James?
He's like a brother to me.
I owe him my life.
What do we have here?
What are you doing?
This is my turn to ask questions.
Don't be harsh.
Do you like biscuits?
Yeah, I still love him FYI.
I bet you were bossy.
I was too.
Is this your brother?
Yes.
How long has it been since he died?
About two years.
He is the one who taught me to ride motorcycles.
We were inseparable.
Can I ask what happened?
One of his team members introduced him to steroids.
And I think…
That stimulants turned into stronger drugs.
We were driving around in the car.
He must have been under the influence of some drug.
We had an accident.
I couldn't save him.
I'm sorry.
What a huge loss.
Damn.
I thought my feelings would calm down about that.
John, I am truly saddened by your brother's loss.
But what Austin is injecting me with...
Completely safe.
All he wants is for me to give the best performance possible.
I'm not your mother.
Do what you have to do.
Wow, you're making me angry.
Why?
Because I care about you.
You are better than that.
How do you know?
You think that everyone in this life wants to take advantage of you.
I take advantage of them as well.
Everything in life is subject to negotiation.
Everything? Even friends and relationships are just a benefit?
Without a doubt.
Love should be an unconditional feeling.
It is assumed.
But it's not like that.
Absolutely.
Not at all?
You are walking towards danger.
As if you don't like danger.
Yes.
But this is too much.
Even for me.
"James."
Go to sleep.
I will leave in the morning.
Are you sure?
Believe me. This is going to end badly.
Good night.
Please.
John, what are you doing?
Did you stay up all night?
I have good news.
After you defeated Pietro,
I can get you into better fights.
We'll make a hero out of you, J.
What happened between you and John last evening?
What are you talking about?
Did I tell you something?
I don't trust that bitch.
No, you didn't tell me.
But you did.
Hey, can you lay your hand on me?
That's me, J, come on.
-Will you lay your hand on me?
- Stay away from her.
Okay. Take your hands off me.
I don't want your dope anymore.
Really?
Our work together is over.
Come on, calm down and then we can talk.
"Jeh!" Calm down and then we'll talk.
"Jeh!" Calm down and then we'll talk!
- This?
- No.
For your sake. It looks beautiful.
Maybe.
Yes, I think it would fit
With my Ferragamo shoes.
John, what do you think?
"John"?
John, can you hear me?
Excuse me, what? What did you say?
My birthday party dress.
- Yes, that's nice.
-I know.
Brian will bring it to me from Paris.
My father is a college professor, and Brian is currently visiting him.
He will return next week.
"King of Drama."
Guys, excuse me a little.
"James."
Thank you again for last night.
The night before didn't happen.
Did you understand that?
Yes, nothing happened. Is everything okay?
-I can't do this with you.
-You can't...
What can't you do with me?
- Hello.
Hello.
I missed you.
How are you?
I'm fine. Last night was crazy.
Yes.
Listen, I have to go to class, but...
I wanted to take you shopping this afternoon
To buy you a dress for Emilia's party.
You don't have to do that.
I know I don't have to do that.
But I want it. I will make you happy.
Okay.
You are mine.
-Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
You really excelled this time.
I know.
Approach with drinks.
Here you go.
What is this?
His name is "A Dirty Little Virgin".
Taste it.
He's with Ari. Okay.
Go say hello to him.
I don't feel threatened.
I don't want to say hello. I'm here with you.
Are you sure?
Sure.
I'll borrow it from you for the dance.
No, I can't.
- My mother allowed me one drink.
-It's my birthday.
What are you doing?
I'm texting your mother to tell her that you'll be staying with me.
She's out of town. I won't...it's no use.
It's too late.
Don't be silly.
- Enjoy.
- Okay.
- Are you coming?
Okay. I will follow you shortly.
- Have you seen the birthday girl?
-She's dancing with John.
"Incredibly sexy"
"Hi, I'm promiscuous"
"I'm promiscuous!"
"I do what I want and I don't care about anything"
"John's house this morning."
"I don't care if you're circumcised."
"James, how dare you?"
“I'll tease you with my mouth for luck.”
"Shame on you!"
"Hi, I'm promiscuous"
John and James.
Wow.
Have another drink! Come on!
It's very exciting.
I see why you want it.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Yes, you know.
"Hi, I'm promiscuous"
- Where did you get this?
- It doesn't matter.
"I don't care about anything"
It's not what you think it is.
Come on, can't you leave one thing for me?
Can you do that? Just this once?
But I never deprived you of anything.
I was keeping her away from you to protect you from what happened with Ari.
So, are you telling me you don't have feelings for John?
Yes.
- You bastard.
- "Will."
"Woe!"
"John."
- Tell me what you want.
- What are you doing, Will?
You both suit each other.
"Shame on you!"
“I'm promiscuous
"I do what I want and I don't care about anything."
- How did this get to them?
- What do I know?
“I'm promiscuous
I'm promiscuous
I do what I want and I don't care about anything
"I'm promiscuous"
This is terrible.
How did you do that to Will?
"I do what I want and I don't care about anything"
You have to leave. Go!
"I don't care if you're circumcised."
Wow. I just watched the video.
Are you well?
-What do you think?
- "Woe!"
- What's wrong with you?
- Don't you know what he went through?
- For your sake.
As if you had nothing to do with what happened.
What are you accusing me of? By installing these pictures?
They are pictures of me. This is insulting.
I'm not the scapegoat, John.
"White"!
Who made this video?
We never kissed.
Can I get you some medicine or a glass of water?
I'm fine.
Thank you for taking care of me.
This is my pleasure.
I'll stay in the guest room.
James, can you stay with me?
I don't want to be alone.
"(Ari): I didn't send that video."
I'll deal with it in the morning.
Thank you.
Everything will be fine.
Hello!
Hello John, I'm back.
"Anonymous: There is a girl whose behavior was disgraceful!"
"Hi, I'm promiscuous"
What is this?
John, wake up!
Will you talk to me? Nothing happened.
How do you know that? I was drunk.
Because I trust him, just as you should trust me.
Why would I do that when everything I said was a lie?
This is not true.
Do you realize what you've ruined?
Jordan is my boss.
I asked you to babysit his little son.
- Not sleeping with the big one.
- This is not fair.
Great.
Let's hope my career doesn't collapse,
And that we still have a home to shelter us.
"(Emilia)"
- Good morning.
- Did you have a good time?
- Yes.
This concert will be remembered for years.
My battery ran out.
Do you mind if I use your phone?
To call a taxi?
Yes, definitely. Would you like a cup of water?
- No, I'm fine like this.
- Okay.
“Awesome, Emilia!
Send as (Anonymous) to: Everyone"
"James, how dare you?"
Emilia, you promised me
To do better this year.
"Open your eyes, Will!"
Are you okay?
It's all good.
"Hi, I'm promiscuous"
"I'm promiscuous!"
“Girls and boys are lining up at my door
"I fuck everyone until I'm exhausted."
My mother?
“Three, four, or more
Yes, I am international...”
- "Blaise."
- Hello.
What are you doing here?
I have something to tell you.
- Enough. The fight is over.
- Yes!
Yes!
Cheer! That's how to win!
Do you know who you are?
You're the only one who can
Defeat the dreaded James Hunter.
No one will think you can win,
This is precisely why I bet all my money on your victory.
Hey, are you okay?
I'm going to crush him so hard.
You can.
Is there a problem?
Good.
And now I present to you a fighter appearing for the first time...
"Will Cooper!"
Are you the one who did this? I won't fight him.
This is your problem, you spoiled man.
What are you doing?
I won't fight you.
To the fight!
You are dead.
Will, please.
Fuck you.
Stop, Will!
I will kill you!
If she thinks I'm flying economy class
Fuck her.
Are you serious about coming here?
Damn!
"Woe!" Stop!
Stop fighting!
"Woe!" Stop fighting!
- Get her away from here.
the curse! No!
No! Put me down!
- No!
- Come in!
Fuck you!
Eliminate him! Kill him!
What... No, stay!
Please leave the club,
Stay calm and follow emergency procedures.
Stay! The fight is not over! This is my money!
Bring it before the police arrive.
You!
Let's see if you like it!
"James"!
Damn.
Will, I need your bike.
- Why?
-For James.
Go away, John. What are you doing?
James would have rushed to save you if the roles had been reversed.
I thought you two were like brothers.
Get out of my way.
No, wait. "John"!
What will we do with it?
I don't know, but I don't want to
To talk to the police about our work.
Slow down.
Damn you both!
What is this!
We got rid of both.
Stop the car!
"James"!
Okay. Let's go.
-Are you okay?
- Yes.
Drop me here, please.
So, it all happened.
Do you want me to call an ambulance?
I've done enough so far.
So, does this mean we're on the same page?
We're not even close to this.
-Are you serious?
both. I've suffered enough.
Fuck you, Will.
I love you too, James Hunter.
Do you want me to leave you alone? To be alone?
Are you still here?
I saved your life, you idiot.
Whatever.
As Shakespeare said,
"The lesson is in the rings"
Suitable.
We escaped death, and Will forgave us.
And maybe James and I could swap.
Our first kiss at last.
"The end?"
Quality Supervisor Marwa Abdel Ghaffar