[In-season Angry Snapper]
- Yes! It's an angry snapper! - Angry!
What?
Man, another bust today.
Meet another cell who's half-unemployed now.
Fishing Cell.
894 days of going home with nothing.
And then...
Then came day 895.
- Angry!
- I caught one!
At last, he hooked one.
- An angry snapper!
- Angry!
- It's the angry snapper!
- Angry snapper.
It's a rare fish only caught
when Yumi gets mad.
The angry snapper
came back from near extinction...
It's an angry snapper!
right when PD Shin forgot all his manners.
Angry!
I came for those too.
That was the last batch.
They sell out fast.
Right. So...
Anyway, I'll get going.
See you next week.
- Score, another angry snapper!
- Angry!
When PD Shin grabbed them all for himself.
But Maltese aren't that smart.
Angry!
Don't all dogs do that?
Unless it's a lizard.
Angry!
Maltese... Don't they eat poop?
[PD Shin]
Angry!
- Angry!
It's a full catch!
Yumi's absolutely furious!
Hey, Lullaby Cell, get up.
What is it?
Help Yumi fall asleep.
It's after two in the morning
and she won't sleep.
What?
Seriously, the more I think about it,
the crazier it gets.
♪ Go to sleep, go to sleep, sweet Yumi ♪
Since Yumi's too furious to sleep,
- I'm stuck on the clock too.
- Sleep well.
My stomach's empty.
Hey, look at the clock. You're hungry again?
I want fried dumplings.
Fried dumplings!
Hungry Cell wants a midnight snack for once.
I'm so ticked off I can't sleep.
That Shin Soon Rok.
Hey, Coco.
You can't sleep either?
You're all worked up too, aren't you?
It was just humiliating.
I'm so sorry, Coco.
Poor thing.
Sorry I let him say that to you.
That was humiliating, wasn't it?
I bet that guy's actually a sociopath.
Who's that heartless to an animal?
Sociopath? Or personality disorder?
Or maybe both?
Definitely both.
So how do sociopaths
and personality disorders connect?
I bet there are tons of personality disorders.
Let me dig into this.
Oh hey, Bulletin Board Cell.
You're still awake?
I got slammed with new notes.
Can't remember the last time.
[Talking trash about a Maltese?!]
[Replace him, Shin Soon Rok]
[How should we get revenge?]
"Replace him, Shin Soon Rok."
"What a jerk. How do I get back at him?"
"He insulted a Maltese?
I'll never forgive him."
Oh no, what now?
You need to look after her.
Coco's stressed out because of this.
Look, her coat's gone all dull!
Don't let it get you down.
You okay?
Wait, there's no bungeoppang left.
Is he kidding? He took all eight for himself?
You're kidding, there's none left?
After the fried dumplings,
it was bungeoppang's turn.
I have to have it, right now!
I'm craving
Strawberry Cream Custard Bungeoppang!
Bungeoppang!
Hey, you guys!
What's with all this racket
in the middle of the night?
- I have to sleep now to write tomorrow.
- My bungeoppang!
It'd been a while
since the town stayed up all night.
Ready to go?
Man, I'm so tired.
Lost so much sleep because of that jerk.
Coco.
Your mom's coming today.
She said she's coming to pick you up.
Lucky you, Coco.
- Isn't that PD Shin?
- What?
Seriously, why do I keep seeing him?
The bungeoppang place is that way.
Don't tell me he's buying bungeoppang already?
Like I'm letting that happen.
Hold on, Yumi's wearing those raggedy sweats!
And Yumi didn't even wash up!
Like that even matters right now?
Excuse me, sir!
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Give me every Strawberry Cream
Custard Bungeoppang here.
- Every single one?
- Yes, please.
Every last one.
Oh, is it a group order?
How many per box, then?
Skip the boxes. I'll take whatever's here.
One second, let me count them up.
No, just give them all to me.
Just all of them. Every single one.
- That's more than 40.
- More is better!
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Could you hurry a little, please?
- Okay.
- I'm running late for work.
- Oh, are you sharing at the office?
- No.
I'm eating every last one myself.
Oh, okay...
Oh, hi, PD Shin!
Hi, Writer Kim.
[Bbang-eo Bbang-eo]
What a coincidence seeing you here again!
Yeah, small world.
You're really into bungeoppang, huh?
Strawberry Cream Custard ones again?
Yeah.
Wait, seriously?
You might be out of luck.
All set.
Thanks so much!
Thank you.
All right, done.
- So all of those are...
- Yes.
These are all
Strawberry Cream Custard.
Catch you next week!
Writer Kim...
The bungeoppang...
Hello.
Oh, hello.
If you came for the Strawberry Cream Custard,
sorry, but we're sold out.
I have to make more filling,
so they won't be ready till the afternoon.
Right then...
[Endorphin]
It'd been a while since Endorphin showed up.
Coco, did you see that? Did you?
That stunned look on his face.
I got payback for you, Coco.
Pretty good, right?
Oh, that felt so good.
♪ Pissed off? Eat some angry snapper ♪
- Let's eat!
♪ Fired up? Cook some angry snapper ♪
All you Cells who love Yumi!
Make a circle over your heads!
One, two, three, four!
♪ Let's eat, let's eat, let's eat ♪
♪ Dig into that angry snapper ♪
It was party time again after forever.
What a nice breeze.
Beautiful day, isn't it, Coco?
Who cares how smart a Maltese is?
That's not what my writing's about.
Would a poodle change the whole theme?
Does it change the male lead at all?
Coco, what's got her so mad?
And then guess what he said?
He said Maltese eat poop too.
Is he out of his mind or what?
Eating poop?
Yeah! He said Maltese eat poop.
As a Maltese owner, isn't that ridiculous?
That's straight-up disrespect.
Disrespect to all of us owners.
Though Coco eats poop, so I can't fight it.
Wait, what?
She licks her own poop sometimes.
No big deal, just brush her teeth.
Isn't that right, Coco?
Hey, by the way,
why do you look so happy?
Me? Happy?
You totally are. It's been a while.
No, I'm really not cheerful.
I'm just mad.
Why? You're mad too, right?
Oh, right.
Here, take it.
Huh? Is this Bungeoppang?
I never confront people directly.
I take revenge gracefully.
That's pro Writer Kim's way with amateurs.
Gracefully, yeah.
Bye Coco, let's hang out again, okay?
Thanks so much!
I'll treat you to a meal next week.
Alright, off you go.
- Bye.
- Say bye-bye. That's a good girl.
- Bye now.
- Bye.
[Take care of yourself. See you next time]
- Have a safe trip home.
- Now the Maltese is leaving too.
- Bye-bye.
Once the angry snapper festival ended,
the village felt empty all over again.
Finally, I can get some work done.
Haven't gotten a word down since yesterday.
It's all Shin Soon Rok's fault.
- Yes, who's there?
- It's a delivery.
I didn't order anything.
What is this?
[To Writer Kim, From Shin Soon Rok]
From Shin Soon Rok?
Shin Soon Rok?
What's he up to now?
Soiel Bakery?
No way!
It's Soiel Bakery!
The chef worked at a top 3-star Michelin spot,
famous for seasonal course desserts!
A bakery that's all about desserts!
Money won't even get you a table there!
PD Shin actually sent that?
PD Shin, who wouldn't even share
a single bungeoppang?
Oh, these look so cute!
These are so adorable!
Wait a second.
This isn't something
you can get delivered online.
He went there himself to buy and send these.
Bottom line,
this is heartfelt.
What's this about?
That spooked him earlier.
He realized he slipped up.
Seeing me buy out
all the bungeoppang scared him.
Gosh, he's so pathetic it's actually endearing.
These must be amazing.
These are too pretty to eat, honestly.
Maybe shoot him a thank-you message first.
Right, good thinking.
He's not a terrible person or anything.
He was just immature, that's all.
Right.
Who is it this late?
Who's there?
Writer Kim, it's me, PD Shin.
Excuse me?
Why is he here?
Did he come to say sorry?
He sent food and now he's showing up in person?
Oh, PD Shin.
Sorry for showing up so late.
It's fine.
But what brings you here at this hour?
- Were you maybe...
- I was just thinking about...
Sorry?
The dessert I sent...
Oh yeah, I got them.
I was literally just about to message you.
- Oh, they look so delicious...
- Oh, you already tried them.
What?
Got it.
Hold on.
This feels weird again.
Something's not right again, is it?
Oh wait, I think I get it now.
Wait,
did you send this by mistake?
Was it meant for another Writer Kim...
Yeah.
Angry!
Angry! Angry!
- Well now, it's prime time for Angry Snapper.
- Angry!
Angry!
[Episode 5: A Delivery from PD Shin]
There's something called a compliment delivery.
Delivery!
No way, it's a compliment delivery!
Every praise is delivered directly
to the specific cell it's meant for.
These delivery boxes contain a soul...
Hi! I'm here to give you something.
No way, it's a present!
This is so exciting!
Which then presents a gift to the cell.
Sir.
Here's everything you asked for yesterday.
Oh, thanks. Right.
Man, you never miss a thing.
Compliment delivery for Rational Cell!
No way!
- It's a compliment delivery!
- Here you go.
- Thanks a lot!
- Back in my rookie days,
- Awesome. Time to ask for more focus.
- a single compliment delivery really lifted me.
Hello, Writer Kim.
Hey, you're here.
One thing's different now
after all these years.
I didn't have quite enough time,
so it's not super detailed yet.
Alright, ship it off to Na Hui.
It's that Yumi has become
a person who praises others now.
Good job.
Seriously?
Yeah, this is good.
It's gotten so much better.
Thanks for all the hard work.
I was bracing to get chewed out.
Thanks so much.
But it feels really light.
Isn't this a little half-hearted?
You can't mean it every single time.
She's been kind of discouraged lately.
Sure, I'll see you tomorrow.
She actually praised me.
[It's just a brief idea,
but I'm suggesting it for your review]
Why is she not improving at all?
Sometimes even hollow praise is necessary,
she figured that out with age.
But...
[Maltese wins dog show]
Shin Soon Rok...
I know exactly what kind of guy you are.
[Winner at the dog show, too!]
Bet he opens the meeting with Maltese talk.
Alright then.
That dog show story was made up.
It was a complete fib,
but I'll find something similar
and send over the link, no matter what.
I mean, with so many competitions out there,
there's got to be a Maltese runner-up.
[Most wins at the dog show!]
Oh, hey Na Hui.
Did you read PD Shin's email?
Email? No.
He reached out and mentioned
he sent the script feedback two nights ago.
He noticed you haven't seen it yet
and asked if you could
check it before the meeting.
There's more feedback?
He's still not done with the Maltese thing?
Did PD Shin fight a Maltese
in his past life or what?
I don't really know what it says either.
Got it, I'll take a look.
Okay.
Seriously.
[Maltese wins dog show]
[Shin Soon Rok]
Writer Kim, it's Shin Soon Rok.
Here's some more feedback for you.
[Sent at 02:12]
Seriously?
Two in the morning?
So the Maltese is absolutely off the table?
Important enough to email
at two in the morning?
I've had it with you, Shin Soon Rok.
And why is it this long?
He barely talks but writes forever.
The thing that caught my eye in this draft
was the way the emotions change.
Like,
"How could someone
- in love be so calm?"
- He gets it.
He really gets it.
He gets exactly what I was going for.
I've been waiting for notes like this.
Yes, exactly!
What?
Since when is he this insightful?
I'm kind of thrown.
I think it'll land as a big turn.
The emotional void in this scene
does more than just explain what's happening.
It makes you reconsider when to end things.
This one's the real deal!
Finally, a compliment delivery from the heart!
- Deliver this to PD Shin.
- Got it.
This kind deserves a reply.
Hi PD Shin, I just read your email.
The feedback's really going to help.
The part I was stuck on is...
Hey, where're you going?
You...
[Pride Cell]
When did you wake up?
- Give me that!
- Hey, what's your problem?
No compliments for Shin Soon Rok.
I, Pride Cell, won't allow it!
This is heavy.
Compliment deliveries for Shin Soon Rok
are suspended for now, understand?
Forget it.
[PD Shin]
He did one thing right
and I'm overreacting.
PD Shin,
I've read your email.
A compliment would be wasted on you.
[PD Shin]
Hey, PD Shin.
Hello.
Writer Kim,
you're not at the studio?
I just stepped out.
What's up?
Well...
I came by to give you something.
Then...
I'll leave it with security.
Wait, I'm down at the parking lot.
Oh, PD Shin.
Hello.
What brings you here unannounced?
Just wanted to drop this off.
What is it?
This is the same dessert as yesterday.
Oh my.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
Writer Kim Ju Ho specifically asked for it.
Oh, these things happen.
You didn't have to...
Yes, dessert!
Three Michelin-star dessert!
I've wanted this so bad!
Smooth move, PD Shin.
Deliver this to PD Shin.
Put my whole heart into it.
Okay, I got it.
What?
Hey! Where are you going now?
Hungry Cell really wants this sent.
I, Pride Cell,
still don't allow it!
I'm really...
This is so heavy.
This wasn't necessary,
but thanks, I'll enjoy it.
Okay.
See you on meeting day.
Give him a ride, at least.
That much, I, Pride Cell, allow.
Where are you going?
Headed to the publisher.
- Let me drop you off.
- No, I'm fine.
Get in.
I'm heading to the publisher to see the editor.
Come on, get in.
Okay.
Let's head out.
Sure.
She shouldn't have offered him a ride.
- How come?
- I'm so anxious.
The publisher's like 20 minutes away.
What are they supposed to talk about?
PD Shin's not gonna talk.
What then?
They're going the same way.
She can't bail on him.
She could die from how awkward this is.
This isn't going to work.
- Reaction No. 1!
- Yes!
Hey, Reaction No. 1, what're you doing?
Looking through the chat list.
Hold on a second.
It's already silent.
What do they do?
Let's play music.
That way they can stop talking.
Any music you're into?
Not really, no.
Oh, okay.
Then...
Hey, there's a car!
Oh my!
What's wrong with that car?
Why's he coming in the exit?
What's up with him?
Writer Kim, you came in the wrong way.
What?
Look over there.
- Oh, what do I do?
- Hey, what're you doing?
Oh no, what now?
- No...
- You should back up first.
Back it up.
A bit further back should do it.
Right, reverse.
Reverse...
- Let me help you.
- Sure.
Stop!
Watch the right side!
Try going forward first.
- And then reverse.
- Got it.
Wheel to the right.
Stop there.
Go ahead and reverse now.
- Just keep backing up.
- Got it.
Slowly crank the wheel to the right.
To the right?
Stop there!
How about I take over?
Yeah, that sounds good.
Writer Kim?
Step out, please.
I can't really get out though...
- Come out this way.
- Okay.
Hold on.
Thank you.
Get in.
PD Shin's a good driver.
What a relief.
- What're you doing?
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Gosh, he scared me.
Let's grab a cab.
I'll handle the parking.
Yeah, that works.
I got so startled too...
Okay.
I was really on edge.
What would she do without PD Shin?
Take this as a rush delivery.
Got it.
Hey, where to this time?
It's a rush job.
Not happening!
My pride still won't allow...
You're still at it?
It's only polite to compliment him.
Don't let pride wreck Yumi's manners!
Manners Cell, good job.
Hurry, deliver it! Go, go!
Okay!
Go!
I'll call a taxi.
Thank you so much.
You drive really well.
It's nothing.
No, really.
What if you hadn't been there?
That was such a mess.
How long have you been driving?
Well...
About six months since I started again.
Six months?
Yes.
- Who's there?
- Who is it?
Hi, I'm from Soon Rok's village.
I've got a delivery.
Soon Rok sent a delivery too.
- What is it?
- I hope it's nice.
This could help them get closer.
What's this?
- Not every delivery is a compliment.
- What is that?
It's totally blank.
Why's the paper empty?
Wait a second.
It's not empty.
Wait, there's a secret message.
A secret code?
Look, it's showing up!
- "Quit"
- "driving"
- "already."
Some deliveries are silent mockery.
[Quit driving already]
- Quit driving already.
Whoever gets this delivery
- feels upset for no reason.
- That jerk...
They feel completely insulted.
That was fast.
Going up.
The doors are closing.
Writer Kim?
[Episode 6: Time for a Change]
Hey, Fishing Cell.
- Yeah?
- Got another angry snapper today?
If every day were like this, I'd be set.
PD Shin deserves a thank-you gift.
Rational Cell.
I'm freaking out again.
Seriously, what's wrong now?
I'm so nervous.
She's got Busan tomorrow, needs sleep.
What if she misses the train?
Really.
Seriously.
She's still wide awake.
She'd sleep if you stopped panicking.
So hungry!
Let's eat something!
Let's have a midnight snack!
What's wrong with you?
I'm starving.
I'm hungry.
Yumi, let's eat the 3-star dessert.
Come on, let's eat it.
I've been craving it for a while.
Forget it, I won't touch it.
I'd rather eat my bungeoppang.
Because of that guy, I keep snacking.
My blood sugar's dropping.
How long have you been driving?
Come on, I'm still learning.
He reversed once and looked at me like that?
Unbelievable.
[Quit driving already]
Told you not to send that package.
You sent it on your own, your fault!
I didn't know he had zero manners.
I want dessert!
Let's eat dessert!
- Hey! Have some pride, please!
- Dessert!
- You'd eat his charity dessert now?
- I want dessert!
But I want it!
Dessert!
Guys, aren't you going to bed?
- Dessert!
- When am I supposed to work?
Hey.
We hired PD Shin to help me write.
Not to piss me off every day!
Can't get a moment of peace here!
Calm down.
She'll adjust to him eventually.
No, swap him out.
Swap him out?
Tell Editor An we want a new PD.
If he's in the way, he must be removed.
Should I
just ask for a new PD?
You see Editor An in Busan tomorrow.
No PD Shin around. It's the perfect time.
Didn't you say his feedback was useful?
If I can't write just to get his notes,
I'd rather skip it completely.
That might really be the better choice.
Shin Soon Rok, the pain in the neck,
isn't going to change anytime soon.
Exactly my point.
All right, let's say she meets him.
Then what does she tell him?
So...
You're saying kick PD Shin out?
Yeah.
Sure, understood.
If he's no help to your work, he's out.
But...
could you tell me
what specifically bothered you?
Oh, well...
He called Maltese dogs stupid.
Because he called Maltese dogs stupid?
Is that really a reason to replace him?
That sounds kind of petty.
He took all eight Strawberry Cream
Custard Bungeoppang I love, and it upset me...
Over eight Strawberry Cream Bungeoppang?
Gosh, that's pretty petty too.
Bungeoppang? Really?
We rode the bus together,
and he just put his earphones on alone.
Over earphones?
Gosh, that's super petty!
He laughed at me
for being a bad driver.
He was definitely laughing at me.
His face,
it was exactly like this!
No way!
This is way too petty!
No.
There's no real reason to replace him.
No justification.
These reasons are just lame.
I'll only embarrass myself.
But
the lame reasons make me even madder.
Why am I so annoyed?
Come on, let's calm down.
A trip to Busan will clear your mind,
and you may see it differently.
Shin Soon Rok isn't worth it.
- Shin Soon Rok isn't worth it.
Yeah, let's do that.
I'll decide when I get back.
Why am I even stressing over him?
9 a.m.
I'm here a bit early.
Hi PD Jang, I made it.
Rational Cell,
something's bugging me.
What are you worried about now?
You know,
what if PD Jang suddenly can't make it
and PD Shin shows up instead?
- What would she do then?
- Hey!
Quit saying horrible stuff like that!
Take the train to Busan with that guy?
For that many hours?
Yumi seriously couldn't breathe.
She could die!
- Hi, PD Jang.
- Writer Kim!
Where are you?
What do I do?
Something happened.
My younger sister's having early labor,
and nobody's home right now.
I need to go with her.
Oh my, that's terrible.
So I asked PD Shin to go instead.
PD Shin?
I knew it!
I said I was worried!
He just left, but he may run a little late.
Wait,
am I traveling with PD Shin?
Yes, why don't you get on first?
He can take the next train if he's late.
Oh, sure.
Yes, understood.
Come on, be late, please be late.
Don't come!
Good morning, passengers.
This is the express train to Busan Station.
Our crew will do everything we can
to make your ride pleasant.
No way I can ride with Shin Soon Rok.
How do I put up with that awkwardness?
Even seeing his face bugs me.
Come on, be late. It's better that way.
[Busan]
Train's moving.
- Hurray! We're saved!
- Hurray!
Is this really something to celebrate?
We're supposed to be a team...
Oh, I don't care.
Writer Kim.
I barely made the train.
You heard about it, right?
I'm going with you instead.
Oh, right.
Oh, sure.
So, you made it on?
Yeah,
I had to run.
Oh, you had to run.
Oh, good thing we're going together.
You usually wear glasses, right?
Yeah, I left them behind.
I see.
Without glasses, he seems like someone else.
Yeah, and his hair's down in front.
Everyone, no time for gossip.
Red alert!
Okay, everyone get ready.
Especially you, Reaction No. 1!
- Stay sharp.
- Got it!
Emotion Cell, Pride Cell, stay calm.
You've got Cursing Cell locked up, right?
Don't let her say a word.
Manners Cell,
stay chill if he puts earphones on.
- Hungry Cell!
- Yeah?
Be ready if he eats snacks by himself.
It's two and a half hours to Busan.
We just need to hold on for that long.
When we're in Busan,
the super friendly Editor An is waiting.
- We got this!
- Right!
Great, going alone would've been dull.
Please sit down.
No, my seat is over there.
Oh, is that so?
They didn't have a seat next to yours.
Got it.
- He's sitting somewhere else!
- He's not sitting with us!
See you when we arrive.
Sure.
Oh, thank goodness.
All right, emergency's over.
Get some rest until we reach Busan.
Hold on.
This seems weird.
You think he sat apart on purpose?
Because he didn't want to sit with Yumi.
- What?
Look how many empty seats there are.
Doesn't that feel weird?
So many empty seats around,
he chose the farthest seat?
He actually sat far away on purpose?
If that's the case, I'm not letting it slide.
No way, it can't be.
If that's real, it's outrageous.
I'm the one holding back here!
Hello?
Hey, Writer Kim, traveling okay?
Yes, I boarded a little bit ago.
I heard something came up for PD Jang.
Right, so I'm going with PD Shin.
Right, I was told.
I've got work, I'll come down later.
Let's grab dinner tonight.
Sounds good.
Well...
The thing is,
so, about PD Shin.
Okay.
Is he with you? I can call you back.
No, our seats are separate, he's far away.
So regarding PD Shin...
What now?
Why's he dragging it out like this?
I'm already nervous.
It's only been a few days since he joined,
so I just wanted to check,
is it all right if we reassign him?
Reassign? So you're...
swapping the PD out?
Right, if you don't mind, can we swap him?
Make some noise!
Shin Soon Rok's out, oh yeah!
- Shin Soon Rok's out, oh yeah!
Oh, sure,
I'm fine
with that.
Really? You don't mind?
It is a bit of a shame,
but...
we just started working together,
so it won't really set things back.
Oh, that's a relief.
Thanks for understanding.
No problem.
I'll look for another solid PD for you.
All right, see you there.
Yes, see you later.
Is it really working out this easily?
Perfect timing.
He's out without her saying anything petty.
Good thing she held back.
Patience really does pay off.
Finally, I can focus on writing.
Wait.
So this trip is my last one with him?
Oh my.
Now I'm actually enjoying this ride.
Please insert your card.
Why not, I'm in a good mood.
Here, drink this while you work.
Oh, thank you.
I just talked to Editor An.
We just started, and already it's goodbye.
Right?
Guess we need a farewell party.
I'll miss working with you.
I'm sorry.
You've got nothing to be sorry for...
Thank you for understanding.
Go ahead and answer it.
Hello?
Yeah, I just left.
Something feels off.
Totally off.
Let's check it out.
Hi, Writer Kim.
Hi, Editor An.
I've got a question.
Why are you swapping him all of a sudden?
Sorry?
Did PD Shin ask for it, by any chance...
Oh, he already told you?
Juggling it with his other work was hard,
so he wants to focus on just one project.
Seems it was overwhelming him.
What the heck?
So he's the one who wanted out?
Yumi was holding back this whole time.
Now he's the one leaving?
If anyone's dumping anyone, it's Yumi!
Who's he to drop Yumi?
This is killing me!
He's leaving anyway.
He's leaving even if you hold back. Let it out!
You're old enough to speak up, Kim Yumi!
Let me sit beside you for a moment.
We need to talk.
- Pardon?
- You don't like working with me?
What is it exactly?
Could you be specific?
I want an answer.
Wait, lightning? Out of a clear blue sky?
- Hey! What the...
- Didn't he miss it intentionally?
Come on, why?
We're in trouble.
The whole village is in chaos!
Did Love Cell wake up?
What for?
- Thump, thump.
- Writer Kim.
Thump, thump.
Why's her heart pounding out of nowhere?