(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 23]
See? What did I tell you?
Ming,
what's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
He's choking.
What's wrong?
I think he's choking.
Are you choking on food?
Right?
What should we do?
Here, let me help.
How are you?
Get up.
Slowly.
-How are you?
-Let me help you.
I'll help you get it out.
Ready? One, two, three.
One, two, three.
How are you?
Sit down first.
Come on, slowly.
You scared me to death.
Just now,
it felt like
my whole life flashed before my eyes.
A life flashback?
You...
You practically got
a second chance at life.
Ming,
are you okay?
Are you okay or not?
I'm fine.
I'm fine now.
Thank you,
Mr. Ji.
It's nothing. Glad you're okay.
Are you really okay?
Yes.
Of course I am.
I don't think you are.
You'd better go to
the hospital for a checkup.
You still need to go to the hospital
for a further checkup.
You can't take this lightly.
-I'll send him there.
-Come on.
Come, slowly.
Slowly.
Let's go.
Can you do it?
Leave it to me.
Okay.
Wait for me.
I'll be right back.
-I'll wait for you.
-Be careful.
Hurry up and get checked.
It's not like we're playing mahjong—
we're not waiting for a fourth player.
What happened?
The old man choked.
I'm taking him to the hospital.
Be careful on the way.
Okay.
Go quickly.
Are there any other solutions?
I'll make some calls to find someone.
Now?
It's too late for a last-minute effort.
We haven't worked together before.
How can we perform?
Can the performance still go as planned?
Ms. Xu, the guests are about to enter.
Copy that.
Take care of the guests outside first.
What about the band?
Leave the band
to me.
Don't worry.
I've got this.
[Lusia University 60th Anniversary]
Hello. Please come in.
Ms. Dianjiangchun.
It's me. I heard your hotel
has a jazz performance tonight.
I just came to join the fun.
Let me find you a seat.
Follow me.
Thank you.
This is a good seat.
Please have a seat.
It's okay.
Thank you.
It's fine.
Go do your work. Don't worry about me.
Let me know if you need anything.
Miyu.
Chairman Wei.
The decoration has quite a nice vibe.
How did the rehearsal go this morning?
Those old guys won't
sing out of tune, will they?
They...
They are here.
Please take a seat here.
[Lusia University 60th Anniversary]
Do you want to watch our performance too?
Yes. Can we?
Of course.
Come.
Thank you.
This way, please.
Sit here.
You can stay here.
Thank you, Mr. Ji,
for saving us.
Here's to our cooperation.
Thank you.
What does it say?
Let's see.
Ji Feng.
Thank you.
[A jazz performance by Shanghai's
old-school gentlemen]
[Old Shanghai jazz performance]
[Uncles' jazz music]
[The most stylish in Shanghai]
[Comments]
[Where is this show?]
[Everyone, this is the jazz performance
at Purong Hotel]
[The guy in the white suit
playing saxophone is so handsome]
[I didn't know jazz could sound this good]
[Purong is amazing]
[Ahhh, I'm here live—
the location is Purong Hotel]
[Everyone, hurry and come!]
[I'm so happy.]
[It's nice.]
[Purong Hotel jazz performance
recap is here]
[A reunion after sixty years,
an unforgettable night]
[Meiling's life]
[Sort by popularity]
[Come copy this idea together]
[Purong Hotel's senior jazz performance
is going viral!]
Take care.
Okay.
Goodbye.
We will meet again.
Definitely, we will meet again.
Bye.
Bye. Bye.
Goodbye.
Daniel,
congratulations
on your successful performance.
Thank you.
This is just a beautiful dream.
What a nice dream.
It is a good dream.
But wouldn't it be great
if we could
never wake up from this dream?
Come to the Western restaurant.
Although the reaction was good today,
there are still many areas to improve.
I saw everyone really
enjoyed your performance.
Please give me more feedback.
Mr. Ji, you were looking for me?
Yes.
Aren't you going to introduce us?
This is our lobby manager, Xu Miyu,
and she is also the person in charge
of the concert tonight.
This is...
Ms. Dianjiangchun,
I'm a big fan of yours.
Really? Thank you for your attention.
My name is Jiang Zhichun.
Tonight's concert was really amazing.
Especially since
I didn't expect Mr. Ji
to have such talent.
Seriously, consider
appearing on my channel.
I will definitely turn you into
a superstar of the hotel industry.
No,
please don't joke with me.
You guys can talk.
We'll be in touch later.
Okay.
I'll walk you out.
It's fine, you guys talk.
Alright, take care.
Have a seat.
Try this.
What do you think of this place?
I want to hear your opinion.
I think
the equipment is pretty complete.
But
it lacks refinement.
Take these snacks for example. Look,
they're barely touched on the tables.
An amateur setup, right?
I didn't say that.
I think you're absolutely right.
We're on the same page.
Next, I want to
upgrade this amateur setup
and make it a truly
high-class performance venue.
What do you mean?
Didn't you hear what I said?
You want to continue the performances
in the Western restaurant?
As you saw,
tonight's performance
actually had a really good response.
So I decided
that the next performance
will be this Friday.
If Daniel finds out,
he'll be thrilled.
But I have other considerations.
Daniel's band
has an average age of over 70.
It's good. It's a selling point.
But at the same time, it's a risk.
Isn't this
exactly the value of Mr. Ji?
Health issues at an advanced age
are indeed a pain point,
but if we manage the risks well,
this pain point can also become
a rare highlight and selling point.
What do you think, Mr. Ji?
You're leaving this question to me.
So you were testing me.
So what kind of answer
do you want to give me?
Every close call without disaster
helps us rise to the next level.
So,
I won't be scared off by a minor accident.
After all, people always aim higher.
Then,
how about you and I share the risks
together?
I think the performances here
can continue long-term,
but on one condition—
I want the person managing them
to be you.
Me?
Yes.
Really, I need you.
[Party A: Purong Hotel Co., Ltd.]
[Party B: Daniel and his friends' band]
Really?
Yes.
Really.
Yes!
You were right to come back.
[Daniel and his friends]
Attention, everyone.
Starting today,
Ms. Xu will not only be our lobby manager,
but she will also work
at the jazz bar at night.
So please be understanding.
If you can solve a problem yourselves,
don't always bother Ms. Xu.
All right.
Back to work.
How impressive can she be?
At work, she's juggling two jobs at once.
Well, she's got powerful backing.
[Purong Hotel]
Lu Xiaoyan, make three copies of this.
What are you doing?
In broad daylight,
you're giving me a heart attack?
Come up.
Director Bai, ever since I joined Purong
and the Front Office,
I've been working under you.
You know how much overtime I've worked
and how many all-nighters I've pulled.
But what happened?
Xu Miyu came out of nowhere,
stole my lobby manager position.
She's holding onto the jazz bar too.
Why does Xu Miyu get
all the benefits to herself?
Why?
You didn't say a single word for me.
Don't cry.
Alright.
Stop crying.
I highly recognize your ability,
and I feel it's unfair to you too.
But the way Xu Miyu does things
is truly flawless.
Besides, she has
the general manager's backing.
What am I supposed to do?
Then what do you want me to do?
You make empty promises all day
without giving anything practical.
Should I even keep working here?
Are you asking me
to fight a losing battle?
If I can't survive here,
who will promote you?
But I...
Cut the crap and get out of the car.
Get out!
Wait.
The height of that light is wrong.
Move the whole chandelier up
by about a meter, okay?
Alright, let's step it up, everyone.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Mr. Ji.
Mr. Duan.
The stage looks great.
You really know how to spend my money.
You have to spend money to make money.
What's wrong, Mr. Duan?
Why didn't you find a comfortable place
instead of coming here?
I'm on-site inspection.
Did you think I was just pampered?
The tableware doesn't match.
The cooking is bad too.
Brother, come help out.
Hurry up and help.
Waiter!
The service is a total mess too.
How can you expect me to trust you,
Mr. Ji?
Mr. Duan,
you need to
trust your own investment vision.
But when I invested,
I didn't expect you would come.
Surprise.
Do you know what they said
when the Jazz Bar project was approved
by the board?
What did they say?
Flashy but impractical,
with short-term effects.
You worked your heart out
for the whole hotel,
but they don't appreciate it at all.
I don't need anyone's appreciation.
I'm just doing what
a hotel general manager should do.
Mr. Duan,
when our jazz bar opens,
do you want me
to save a few tables for you?
Just this?
I think you should forget about it.
You are definitely going to lose.
I will accept my defeat.
Take care.
Didn't you go see Duan Aoxiang?
He invited you for afternoon tea?
Duan Aoxiang is right.
Before our jazz bar opens,
we must get our refreshments
sorted out quickly.
And stop restocking
that durian puff.
Okay.
By the way,
you and this VIP Chun
have been interacting a lot
and chatting quite happily.
She called again
to ask about your schedule.
What VIP Chun?
[Jiang Zhichun]
I have a new idea.
Let's have dinner tonight and talk.
I'll pick you up.
Stop pretending.
I have a feeling
that she may not necessarily
be coming for our Purong Hotel.
Dianjiangchun is indeed
a valued patron of our Purong Hotel.
No matter what she's after,
as long as it's a win-win situation,
we should do our best to cooperate.
What if she takes advantage of work
to talk to you about something else?
Outside of work,
we
have nothing else to talk about.
Junior,
do you have someone in your heart?
Right?
Does she know?
Ms. Xu.
Ms. Jiang.
Are you here to check in?
No, I have an appointment.
I bought you some milk tea.
Oh, how can I accept this?
It's a perk for my followers.
Take it.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
We'll be seeing each other often.
By the way,
why do you think milk tea
is so appealing to young people?
Sorry, it's an occupational hazard.
A few milk tea shops
have been talking to me
about partnerships lately.
For someone
at my age,
I really can't tell the difference
between the different brands.
How do you think I should choose?
Could it be because
milk tea conveys
goodwill better than water?
Not only is it sweet,
but it's also versatile.
You can add anything to it.
It rejects nothing,
which makes it a very easygoing drink.
That's a good angle.
My appointment is here.
I'll get going.
Thank you.
Ji Feng.
Let's find a place to talk.
Let's go. My car is outside.
Did you drive here?
Then I'll ride with you.
Let's go.
Okay.
I'll show you something.
You've published a new book?
Take a look. What do you think?
[Chun's Daily Taste]
It's great.
The photos are very good.
This is my first time publishing a book.
It records my travels, shop explorations,
and some food notes.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Recently, our team
is also choosing a venue
for the new book's signing event.
We are dazzled by the choices,
and the more we look,
the less satisfied we become.
So,
could I hold the signing event
for my new book at your hotel?
Of course.
If it's not too much trouble.
Of course. It would be our pleasure.
Okay.
Hello, I've decided.
The book signing will be at Purong.
Eliminate the others.
Can I check out the venue next week?
I'll be at your full disposal.
Okay.
Hello, your fish is ready.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
Try their fish.
It's delicious.
Okay.
The fish is so tender.
It really is delicious.
It really is Dianjiangchun!
Let's go.
We really like you.
Hello. I really like your videos.
Can we take a picture with you?
Sure.
Sir, could you take a picture for us?
Thank you.
Okay.
One, two, three.
-It should be
-Thank you.
fine.
Are you that general manager
of Purong Hotel
who plays the saxophone?
I've seen you in a video.
Hello.
Really?
Are you two dating?
You misunderstood.
Can I take a picture with you alone?
Me too!
-I'll take one later.
-I need to use the bathroom.
Thank you.
My turn!
[Mei Restaurant]
How is it?
Their food tastes pretty good, right?
It's really delicious.
It's not easy.
Our tastes finally align.
You don't need to see me off.
I'll take a taxi back.
Why?
You're a public figure.
Why do you have more
of an idol burden than me?
I'm just kidding.
You don't work in the internet ecosystem.
So you don't understand
my work environment.
Let's talk in the car.
I promise you won't affect
my public image.
Let's go.
Okay.
We created this Dianjiangchun persona
in a way that naturally invites shipping—
she's single, beautiful,
tasteful, and romantic.
Almost any male guest around my age
with decent looks
who shows up on my livestream
ends up being pushed by the audience
as my rumored boyfriend.
But,
this does nothing but good for my traffic.
The other side of traffic is scandals,
you know?
Being my rumored boyfriend
is not a bad deal.
They've all become popular.
I am very valuable.
Thank you.
Thank you for being willing to
help Purong Hotel.
Is that all?
I've arrived.
Thank you.
Bye.
Ji Feng!
When will we meet next time?
I'll ask the PR department
to contact your team for
your signing event.
What about me?
What?
Can't I ask you out?
Keep in touch on WeChat.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
I'm off work.
♪ Love is truly not easy to obtain ♪
♪ I can't hold on to you
even if you want to leave ♪
♪ I tell myself I'm not hurt
once things settle down ♪
♪ but I realize I can't deceive myself ♪
♪ I always say life is already
hard enough ♪
♪ so what else is there worth trying for ♪
♪ Friends comfort me,
telling me to have a drink ♪
♪ But I've already started living
like I'm not myself anymore ♪
Dianjiangchun's team will come to
the hotel to check the venue tomorrow.
We must treat them
[Purong Hotel]
with the highest standard for VIPs.
We must provide the service
that best reflects
the style of Purong Hotel.
No department
can take chances.
Any negligence
will be strictly punished
according to
the hotel's management rules.
Director Li,
[Purong Hotel]
make an interview flowchart for me
and send it to the work group.
Okay, Mr. Ji.
Who's in charge of your department?
Is it still Lu Zhenzhen?
She was rejected
right after I submitted the list.
It seems our Mr. Ji
isn't interested in her.
This place needs to be decorated
more exquisitely.
Let me know if you
have any questions later.
No more kissing up to the new boss.
Just wait.
She'll come back to kiss up to you.
Come in.
Mr. Ji,
you asked for me?
Yes.
I've already informed
the other departments.
Our hotel will soon host
a new book signing event
for Dianjiangchun.
I want you to
follow up on this project.
Okay, Mr. Ji.
This is her new book.
Take it back and study it.
I see.
[Chun's Daily Taste]
Mr. Ji, did you meet Ms. Jiang before?
Sorry, I asked too much.
We were
college classmates.
I'll go back
and study this book carefully.
Don't worry.
[Purong Hotel Staff Apartment]
She is indeed a top blogger
with 10 million followers.
Her book is like a pictorial.
I'm starting to understand
why you like her.
So, we need to do a good job
with this book signing event.
We can't let her down
for trusting our Purong Hotel.
You're about to work
with your favorite blogger.
Why don't you look excited at all?
Of course I'm excited.
I am excited.
Are you?
You look like you have something
on your mind.
I don't have anything on my mind.
That's good.
Then I won't bother you anymore.
I'll go make you some supper.
Thank you, Qi.
[With old friends, let the past rest;
brew new tea, and begin again.]
[Let poetry and wine carry us
through our youth—Chun]
We were
college classmates.
[With old friends, let the past rest;
brew new tea, and begin again.]
[Let poetry and wine carry us
through our youth—Chun]
[Chun's Daily Taste]
[Always on the road
recording the flavors of the mortal world]
[Dianjiangchun – "Chun's Daily Taste"
New Book Sharing Event]
Ahead is
the multi-function hall prepared for you.
This way, please.
[Dianjiangchun –
New Book Sharing Signing Event]
Let me.
This is the main venue.
[Dianjiangchun –
New Book Sharing Signing Event]
[Always on the road
recording the flavors of the mortal world]
[Dianjiangchun – "Chun's Daily Taste"
New Book Sharing Event]
It's so beautiful.
I really like it.
[Dianjiangchun –
New Book Sharing Signing Event]
Thank you, Ji Feng.
Let's
take a look up ahead.
We chose to use blue and white
because...
Director Bai,
there's a situation
at the banquet hall entrance.
Ms. Xu, go take a look.
Okay.
So many people today.
[Always on the road
recording the flavors of the mortal world]
Miss,
when will the signing start?
[Dianjiangchun – "Chun's Daily Taste"
New Book Sharing Event]
Miss,
when will it start?
Excuse me.
It will start exactly at two o'clock.
Please wait a moment.
Everyone, please wait outside.
Ms. Jiang Zhichun has already arrived.
Once it starts, everyone
will have a chance to see her.
Please be patient for now, okay?
Okay.
Just a moment.
Calm down.
-Where is your director?
-I don't know.
Security Department.
We need help at the banquet hall.
Can you send some more people over?
Don't worry!
I know.
Please wait a moment, everyone.
You'll all get a chance to see her.
Just a moment.
[Always on the road
recording the flavors of the mortal world]
[Dianjiangchun – "Chun's Daily Taste"
New Book Sharing Event]
Why didn't you ask for help?
-Come on.
-It's OK.
Give this to me.
Thank you, Mr. Ji.
How are the preparations
for the upcoming talk?
The wiring is all set in the venue.
The cold buffet is being prepared.
As for the guest speaker,
I will personally be responsible
for bringing him to the banquet.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
[Banquet Hall]
Wait.
Your foot.
Thank you.
Let me help.
Lift it up.
[Banquet Hall]
Hold me.