=Eight Hundred=
(A week ago)
I found the person you were looking for.
Who is it?
Chen Hui didn't tell me.
He told you to go
to the Photo Studio to find him at 1 PM.
(Shiguang Photo Studio)
It's a deal.
I'll give you a discount.
When we're done,
I'll put the photos in the window
as a display.
No problem.
Alright, I'll get back to work then.
Sure thing.
It's okay.
Go change your clothes.
Like I said,
let's just
have a happy photo shoot today.
(Shiguang Photo Studio)
Did you find out who it is?
I did.
I'll take you there.
I haven't met the person either.
I have to pick them out for you.
Otherwise, you might get the wrong person
and say I'm lying to you again.
Where did Hui go?
Why isn't he back yet?
I'll go out and look for him.
Wait...
Which way?
Up the mountain ahead.
Where exactly are we going?
You'll know when we get there.
(Dialing)
The road is ending soon.
Where exactly are we going?
We're almost there. Just ahead.
Listen, don't you dare trick me.
I'll burn you alive if you do.
(Dialing)
Limin, Huo Kaiming wants me
to hand Cai over to him,
or he's going to burn me alive!
=Episode 9=
(Rainbow Glow)
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
Songge, the soda is here.
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink.
Get Active)
Songge.
Mr. Hu.
Could you come over and help me out?
What happened?
You'll see when you get here. Let's go.
Mr. Hu,
could you watch Chen Hui for a bit?
I have some
urgent business to attend to.
I still have deliveries
to make in the countryside.
It'll only be half an hour.
I'll give you an extra 100 yuan.
It's not about the money.
Mr. Hu,
when Chen Hui was well,
he treated you well, didn't he?
Now that he's sick, you're just going
to turn your back on him?
Songge, look at what you're saying.
Fine.
Go on now.
I'll keep an eye on him for you.
Thank you.
I'll be back soon.
(Welcome to Yingxiong)
I was wrong then.
I shouldn't have framed Huo Kaiming
for the cough syrup business.
The police will surely find out
that he wasn't the source of the traffic.
Now that I'm sick,
we must keep shipping goods
to divert the police's
suspicion away from us.
But all our downline dealers
have been arrested.
How can we ship anything?
I have a way.
A switch.
(People's Public Security)
Chief Liu.
Are you heading back
to the municipal PSB?
Once the colleagues
from the municipal PSB
finish handing over the evidence,
we'll go together.
Actually, I should have gone
to say goodbye to Mrs. Chen.
But your family has been so busy lately,
I didn't want to trouble you.
That's alright.
So, Chief Liu,
regarding this case,
does the municipal PSB
have any instructions?
The next step is to put all our effort
into capturing Huo Kaiming.
Right,
Jiao Yuqin who conned Huo Kaiming,
whose real name is Yu Susu,
has been caught in Yunchuan.
Colleagues from the municipal PSB
are escorting her back now.
Also, Yu Susu's
husband in Yunchuan said
Huo Kaiming once went to their house
and saw a photo of Yu Susu there.
No wonder.
I was wondering how he knew
Yu Susu and Jiao Yuqin
were the same gang.
Director Chen,
this should be
the last case I ever handle.
It's been a pleasure
working with you.
Chief Liu,
look,
who isn't intimidated by difficulties?
As long as we don't back down,
there will always
be chances to work together.
I'll remember that, Director Chen.
Thank you.
Chief Liu, I've finished
recording everything.
We're ready for the handover.
Good.
Wait.
Give me a glove.
Look, there's a glimmer
on the rim of the bottle.
Do you see it?
No, I don't.
You're looking with the light.
Come here. Everyone, come over.
Take a look, Chief Liu.
There is a ring of light.
It's colorful.
Limin, bring the cough syrup
we found in the lottery shop.
Okay.
(Peidun Cough Syrup)
Why don't those three bottles
have the colorful light?
I feel like I've seen
this rainbow glow somewhere before.
(Peidun Cough Syrup)
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
I heard from Han Ning
that you're going to
sell the lottery shop?
I'm afraid my mom won't be getting out.
I was just thinking
of saving some more money for her.
At least she could
live a bit more comfortably inside.
What about you, then?
Songge,
today is the last time
I'll be singing here.
I want to try my luck in Beijing.
Beijing?
How can you go out
and make it on your own?
It's too worrying.
Xin Yu, why don't you just stay
and sing at the skating rink?
My mom
harmed so many miners.
How can I stay in Fengyang?
Right now,
all I have left are my so-called dreams.
Xin Yu,
this is your salary.
It's calculated for the full month.
We can't help you
with anything else.
Take this
as our small investment
in your dream.
Thank you, Songge,
but I can't take this extra money.
You have plenty of your own expenses.
Just take it.
Thank you, Songge.
Among all of us,
you're the first to leave
this 800-meter radius area.
You can turn your back so decisively
for the sake of your dream.
I'm sure you will succeed.
Maybe one day,
I'll be famous, who knows?
Songge,
you're a kind-hearted girl.
I believe that your illness
will get better.
Chen Hui,
you'd better get well soon, too.
Songge is still waiting
for you to take care of her.
I'm off.
Keep it up.
What I'm about to sing
is my final song here.
I hope that within
this 800-meter radius area,
every one of you
has the courage
to chase their own dreams
and realize their truest selves.
"Boundless Oceans, Vast Skies,"
this is for you.
♪Today, I♪
♪Watch the snow
drift by in the cold night♪
♪Drifting afar with a chilled heart♪
♪Chasing in the wind and rain♪
♪Unable to distinguish
shadows in the mist♪
♪The wide sea and sky, you and I♪
♪Could we change? (Who isn't changing?)♪
♪Forgive me for being wild
and unfettered my whole life♪
♪I'm also afraid
that one day I might fall♪
♪Forsaking my ideals♪
♪Anyone can do that♪
♪What's there to fear
if one day it's just you and me?♪
♪Forsaking my ideals♪
♪Anyone can do that♪
♪What's there to fear if one day♪
♪It's just you and me?♪
Xin Yu,
keep it up!
Go, Xin Yu!
Xin Yu, you're the best!
Go!
(Ding Yue Clinic)
It runs on batteries.
Look.
- Open it here?
- Open it.
I should show you how.
No need.
Isn't it just like making a phone call?
Don't break it, okay?
There's only one in the whole station.
It's for official business.
It was just approved.
Come on, how could I break it?
I'm making a call.
What call?
This is public property. Don't...
- Don't use it for personal calls.
- No.
I'll just give you
the money for the bill later.
- What do you mean?
- Hello?
Liu Na, it's Ding Yue.
Mrs. Chen.
Well, Hongbing's police station
issued a phone,
and he told me to try it out.
I don't have many friends,
so I called you.
How have you been lately?
I'm all right.
I had a slight fever last night.
Well, then,
did you take medicine?
I did.
I'm much better.
How is Hui doing?
Hui is doing well.
The doctor said
his chances of recovery are quite good.
That's good.
Next time you bring him to the city,
make sure to let me know.
Sure. When we go to the city,
(Cyclophosphamide Tablets)
we'll come visit you.
We'll come see you.
Limin is here. Give me the phone.
I'm not finished.
Limin is here. I have to go.
Chief Liu,
Ding Yue still has things to tell you,
but I have to set off now.
Goodbye, Liu Na.
Chief Liu,
how is the case going?
It's already in the litigation process.
Cai and Yu Susu
are charged with attempted murder.
They're likely to get a life sentence.
The evidence that Huo Kaiming
committed murder and burned the body
is solid.
We just need to catch him.
Is there still no news from Tang?
They found a type
of crystal on the bottle
of Peidun Cough Syrup
with the colored light,
but it's not a common chemical.
There's no way to identify it yet.
Just wait and see.
All right, then.
Chief Liu,
you're always welcome
in Fengyang. Goodbye.
Okay, goodbye.
What's wrong, Master?
The light spots
on the cough syrup bottle,
the multicolored ones,
I've definitely seen them somewhere.
I just can't remember.
Master, it's just that there's
too much going on at home.
Once this is over,
I'm sure you'll remember.
What's going on now?
Let's go over and take a look.
Pay up! You're drinking and not paying?
Everyone, come and look at this.
- Hurry up.
- He's not paying for his drink.
Move aside!
What are you doing? Don't move!
He drank something and didn't pay.
- Don't move!
- He won't pay for his drink!
What's happening here?
Call and get him to the hospital.
Step back.
Hello, is this the Workers' Hospital?
Someone collapsed
in front of the Electronics Mall.
Come quickly.
Director Tong.
- Hongbing.
- We're back.
Director Tong,
(Fengyang Mine Workers' Hospital Lab Report)
the miner's test results are out.
It says he has a high level
of Kejianin in his body,
which caused a hallucinogenic reaction.
A hallucinogenic reaction?
Didn't we already take down
the Peidun Cough Syrup
distribution network?
Why is the cough syrup appearing again?
This isn't the only case in town.
We tracked these people down
and checked again.
They all claim they're innocent.
They all say they
never bought cough syrup.
After investigating,
it turns out they're telling the truth.
This matter
is a bit strange.
We've arrested so many downline dealers
and so many sellers.
This situation had stopped
for quite some time.
So, how did these people
who suddenly hallucinated
come into contact with the cough syrup?
This opponent is out of the ordinary.
He can pull off
many inexplicable things.
To be honest,
I still haven't figured out
how he's doing this.
Regarding the recent cases
in Fengyang involving
the cough syrup
and the body-burning homicide,
the nature of these crimes is vile,
causing great harm to society.
On behalf of the Fengyang Police Station,
I solemnly promise here...
You haven't even caught
the person in this case yet.
That's enough, Dad.
Just eat your dinner.
We'll bring
the criminal suspects to justice.
Look at this child.
He's not eating or drinking.
This can't go on.
Come on.
Dad, what are you doing?
Let's feed him some porridge.
Fine...
I'll do it. I'll feed him.
He has his own.
Okay.
Hui, please get well soon.
Come, here.
Come.
Blow on it.
You're taking too long.
Let me do it.
See?
Look at that.
I said let me do it,
- but you still fought me for it.
- What happened?
Aren't you just making a mess, Dad?
You've gone and scalded my grandson!
Hurry!
Go get some cold water and a towel.
You sit down.
It's okay, Dad. It's okay.
I'll take care of it for him.
Let me see.
Quickly.
It's red.
It's fine. Just don't touch it.
It doesn't hurt, does it, Hui?
Son,
today,
Mr. Huang's trial starts.
I
have to go to the city.
After lunch,
I'll be back.
Okay?
Before,
I always linked you
to this case.
Maybe because of those things,
it turned you into this.
Do you hate me?
I had no choice.
I am a policeman.
Try to understand me.
Dad.
You can speak?
I knew
you'd get better.
This is great.
My boy,
you've finally recovered.
I knew
you would get better.
Good boy.
Don't cry.
It was my fault.
It was all my fault.
(Radiation hazard.
Do not enter when light is on)
Thank you, Doctor.
(CT Room)
We have to wait two hours
to get the scans.
Hui,
Mr. Huang's trial is today.
I have to go to the court.
Songge
and your mom are with you, okay?
It's fine, Dad.
Go ahead.
Good boy.
Come back early.
Okay, I will.
Thank you.
Hurry up.
Don't worry.
Does the defendant have
any objections to the criminal facts
(Judge, Presiding Judge, Court Clerk)
alleged by the public prosecutor?
No objections.
The case of defendant Huang Liang
for illegal coal mining
is now for sentencing.
The judgment is as follows.
All rise, please.
Defendant Huang Liang
(Jiangbin Municipal People's Court)
mined coal without
obtaining a mining permit.
His actions constitute
the crime of illegal mining.
The charges
by the prosecution are established,
and this court supports them.
(Defendant)
Defendant Huang Liang surrendered himself,
and a lighter or reduced sentence
may be given by law.
In accordance with Articles 343
and 67 of the Criminal Law
of the People's Republic of China,
the judgment is as follows.
Defendant Huang Liang
is guilty of illegal mining
and is sentenced
to three years and six months,
with a fine of 370,000 yuan.
If you disagree with this judgment,
you may, within 10 days from the
second day after receiving the judgment,
file an appeal
through this court or directly
with the Intermediate People's Court.
This trial is adjourned.
Defendant Huang Liang is to be taken back
to the detention center
to remain in custody.
(Jiangbin Municipal People's Court)
Chief Liu.
Director Chen, get in.
Sorry, I'm late.
As soon as I got to the city,
I took Hui to the hospital first,
which delayed me.
What's wrong with Hui now?
It's good news this time.
He can recognize people,
and he can even speak.
Really? That's great.
Isn't it?
This past month,
Ding Yue and I have been worried sick.
Is your wife here?
She's our family's
"Health Commissioner."
How could she not come for this?
She's at the hospital with Songge.
By the way, Chief Liu,
any news on
Huo Kaiming?
Judging by the blood at the scene,
Hui's blow must have wounded him badly.
He likely died in some mountain gully.
Lately,
I've been mulling something over.
It's not exactly new information,
just a line of thinking.
What's that?
Back then,
when Gao Ying's incident happened,
Huo Kaiming was
the safety officer on duty.
At the very least, the method
of burning the body was the same.
I was thinking,
could we...
Director Chen,
regarding the application
to reopen Gao Ying's case,
the municipal PSB says
they need more supporting materials.
I'll have to go back and pull
the original files from back then.
Alright.
I'll wait for progress on your end.
Director Chen,
please don't mind me asking.
Go ahead.
Now that Hui is awake,
and things are going well
between you and your wife,
why bring this matter up again?
Speaking of our relationship,
Ding Yue and Gao Ying
were besties back then.
Even though so many years have passed,
if I don't clear this up,
I'll always feel
like I've failed Gao Ying
and failed myself,
especially being a police officer now.
I understand.
I'll find another way.
Thank you.
Hello?
Tang,
what is it?
It's about the cough syrup,
Director Chen.
We finally identified
the crystals on the bottle.
It's a substance called polyacrylamide.
I've already faxed
all the materials to your station.
Great.
The case
finally has a new lead.
Tang, thank you for your hard work.
Did you find out
what the substance is used for?
Its most common use for civilians
is in water treatment plants,
used for water purification.
A water treatment plant?
The scans show the blood clot in his brain
is already very small.
It's not a major issue.
Next, focus on restoring some movement.
After all, from lying down so long,
some of the muscles
have already atrophied.
He needs to stay active.
Come back for a check-up
if there are problems.
Thank you, Doctor.
Hearing you say that
puts us much more at ease.
Mom, I'm feeling a bit cooped up.
I want to go for a walk.
I'll go with him,
Mrs. Chen.
- Alright, take good care of him.
- Will do.
Get plenty of exercise.
Careful, Hui.
I'm fine.
Easy.
You two be careful.
Got it, Mrs. Chen.
(Management Promotes
Quality and Standards)
How could you just say you were fine?
You didn't even tell me in advance.
You scared me to death.
Every day I watched
my dad working so hard,
worrying until his hair turned white.
I really couldn't bear
to keep pretending.
This matter is finally over.
It's a relief.
No.
We can't completely
let our guard down yet.
Why?
To be honest, whether it's Lu Yuan,
Xin Yu, or Huo Kaiming,
I've never been afraid of them.
But there is one person
I can never win against.
Who?
- My dad.
- Hui.
The medicine is all picked up.
In two weeks,
just come back for a check-up.
- Okay.
- I'll take this.
Let's go home, and I will cook
something delicious for you.
Okay.
- Let's go.
The sun is really nice today.
Look at that.
- Dad.
- He's waiting at the door.
Look.
My eldest grandson, you're back.
I
have been worrying about you.
Who is he?
You don't know who he is,
- I'm your grandpa.
- Hui?
You don't even recognize your grandpa?
Hui,
look closely.
This is Grandpa.
You don't even recognize
your grandpa anymore?
This...
How could it turn out like this?
Didn't the doctor check
and say everything was fine?
How about this?
Let's go back to the hospital
for a check-up.
- No, we're not going back.
- Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
We're not going.
I was just joking.
How could I not recognize my grandpa?
You really scared me.
Was it you who burned my hand?
I don't remember that.
But I remember
that you said
you'd go fly kites with me.
- You rascal, you even fooled us.
- Let's go home.
I'm teasing you.
Let's go.
Seriously.
I really thought something was wrong.
- Stick.
- Chicken.
I told you.
It would've been better to go
to Liusan Mutton Restaurant
and buy some.
You insisted on making it yourself.
Well, after all that work,
it might not even
taste as good as theirs.
What do you know?
The stewed meat outside is so salty.
His nervous system has just recovered,
so can he have that much salt?
Songge can't eat out either.
Besides, the meat I stew
versus the meat from the restaurant,
- how can they be the same?
- Right.
- Isn't that right, Dad?
- It's not the same.
Nothing's as good as your cooking.
- Even Dad said so.
- Home-cooked is always best.
Fine.
You're right.
Come on, man.
Dad,
is this one okay?
This is good.
Hui, do you know?
Your mother,
for your sake,
hasn't had a single night of good sleep.
That you could pull through this time
is all thanks to your mother.
It's been very hard on her.
What can I do?
I've been used to it all my life.
After all, Fengyang
can't do without
your dad.
Don't even say it.
In this family,
if we didn't have your mother,
it'd be even worse.
That's true.
If I don't look after
our family, who will?
I'll do it.
You've got me too.
I'll look after things.
Dad,
you're the best
at looking after everyone.
Indeed.
Songge has been working hard lately too.
Between the roller skating rink
and taking care of Hui,
she's running back and forth.
It's painful to watch.
I'm fine.
Mrs. Chen,
lately, you and Mr. Chen
have been much more tired than I am.
I can see you both
are starting to get white hair.
Besides, I've been in this family
for so many years,
and you've always
been the ones taking care of me.
The things I do
aren't much at all.
Songge,
we are all one family.
Let's not talk about that.
Dad, your grandson is back today.
Even though you're happy,
the rules cannot be broken.
Only half a glass.
Half a glass.
That's enough.
Why did you pour it so full?
Look at this.
This is a waste of good grain.
But this liquor really does smell nice.
Is it good?
Nice. Good.
Come on, Hui.
Yes, Dad.
What kind of father are you?
Hui's just recovered.
Can he even drink?
Right, it's best
to listen to the doctor.
Here, you have a glass.
Mrs. Chen, you drink this juice.
Songge, I'll do it myself.
Alright.
Is everyone ready?
Come on, let's have a toast.
Come on, everyone is here today.
Let's congratulate Hui
on his full recovery.
Shall we?
- Welcome back.
- Thanks, Dad.
I wish you a speedy return to health, Hui.
Thanks, Grandpa. Thanks, Mom.
Dad, I wish you good health too.
Good. Good health to everyone.
Good health to everyone.
Dad, slow down.
Mrs. Chen,
these vegetables are delicious.
- Not too salty?
- No.
- Eat more.
- Alright, will do.
Come on, eat more.
Hui,
now that you're technically recovered,
there's something I need to ask you.
What is it, Dad?
The day of your accident,
what exactly
did Huo Kaiming say to you?
Yes,
what did he say?