Is Avi still coughing?
Not really, Doc.
Doc, they’re looking
for you in the ward.
We know each
other already, Doc.
She was my fiancée.
Go, Auntie! Go!
Be careful, Avi.
- Auntie… Auntie!
- Oh my god.
Baby! Avi!
Rich, I need to take her
to the hospital.
There's one nearby,
Ramirez Medical.
It’s okay.
There’s no more bleeding.
You’re okay.
Can I join you?
My… My wha—
Oh! Are you okay?
Haze, don’t you
have a girlfriend?
- Take a video.
- Hurry up. Here.
- All right.
- Let her go.
- So stingy!
- This way please.
Let’s sit down first.
Let’s wait for them to leave.
I’m sorry.
They’re not usually this wild.
Maybe because they still
couldn’t get anything from me
with those rumors going around.
Rumors.
I heard your conversation
with your friend.
You didn’t go for surgery?
No.
It’s gonna take me
five years more—
And I guess I was...
impatient.
I wanted to prove
myself quickly.
Ah, okay.
He wanted to prove
himself quickly?
To whom? His parents?
His siblings?
To me?
By the way, congratulations
on passing the boards.
Better late than never.
Thanks.
I’m sure your parents are proud.
Congratulations on
all your success, too.
Thanks.
Thank you for saving me earlier.
I think I can take it from here.
I’ll go ahead.
Hey, Sam. You left your—
They didn’t get any scoop
from you. Right, Sam?
Nothing really.
I was able to hide.
Actually, the guy you were with
in Japan is a hot topic.
The gossip sites and
vloggers are all over it now.
Anything for
the views, right? Jeez!
I even thought you
started this new rumor
to cover up the ones
about Avi being my daughter.
I wish, but someone
beat me to the idea.
It did take the spotlight off
the whole issue with Avi.
So, who was that guy
in the picture with you?
Haze Juarez.
You guys probably know him.
Of course.
I know all the hot men.
He’s FlyAsia’s CEO.
And he’s a pilot, too.
I heard about Akihiro Juarez?
Are they brothers?
Yup.
Hiro is Avrielle’s dad.
So, Avi is a Juarez.
Oh my.
So much tea!
You really know a lot
of high-profile people, Sam.
A supermodel and a socialite!
But seriously, Sam,
you need to stop
taking interviews.
You’ve got a big
fashion show coming up,
and people should be talking
about your modeling career,
not your love life.
Exactly. Stay away
from drama for now.
Avi’s birthday is coming up,
and I’m sure
I’ll see Haze there.
Just steer clear
of Haze for now
to avoid gossip, okay?
- Is the food ready?
- Yes, it’s all set.
Thank you.
- Hey!
- Hi!
Sit down.
Why are you doing that?
Didn’t you hire helpers for today?
Come on, I just want to help.
It’s my daughter’s birthday,
after all.
Wow.
Jeez, stop laughing
and help me out here.
Can’t you see
I’m already struggling?
- Help me, my hands are starting to hurt.
- Okay.
There you go.
So—
A few days ago,
I went to see Raylee
near Ramirez Medical.
I got caught in the middle
of a bunch of vloggers.
And…?
Clyden helped me
get away from them,
and he congratulated me
for making it as a model.
How did that make you feel?
Actually—
it felt nice.
I thought he was mad at me,
but maybe there’s still
a chance for us to be civil.
Or even become friends.
After all, he’s Avi’s
regular pediatrician
So, you’ll be seeing
each other regularly?
Yes.
No big deal.
We’re just regular friends.
Not special?
Whatever.
Let’s just inflate this already.
Your guests are about to arrive.
- Faster.
- Okay.
Wow, yours is huge.
How did you—
Was it supposed to be small?
I thought you liked them big?
I already have one.
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday,
happy birthday…
Happy birthday to you!
Thank you everyone!
Happy birthday!
Make a wish.
Wow!
Yay!
Okay, everyone…
You can have your seats.
And kids,
you can play again.
Okay?
Go, go, baby, go.
Stay here.
I have an announcement to make.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Uh...
So, everyone…
We’d like to
thank you for coming.
It means a lot to us.
Especially since
it’s Avi’s first birthday
with all of us complete,
as a family.
And because today
is such a special day,
we have an
announcement to make,
as a family.
Huh?
What kind of announcement?
You’ll see there are
envelopes under your plates.
Oh my god!
We’re getting married
in a few months.
Congratulations!
Must be nice.
Some people really have it all.
Don’t start with the
“must be nice” drama,
you all better show up, okay?
I want full attendance,
all right?
Hopefully all your
schedules line up.
- Just sit down already.
- Here, come on.
Sit here, Sevi.
Stop being emotional.
Come here.
Cheers!
Thank you.
Where’s the birthday girl?
She fell asleep.
Probably got tired from
all that dancing, huh?
I’m very happy for you and Hiro.
Look, if I’m not the
maid of honor, I’m not coming.
Come on,
who else would I even
choose as my maid of honor?
So, what now? You and
Avi are moving in with Hiro?
Most likely.
That means I won’t get to be
with Avi all the time anymore.
What am I gonna do now?
What if I just move to New York?
I’ve been wanting to live
there for so long anyway.
And now that you
and Avi have Hiro,
I can do the move.
What?
Jumping straight to New York?
You can always visit
us anytime you want.
You’re not just my best friend, okay?
You’re family to me and Avi.
You’re just drunk!
That’s why you’re talking
about all that moving nonsense.
No, I’m not. I’ve actually been
thinking about it for a while.
I didn’t even know you
were already apartment hunting.
Are you sure about this?
What about the people in
your life here in the Philippines?
Well, you’re right.
We can always see each other.
Just one word to Hiro and
you’ll find yourself
flying to New York already.
Wow.
And I can always visit
Manila whenever I can.
I’ll always support you in
whatever decisions you make in life.
But you have to be
really sure about it, okay?
Deep down, what do you really want?
Look at you!
You’re drunk.
You’re definitely drunk now.
I’m not drunk.
Well, I can still walk, see?
- Look.
- Uh-huh...
Wait, I’ll just go to the restroom.
- I’m not drunk.
- I’ll get back to you.
- That’s always how it starts.
It seems like you’re always drunk
when we see each other, huh?
What?
You might fall for me even more.
Hey!
You okay?
Feeling dizzy?
I want to sleep.
Sleep with me.
What?
Sleep with me, please.
I miss you.
I miss you, Clyden.
You’re really losing it, huh?
Begging someone to sleep with you.
I haven’t had sex for years.
Really?
You know,
if you told me that sober…
I will gladly accept it.
I’m curious—
Do you guys do it with other
women after you break up?
After my last breakup,
I just can’t do it with other guys.
What’s “it”?
Can you elaborate?
Is it—
Is it sex?
Are you asking me about sex?
Why are you saying it out loud?
But, yeah!
So?
Well—
I do it with other women,
depending on my mood.
It’s also because my last breakup
didn’t really affect me that much.
But, anyway—
I don’t know about your man.
Wait,
why are you curious?
Nothing.
I wanted to feel good.
But your answer
made me feel worse.
But I know how to
make you feel good.
Sleep.
Sleep will make you feel good.
Don’t overthink.
I’m not gonna do anything.
Unless you want me to.
You know what,
you’re just like your brother.
That’s why Yanna got pregnant.
Both of you are—
something.
I can bring you home if you like,
but someone might
snap a photo of us again.
That’s just gonna add
to your list of issues.
Thank you but,
I’ll just ask my
assistant to pick me up.
Bye.
Now, give me a soft smile
but keep those
eyes fierce, okay?
Yeah. That’s it.
Yeah. That’s really good.
Keep it there.
Oh, that’s nice.
Looking good.
Keep moving.
That’s really good.
Yeah, hold it there.
I’m feeling a bit worse
because of how hot it is out here.
I didn’t get much
sleep last night
since I came from
Avi’s birthday party.
Sam, you need to rest.
Maybe skip the gym today.
I can’t. The fashion
show’s coming up,
and I can’t afford
to miss a workout.
Are you sure?
Take some vitamins.
- Oh my gosh!
- What?
My cardholder is missing.
All my credit cards
were in there.
- Okay.
- Geez...
Maybe you just left it
somewhere, or forgot it.
I don’t remember
how and when I lost it.
The last time
I brought it was—
I think I can take it from here.
I’ll go ahead.
Maybe I left it with him.
With who?
Oh, shit.
I wonder if this
is still his number.
It’s been a while
since I last called him.
All right, we’re going
to wrap up the shoot
so you can rest.
We’ll leave you here.
- Come on. Let’s go.
- Okay, okay.
Hello?
Hi.
It’s Sam.
Yeah, I know.
So...
He still has my
number saved, huh?
Sorry to bother you,
but did you happen to see a
cardholder the last time we met?
It’s a brown monogram—
Yes, I have it with me.
Sorry, I forgot to tell you.
Thank goodness,
it fell into good hands.
Are you sure it did?
Stop fooling around.
I’ll just pick it up
later, okay?
I’ll text you before
I head to the hospital.
I’m going to the gym first,
hope that’s okay?
Or maybe I can
have my driver get it?
No. I’d rather you get it.
Okay... Okay.
I’m here at the hospital.
Where can I find you?
I have a lot
of patients right now.
I might not be able to reply,
but you can wait for me, if you like.
Just let me know where.
Sam.
Sam?
Sam!
Hey.
I’m sorry. I fell asleep.
Um...
Your cardholder.
I have to go now,
I still have a lot of patients.
Thanks.
Me too, I’m heading home.
Sam?
Oh my god.
What were you doing all day?
When did you start
feeling dizzy?
Well, I drank last night.
I woke up early
to go to a shoot.
I was under the sun for hours.
After that, I ate a salad
before heading to the gym.
I felt really tired, and...
went straight here.
Fell asleep while waiting,
and when I woke up,
I felt sick.
Didn’t you drink enough water?
Didn’t I tell you?
Once you drink alcohol,
you get dehydrated.
You’ve had enough,
believe me.
And you’ll get dehydrated,
that's bad for your kidneys.
Did you know your kidneys
filter the toxins in your body?
Including alcohol, by the way.
So if you overdo it,
they’ll really get damaged.
You’re so cute when
you go all medical on me.
You’ve got a really high fever.
You should take better care
of your health next time.
Okay.
All right, I still have
patients to see.
Um, I’ll just come back later
with your meds.
There’s also food
and water here.
Wait, where are we?
Um...
We’re still at the hospital.
You’re in my study
and sleeping quarters.
My parents gave it to me.
But don’t worry,
just make yourself comfortable.
Hmm...
And here.
Wear this so you don’t get cold.
Thank you, Cy.
I mean, thank you, Doc.
All right, get some rest.
I have to go now.
There really are perks
to being the owner’s kid.
This place feels so him.
He’s still so organized.
I wasn’t there when
you achieved your goals.
Now I remember why
we had to break up.
You needed to be
the doctor that you are now.
So this is your
future without me.
I’m proud of you
and happy for you.
Wait,
all of these
are my covers.
He has them?
Why?
Hey…
- Are you okay?
- Just rest.
You’re sick.
Uh...
Are you comfortable
having me here?
I can sleep on the couch.
You can stay here on the—
A kid died, Sam.
I’m sorry.
She was close to me.
When I visited her room,
she was already having
trouble breathing.
And then she,
she was already—
I’m sorry.
Is this your first time
witnessing someone’s death?
No.
This usually happens
with critical patients.
But kids…
seeing them suffer
is something
I’ll never get used to.
That’s why I wanted
to quit in the first place.
Cy, you can’t save everyone.
Yeah, but,
as long as we still can,
as long as we’re able,
we can’t give up.
Someone's life is on the line.
It’s not something we can
just let go of that easily.
Keep going for those
you can save, Cy.
For those you can heal and help.
That’s how it should be, right?
That’s why you became a doctor.
Remember why you started.
Thanks, Sam.
Anyway, you look tired.
I’ve been awake
for 38 hours now.
So you really need to rest.
Actually, you need it more.
You need to rest now.
I still have a lot
of paperwork to finish.
Go on, get some rest.
I’m okay.
Okay.
Cy, I’m ready to go.
Oh...
You didn’t use my cards
or anything, right?
Excuse me?
Well, when I said it fell
into good hands,
you said,
“Are you sure it did?”
So I was just thinking,
maybe you bought something
with the cards, you know?
If I were to use your cards,
I’d use them to buy
food for our dogs.
Of course, their mom’s gotta
contribute too, right?
Our dogs?
So, who’s taking care of them?
Colin.
Okay.
All right, I’ll go ahead.
We can meet up again soon
so I can return your sweater.
I promise, I’ll have it
washed first.
Okay.
Hey, um, thanks for listening to me.
I just really needed
someone to talk to.
Thank you for taking care of me.
It’s nice to have someone
to remind me
to take care of myself
once in a while.
Take care of yourself,
too, okay?
Yeah, of course.
I’ll see you soon.
Maui.
Yes?
Do you have a boyfriend?
Why would he even ask this?
Maybe he saw
the rumors online?
I don’t.
And Avi’s not my child,
she’s my best friend’s daughter.
- Okay.
- Do you have a girlfriend?
Do you really think
I have the time
to entertain somebody else?
Okay. I’ll go now.
Thank you.
Okay.
Take care.
You too.
Maison Lorent captivated the fashion world
with its latest collection
during New York Fashion Week.
The runway featured powerful
silhouettes in black,
from sharp tailored coats
to sheer layering
and sculpted tulle minis.
Critics praised the collection as
“confident, minimalist,
and unapologetically modern,”
with Maison Lorent once
again proving its place
- at the forefront of high fashion.
- I love the volume on the hair.
Great work. Stay relaxed.
Still feeling nervous?
You know, everyone wants you
to walk their shows.
I’m serious. What?
This has been the...
nth time you’ve worked for us?
Did you bring a companion?
To watch you?
A beau, perhaps?
Maui.
Yes?
Do you have a boyfriend?
It’s just me.
Oh, come on.
Why don’t you find
a New Yorker boyfriend
when you move over here?
Anyone would be
happy to have you.
Anyway, Sam.
You’re going to do great.
This is New York Fashion Week.
Let’s make it happen, okay?
- Good luck!
- Thank you.
This is it, Sam.
Your biggest show so far.
You got this.
Thank you.
Models, let’s go!
Five minutes to show time!
Let’s go!
Sam, focus on your walk.
One step at a time.
And most importantly,
enjoy! Yeah.
And if I’m not in the audience
and you’re nervous,
just imagine I’m there yelling
and cheering for you.
Guys, let’s go! Line up.
We’re live on broadcast
and streaming.
First look—
Go.
I’ll always be your
number one fan, Sam.
Samantha Vera, let’s go!
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
I’m glad you liked it.
Sam, great job. High-five!
- Great job.
- Thank you.
You looked amazing out there.
Haze! What are you doing here?
This is definitely
not your thing.
How did you end up here?
Well, a friend invited me.
Who am I to turn it down, right?
- Here.
- Wow, thank you.
You’re so sweet.
Makes me wonder if
you’re already falling for me.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but I don’t fall for people who
are busy falling for their ex.
Wait, what?
Am I that transparent?
Am I the only one
in denial that I still love Cy?
I’ll be right back.
I just have to talk to a friend.
Okay. I’ll see you later.
Slay! So proud
of you @itsamantha!
That’s my BFF!
She owned the runway!
So proud of you, auntie.
Good thing
you didn’t trip!
Congrats, Sam! Slay!
So beautiful!
A goddess!
Couldn’t be
prouder of you, Sam!
Did he watch?
I guess it’s fine
if I check his stories.
After all,
we didn’t even
unfollow each other.
How hard is it to say,
“you did good”?
A congratulatory message
wouldn’t hurt.
Wear this so
you don’t get cold.
It’s so silly of me to admit,
but I really do miss him.
Hi. I’m back in Manila.
I’m free tomorrow
to return your sweater.
I won’t be at
the hospital tomorrow,
but we can meet somewhere else.
I’m going to see him tomorrow!
Cy. I miss y—
Let me know.
Oh no.
I didn’t mean to send that!
How to unsend?
It’s okay to be afraid.
Everyone’s afraid of pain.
He’s here. Yay!
Well, does it hurt?
Before I forget…
You can keep it.
What?
Then why did you
agree to meet me?
Isn’t it obvious?
I wanted to see you.
You and Haze are trending.
Your photos during the
fashion show are circulating.
Special delivery.
Do you have a girlfriend, Cy?
Not looking for one.
Sucks to be single, huh?
Watch your words, man.
I can’t believe we’re
doing yoga right now.
Screw you.
Screw all of you!
I felt so alone and left out.