=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 12=
Hurry.
- Do it.
- Hurry.
- Kill her.
Kill her.
Kill her now.
Don't you want to go to war?
Kill her and you can go.
Be quick.
Kill her.
Kill her now!
- Do it now!
- Hurry!
- Kill her!
Kill her!
Kill her now!
Do it now!
You...
I knew it.
You aren't the real Xiaoxiao.
Xiaoxiao is a nice person.
She would never make me kill anyone!
You're the real Xiaoxiao.
Take it back.
Very well.
Since you refuse to kill her,
you'll die with her!
Captain Han,
you go on scouting.
Qingsheng and I
will join you in three days.
Yes, General.
Qingsheng, we're going back to Shuozhou.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
Why did you protect me?
You may die.
But I can never die.
I just feel pain.
Xiaoxiao, please don't die.
I... I promise I'll grow stronger.
The General said
those who always protect others
are very lonely.
The General and I
will protect you together
just like how you protected us.
All right?
Xiaoxiao, please don't die.
Take it.
With this,
no spirit can ever hurt you.
Go find Meng Wan.
Don't get in my way here.
You...
- He...
- He has the Lantern.
I can't hurt him.
You go after him.
But I... I...
Go after him.
Or I will kill you now.
Fine.
All right.
I...
I'll... I'll go after him.
You just gave that boy
the Spirits Lantern?
What if it gets him killed?
Chenying...
He's no worse than any of you.
Before the sun rises
when I get back my power,
if you still can't find
my vital center,
prepare to vanish.
Fang Chang,
take off this guise.
So you knew it was me,
Your Grace.
Without your obsession
with being a mortal,
I wouldn't have this great opportunity.
After I knew
you were controlling that woman,
I kept watching secretly
until you abandoned her body.
Stay back!
I found her.
With your lingering power in her body,
I took your form
and manipulated her.
When you have no spirit power,
I'll kill you
to avenge Yinyin.
I've sensed your aura
all along.
I was just wondering
what kind of trick
you were going to play.
I never thought
it could be so boring.
As for Shao Yinyin...
She violated the Golden-wall Decrees
and reaped what she sowed.
She was your lover.
To secure your position as Vice Lord,
you killed her yourself.
But now you seek revenge on me.
Isn't that ridiculous?
Shut up!
Fang Chang,
you've lived for centuries.
Is this all you've got?
He Simu!
To uphold the Golden-wall Decrees
and protect mortals,
you prey on spirits, your own kind!
So today,
I'll make you die
at the hands of the mortals
under your protection.
I didn't know
you could do the Puppet Technique.
Die, He Simu!
Stop!
Don't run!
Stop right there!
Stop!
If I catch you, I'll get rude!
Stop right there!
If I catch you, I'll show no mercy!
Keep running.
Try if you can.
Boy,
give me the jade pendant.
After I kill that woman,
I can give you some money.
Give it to me.
You wish!
It belongs to Xiaoxiao.
I won't give it to you unless I die!
You little brat.
We aren't enemies.
But today,
one of us has to die.
Don't blame me.
Who? Who did that?
Who?
Chenying.
General.
Who are you?
You...
Who... Who are you?
You hurt him?
So what?
Want a fight?
General,
Xiaoxiao...
She...
Clean up the mess.
Are you all right?
Without the puppets,
can you not even
find my vital center?
Don't talk tough.
When I make the puppets
pierce you all over,
I'll find your vital center.
(My sense of touch is back.)
♪Spirits are intoxicated♪
♪With obsessions♪
♪Forget the form to achieve♪
♪Yet I can't♪
♪Today, a home is granted♪
Got any more moves?
Bring them on.
Stay back.
Or I'll kill her.
She's no threat to me.
Say something else.
Why don't you tell me
where you managed to learn
the Puppet Technique?
You'll never know,
He Simu.
Simu.
So this is how much it hurts
when you're injured.
I didn't lend you this sense
to make you feel pain.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Calm down,
young general.
I'm calm enough.
I cleaned you
with three buckets of water.
Luckily, you aren't a mortal.
Or you would have bled out.
Meng Wan.
How do you feel?
Is anything hurting?
Feel?
I can't feel anything.
Soon, these wounds
will heal on their own.
A spirit
heals quickly.
Besides,
I'm the Sovereign.
I never die.
General Duan,
isn't it very rude
when a mortal like you
stares at a lady like this?
What on earth happened?
The mortal
I used to possess
is Qiao Yan.
Before dying of illness,
her mother made a deal with me
that I'd protect her.
So, I kept her by my side
and nurtured her
with aura of my lantern.
Later, her health
improved a little.
Besides,
during the spell of senses,
my own body was needed.
So,
I let her leave.
You protected her.
Why did she hurt you?
She was just being manipulated.
In Shanling Temple,
someone called Fang Chang
hated me for killing her lover.
So when I didn't have power,
he manipulated Qiao Yan's body
and did such a thing.
How is Miss He?
Her wounds are healing quickly.
She'll be fine.
What a surprise.
So Miss He really is a spirit.
Her identity doesn't matter.
I just know
she did a great service to us.
That makes sense.
Without her,
we wouldn't have taken Shuozhou.
Miss He.
She's a good spirit.
She really is.
Well, I'm quite curious.
How did he know
I lost my power?
You didn't tell him, did you?
You suspect me?
I swear to you
by my past,
my future,
my body, my heart,
my family,
my dream,
my name,
and everything I have,
I will never
ever
do anything to hurt you
even if I die.
You can just deny it.
Why are you overreacting so much?
Oh, you're angry.
I've never seen you angry before.
Marshal Qin exiled you to the north,
Wu Shengliu questioned you,
and Qin's soldiers isolated you,
but you were never angry.
Now you're angry
over such an ordinary question.
Funny, indeed.
But this time,
I experienced what felt like dying.
I felt this pain
to its very limit.
Getting this sense
is worth it.
Only someone who never dies
would say something so arrogant.
When I saw fresh and old wounds on you,
I never felt anything.
But since I've experienced
such wounds,
it breaks my heart to see you like this.
Mortals like you
are really fragile.
If only I had found you
when you joined the All-Knowing.
In that case,
you would have had fewer wounds
and less pain.
No.
If you had met me at that time,
you wouldn't have been interested.
Now I've met you.
I think
it's the perfect time.
You don't want me to save you earlier?
No.
Back in the All-Knowing,
I was in pain and confused.
And I was always fearful.
My soul was a crucible.
There was no room for love.
I'm glad that you see me as I am now.
Now I'm clear-minded
and resolute.
I need no redemption.
I'd rather fall,
survive rough times,
rebuild my body, reshape my soul,
and get worldly-wise,
in exchange for...
♪Miracles, eternity, and radiance♪
Meeting you again.
♪Worth more than any barren land♪
♪I might as well
spend the rest of my life♪
♪Walking with you through eternity♪
I just asked casually.
Don't be so serious.
This is how I honestly feel.
My heart only holds evil thoughts
instead of true love.
Say that to someone else.
♪A dream I'm lost in♪
♪If I could kiss your hand♪
I've recovered.
♪I'd bear your feelings♪
♪Thanks to fate♪
♪I'm blessed to have met you♪
♪Then I won't let you go♪
♪I wish I could be a firework♪
♪To burn out for the moment you turn♪
(Since you've come,)
(don't expect)
(to disappear from my life.)
Help me, Your Lordship!
Help me!
Your Lordship.
What makes you so flustered?
I'm too old
to hear or see well.
So I entrusted Fang Chang
with all the affairs of my branch.
I never thought
he could do something so terrible
in the Mortal World.
He manipulated some mortals
to assassinate Her Grace.
The older you grow,
the more cowardly you get.
Since Her Grace took the throne,
being assassinated
has been like a daily occurrence.
Not this time.
I don't know
how Fang Chang did that,
but he severely wounded her.
She was injured
from head to toe.
- Chenying.
- General.
- Awake?
How is Xiaoxiao?
Don't worry.
She's fine.
But General,
that imposter
pierced through Xiaoxiao's body.
She bled a lot.
Is she really fine?
She must be in pain.
It's true.
She's formidable.
She's the Sovereign.
Nothing can harm her.
She's resting now.
You can have something to eat
and see her when she wakes up.
Sovereign?
Xiaoxiao told me
the Sovereign is the head of spirits
with great power.
That's right.
General,
I've made up my mind.
I must grow stronger.
I'll learn martial arts from you.
I will protect both of you
so that you won't get hurt
and you can do greater things.
But I remember you wished
to eat eight pancakes at a time.
With meat filling.
I don't want pancakes anymore.
I...
I wouldn't wind
eating no more pancakes.
All I want is to protect you.
This will be my only wish.
All right.
I'll make you stronger.
What's wrong?
General,
if Xiaoxiao is a spirit,
does it mean she can't
stay with us forever?
Will she leave us?
General,
Xiaoxiao...
She... She really likes you.
Because of you,
she's been lovesick.
Don't... Don't you like her?
If you have feelings for each other,
she will stay.
Lovesick?
She said that?
She says anything
that comes to mind.
Chenying,
I'll tell you something.
Can you keep it to yourself?
Yes.
I won't tell anyone.
All right.
Xiaoxiao often says
she likes me
or adores me,
but that's all fake.
She doesn't like me at all.
Those are just jokes.
To her,
I'm merely a special mortal.
I'm special enough
to make her forgive my offense.
But I'm not special enough
to make her love me.
I've never said
that I like her.
Actually,
I really like her.
Really.
Are... Are you sure?
You promised me
you'd keep this secret.
You must not tell her.
I... I won't tell her.
Then General,
let's try together
to make her stay.
Shall we?
We'll make her stay.
Eat up.
Xu,
Commandant Xia is ready.
You can leave anytime.
Watch over Mingfeng.
Take care of the manipulated citizens.
Keep this under wraps.
Wait until I'm back.
Take care of Xiaoxiao.
(Yiyuan Courtyard)
Great Ancestor,
you've finally summoned me.
Tell me.
What does it feel like to have senses?
Which sense did you have this time?
Fengyi,
I experienced
what death felt like.
I had the sense of touch.
When I lost my power,
some evil spirits knew about it
and tried to kill me.
It was really fun.
Having a sense
will make you lose all your power?
Then Great Ancestor,
will you continue
to get other senses?
Why wouldn't I?
It's a rare opportunity.
And the time
when I had the sense of touch
left a deep impression on me.
And thankfully,
those brainless fools
added to the fun.
Great Ancestor,
it seems
you've been away for so long
that you can't suppress
those ambitious spirits.
I've never suppressed them.
I've just killed them,
haven't I?
They have to bow to me
unless they defeat me.
I just never thought
Song Xingyu was behind this,
as the long-lost lord
of Jiling Temple.
What exactly happened?
Fang Chang from Shanling Temple
colluded with Song Xingyu
and learned his unique skill,
the Puppet Technique.
When I lost my power,
Fang Chang set up
that clumsy trap.
Song Xingyu has hidden
in the Mortal World for so long
without being caught.
As master of the Starhaven Sect,
aren't you being irresponsible?
Spirits like you
didn't catch him either.
Sorry, Great Ancestor.
I'll widen the search scope immediately.
Once we get news of Song Xingyu,
I'll let you know.
Confess.
How did you wound Her Grace?
A lot of spirits want to kill He Simu.
This time,
I waited until she lost her power.
I shouldn't miss that chance.
Do you know
how great it felt
when I was torturing
our sovereign?
The bright red blood
kept streaming down!
She was trembling all over with pain!
Though she was the Sovereign,
she lost her power and felt the pain.
I really should have let you see
how she looked as she was dying.
She was truly pitiful.
Who conspired with you?
Your death is upon you.
No point in hiding it!
I'm going to die,
whether I confess or not.
Yan Ke,
you're just He Simu's lapdog!
you humble yourself
and obey her completely, and then?
She goes through men
one after another.
But you'll never be chosen!
(Yiyuan Courtyard)
Yan,
there you are.
Simu.
You're going out?
How's your injury?
Guan Huai is quick-tongued
only when he wants to live.
You must have caught Fang Chang.
He's now in the Nine-Square Maze Prison.
He awaits your judgment.
I knew you'd bring me good news.
That's perfect.
Hey, Simu.
What exactly happened?
How did you lose power
and get wounded by him?
I hate it most
when someone wants to poke around.
It's been 300 years.
You're the Sovereign
and I help you rule the Spirit World
perfectly in sync.
Do you and I
have to be so precise about that?
Do you have feelings for that general?
Right Hand,
you know very well
that I am the Sovereign.
Sorry, Your Grace.
You should go back.
Keep our world in order.
When I'm back,
don't let me down.
Yes.
I shall be there,
awaiting your return.
(Yiyuan Courtyard)
(Liang)
Evil spirits. Evil spirits everywhere.
They eat people.
They're evil spirits.
General Duan.
Don't eat me.
What's all this about?
He's a mere swindler
who fools people.
He set up a stupid scam.
And due to those baseless rumors,
the one contributing greatly to our army
was thrown into prison.
Don't eat me.
General Duan,
there was a spirit in your army.
Marshal Qin dealt with her
and calmed your army.
Instead of feeling thankful,
you blame him now.
Don't tell me
you recruited that evil spirit.
He Xiaoxiao colluded with evil,
as everyone witnessed.
She's still alive
because Marshal Qin showed mercy.
General Duan,
don't you push it.
How come I didn't know
our soldiers
should be judged
by a swindler?
Don't eat me. Spare me.
Did someone deliberately
disrupt our morale
or did someone maliciously try
to frame my capable strategist?
You...
Evil spirits. Spare me. Don't eat me.
Now that it's a misunderstanding,
then have this swindler
taken away
and have him beheaded.
- Yes.
Evil spirits.
They eat people.
So many evil spirits.
Evil spirits.
General Duan,
we'll have a major battle
against Chong troops
and we need talents.
We must make concerted efforts
to fight our enemies.
Let's not blow our recovery plan
over such trivial things.
This is the information I collected
as fast as possible
on reaching Yunzhou,
including city defense,
garrison troops, formations,
supplies, and weapons.
Take a look, Marshal.
Yunzhou is very far away
in a messy situation.
But you spied on the enemy
and returned safely
within only a few days.
Impressive, indeed.
Good job.
Thank you, Miss.
You gave all your salary
to someone else.
How will you survive this month?
I spared no effort
to predict the weather
and I was even in prison because of you.
With no compensation,
won't I at least get a raise?
Whatever you need
should be offered.
What did Miss Qiao say
before she left?
She's fully recovered.
She'll return to her hometown
for a peaceful life.
Your Grace, what does
your hometown look like?
I'd like to visit it.
When dead trees blossom,
I'll grant your wish.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪