'What's the impact of
all of this on the market?'
'You will just have to take a minute to
assess how the market has digested this news'
'of this crime...'
Mom, you used to say
that making a will is ominous
as it nears a person's death.
But you died young even
though you didn't make a will.
Now I can't even say,
'Where there is a will,'
'there is a way.'
Look, mom. I had invested in shares.
Even that is incurring a loss.
Saturn is not in a favourable position.
And today, I have to
again go to the registrar.
You didn't give a will. At least
give me blessings. Please.
Offer Rs 500.
The blessing of Gods and
Goddesses is also important.
Mr Lal.
Yes, sir.
If I say something wrong,
you will file a case against me.
No, sir.
But what to do? I can't do anything.
Look, Ranvir. The land
isn't in your mother's name.
Sir...
Kukreja builder claims
that your late grandpa
had made a will.
But he gave it to a trust.
Later, the trust transferred the
entire property in Kukreja's name.
No. No. That's impossible, sir.
The matter got closed then.
In my family there is no
system of making a will.
Oh!
But legally...
Legally.
The next generation family
has a claim on ancestral property.
Yes.
It means, after my grandpa's death
my mother inherited the property.
And after her death, I am the rightful owner
of this property. Because the paperwork...
And your uncle.
What?
Uncle?
What uncle? What do
you have to do with uncle?
According to document, if
someone can claim that land
after your mother's
death, it's only your uncle.
What's his name?
Sir, invitation from the builder in Mahim.
Madho Singh Rathore.
But he went away. Went far away.
We tried to find him. We even
gave ads in the newspaper.
But...
But we didn't get any response, sir.
Yes. It means, the property
should be transferred in my name.
Sir, look. She is my mother.
The land belongs to my mother.
What belongs to my mother why
do you want to give it to my uncle?
And Kukreja's claim is totally baseless.
This is crime.
Fraud and forgery.
Total.
Look. If you want to file a criminal
case, why did you come here?
I look after civil property matters.
Yes, sir.
And you know. You are
his lawyer. Explain it to him.
Sir, you see, we are looking for his uncle.
But we got this notice from your office.
So we thought we should meet you.
Now you have only one chance.
Within a month bring your uncle
and his no objection certificate here.
Then we will think about it.
Yes.
Goodbye.
Thanks...
Hello.
Yes. He just left my office.
He had brought that buffoon along with him.
Yes.
I gave him one month's time.
Don't worry about
that. I'll take care of it.
I am after him. I am
following him like a shadow.
Yes.
I'm just waiting for
one mistake on his part.
I'll set the wheels in motion
as soon as that happens.
Now, how will you escape
from Kukreja's clutches?
I am Kukreja. Right now, I'm a
contractor. Soon I'll become a builder.
Nobody can stop me
from constructing Sun City!
Whose call is it?
Oh God, Salim.
Kukreja.
Salim, hello.
Can you hear me?
Yes, Salim. Tell me.
What happened about Shakuntala Niwas?
I've given you my word. I'll have
it vacated by the deadline. Period.
Listen, you moron.
If it doesn't happen this time, I
will kill you before the deadline.
Mr Lal, listen to me.
Tomorrow I will go to the
registrar's office for the last time.
If fair means don't work,
I will use foul means.
You just trace uncle anyhow.
Why do you worry?
Everything can be done in half rate. You just
have to grease their palms. I will get it done.
Yes. I will hang up now.
I told you. Nothing can
be done without uncle.
Sir, I will bring him
provided I know where he is.
Sir, I just want you to delay
the hearing as much as possible.
If you want, you can do anything.
Yes. Right.
You know what to...
That's better. I was also
waiting. For the money.
Please help me.
What is this? So less?
Pennies for property worth billions.
Look, this is the true state of our courts.
This is what happens at our courts.
The person who is giving the bribe... His name is Ranvir Singh.
- Ranvir Singh.
'Yes. Let me tell you.
His name is Ranvir Singh.'
'See for yourself how
an innocent looking man'
'is impugning the nation with
his illegal deeds and black money.'
'Okay, ma'am. Tell me. For
how long have you known Ranvir?'
'I know him since the time he
broke the glasses of my house.'
'He is a notorious child.'
'Notorious! Did you hear that?'
I live in Mumbai, sir.
You just heard what he
neighbour had to say about him.
I don't say much.
I am saying that I was not giving him bribe.
I was giving him money to fetch cigarette.
The entire nation saw you
asking him to get you a cigarette.
Did you understand?
'Let's hope that the court gives
him the severest punishment.'
Whose call is it?
Sir, it's my share broker's
call. I will make a call, sir.
Did you hear that? Mr
Smarty-pants wishes to take the call.
What work do you do?
Event management, sir.
You mean, catering.
Not catering, sir.
Arranging for food and lodging for people.
Handling big actors' needs.
Sir, let me make just one call.
Why did you go to that office?
Sir, I had gone to transfer
my own property in my name.
Property?
Yes.
Property.
Where is your property?
Sir, Bandra.
Bandra?
Yes.
Shinde.
Yes, sir.
Did you see that?
He owns a property in Bandra.
And he had only Rs 800 in his pocket.
He gave a self-cheque.
Get cash for it. And listen.
Yes.
In the report write that the
guy gave money for cigarette.
Okay?
Yes, sir.
And get me a cigarette on your way back.
What are you saying, Mr Parekh?
It's gone, Mr Ranvir.
How much?
I'll be left stranded on the streets!
The market has crashed
further due to the rallies.
Crashed? What do you mean?
Excuse me. Give me Rs 100.
Darn! What rotten luck!
Excuse me, sir.
What is it?
Give me Rs 50.
Didn't you hear me talking?
Shall I connect you to the stock exchange?
Give me Rs 25.
My shares are gone.
I am sorry. It's not your fault.
But if this goes on, I will have
to become your business partner.
Mine?
He has left.
Give Ranvir an offer of Rs 10 million.
Give him a cheque.
And make him sign the documents.
Okay.
Later, I will do stop payment.
But, sir.
Yes.
That plot is worth Rs 200 million. Right?
If you're going to stop the payment later
on, give him a cheque of Rs 200 million.
Moron!
How many times will you remind me
that there is no money in the account?
You fool.
Do as much as you are told. Understood?
Yes.
Get going!
But how could you do this?
And that too in front of the
press. In front of the media.
Sir, I didn't know that
the press would be there.
If you just...
Listen.
I can't tolerate bad publicity of
my dream project at any cost.
It is better that you yourself
leave the project immediately.
For good.
Move!
Hello.
Hello, Mr Ranvir. Hello.
Be careful.
Yes, Mr Lal. What's the bad news?
It's not bad news. I have
good news. Good news.
Your uncle has been found.
Yes! Where did you find him?
He is not in London. He is here, in India.
I am speaking the truth.
No! How did he find his uncle?
This is not going in our favour!
Hello. Yes, Mr Lal.
Mr Lal, I am in the lift. I can't hear you.
Mr Lal. Hello.
'Uncle, I am coming to get you.'
We've reached Jaipur. In an hour.
Jaipur has its own beauty.
How much did it cost?
Sir, Rs 880.
What? How? How come Rs 880?
Sir, he said to bring 1 cup tea
and 2 'samosas'. What can I do?
Hey!
You were craving to have tea in the air.
Couldn't you have waited for an hour?
Look, handle your goat.
Sir, carefully.
Darn!
This time Congress
will surely win. I swear.
So let's bet for Rs 125.
I will shave off my moustache.
This time the opposition will win.
Fine.
It is so cramped in here. Three
people are sitting on two seats.
What have I got myself into!
He is bothering me.
Hello.
Hello, Ranvir.
Yes, Mr Lal.
Did you reach Rajasthan?
Okay. I am coming in two days with uncle.
Hold on. Listen to me.
Kukreja has given an
offer of Rs 10 million.
What do I do now? Shall I accept it?
I just don't understand.
Rs 10 million?
Yes.
No way!
Hello. The signal is breaking. Hello.
Hello. I can't hear you.
Hold him.
Looks like he had eaten
sprouts this morning!
Stop the bus. Stop the
bus. I want to get down.
Stop the bus.
He got scared.
Idiots!
He sat down, sir.
Look there.
So many mutton dishes.
Hey! Stop! Stop the rickshaw!
Stop!
Excuse me...
Are you crazy? Why are
you showing me your thumb?
Sorry. I was asking if I could get a ride.
Then why don't you just say it?
No vehicle will stop if
you show your thumb.
Please stop.
Come on! Come quickly.
Come on!
Come on, let's get going.
Darn!
Hello.
Why did they make a door here?
They should have made a wall here.
Hello.
Excuse me.
I am your nephew. Ranvir.
Madho Singh Rathore.
Shakuntala is your sister.
I am Ranvir Singh. Her son.
He has a striking face, sir.
Show me.
His features are also okay.
But his physique and height
are not like that of Thakurs.
If you are really my nephew Dholu.
Ranvir.
Remove your pants.
Remove them.
Your dignity won't wane
by removing the pants.
Look, if you are my nephew
then there should be a
mole on your derriere.
I am sorry. What?
In Rajasthani language
it means your buttocks.
Buttocks?
Yes. Buttocks. Your behind.
Remove them.
'There is no coyness in behaviour.'
'People have become shameless.'
'Despite being clothed, everyone's naked.'.
What?
Are you waiting for the right time?
Show me.
That spot.
Dholu!
What are you looking at? It's Saturday.
He observes an oath
of silence on Saturdays.
Painting from Oxford...
Hello.
Hello. Where are you?
Did you find your uncle?
Yes. I found him, Mr Lal. I found him.
Great. Come back soon.
By the way, I got a cheque of
Rs 10 million from Kukreja's office.
Tell Kukreja to take the
cheque and keep it for retirement.
When I will win the case,
he will become a pauper.
An offer of Rs 10 million. What a...
Okay. Tell me something.
Our court's hearing is
not on Saturday, is it?
Because uncle observes an
oath of silence on Saturdays.
What? He observes an oath of silence?
Yes.
Are you sure your uncle will sign the will?
I mean, what kind of man is your uncle?
He is quite different.
But he is highly educated and qualified.
Listen, it's a very important matter.
This time we won't get an extension.
For sure. And another important matter.
You have to pay my fees
of the past four months.
Do something.
Hello. Hello.
Yes. Hello.
Hello, Mr Lal. Hello. I can't hear you.
Don't try to fool me, Ranvir.
Hello...
Hello. I can't understand
what you are saying.
Mr Ranvir, don't do this. Please.
Just listen to me...
I can't hear you. Hello.
Because of you I will
be sitting here all my life.
Hello, Bhairav. Where is uncle?
Did you see him?
He has gone to the nearby
temple. For the 'puja'.
Is it a special occasion?
You did all the necessary rituals
on your mother's death anniversary.
But he found out about
his sister's death last night.
That too from you.
Tell me something.
How did you remember
him after so many years?
Have you come to enquire
about his well-being?
Or have you come for some work?
After my parents' death,
I had become alone.
Then I thought instead of
living alone for my whole life.
I should reconnect to my roots.
That's why I came here to meet uncle.
I want to take him to Mumbai with me.
To my house.
I had to inform him too.
Tell me something. What took you so long?
If you had to inform him, why
didn't you find him a year ago?
As far as taking him along with
you to Mumbai is concerned...
Yes.
You should forget about it. He won't go.
I think he is here. Hold on.
Sir!
Sir, bill.
Are you smoking?
No.
Are you tourists?
No, sir.
Why were you celebrating with drinks?
We made a mistake.
Here, I am in trouble. And
you guys are having fun.
Today, after breaking your oath of silence
which is the first word
that you will speak?
Dholu.
Come here.
Take the holy offerings.
Thank you, uncle.
Uncle, I will surely finish this
board before I go to Mumbai.
Tea is here.
Tea.
Special tea.
Hi, 'tea'! Thank you.
Uncle Bhairav.
Which one is mine?
It's all the same. Take anyone.
Listen, Bhairav. Where are you going?
Tea.
Thank you.
She is Gulabo. We call her Gul.
Hello, Gul. Sorry. I mean, Gulabo.
I mean your name.
She is my daughter.
He means that he considers
her like his daughter.
Biscuit.
No, thank you.
You see, the entire village
considers him as a father figure.
She loves music and dance.
Amazing.
Music and dance.
Yes. Tell me, Ranvir.
Mr Lal, listen. I will send your
cheque as soon as I come there.
Great.
Why are you dying for money?
You keep that cheque
of Rs 10 million. Fine?
Okay, listen.
Yes, tell me.
I had an idea.
You got an idea.
If uncle is unwell, can't you bring
the registrar here for the signature?
Impossible!
Please leave the task
of thinking of ideas to me.
And you just focus on
bringing your uncle here.
Hello.
Yes, sir.
Listen, this time there
should be no mistake.
Yes, sir.
As my count ends, push him. Okay?
Okay.
Come on. Ten, nine...
Eight...
I am not telling you. You got angry.
Two, one...
One.
Zero.
Push him. Yes. Push him.
Hello. Is the job done?
We have fallen in the well.
What are you doing?
We are bathing.
In the well?
There was no water in our well.
I don't know how to swim.
This is a strange village.
What are you doing there? I asked
you to push him. And you guys jumped in.
Look at this. It's over.
I told them to push him.
Sir. Sir, call for you. It's Salim!
Kukreja. Kukreja are
you listening? Hello. Hello.
What? Covertly, secretly. Come here.
Let's have a bet. If you
use this song in any film
the film will be a hit for sure. I swear.
Wow! Who knew that I'd also
get to meet a talented poet?
Which poet?
Never mind. The point
is that you sing really well.
Me?
Yes.
Rainfall.
Rainfall. Shall I sing a rain song?
No. Don't.
No. A rain song.
No?
No.
Bhairav, tell me something.
Don't you ever go to the city?
Don't you get bored in the village?
What do I tell you?
It's been ages since your uncle
has stepped out of this village.
How will he go to the city?
Okay, Bhairav.
What other interesting
things are there in the village?
There are many more things.
Okay. I will sing and tell you.
Sing?
One.
Uncle, there is nothing here.
This...
Yes. Eating out means eating out.
This is what your mother Shakuntala liked.
Every Saturday after going to the
temple we would come here and eat.
Yes. And look, today, he has come to this
place near the hill after 1 year and 3 months.
And that too because of Dholu.
This evening is for Dholu.
Dholu, today when you will eat food
cooked by sir you will lick your fingers.
Filmy songs in this lovely place, Dholu.
Yes.
Uncle filmy songs are also songs.
No. No.
Bhairav.
Sir.
Teach Rajasthani folksongs to Dholu.
Yes.
Uncle.
Sing folk songs.
No. Uncle.
Enough. Enough.
Let her hear the entire song. Okay?
I will just come back. Don't worry.
Dholu, look, he came today after
one and a half years because of you.
Otherwise sir doesn't
venture out of the village.
Sir.
Do something.
Yes.
This sand.
What is this?
Where are we stuck?
Where is the binocular?
Oh God!
Where do we have to go?
Sir, here.
Sir, there.
What?
Sir, here.
Sir, there.
If I depend on you
guys, I will reach Nepal.
Pakistan is that way.
What?
You fool, Pakistan is in Kashmir.
Come on.
You fool, where did they go?
Come on. Look up.
Why are you carrying the bottle, you moron?
Did I tell you to sleep?
Sir, we will get buried in
the sand, hungry and naked.
Look, vultures are also circling above.
Keep quiet. Keep quiet. Or else I will
bury you here alive without a funeral.
Uncle has already driven me crazy.
I swear. If we get out of here,
I will bury uncle right here.
Beneath the camel.
Sir, speaking of camel, I remembered.
In desert people use camel.
Bend. Bend.
I won't bend. He will bend.
Why should I bend?
Bend.
Why? Do I get salary for this?
Signal.
Bend.
I won't bend.
There is sand in my underwear.
Bend.
What is all this?
Why is he doing all this?
Got the signal. Got the signal.
Hey! You scoundrels!
My decision is that
Dalchand will cook for a week
and the wife will eat first.
Well done.
A special thing. I want
you to meet someone.
Dholu. Come here. This is my nephew.
He has come from Mumbai.
Dholu, come here. Come.
Dholu, wish everyone. Wish them.
Hello.
Hello. Hello, Mr Dholu. How do you do?
Very good. Thank you.
They speak English.
Uncle...
But Dholu, what do you do?
I manage events.
Event?
We also manage sheep and goats.
I don't understand.
What do you mean?
Do you people watch TV?
Yes.
The dance shows you see on TV.
Arranging it. Getting
sponsorships. Nothing much.
I understood the song and
dance. But what is a sponsor?
Tell them.
Okay, tell me something.
Who plans wedding here?
I do.
Do this. On the next full
moon, you'll plan it for free.
Dholu, have I gone
crazy to plan it for free?
In return your name
will appear in bold letters.
Picture too. I mean photo. A big one.
That can happen.
And who'll arrange the food?
Food and liquor is on me.
I don't have that much time.
Pick up uncle by evening
and get the signature.
Okay.
So tell me. What is the program?
Program?
Rajasthan's folk song and dance.
This evening in Shekhawati
will be for Gulabo.
Superb.
Wow. Superb.
They clap for everything.
Take care. Come here.
You have gone mad, Ranvir.
Let's go.
Gulabo will not dance in front
of public in such programs.
That's it.
Father.
Hey, girl.
Uncle, it's for a good cause.
It's the full moon.
Will tourists do the folk dance
of this place if not the locals?
As if you know a lot about the culture here?
- Greetings, aunt.
Have you ever lived in Rajasthan? Mr Dholu.
What is wrong with you?
You are also like me.
You studied abroad.
In fact, you taught them.
So tell me, uncle.
Why did you come here after
earning so much of fame and money?
Tell him, sir. The boy is
asking so sweetly. Tell him.
I was teaching the
foreigners there in Oxford.
You must give back society
because your society
has given you your identity.
Understand your roots.
Respect your culture.
The voice was echoing in
the hall packed with foreigners.
I wonder where this voice came from.
'Madhav Singh, you
yourself never acted on it.'
'When you did you do
what you are teaching?'
And I got it. I packed
my bags. Left everything.
This is quite a good place.
Painting in every house.
I mean it's like yours. Yours is nice.
But where are we going?
Hello.
Hello. God bless.
Dholu. My sister Shakuntala's son.
Dholu, seek their blessings. Come on.
Don't trouble me during the match.
Uncle, don't start again. Come, have food.
Yes.
Coming.
Good.
Come.
Have some 'Gatte ki Sabzi'. 'Daal Baati'
is our famous dish. Have one at least.
And give me ghee. Where is the ghee?
Ghee is a must.
Why do you love ghee so much?
You will build muscles,
Ranvir. A little bit.
It will fall. You'll have to eat it.
Okay.
You are good at sketching.
Uncle.
Tell me.
If you come with me to
Mumbai that'll be great fun.
Give it to me.
You'll get a change.
Change?
Yes.
How will going to Mumbai give me a change?
It's a concrete jungle.
It is a concrete jungle. Alright?
Concrete jungle, that's right.
He should be riding the camel.
It's just that... If you'd come to Mumbai,
And sign the no objection
certificate of my mother's plot.
And I could get it transferred.
It will take just 5 minutes.
Here. Go.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
Come on, Gattu.
Dholu, come here.
Look,
history has been a witness that land
and property create rift between brothers.
With God's grace, there is a
special thing about our family.
And that is trust.
Uncle.
That is your land. This
is a Rajput's promise.
Gul, the tea...
Uncle.
Look, you are really educated. I agree.
But promises don't mean
anything in the cities.
There is a builder named
Kukreja. He is really big.
He wants to grab the property.
And since 8 months, I have been...
Please try to understand my
situation. It is not good, uncle.
Let me tell you something,
and it's very important.
A man who fights for his land
is a true blue Rajput.
I didn't get you.
You will understand
everything when the time comes.
Gul, don't worry.
This is just a couple as such.
But the real meaning is in your blood.
You'll understand when the time comes.
We ate worth Rs 150. You ate
food worth Rs 80 and I worth Rs 75.
Okay.
So Rs 150 plus Rs 75, makes it Rs 200.
Where did Rs 250 go? You've
done this addition previously as well.
You studied Maths till
the eighth grade, right?
Because Rs 70, Rs 80, Rs 90...
Yes. What is it?
Sir, I just saw everyone leaving.
We won't get a better
chance to kidnap the uncle.
Uncle is home alone. That's great.
We'll come to do away with his loneliness.
Hello. Welcome.
Have you ever thought
about becoming an actress?
Darn it.
Actress? I am not crazy.
Crazy?
Then think a little crazily.
Think big. Get out of this place.
And take Bollywood by storm.
That's it. Tell uncle that you
want to come to Mumbai with me.
No. I am sorry. Father says you have to
become corrupt before you become an actress.
No. No. It's not that.
You have a wrong notion.
What?
You have a wrong family.
Your father. He is
telling you wrong things.
Do you really think that I dance well?
Okay. So you guys are kidnapping me?
Hello. Hello.
Hello.
Look, tell me when you feel right as to
who are you and where are you taking me?
Hello. Hello, uncle.
God bless. No worries.
He is bigger than police. He is our uncle.
Yes, he is right.
Today all the problems will be over.
And Kukreja will become builder number one.
How is the business of kidnapping?
Do you do any other business
in your spare time or no?
Who is the leader? Are you the one?
Keep quiet. Shut him up.
We have kidnapped
him. But he is torturing us.
No.
Gag him. Gag him.
Show me your hand.
Get lost, uncle.
Jalebi Bai. Jalebi Bai.
Let's go.
You go alone.
What did I tell you? Out with my Rs 125.
What do I say, Parikh?
I don't have much money either.
That's why I suggest you buy it now.
Now is the time.
I don't understand what I should buy.
Buy fertilizer. Fertilizer.
Girl, would you like to eat something?
No.
Parikh.
Yes.
Parikh, buy fertilizer.
Fertilizer?
Yes. Fertilizer.
Alright.
I am buying it on your suggestion.
You win all the bets, right.
You must have got a tip.
Waiters get tips, dear.
My words never fail me.
And look, there will
be rain. Crops will grow.
Grow.
Yes.
Bulls will take a dump.
So fertilizer will sell.
It means there will be bounty
of crops this time in the market.
Uncle, I need a small
sweet signature from you.
On this paper.
What signature?
What paper?
No. Nothing.
Uncle.
Yes, you bug?
Are you going to sign it or not?
No.
Sir, uncle can't sign even if he wants to.
He is buried in sand. I mean in the soil.
I also know that.
- Uncle, you won't sign it?
- No.
Alright. Great. Let us go.
Go. Alright.
Uncle, don't trouble the snakes
and scorpions that come here.
No.
Do you see those vultures circling above?
If they peck you, rip your
flesh, then don't scream. Okay.
Don't worry.
Because there is a desert rule.
Fittest of the survival. Alright?
Alright.
Take care of uncle.
Let's go. Let's take a walk for 15 minutes
and come back. He'll sign immediately.
What happened?
Forget it. Forget it.
Let's go on foot. Forget it.
Where is it? Where are the huge tyre marks?
Where do we have to go?
There.
South pole. North pole.
Put your hands down. Down.
Uncle. Uncle, we are back.
I don't feel like leaving you.
Don't you have anything
else to do? Good for nothing.
The plan of the signature
has been cancelled.
Do us a favour. Show
us the way out of here.
Useless. Change the path of your life.
And you'll find the right way.
Uncle, please. Please try to understand.
We have no other way. Except
that you show us the way.
I know.
Please. Get us out of this sea of sand.
Goodness counts for nothing these days.
Uncle, look at him. He
has two lovely wives.
Four small children.
Uncle, if you don't show us the way
then his family happy will be ruined.
Hey this is not funny.
Funny? You think this
is a joke? This is a joke?
Help me. Uncle, please help me.
Why are you so upset? You thought I'd
shoot you? No way. You are my brother.
Does he think he is some great saint?
This is it. This is it. Enough.
What happened?
Friends, in the desert,
it is survival of the fittest.
This is so beautiful. I'll be dancing here?
Yes.
These are the girls of my village.
Great. Great job.
You have created an oasis in the desert.
Will you have some milk?
Oh no.
My big picture.
Radhe Shyam.
Yes?
Gul Gule Gulistan. See this, Bhairav.
Yes, dear. One minute. Where is the speaker and the
curtains? Where is everything? What is all this?
Presenting to you the pride of Rajasthan.
And the future actress.
Gul, Gule, Gulistan.
Gulabo aka Gul.
Wow. Mind blowing.
Check it out.
'You'll have to understand
what I am about to tell you.'
'Go ahead, dear.'
'I want to go to Mumbai.'
'Dear, is there already less crowd there?
That you are going to add to the crowd.'
'I want to make a name
for myself in that crowd.'
'I want to make a name. Do something big.'
Uncle, come on, smile. Forget it. Enjoy it.
'Gul, I understood what you said.'
'Go. Go to Mumbai.'
'Really?'
'Don't worry.'
'But I have a condition.'
'What?'
'I'll also come with you.'
'I'll go to Mumbai in my car.'
'We'll go to Mumbai in this?'
'Yes. Yes.'
'I am not travelling in this.'
'Mumbai trip cancelled.'
'Father. Please agree.'
'Okay. Okay.'
'Please agree.'
'As you say.'
Hello. Hello, Mr Lal.
There are still 12 days left.
Hello. What? Hello. Ranvir.
I will do it.
It is all set.
Dholu. We have reached Mumbai.
It is so bright. And it
is so crowded as well.
All hail Lord Ganesh.
So Dholu, you live here?
Here.
I'll take the stairs.
What?
I'll go with the girl.
But this...
This is a lift.
Uncle...
Bhairav! Darn it!
Life means to keep moving.
Uncle, our forefathers
were not hill dwellers.
But they were apes.
Hello. Uncle.
Eat. Eat.
You are city birds. Talk in English.
No. No. Let me do it. Okay.
Let me do it.
- Do it.
- But I...
Darn it!
Dholu, do all these
girls live in this city?
No.
What girls?
These aren't mine.
So whose are they?
Mr Lal's.
So what did Mr Lal think?
You need them more?
You dog!
Listen. Return the pages at least.
Like this.
What are these?
Clothes.
For you.
This...
I have to take you day
after tomorrow. So be ready.
Ready? Where do you want to take me?
A true Rajput warrior always blah
blah. Always keeps his promise.
I told you that you had talent.
I will take you to Mumbai.
Well, what I said...
Darn you. Dholu. Look.
What happened?
How do you sit on this? How?
That is not how you are...
Hello, Ranvir.
Yes, Mr Lal.
That rascal has started construction
at the site. Hold on, will you?
You better cut the call right away.
What?
Bulldozer? Hold on.
Bulldozer. I am coming there. Wait.
No. Stop.
Hey, stop it.
That's a real hero.
Anyone who messes
with me will be destroyed.
Be it a bulldozer.
Myself Cookie Kukreja.
Ranvir.
Ranvir?
Yes.
Ranvir, since you are here.
I would like to talk to you.
Come to my palace. Come on. You are
my brother. We'll sit up and chat. Come on.
Come along. Even our morning walk is done.
Look at this. This is
called fresh air. Come on.
Why have you brought me here?
Don't worry. I will neither push
you nor betray you. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Grab me.
Come on.
Don't be scared. Lie down. Lie down.
Your own building looks so nice
when you look at it from down there.
It looks scary from above.
Look at that. The heights. Tall buildings.
Now look down.
What is that? Shakuntala Niwas.
A small bird's nest.
The rest have gone so far
ahead. And he is still where he was.
Don't you see his pain?
I can. He cries every night.
Kukreja, I also want to touch the sky.
I also want someone to jump
by a parachute from my roof.
So that's why I say
that join hands with me.
You solve a small problem of mine.
I will make sure you benefit greatly.
I will give you Rs 30 million.
So is the deal on?
Done.
Listen.
Hey, what are you doing?
But...
But not for Rs 30 million.
Then?
Actually Mr Kukreja, the
rate of dowry has gone up.
So is the deal on?
Let go.
People keep ringing bells all the time.
People don't ring temple bells so much.
Yes. Welcome.
What is this?
What?
Who are you? Call the boy who lives here.
Okay. Okay. You are Ranvir's
friend. Welcome. Welcome.
I am the secretary.
Ranvir didn't tell me that he
has hired a secretary as well.
Not his. I am this building's
secretary. I am your neighbour.
You can't roam around naked like this.
Welcome. Welcome.
I am Ranvir's uncle. Madhav Singh Rathore.
I've come from Rajasthan.
Come in. Let's have a cup of tea.
I am Swatantra Bharat Bhushan.
Nice name.
I don't have time for
tea. And what is all this?
Painting.
This building has been
painted with the society fund.
Painting on it is prohibited. Get it?
Send Ranvir to the
society office immediately.
To report. One more thing.
This is gross... This is vulgarity.
Moreover, destroying
society property. Disgusting.
Small plants. Small
scissors. Small temples.
Small Gods. Small venerations. Small...
Darn you. Girl, what you have you worn?
Come on.
Small clothes.
Bhairav, come on. We'll
be late for the audition.
Come on, let's go.
Tell Nissan not to move from there.
And ask others to follow him on the bike.
Ask Diwakar to...
Darn it. What's with the
name of goons these days?
Boss, all is good. Everyone
has taken their positions.
Yes, boss. He is twirling
his moustaches right now.
Uncle is coming this way.
Stop the commentary.
And give me the live feed.
Okay.
The car is approaching, sir.
He is still dancing. Hey, hit him.
The car slipped. And he missed, sir.
Missed him? Missed him.
You couldn't hit such a
small man with such a big car.
You are good for nothing.
I wish you had been run over by that car.
Missed him.
Was there a banana skin on the road?
Yes.
What is he doing?
Uncle is looking around like a maniac, sir.
Maniac. Maniac. Listen to me.
Yes.
Rush to the nearby police station.
And tell them that uncle
has caused this accident.
And tell them that he is a maniac.
He should either be in the police
station or at the mental asylum.
Okay. Okay.
One!
Hi.
Hey, Arjun.
Hello. Hello.
I'll get Gul auditioned.
You stay right here.
No. I will not be able to dance here.
It's all good, Gul.
There are so many people here. This is really
weird. I will not be able to do it. And this...
Wait...
What are you doing? One minute.
Until today, only I was your fan, right?
- But...
I promise. You go inside and dance.
All of them will become
your fan in 5 minutes.
So you need not fear. I am right here.
Okay?
Yes.
You?
What are you doing here?
This is Gul.
I have brought her here for audition.
This is the only job you can do now.
You beguile girls, show them
big dreams bring them here
and get them auditioned.
You...
You need courage to dream.
And you need just a
sharp tongue to talk trash.
Someone might have explained this
before. But you didn't get it, did you?
Because you have no brains.
Come on, Ranvir. Move.
Superb.
Can we start please?
One minute please.
Come on.
Let's go, Bhairav.
'There has been a horrific accident.'
'It is said that an old man
has caused this accident'.
Father.
Oh God!
We let him go out for the first time and...
Ranvir, this...
And he got arrested.
Let's go. Hurry up!
Come on, Gul. Come on.
'Oshiwara Police Station.'
Sir.
Father.
I am sorry.
Sir.
One minute.
Father, listen.
Oh, Mr Singh.
Yes.
Mr Singh,
your uncle has gone insane.
What...
You need to get his mental state
checked. So we'll keep him in custody.
Mentally unstable. Are you...
Look, he is a very well
respected and educated man.
Look Mr Singh...
Educated people fall victim to madness.
He has testified.
He has testified. He was getting
a hair cut in Sakhi Hair Salon.
Right, Prem?
Yes.
And we have checked with them.
And he has given witness that your
uncle stopped in the middle of the road.
And started dancing in the middle of the
street listening to a song on his headphone.
Look, uncle. It's Saturday
today. And it's Sunday tomorrow.
If you don't say anything, how will I...
It's Saturday. He
doesn't talk on Saturdays.
He won't talk.
'A horrific accident happened in
Oshiwara today. The damage was heavy.'
We shouldn't have come
to Mumbai. Father was right.
We should've never listened to you.
'It is said that this man's
mental state is not right.'
'Through the CCTV
footage in Bright Electronics'
'we want to ask you as to who
is responsible for this accident.'
'Is that man really mad?'
'Terrorists were the only
threat to this city until today.'
Oh yes.
'We need to check with our correspondent.'
What has got you so excited?
This is Mumbai. There
are cameras everywhere.
Everything will be clear tomorrow. Yes.
Sir, we found this from
the shop's recording.
This footage shows that this
accident happened due to this car.
Yes.
We'll have to evict him and
his mad uncle out of the society.
Do you understand?
We'll have to evict them.
He roams around in the society naked.
What effect will this have on our society?
And his nephew was caught
bribing on national television.
Think of the devil and devil is here.
Come here all of you. Quick.
Members, this is the
person I was talking about.
He should be thrown out
of the society immediately.
Lord, forgive them for
they know not what they do.
Sir.
What did you see?
Nothing, sir.
Come to the point. Why did
you come in without knocking?
I had entered uncle's
mansion after those people left.
Yes.
I found this photo there, sir.
And sir, there I came to know that
this man is Ranvir's mother's brother.
Her elder brother at that.
What the heck! Yet another uncle.
Uncles galore.
And I also found out that this man
had gone missing a few years ago.
No problem. Your promotion is on.
Your salary will be double from next year.
Find him.
Yes.
Find him. Here.
He also went missing.
All of them are forgetful.
Flat no. 801.801.
Remember this. Either get the sign
tonight or resign from this business.
Get it?
Leave me. You don't who I am.
Leave me. I will get you arrested.
Leave me. Where are you taking me?
Keep quiet or I'll blow your head off.
What are you talking about? Let me go.
Forget the servant. Find the boss first.
Tell me where is the uncle and nephew.
Shall we call the police?
Pizza arrives first in Mumbai.
And then the fire brigade.
And then the police follow.
So order pizza first. Do they have guns?
Leave me.
Shut up!
Darn it. Run.
Come on.
Where the hell is everyone?
Run. Run.
I am the secretary. I cannot run like this.
I am the secretary. He
is calling me a servant.
Idiot. Rascal. Knucklehead.
The people I was thinking
of throwing out of the society,
today those very people saved
my life risking their own lives.
You are ungrateful. You are an idiot.
Please forgive me. Please. Please.
Please.
It's okay.
Kukreja, you will always
remain a contractor.
You'll never become a builder.
Salim, he is not a man.
He is a cocktail between.
Rajnikant and Gandhi.
I have tried so many times.
He survives every time.
I am coming in two days.
If you don't get the job done by then, Kukreja
will not see the light of the next day.
Boss, don't say such things.
If you can't do it, then call
my brother. And call his men.
There are only two days left.
Heard that? Only two days.
Not only a contractor. Kukreja
will become a builder. For sure.
What are you looking
at? Go and eat that rascal.
Yes.
What?
Well done. Well done, champ. Well done.
Bring him by the first flight. He
should be here tomorrow morning.
Well done. Well done.
Why didn't you let me sit in that bus? Why?
Calm down. What is the need for
buses when there is such a nice car?
Really?
Hello.
Yes. I am Ranvir. I had come
for the audition of Gulabo.
Let me hear it too.
Yes, yes. One minute. Yes.
Yes.
What happened? What are they saying?
Yes. Thank you.
What happened?
Hey, tell me. What did they say?
For the semi finals, your selection...
Has been done.
Wow.
I am going to dance like this.
You were going to cry, weren't you?
I think you are joking here.
Hey, I am telling you. I am
a builder. Not a gangster.
Just sell it and take
the sum of Rs 50 million.
That is it. Take this.
You don't have to do anything.
You just have to sign. Read it.
The sum of Rs 50 million is a lot.
Look, Mr Kukreja.
Stop dreaming of making a
building on our ancestral land.
You will never be able to get the land.
Come on. That is okay.
Here you are. Your youth. Take
this. Even you can take a look.
I am sure you know them.
They were running a kite shop in Rohtak.
I called them by flight.
So that he can meet you.
They are restless to claim
their right on their ancestral land.
Uncle, they...
Don't worry about them.
Who are they?
Your uncle. Take a look.
Whose uncle? Please get out of here.
Yes.
Just as kids are born every day in the houses of
people a new uncle is born here every day. I am...
Suresh is not my real brother,
but he is like my elder brother.
His father, the great Parvat
Singh used to work at our place.
Your maternal grandfather
used to treat him as his son.
Suresh and I have been brought up together.
After I went off to London and
after the marriage of Shakuntala,
Suresh disappeared somewhere.
Along with
some money and some jewellery.
A thief.
And today? Today, he has
been found after so long.
And the scoundrel has shown
his true colours once more.
Please forgive me, sir.
But these people should be
hung downwards from a tree
and they should be treated very
badly and thrashed with a stick and...
Bhairav. Bhairav. Don't be rude.
Listen to me.
Make a call at the village.
Come on. Yes. Yes.
Please. Please, make a call.
Tell them that I am coming there as well.
After twenty years, I will sit with
you and recite poems for you.
Decked up and with attitude,
Rajput... And all of that.
I told you, Dholu.
Everything will be fine. Don't
worry at all. Don't worry at all.
Just listen to everything and speak only after that.
- Raichand.
Hey, dear, we don't have to carry our
land and property when we die. Don't worry.
I think you have really
become a priest. Yes.
It is a good idea though.
Whenever there is a difficult situation you can
get relaxed after saying something spiritual.
Exit.
'Dholu, don't worry.'
Uncle, there is a fire. 'Don't worry.'
Earthquake. 'Don't worry at all.'
This worry will get us in a mess one day.
Hey, watch my dance.
It is for the semi finals.
What happened here?
Gul, leave me alone for some time.
Why?
Because I am in a bad mood.
I had a nice property. And I
lost it because of a new problem.
Okay, tell me something.
What would you do with the land?
I would have bought a new house.
Yes.
Sea facing. Okay? BMW car.
Okay. Then?
I would have gone on
a trip around the world.
Then?
Then? Then what?
I would have been rich.
Hey, so what is the problem?
If it is about money, when I win the dance
competition I will give the entire money to you.
You will be able to buy all
your stuff with that, right?
I am here, right?
Are you that confident? Will you win?
Yes.
You are the one who
says that I dance very well.
If I spread my wings, I
will win Mumbai over.
Do you trust me that much?
Yes. Why not?
You are a Rajput. And that is the word of a
Rajput. I am sure you will keep your word.
Come on.
Dance for me.
Okay.
Where have you been for all these years?
Where?
Without you, my whole life was lonely.
Suresh is my elder brother.
Did you hear that, sir?
Suresh. Suresh. He means elder brother.
Elder brother. He is Suresh.
The real heir of this land.
And you can see the love between brothers.
According to Hindu undivided property law
elder brother is the first person to inherit.
So sir, actually this is his
signed will. For my name.
Will? What will?
Mr Singh, after seeing all this I am
convinced that Kukreja's claim is correct.
What is this, Mr Pudhe?
In order to record the statement of our uncle
you got him here all the way from the village.
Since two weeks, you have been
verifying all his documents. It is okay.
But you agreed to the
statement of this man in one go?
My name is Swatantra Bharat Bhushan.
I have made an IAS officer go to jail.
He was charged for corruption.
In my presence, think over the
decision carefully before you take it.
Who is this?
You are absolutely right, Mr Bhushan.
But I really have no
choice. I have no other way.
Dholu. He is your elder uncle. Greet him.
Suresh, he is Dholu. Your nephew.
He is the son of our
younger sister Shakuntala.
Shakuntala is no more.
She is gone.
And he is Shakuntala's
sign. Take his blessings.
The same sign that you
are giving off to Kukreja.
Dholu, take his blessings.
Greetings.
Suresh, let us go home.
We have lots to talk about.
Yes. Talk. Talk as much as you want. Go wherever
you want to after you give your thumb print here.
I will send you tickets for
the flight. Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Come on. Come on. Let's do it.
Suresh, sign here.
Come on. You have to sign at three places.
At this point, at this point and
the last one would be at this point.
Here you are.
Come on. Let's do it.
Come on, sign it!
Yes. Yes. Do sign.
Suresh?
Hey!
Want to give your thumb print?
Rude man.
Suresh Singh.
You are under the oath of the late Thakur.
If you are lying...
Let him go ahead and lie. Let him lie.
Hey!
We will make him meet Mr Thakur.
If you have any shame do go ahead and put your
thumb impression. Even I am standing here.
No, no, don't do that.
Hey, hey, don't be scared. Don't be scared. Put
the impression. Come on. Put the impression.
Can you see that, Mr Pudhe?
Hey, come on, put the thumb
impression. Come on. Hey, what is this.
This land doesn't belong to me.
This land
was given by his father to
his daughter called Shakuntala.
That's it!
Hey, you told me that it is your land.
Suresh. Suresh... Someone stop him.
He...
According to the situation and
the papers, I have no other choice.
What do you mean?
According to the NOC, they are
the real owners of the property.
Yes. Actually my nephew
is the real owner of the land.
The land belonged to his mother.
And now he is the rightful owner of it.
Right, Dholu. Great.
'Dance India. All India.'
Gul seems a little
heavier on going to the city.
It seems the water of
the city has suited her.
Hey, blind man. Not Gul
but your brain has become fat.
Hey, she is the same girl.
You have won the semi final.
But the grand finale is still left.
Grand finale.
What are you thinking of?
Till yesterday.
Till yesterday, my village was my world.
And today,
I am seeing a completely different world.
You have made an unseen
dream turn into reality.
It is just the beginning.
Now you will be very famous in India.
Producers will run after you.
And they will give you offers for films.
Really?
Yes.
By the way, I have a lot
of fun during the shoot.
I had seen a serial shooting in Mendava.
Really.
In that, the girl was telling
the hero about her heart.
Should I do it?
Yes. You will rehearse as well.
Okay.
My lips haven't yet
told you anything.
But don't my eyes say anything to you?
When I run my fingers through my hair.
If you would have noticed
carefully, you would have known
that I keep on writing your name.
Did you...
Didn't you ever feel this love?
Tell me.
Yes, I think.
I love you very much.
Did you see that? Even I can act so much.
We must talk to the
director about me as well.
Now you wouldn't give me attention.
Yes. By the way, this is right.
By the way, whatever
I told you wasn't an act.
And even what I told you wasn't an act.
Boy.
We will have the engagement here in Mumbai.
That's good.
And the wedding will take place in
Rajasthan. After the final program of Gul.
And I will come from the bride's side.
Father.
Thank you, God.
That is it. We just
need to find a good date.
Bhairav.
Yes, sir.
Let us know of a good date.
Day after tomorrow. It is a
full moon night. It is nice date.
Okay.
Engagement on the full moon night.
Bhairav.
Come on, come on. Come
here. Yes. Be happy. Yes.
One minute.
What did I tell you?
Yes, Mr Lal. Tell me.
How are you, my friend? My brother?
Get ready to listen to good news.
I have got an offer of Rs
150 million for your plot.
Yes, Rs 150 million.
But this time I want 10% commission.
And the party is coming to Mumbai in a few days to
finalise the deal. You tell me. Should I tell them to...
Mr Lal,
Yes?
I will call you later. Okay?
Hey, but...
What are you doing? I will get hurt.
Hey, call those goons now. The ones
who were recommended by Stanley.
I have called them.
They are sitting outside.
Yes.
Fool, even you will turn
me into a gangster like you.
And if this is what you
want, this is what you will get.
Hey, but we lost out on the land, right? So
what is the point of calling those goons?
Have you forgotten Meerut?
What did they do in Meerut?
If you lose from the law, take control.
Take control of the land.
I hope no one among you is a Rajasthani.
Okay. Start their work from tomorrow.
Give them advance. Give them money.
Okay.
Hey, this fool. He has called me again. He has
called me again. He doesn't spare me. Get lost.
Darn it!
'Hello. Kuki. Kuki?'
God of mobile.
'Hello, Kuki?'
'Hey, fool. I am waiting
for you at the airport.'
'You had told me that you will wait
for me with a garland. Where are you?'
Hey, you are a fool. Your father...
'Kuki.'
Hey, did you understand what I said?
Everyone must surround the land and sit.
No one must move from their place. No one.
Let there be storm, winds or rain. Let
there be the ultimate natural calamity.
We must take the land in control. Got it?
Yes.
Kuki, what if we have to use the bathroom?
What?
Bathroom?
Hey, one minute. A very important
task has come up. One minute, okay?
Yes. Do it. Do it. Do it. Open it.
Open it. I will make you
do it. Open it. Open it.
Hey, what are you doing?
The boy has to urinate.
What happened? Listen
to me. I know you are a fool.
You don't make mistakes.
But if you make any mistake today,
I will bury you alive, fool. Get lost.
I hope no one else has any questions.
Sir, come here once. Look at
what is happening downstairs.
Hey, I had told you. You
should have brought a tent. Tent.
It is monsoon. Hey, don't
you understand what I tell you?
Even if half a mantra is mispronounced...
I hope you know how
grave the results for that are.
Yes, sir.
Do remember.
Yes.
Okay, keep this here and fill it up.
Like water and flowers and other things.
Greetings to you, Bhairav.
Yes. Greetings to you too.
I am finally at peace
because of your blessings.
Wait for me.
Hey, don't close my
eyes. Don't close my eyes.
No, no, no, they will be opened right away.
Hey, not like that.
Yes, yes, move it. Move it.
Move it away from his eyes.
Don't worry about that.
Dear, the auspicious time for the
engagement is here. Come here.
My daughter is looking very nice.
Come on, the auspicious time is passing by.
Hey, have you gone mad?
Yes? Put the gun down.
The engagement isn't done yet. We will do
this after the engagement. Gun shots and all.
Such a big function. And you
didn't call your neighbour. Very bad.
What is this?
Ranvir.
Ranvir. Leave the girl. I am warning you.
- I am Kukreja.
Leave me.
Girl, please wait.
Dholu.
Calm down.
It is such an auspicious occasion.
I'll get the land, you will sign
the documents. Both will be done.
Hey, she is looking so nice.
What do they call in Rajasthani?
Sir, beautiful girl.
Yes.
Hey, hey, hey.
Kukreja.
Stop.
Father.
Leave my kid alone.
You want the land, right? Give me the papers.
I will give you the land. Give me the papers.
I will sign it.
Hey, no, uncle. I don't need your sign.
You have already signed the NOC, right?
Now the star is your nephew.
Ranvir.
Hey, the one who has
the guts to run and win.
What?
And also win over the Sun has...
Hey, sign now. Sign. Sir, please
sign. Please. I am a huge fan of yours.
Ranvir, don't sign.
Hey, quiet. Keep quiet.
Hey, make it quick. I don't have time. Hey,
take it. Hold it. Hold it. Hey, fool. Quiet.
Hey! Just leave her.
Hey, look. Look.
Hey, you idiot. Leave
me. Ranvir, no. Ranvir, no.
Leave the girl's neck.
Hey, take it. Take it.
Now give it to me. Here you
are. I have given her back.
Uncle says that for a Rajput,
duty is the biggest thing.
Not this land.
Hey, dear. Your uncle and you...
Stop teaching each other
about the history of Rajputs.
You signed it and I gave the
girl back. The matter is over.
Congrats for the engagement.
Salim.
Greetings. Greetings.
Salim, you have reached at the right time.
At the perfect time. Just like police.
After all the work is done.
Salim.
Salim, look at this. We have the land in
our control. And the world is at our feet.
You fool. You don't take my calls.
That long car has been
bought by you with my money.
Even the mobile was
bought by my money, right?
Yes, all of it was yours, Salim.
I asked you to buy a small
piece of land. You couldn't buy it.
The work that couldn't be done by
you was done by me at a snap of a finger.
Meaning?
Look.
Look at him. I have given
him an offer of Rs 150 million.
What?
He took the project in his hands.
So give this to me. And you.
Yes?
Go.
Where?
Go home.
Salim.
Salim, I have taken care of
this project like my own child.
Salim, that wasn't right on your part. No.
Hey, stop.
Where are you going?
They are my men.
Do something.
Yes.
You can go back to Meerut.
Go by train and buy half a ticket.
When the TT asks why did you buy
half a ticket? Tell him that you are a kid.
Go, go away. Go away. Take
his clothes off. Make him nude.
Get on with it. Everything is mine.
The whole building standing
here is mine. Don't do this to me.
I will be ruined. I will
give you all your money.
Come on.
Salim.
Have pity on me.
Salim, I had to tell you something else.
He is finally silent. You had a lot of
demands, right? A lot of demands.
What is this?
Kukreja Sun City. And not Salim city.
Clothes? Who took my clothes off?
What is it? Even you want to have fun?
Spend your honeymoon
well. She is a good looking girl.
And if you don't get a place, then...
What is this? Where have you got it from?
I'm good at aiming things.
Move aside!
No, Dholu. No.
Dholu, calm down.
Make it fast. Make it quick.
Give a check of Rs 200,000 to the fool.
More?
Quickly. He got a lot of
abuses from me. A lot of them.
And he has done a good job, right?
Okay, sir. I will send it.
Salim? Is he still alive?
Hello.
Mr Kukreja.
Who is it?
Ranvir.
Ranvir? Tell me.
You are feeling sad. What happened?
You took everything away.
Now look, everyone is destined to
have the food they are supposed to eat.
Right?
They are.
Come on. Read it.
What?
What are you saying?
Yes?
Come on, read it.
Sir, take a look at it.
He cut the call.
What?
Sir, look at this.
'Don't worry!'
Don't worry!
Hey, I thought he is a good man. Now
we cannot see faces on the phone, Ranvir.
Hey, don't be mad, Ranvir.
They have made a... Ranvir.
Please. It is a big company.
They have made an offer of Rs 400 million.
Rs 400 million. I have
explained them the offer.
I had told him. He will understand.
Uncle. Make him explain. Please.
Yes, dear. Choice is yours.
Great. Choice is yours. Say yes.
Mr Lal.
Yes?
There is a saying in Raghukul.
One can lose life but not the given word.
Ranvir, don't recite poems for me.
Give me your decision.
You will be super rich.
Mr Lal, my word is
better than super, right?
Yes. That is right.
Bhairav, I forgot to tell you something.
Cow dung has turned into a gold. The
rates of fertilizer shares are sky high.
Better than super.
Hey, what are you saying?