I like you.
Having these feelings right now,
I think I must be crazy.
But I can't hide it anymore.
My feelings just won't stop.
I like you.
I…
like you, Se-na.
Do La-ik, I…
I'm sorry. It's just…
This is so sudden.
I'm not even sure what these feelings are.
I'm just really…
confused right now.
Yes.
It's okay.
I'm not asking you to answer right away.
I'll wait…
until you sort out your feelings.
I'll wait as long as it takes.
I'm going to sleep.
Okay. Good night.
What do I do?
What am I supposed to do?
How am I supposed to look him in the face?
I really need the bathroom.
Wait.
Let's just calm down.
Calm down. Wipe my eyes.
La-ik?
Se-na.
I figured you'd be feeling uneasy,
wondering how to face me,
and then you'd come across this letter.
So I left without saying anything.
I was afraid
that seeing you would shake my decision
to return to my place.
Thanks to you,
I have the courage to face my reality.
I want to get my life back on track,
so I can stand before you and myself
without shame.
Whatever choice you make,
I'll be here,
with these feelings unchanged.
Thank you for helping me get back
on my feet when I was at my lowest.
From the bottom of my heart.
I like you.
I…
like you, Se-na.
No way.
How could La-ik…
That La-ik…
likes me?
No, that can't be it.
Well…
He's going through a lot right now.
He must've leaned on me
without realizing it.
He just mistook that feeling.
Yeah, that's what it is.
Let's just think of it that way.
But what about me?
Do I like him?
If you've finished
reviewing the response brief
for Ms. Kim Ha-jin's case,
they're asking for it to be filed today.
DO I LIKE?
Here.
This looks like the sentencing opinion.
Here it is.
They moved Jae-hee to a general ward.
He's out of the ICU for now.
But there's been no improvement.
And they say it's unlikely
he'll regain consciousness.
Everyone's pretty much given up.
I thought you should know.
You always loved this song.
I told you to give La-ik's case to Jang.
Why are you holding onto it?
Sir,
please review this once before you do.
JAE-HEE'S VEHICLE FORENSICS REPORT
What is this?
REPORT
And this is for what?
This is solid evidence proving
that Do La-ik is deeply involved
in both Woo-seong and Jae-hee's cases.
If we merge the charges,
Woo-seong's murder
and the attempted murder of Jae-hee,
we have a real shot at winning in court.
No, absolutely not.
The higher-ups want this
wrapped up quietly.
Sir, if we bury this case now,
we will never clear our name
from accusations of mishandling the case.
We have enough evidence.
Statements, situational proof,
multiple direct and indirect materials.
We can fight this in court.
I'll take full responsibility.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING? ARE YOU UP?
AD,
SAME-DAY TRANSFER WITH NO NEED TO VISIT
Seriously,
how could he leave
something this important here?
So careless.
What am I supposed to do with this?
I mean,
why leave this with me?
What am I supposed to do?
I can't go deliver it myself.
God…
It's not like this thing has legs
and can walk itself over.
Should I have it couriered?
No, that would make me nervous.
It looks expensive.
Something like this goes missing
and it will bother him all day.
He won't be able to focus on anything.
And now it's a headache for me too.
Well, no choice.
I'll just take it to him myself.
Okay, that's too much, Se-na.
What am I doing?
ATTORNEY MAENG SE-NA
No. I said I'd wait.
Let's go.
Did he really leave?
Hey!
What are you doing?
- What do you mean by that?
- I mean,
I heard Do La-ik left, so I thought
I'd celebrate by eating chicken.
But where are you going in that
at this late hour?
Well…
That's Do La-ik's hat, isn't it?
Yes. Seriously…
he left it at my place. Such a hassle.
A hassle?
Give it here. I'll drop it off.
No. Don't bother.
Just eat dinner.
I'll take it to him real quick.
Okay, let's just check if she's asleep.
Just to the door.
Just a quick look.
It's not like…
I have to give this to him face-to-face.
I could just leave it at the door.
Whose car is this?
I've never seen it before.
Only residents are supposed to park here.
Because of cars like this,
there are never any parking spaces left.
Let's see the plate number.
- La-ik?
- Yes, Se-na.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
The weather's nice.
So I thought I'd go for a drive.
What about you?
Huh?
Here.
You left this.
Why did you bring this to me?
What do you mean?
It was at my house.
It looked expensive. So I brought it.
This? Now?
At this hour? To me?
Yeah…
Well…
the weather's nice…
Thought I'd go for a little drive too.
Anyway, I gave you the hat,
so I'll go now.
Sure.
You're…
still…
waiting, right?
Sure.
Okay then.
Bye.
Stop it.
Stop.
She's killing me, seriously.
Attorney Maeng has been
coming in late these days.
Yeah.
She used to get here at dawn.
Now she just comes in on time.
It's weird. Her expression too.
Lately, something's off.
Right? She's been making
mistakes she never makes.
Wait, is she dating someone?
Come on. That's impossible.
If she starts dating,
that's a miracle for humanity.
- Oh, my god!
- What?
Something funny?
What?
Look.
What is this?
Oh, my god.
With the client?
- Attorney Maeng, did you see the article?
- What article?
Something ridiculous came out.
It says you and our La-ik…
I mean,
you and Do La-ik are living together…
What do we do?
Should we demand they take it down
immediately and threaten legal action?
Attorney Maeng,
you need to take action right away.
For the client's sake…
and for your own.
Thank you, Ye-sol.
I'll explain everything to you later.
Hello, what's up?
Hey! Why weren't you picking up?
- I was in the shower.
- What's between you and that attorney?
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
You've been living with her
this whole time?
What?
MAENG SE-NA
She looks awful in real life.
LIVING WITH HIS ATTORNEY IS NOT OKAY
WHAT'S HE THINKING?
MR. DO LA-IK
- Yes, La-ik.
- Attorney Maeng
Are you okay?
You saw the article, huh?
I'm fine.
What about you?
I'm just sorry. Because of me…
because I was staying there…
No, it's not that. But for now,
until things calm down a little,
you shouldn't go outside.
And you can't go looking
for Reporter Baek again, okay?
It will only make things worse.
Why aren't you answering? Okay?
Okay.
I get it. But what about you?
Every time something like this happens,
you're the one who deals with everything.
It makes me angry.
And the fact that I can't do anything…
makes me feel pathetic.
Don't think like that.
I'm really okay.
People always make a fuss
and then forget in a few days.
I'll just stay off
the Internet for a while.
If anything happens,
don't handle it alone.
Call me right away, okay?
Yeah. I will.
I'll call you.
Yeah.
Chung-jae, it's me.
Se-na, did you see the article?
Yeah, I saw it.
I'll head over right now…
No need to come to me. But…
I need a favor. It's about Do La-ik.
I'm worried about him.
Can you keep him
from going out for a while?
It's better if he's not seen right now.
You worry about him, even now?
Attorney Maeng!
Please, help me with this.
TOP ARTICLE BY CATEGORY
All right, just wait.
There's something even bigger coming.
EXCLUSIVE - MURDER SUSPECT
LIVING WITH HIS ATTORNEY
LA-IK'S ATTORNEY EXPOSED
AS A KILLER'S DAUGHTER
You shouldn't have messed with me.
WHERE ARE THE ETHICS?
I told you, if you poke me, I explode.
UPLOAD IMMEDIATELY
EXPOSED AS A KILLER'S DAUGHTER
GOLD MEDAL
INTERNATIONAL MATHEMATICAL OLYMPIAD
Where is she?
Living together? Is he out of his mind?
Seriously!
Who ruined Woo-seong's life?
Exactly. And who is this lawyer woman?
How can she live with a client?
- What is this now?
- What?
A KILLER'S DAUGHTER
CHEON-UN LAW FIRM PROTEST NOTICE
PROTEST NOTICE
NOW IT'S TIME FOR US TO ACT
Damn it.
This…
isn't like you at all, Attorney Maeng.
The Attorney Maeng I know
always keeps a clear head,
always knows where the line is
and never crosses it.
I'm truly sorry.
No, I'm not asking for an apology.
I'm worried about you.
I hate seeing people
talk about you like this.
What happened? Why did you do it?
Do you remember
what you once asked me?
How I managed to stay standing
after what happened to my father.
How I didn't fall apart.
The truth is…
I did fall apart a lot.
But…
I survived because of Do La-ik's music.
I was…
a longtime fan.
What?
So when this incident happened,
I wanted to see for myself
whether he was capable
of something like that. And if he wasn't…
then this time, I wanted to be the one
to keep him from falling apart.
Oh, my…
I see.
What do we do now?
Sir. You might want to come out here.
Daughter of a killer! Step down!
- Step down!
Look.
She's really stirred things up this time.
EXPOSED AS A KILLER'S DAUGHTER
Hey, Wonsan-daero is chaos right now.
The wireless cutomer
you are calling is unavailable.
- Where are you going?
- Move.
Se-na told me not to let you go outside.
If you show up there now,
it will only make things worse.
- I'll go to her instead…
- I said move.
What are you going to do?
Don't you get it?
This happened because of you!
Do you even know how she has lived?
Sleeping a few hours a night,
never getting to enjoy things.
That's how she has lived.
Why do you think she worked that hard?
Because she wanted
to escape from her past.
Because she wanted to stand tall
in front of the world.
But now, all of that…
All of it is on the verge
of collapsing because of you!
Do you know that?
I know.
That's why I'm doing this.
I wanted to protect her
but I never managed to do that.
Just this once…
I don't want to leave her alone.
What do we do now?
Looks like people have completely
surrounded the whole building.
There's no way
they'll come up here, right?
Hey!
Do you know what it's like outside?
This whole mess is because of you!
Attorney Hwang, that's enough. Stop.
I'm sorry. This is all because of me.
Forget it.
Things will calm down soon enough.
There's no calming down!
We can't get anything done anymore!
I said that's enough.
This all happened because of me.
So I'll handle it.
I'm really sorry.
I'm truly sorry, everyone.
No, wait.
Don't go out there! Attorney Maeng!
Hey.
- Come out!
- Show yourself!
This is my workplace.
What you're doing here
is interfering with our operations.
- I'm asking all of you to leave.
- Is it true you were living with La-ik?
As Mr. Do La-ik's attorney,
it's my duty to protect my client
and fulfill my responsibilities.
How I determine
the appropriate method in doing so
is entirely a matter
of my professional judgment.
So I ask that you refrain
from unfounded personal questions
and speculative…
Anyway, did you live together or not?
What is your relationship with him?
- We…
- Your dad was a murderer!
- What?
- Really?
A murderer?
How does a killer's daughter
get to defend anyone?
Did you hear? Her dad killed someone.
I know, right?
She's stinky.
She might have the same genes.
- She might kill someone too.
- Exactly.
- Get out of here!
It's Do La-ik!
- What?
- It's La-ik!
- Hey!
- La-ik!
What are you doing?
What are you doing here, Do La-ik?
I told you,
don't come outside until things calm down!
- So why are you…
- And I told you,
if anything happens,
don't deal with it alone.
And? Coming here fixes what, exactly?
I hate running away and avoiding things.
But…
because of you, it looked like we ran away
from all those people. Do you get that?
It wasn't avoiding anything
or running away!
I don't care what anyone else says.
What matters most to me right now…
is you.
Standing by and watching you get hurt
is avoiding and running away to me.
Just once…
Just for today,
can't you think about yourself first?
Just for today, please.
Let me take care of everything else.
"NO PERSONAL FEELINGS," - YET SEEN
LEAVING THE SCENE TOGETHER
SOMETHING WAS ALWAYS UP
BAD TIMING
CARELESS FOR A CELEB
SHE QUIT TO DATE HIM?
Where are we going?
SO-SEUL MOUNTAIN CABIN
Excuse me,
do you have any rooms available?
Huh?
Most people make reservations
before coming.
How do you two even know about this place?
Someone who was supposed to come today
canceled, so I was cleaning up.
You know "no-show," right?
This was gonna go to waste anyway.
If you wanna eat, go ahead and eat.
I don't know what happened to you two,
but just take your time and rest.
- Thank you so much.
- Yeah.
What a beautiful day.
You're really something,
Maeng Se-na.
These are all the materials required
for filing the indictment.
We meet all the conditions
for prosecution, but…
are you truly going through with this?
Let's begin.
SEOUL DISTRICT PROSECUTOR
DEFENDANT DO LA-IK
Wow, this looks good.
Hurry and eat.
You can eat at a time like this?
Pork belly can really go down your throat?
In emergencies like this,
you have to eat first.
You need strength to fight.
Fight who, exactly?
At least you know it's an emergency.
We should stay here for today.
You really shouldn't have come
to the office, though.
I know. But I can't undo it now.
The fans were…
Eat first.
You can scold me later.
Wow, this is insane.
It's so good.
Are you not gonna eat?
Then I'll eat everything.
No. I'm hungry too.
A MURDERER'S DAUGHTER DEFENDS A MURDERER
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
It all feels like it's my fault.
If it weren't for me,
people wouldn't have found out
about your father.
I'm sorry too.
For running away and avoiding things.
That's actually me.
I think I'd forgotten for a while.
That…
what it feels like
to be called a murderer's daughter.
At some point,
I got used to living just enough.
Keeping people at a safe distance,
pretending to be a little confident,
a little sharp around the edges.
Living like that…
wasn't so bad.
I became a lawyer
because of my father.
To clear his name.
But I kept delaying the retrial
all this time…
saying I needed more time,
that it had to be perfect.
But today, I realized,
I was just running away.
I was scared…
of being called that name again. So I hid.
Pretended nothing happened.
And lived like a coward,
forgetting everything.
That's not cowardice.
You weren't running away.
You were holding on.
To survive.
No one can live every day
picking at their own wounds.
You endured
because you needed to remember,
and to remember,
you had to live.
That's how…
you made it through.
I like you.
I like you, Se-na.
I'm sorry.
Good night.
Come here. Have some coffee.
The birds sound…
sound really nice here.
And the air is really fresh.
Yeah.
Feels like
it's just the two of us in the world.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Do I have something on my face?
Should we stay here one more night?
How can someone be…
this transparent?
Yeah? Me?
Yes.
When I think about it,
you've always been honest
about your feelings.
- Surprisingly honest.
- And?
You don't like it?
I like it.
At first, I was confused.
But now, I get it.
Whether you're on stage
or standing in front of me,
you're still the same Do La-ik.
I like you.
All of you.
Just the way you are.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry. I couldn't come in…
No, coming in isn't the issue right now.
- Sorry?
- We received an indictment for Do La-ik.
The prosecution
has officially charged him.
- What?
- That bastard, Prosecutor Kwak.
He clearly waited for this moment.
You two are in the middle of a scandal,
the public is against you,
and he slips this in right now.
What are we supposed to do?
We can't just sit back and take this!
- Please, just one statement!
- Prosecutor Kwak!
You've filed charges
against Do La-ik today.
It's been reported that a note was found
in which Choi Jae-hee confessed.
What is your reason for indicting him?
The investigation
must rely on objective evidence.
We have secured substantial physical
and circumstantial evidence,
and regardless of Mr. Choi's note,
we are confident in proceeding
with the prosecution.
- Move, please.
- Prosecutor Kwak!
Just one comment, please!
Just a quick comment, please!
You can't just leave like that!
Please say a little more, Prosecutor!
Prosecutor!
If they've indicted him,
that means they've got something, right?
They wouldn't move this fast
without evidence.
But in a situation like this, is it okay
for Attorney Maeng to handle the case?
Articles are saying
they are living together,
and now her past is being dragged out too.
No way she can keep going.
Even for her,
this has to be too much mentally.
She can't do it.
- Can I see the indictment right away?
- Sorry?
Yes!
I need you to request access and copies
of evidence the prosecution submitted.
All of it, as quickly as possible.
Yes.
I wanted to protect her
but I never managed to do that.
Just this once…
I don't want to leave her alone.
LA-IK - OFFICIALLY INDICTED
FOR THE MURDER OF KANG WOO-SEONG
The prosecution
has officially indicted you,
we can't avoid this fight anymore.
This is where it really begins.
Are you ready?
What do you need me to do?
First, we need to fact-check
every single claim the prosecution made.
See if their statements match the evidence
and whether anything
was omitted or distorted.
Whatever I can do, I'll do it.
Then…
there are a few things
I need you to confirm.
And no matter what,
I'm going to break away from you.
Then we can live the way we want.
Fine, do it. Let's do this.
It's going to be a big fight.
Be ready for it.
CALL RECORDING - WOO-SEONG
Did you hear it?
Huh?
Here, this part.
Listen carefully.
Be ready for it.
There.
Isn't that a door-lock keypad sound?
I asked Director Geum
for the raw audio file,
in case something in the recording
might help recreate the events.
I found it
while I was making the transcript.
But there isn't a door-lock
in Director Geum's office.
If what we're thinking is right,
this could be circumstantial evidence
that someone else
entered your home that day.
Then we might be able to prove
the culprit was someone else?
But before that…
these are additional materials
the prosecution submitted.
It's the forensics report
on Jae-hee's car accident.
There are several indicators suggesting
it might not have been a suicide.
It looks like the prosecution plans
to use that to build their case.
Yeah…
He'd never kill himself.
But during questioning,
why didn't you say where you were?
Where were you?
Where do you think?
That was when you left my house, right?
Were you at your dorm?
Sorry?
I was following you.
Following…
Me?
When?
Not like a stalker or anything!
I just happened to be near your office.
And you were getting off work.
So I thought, "Where is she going?"
And then, you were drinking beer.
What?
Well, well.
So…
So what exactly did you see?
Just you chugging beer,
yelling your lungs out on the way home,
dumping all my merch
in front of your house.
So you saw everything.
You have to explain all of that in court!
Why would you follow me like that?
Because I missed you.
Because I wanted to see you.
But why did you go to the place
where I played piano for you?
Were you maybe
missing me a little that day?
Come on, what's that reaction?
What is it? Huh?
You did miss me, didn't you?
Se-na? Why can't you say it?
I missed you!
I couldn't stop thinking about you.
You didn't need to say it that honestly.
What's this?
That's the evidence inventory.
The items the police took from your place.
We didn't request them back,
so they're still at the station.
Wasn't this your signature accessory?
You wore it every day for ages,
but not so much recently.
ONE METAL PIERCING
Why? Is it important?
This…
Sir, can you hear me?
Why are you suddenly acting like this?
So there was one more of this?
I…
think I know.
What?
I…
think I know the person
who came to my place that day.
No matter how painful the truth is,
I won't run away anymore.
Woo-seong had a habit of
recording everything.
I can't figure out the password.
Woo-seong said he hid a secret message
in one of his songs.
I'm leaving now. Take care.
Byung-gyun, can you really live
with a clear conscience?
I want to hear from you directly
why you did it.
Subtitle translation by: Soyeon Kim