(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
So about you and that
guy from the other day...
Is it always just the
two of you meeting up?
Kanata.
Just listen to me.
Don't.
- Kanata...
- I said I don't want to hear it.
That guy...
He's a friend of my brother's.
I've talked to him about a
lot, and he's helped me out...
We just ended up in
that kind of relationship.
The person you said you kissed...
Was it him?
Then why did you kiss me too?
I...
I'm not the person you think I am, Kanata.
I'm not like you.
I'm not that strong.
And I'm not that pure, either.
Akira.
Do you actually like him?
It's not like that.
He's always had someone else he likes.
Then why...?
That's just how we've always been...
It's how we kept our balance.
But...
That's all over now.
Because I...
I've fallen for you.
So...
I'm sorry.
"Contrast"
(Episode 6: Don't Fall for Me)
It's huge! Are you serious?
Pretty crazy, right?
- This jumbo Salisbury steak is insane.
- Right?
Man, I really want to try it.
- You want some too, Kanata?
- Yeah.
Can you even finish that?
Oh, you got a haircut.
It was getting long enough to be annoying.
Though I didn't go that short.
Nice. I kind of want to cut mine too.
You kind of look like you did
back in middle school, Kanata.
Yeah.
That brings back memories.
Oh, by the way.
Looks like I'm playing in the next prelim.
Really?
Well, I guess I have no choice.
I'll have to go cheer for you.
You don't have to force yourself.
I'd just be rotting at home anyway.
Of course I'm going.
What kind of reason is that?
Hey, should we invite Senkawa too?
Good idea.
The more people cheering
for Kanata, the better.
Isn't he busy, though?
I'll go ask him.
So, should we hit this
place after the game?
I'm down.
Let's go. We're getting that steak.
What are you guys talking about?
The jumbo Salisbury steak.
Hey, I want in on that too.
A strong cold front is
expected to hit Japan next week.
According to the Meteorological Agency,
intense cold air will
move in from the north,
causing temperatures to drop nationwide...
It's freezing.
Where is the bus?
Akira, aren't you cold?
Oh... I'm okay.
Hey!
No fair, I want one too.
I only have one.
I don't care.
Ah...
So warm.
Your hands are freezing.
Warm them up for me.
Hold my hand.
Wait, what...?
Hey, Akira.
Yeah?
Even if we go to different high schools,
let's still hang out, okay?
OK.
Damn it...
That shot I took today was the best.
Please, your shot was way more impressive.
No way.
- Kanata's the one who blew it.
- True.
- Kanata really played like crap today.
- Aoyama.
- Shut up, I did not.
- Come here a second.
- I'll be right back.
Yes, Coach.
I heard that for this prefectural prelim,
there will be college scouts in the stands.
Wait, really?
As your coach,
and thinking about your future,
I think this is a great chance
to show what you can do.
- Yes, sir.
- However...
Soccer is a team sport.
You know what I'm getting at,
don't you?
I know...
I have high expectations for you.
Thank you.
It's been a while since we've seen a game.
Yeah...
Back in middle school,
we used to cheer for Kanata all the time.
That's true.
Remember that one time?
They lost, and you were
the one crying your eyes out.
- I was like, "Why are YOU crying?"
- Stop bringing that up!
Don't worry.
Kanata will be fine.
Yeah...
I'm sure he's been doing a
lot of thinking in his own way.
Senkawa-kun.
Are you free this Saturday?
Why?
Kanata's playing in the next game.
I thought we could all
go cheer for him together.
Oh...
Um.
Did something happen
between you and Kanata?
Huh...?
Sorry.
I know I'm being a busybody,
but Kanata wears his heart on his sleeve.
You guys aren't fighting, are you?
Yeah.
But...
I guess it kind of feels that way.
If anything's going on with you two,
it's my turn to help you out.
You can talk to me anytime...
I just think...
Kanata probably doesn't want me there.
No way.
You're the person he wants there the most.
[Math textbook]
[A book about soccer rules]
Go for it!
Nice! Let's go!
Kanata! You got this!
Where's Senkawa?
He said he was coming...
Maybe he got the time wrong.
Kanata! Push up!
Please don't get hurt...
Hey, Senkawa.
With your grades,
I think you should set
your sights a bit higher.
So for the winter session,
I think you should sign up for this class.
It's perfect for your level.
Not only will you master the basics,
- But it'll raise your overall score.
- Sir...
It'll really boost your skills.
And you'll get plenty
of practice problems...
I'm so sorry, I have to go!
Ah, Senkawa!
Move up!
Everyone, press forward!
Pick up the intensity!
Win it back!
Kanata!
Kanata! Pick up the pace!
Sorry... did I make it?
Just barely.
Is this overtime?
Yeah, exactly!
I didn't know much about soccer,
so I did a little studying.
Kanata! Go!
Kanata! Hang in there!
- Are you okay?!
- You alright!?
Wait... Kanata...?
Kanata...!
- You okay?
- Can you stand?
No way...
It's fine.
The way he fell, he shouldn't
have twisted anything.
Is he really OK?
- I think you should ice it.
- I'm fine.
- Really? You're okay?
- You sure?
I'm fine, really.
Can you still move?
I can move. My legs are fine.
- Can you still play?
- I can play.
- You good to go?
- I'm good.
- It's okay.
- Then get back out there.
Alright, keep going. Get in there, Kanata.
If they get a goal, they're tied.
- See ya.
- Good work today.
Good job.
- Nice work.
- Good job out there.
- Thanks.
- You really gave it your all.
Um... you didn't get hurt
when you fell, did you?
No, not at all.
Not a scratch.
I'm glad you're okay.
Sorry we lost after you guys
came all this way to cheer.
Kanata.
What are you doing after this?
Oh, I'm just gonna head home once I change.
I see. Then let's head back together...
Oh! I just remembered there's a
limited-edition donut I have to get!
Hey, let's go. Come on, come on.
If you two are free later,
I'll text you the location!
Oh... okay.
Is it okay if you don't go with them?
Yeah.
I just want to go straight home today.
I see.
Do you... want to talk for a bit?
Sure.
Your hair...
You cut it short.
Yeah.
I was late.
I'm sorry.
Did you see that last penalty kick?
Yeah.
I guess you only saw me at my worst.
Since then,
I've gone back to that
stairwell a few times.
Wait, what?
I'm sorry...
Why are you apologizing over that?
Why say sorry for falling for me?
I don't know.
You said I was strong
and pure and all that,
but I'm not that person at all.
I don't even know what
"pure" is supposed to mean.
I'm too proud for my own good,
and I'm a coward who just
makes excuses to run away.
I kept wondering how to make
up for the time I quit soccer,
and my head was just full of regrets.
Half the time, I don't even
understand what you're saying.
I...
Maybe I was just jealous of how
honest you are about what you love.
Even when you have regrets,
you still face them with
everything you've got.
That's all thanks to you.
If you hadn't been there, Akira,
I wouldn't even be standing here right now.
What about you, Kanata?
What kind of person do you think I am?
Huh...?
What do I think?
Well...
I guess it's your personality.
Even if we're not always
on the same wavelength,
I feel comfortable around you.
And you're so mature.
You've really had a huge influence on me.
So I want you to feel like
being with me is helping you...
to move in a better direction too.
Remember when I said,
"There are things you only
realize by talking them out"?
Do you remember that, Kanata?
Yeah...
Those words...
I was actually just quoting Kanda-san.
Wait...
The words that gave you a fresh start...
I didn't come up with them.
Even when you were struggling,
I just thought about what
Kanda-san would say.
And all the music I listen to...
Kanda-san recommended all of it.
I think even if I stay with you,
I'll never be able to erase his influence.
Even if it wasn't romantic,
back in middle school,
Kanda-san was the reason
I could even be myself.
So, honestly,
I shouldn't be getting
involved with you like this.
What...?
I don't want to be a
stain on your life, Kanata.
Even if I love you,
please don't fall for me.
(Next Episode)
Um...
Is Kanata here?
What's with this cliché
way of avoiding someone?
Maybe I was just jealous of you.
Oh, for crying out loud.
I've already made up my mind.