QUEEN OF TEARS
I'm sorry I yelled.
The truth is…
I don't remember.
I don't remember at all why I was there.
I was in front of your house,
then suddenly I was somewhere else.
I don't know when I went there
or how.
I have no idea.
I was…
so scared.
By the way,
why did you come here by yourself?
Your sister texted me.
She said your father
was losing the election.
His rival was winning
the voters over with food.
That's why you came?
I mean, he was losing
to pork and rice soup.
How could I sit still?
So that's why you counterattacked
with beef and lobster?
You should've witnessed
how I mercilessly beat 200 bowls of soup.
Hae-in!
-Hae-in!
Is she there?
No, she's not.
-Hae-in!
-You haven't found her yet?
Where is she?
Where could she be?
My poor Hae-in!
Call the police!
-We have to!
-Hae-in!
-Where are you?
Hae-in!
-Hae-in!
-Where did she go?
Hae-in!
Gosh!
Goodness.
Goodness, my poor baby!
Goodness! Here you were!
EPISODE 5
We were really startled.
Where were you?
Stop asking her.
Father, you should sleep.
Okay.
Don't mind us.
People here go to bed early.
-So make yourself at home.
-He's right.
-Consider us invisible.
-Right.
Unbelievable.
How can you be invisible
when you're here? Go.
-Let's go. Night.
-Night.
Good night.
I need to dry my hair.
Is there a hair dryer?
One minute.
This is pretty old.
It's okay.
It's not working.
You need to press down on the bottom.
Like this?
Hold the cable.
Let me do it.
There's a way to do this.
-It's all dry now.
-Right.
I think you're good.
Mom!
Check this out.
People don't change that easily.
What's with her?
What is it?
Hae-in must've visited her in-laws
out of the blue.
-What for?
-That's why I'm dumbfounded.
Hillbillies are unbelievable.
They filmed this and uploaded it.
Upload what?
What are you doing here?
I'm glad you're all here.
I missed your last birthday,
so I came to treat
the villagers to a meal.
BEAUTIFUL CEO HONG HAE-IN
She's never surprised me on my birthday.
How unbelievable.
Are you hungry?
Do you want to eat something?
I already ate a lot.
Have some of this, will you?
This is soy sauce marinated crab.
It's full of roe.
We're known for our soy sauce.
This is frozen pork belly
grilled over briquettes.
Have some before it gets cold.
I'm eating them one by one,
so please wait.
-What's next?
-Try this too.
Move over, will you?
You're suffocating my baby.
Don't be so ridiculous.
Chew slowly,
or you'll have an upset stomach.
Drink some water too.
Give her some of the eggs.
Let me do it.
Why are they making her so uncomfortable?
And why is she eating everything
they're giving her?
Frozen pork belly is best when hot.
What?
How does this video
have over 300,000 views?
Why is she eating so much?
Beef, pork, chicken, duck, and fish.
I had all kinds of meat.
I think I've gained weight.
-Really?
-I mean…
A woman offered me chicken that she'd
never even made for her son-in-law.
I think the villagers like me.
They seem to be doing well,
so don't you dare mention the divorce.
You got it.
Have you told anyone so far?
Come on, Mom. I'd be an idiot if I did.
-Why are you so quiet?
-What?
Goodness. Who was it? Who did you tell?
I was having makgeolli
with Yeong-song and…
-What?
You told him that--
You told him that Hyun-woo
almost got divorced?
Well, Yeong-song is like
a marriage counselor of this village,
so I consulted him.
I lamented.
That was all.
What if he told others?
-Yes.
-Word will spread quickly.
Consultation is all about confidentiality.
He doesn't need to keep it a secret
since he's not a licensed doctor.
Jeez. Even still…
You and your big mouth.
Come on.
You were worried,
so you came here at this hour?
Did you tell anyone?
Of course not.
I only told my mother.
Why would you?
Du-gwan, she's the only family I have.
We share everything.
And you know her condition.
When did you come home, honey?
Why are you always away?
Where are you sleeping these days?
Mom, go to bed.
Who are you?
See? So don't worry about her
and worry about your son and his wife.
There's nothing to worry about.
Despite being so busy,
Hae-in came all the way here
to aid my campaign.
-What does that mean?
-What?
It means the two are madly in love.
What's this? How cute.
It's always been my favorite.
Your hand.
You shouldn't be alone anymore.
You always get hurt.
I heard this is your lifeline.
Why is mine so short?
I'm offended.
Come on.
Do you believe in palm reading?
No, but it doesn't feel nice.
I'm terminally ill,
and my lifeline is short.
You're not terminally ill.
You didn't want to be a patient.
You said you'd get better.
You said God was on your side
and that a miracle would happen.
You said the best cancer center
in Europe would cure everything!
I never said they'd cure everything.
I'm just saying.
There's a reason they're the best.
Do you think so?
Will you…
come with me?
It's not that I'm scared of going alone.
You're just the only person
who knows that I'm sick.
Are you serious?
That's a given.
Does it still sting?
Have you gone insane?
What were you trying to do?
Don't tell me
you wanted to kiss her.
Jesus.
You're crazy.
You're insane.
But still,
you shouldn't have left her hanging.
She must be startled.
You're going back in?
What will you say to her?
What will you do?
Do you think you can come back outside?
No, you can't.
No. I won't be able to leave
if I go back.
I can't.
Did he run away?
No.
I'm sure
he had something to do.
Maybe he had to go to the toilet
or make a call.
But for this long?
Can you please quiet down?
Jeez, you're so noisy.
Shut up!
Did you and Hae-in argue?
No.
It's the opposite.
Then are you being punished?
Did she tell you to go outside
and self-reflect for an hour?
-Have you ever done that?
-Many times.
But she'll get even more upset
if you do as she says.
She'll forgive you
if you hurry back and apologize.
That's hot.
So get a grip and go back inside.
I'm only here
so I can come to my senses.
I can't think straight at home.
Why not?
I don't know. I just can't.
BAEK HYUN-WOO
Where are you?
Why isn't he reading it?
Hey, he read it.
Go to bed first.
"Go to bed first"?
He wants me to sleep first?
By myself?
Fine.
That's what he wants.
Go to bed.
Go to bed first.
Damn it.
So he did run away.
Why? Does he think I'll eat him alive?
Is he afraid of me?
Be quiet!
Why is he afraid of me?
How am I scary?
Even the dogs are sleeping.
Let's go back home now.
I'll stay out a bit longer.
Hae-in will sleep alone then.
Yes, that's why.
I'll go back once she does.
Jeez, you idiot.
Why?
Why will you wait until then?
Because I might…
make a mistake.
What do you mean?
You only make mistakes when you're drunk.
You shouldn't have drunk in that case.
No.
I won't make any mistakes
if I drink and pass out.
I have no idea what you're saying.
Listen carefully.
I'm going to drink more
and get totally wasted.
Just do me one favor.
-What is it?
-Don't…
put me…
back in my room.
I'm so lost.
Do you want ramyeon? I'll make some.
I used to be so scared of my wife.
I used to be
okay.
I was sure that I'd be unfazed
no matter what happened to her.
Why? Because I didn't like her.
Just like I've done so far,
I just need to continue disliking,
resenting,
and being tired of her.
I just need to anticipate
the day we part ways.
I don't need to like her.
It's simple.
I've been doing it all along.
But…
strangely enough,
I can't do it anymore.
Fine.
We don't need to sleep together.
We've been sleeping separately for years.
TWO YEARS AGO
What are you doing?
Ms. Hong told us to clean out the room.
The Product Team is in charge
of picking and removing brands.
The Sales Team needs to focus
on the brands' performance.
Hold on.
What is it?
The nursery.
-Are you cleaning out?
-What's the use of it?
It only gets on my nerves.
It gets on your nerves?
We don't need it anymore.
The Product Team can't attract
good brands with poor performance.
Isn't that obvious?
Yes.
Please move my belongings into this room.
Sorry?
I need a bed too.
I'll stay here for now.
Yes, sir.
Don't cry.
You have no right.
You're up early.
Does it look like I slept?
Did you not sleep at all?
What's it to you?
Ho-yeol, shouldn't you go to school?
Dad, why does that matter?
My life mentor
is right here.
What do you mean? Who's your mentor?
She's the family's pillar
who came in a supercar.
It's my aunt,
a building owner and my role model.
There she comes.
-Come on out.
-Gosh, Hae-in.
Thank you.
You did so much.
Go home safely.
Goodbye.
-Hyun-woo.
-Hello, ma'am.
-Goodbye.
-Yes, ma'am.
Your mother is sane again.
Yeong-song, she's all better now.
Goodness, Mother.
Stay strong.
Thank you.
Divorce is nothing.
I wanted to get a divorce too.
I should have when I had the chance.
Goodness, Mother.
Gosh, ma'am.
I think she's out of it again.
You should hurry home.
Let's go.
Honey, did you sleep here last night?
This is exactly why I want a divorce.
Let's just go home.
-I should've divorced you!
-Let's go!
-You should go.
-She's a villager.
She's a bit demented.
Goodbye, honey.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
All right then.
-Goodbye.
-Gosh, you weren't an inconvenience.
This isn't much.
But I used no pesticides,
so make sure you eat them.
Hae-in, I know work is important.
But your health comes first.
You should go.
Thank you.
Okay, get home safely.
-Let's go.
-Thanks, Hae-in.
-Goodbye.
-Go.
We'll get going then.
-Okay.
Call me.
Do you have cigarettes?
No.
Do you think she caught on?
Who knows?
I don't think she did,
but there was cold air
between them even before then.
They even avoided eye contact
before hopping in.
You shouldn't have talked
about how he received
love letters in the past
and how the principal's daughter
had a crush on him. All that useless talk.
-It must've upset her.
-What?
It was just a joke.
Was it funny?
-Are you serious?
-He didn't sleep in his room last night.
-What?
Then what did he do?
We drank together at the store.
That hurts.
You insisted, didn't you?
No, he didn't want to go.
I guess sleeping separately
made it awkward.
How could their love die?
They used to be madly in love.
I'm sorry for this abrupt meeting.
You sure are dressed up for an intern.
You must like luxury brands. I do too.
FOUR YEARS AGO
Mr. Baek is on his way back
from working outside.
I know. That's why I called you.
What is this?
About Hyun-woo…
I know.
He's decent. I'm sure you want him.
He's smart and handsome.
Did he tell you how many cows we own?
-Yes.
-As well as the size of our orchard?
And that we own the only store in town?
What about his house in Seoul?
He signed a two-year lease.
Then you must know.
I didn't know I was materialistic,
but I can't help it since he's family.
I heard you're poor
and that you wear shabby clothes.
No, they're all special vintage…
What does he know anyway?
That's true. Anyway…
Can you stop seeing him?
I will never break up with him.
And that's final.
You're quite selfish.
All the ladies who want to date him
are successful individuals
such as civil servants
and major company employees.
I know it's cruel, but it's reality.
-Mi-seon!
-Goodness.
What are you doing?
What did you say to Hae-in?
-I didn't say much. I--
-Jeez.
I told you to stop watching dramas!
The money is quite little
unlike the dramas.
Hey, I just want you to break up
before you grow on each other.
And let's be honest. She's not your type.
-Let me go.
-Okay.
What exactly is his type?
Soft and pure ladies.
Not someone with a temper like yours.
Someone who needs protection.
He's always said so
ever since high school.
Is that so, Mr. Baek?
Yes, that used to be my type.
But…
the woman I love right now
is you.
So…
don't bother listening to her.
Let's go.
That was impressive.
I can't believe you did that.
Simply put, I helped them get together.
They seemed to grow closer
after that incident.
Gosh.
What in the world
happened to them?
It's okay. Let me do it.
-Yes, sir.
-Thank you.
No problem.
I wasn't waiting.
Don't think I was waiting for you
just because I stayed up.
I don't think that way. Let's go inside.
It's cold.
I just couldn't sleep.
It wasn't my own bed,
the dogs were all barking,
and I didn't have my sleeping pills.
That's why.
All right.
I don't think you waited either.
You've never waited for me before.
You're right. I'm not the type who'd wait.
Yes, I know that better than anyone else.
Hold the umbrella properly.
Okay, so let's just go inside.
It's pouring. You'll catch a cold.
We can talk at home.
I'm done talking.
Where's your umbrella?
Why are you here?
Let's talk inside.
Come on.
Let me get changed.
Okay.
Do you want some tea?
No, thank you.
I feel like the owner here.
By the way, why are you here?
Right.
Hae-in's mother invited me over.
She must've felt bad
that I had to eat alone at the hotel.
So she offered me the guest house.
Hae-in and I have business to do,
so staying here
will be more convenient for us.
-Are you uncomfortable?
-Would you leave if I said yes?
No.
Then there's no point in answering.
What's this?
When did this happen?
What? Why won't it wash off?
Drink. You'll catch a cold.
Where is he?
Mr. Baek?
He went upstairs.
-I see.
-Wasn't he in the room?
No.
Do you sleep separately?
How's their marriage?
Terrible.
They've been sleeping separately.
But it's strange.
It's obvious that Hyun-woo
is sick and tired of his in-laws.
But he keeps saying the right things.
And you know what?
Chairman Hong
actually listens to what he has to say.
Hae-in and Hyun-woo argue
whenever they're together.
But oddly enough, she listens to him too.
So Hyun-woo is helping them
come to their senses?
Exactly.
He could cause problems in our plan.
It's best
to kick him out of the house
as soon as possible.
Are you guys okay?
What?
This is quite unusual.
The husband would be bothered
if his wife's male friend
moved into their house.
But?
I asked him
if he was uncomfortable
with me staying here,
and he didn't mind.
Why would he move out of the hotel?
What was my mother-in-law thinking?
Hae-in and I
had a good relationship in the past.
They had a good relationship.
He's not someone who should be here.
Jeez. What kind of good relationship?
Would I look pathetic…
if I asked her about it now?
So they're all connected down here.
We've never revealed this to the media.
It may look like
our houses are all separated,
but they're actually
all connected in the basement.
Our grandfather
deliberately designed it this way.
I see.
So you have access
to all houses down here.
Yes, and we also have that room.
You know the movie
with a secret room, Shock Room?
It's Panic Room, you idiot.
-I know.
-Then get it right.
Don't be so harsh on him.
They'll bring our dinners down here,
so let's eat together.
You guys can eat. I'm going to rest.
Why? You ate so well at your in-laws
whom you rarely meet.
You ate everything
and smiled from ear to ear.
You know that video became viral,
don't you?
Our PR Team worked hard today
to deal with that.
Why are you so upset?
Because I visited them?
Because I ate everything
and smiled so much?
Or…
was it the video?
Because the PR Team had to cover for me?
I'm not upset.
Sure.
I'm just fascinated.
With what?
I rarely see you smile like that.
I rarely see you smile at me either.
We don't have much to smile about, do we?
Exactly.
So eat without me.
Have a lovely time.
You must've been surprised.
I'll apologize on her behalf.
That's okay.
It's a regular thing.
Can you see how much I'm struggling here?
Right.
But I understand Hae-in.
I'm sure you already know,
but she has a terrible temper.
I'm sure her insecurities toward me
played a part.
I don't think she feels that way though.
She has no idea
that I'm pacing myself for her.
I didn't know you were pacing yourself.
It's not easy to sit on Queens' throne.
There's a lot to do.
Don't you see what's on my shoulders?
Burdens and responsibilities.
They're the reason
why I'm ten centimeters shorter.
Both my fate and Hae-in
are weighing me down.
Hae-in weighs you down?
She recently punched me in the stomach,
and I couldn't breathe for a good minute.
My mom was so shocked,
and they argued so much.
So my mom visited someone.
Who?
She knew who'd become president
and even predicted COVID-19.
She also warned my grandfather
not to go hunting.
Right, the great shaman.
Yes, her.
She paid her a hefty sum and got this.
A talisman?
This will keep me safe.
The shaman said
this would help me subdue Hae-in
so I can spread my wings and fly.
I see.
Jeez, I don't believe her.
It's all superstition.
But my mom checks if I keep it on me.
I don't think it works though.
Hae-in is still just as strong.
The treatment
that the German laboratory proposed
uses CAR-T cells
to treat immune cells.
It's a type of cancer treatment
where they extract immune cells
from your blood, transform them
into CAR-T cells that have the ability
to remove tumor cells,
and inject them back into your body.
This treatment
has often been proven effective
for those with leukemia,
but not with brain tumors just yet.
But…
they said the success rate was over 50%.
I believe they gave you that figure
after seeing good prognoses
in brain tumor patients
who were given this treatment
in recent years.
But you shouldn't consider that
a full recovery.
I will.
I told you many times.
I will find a way.
Even if I have to search the world,
I'll find a way to live.
So don't tell me…
that it won't work.
Their baby is in an incubator.
I felt bad so…
How's your baby?
Hello, ma'am.
What brings you to the hospital?
Is it still in the incubator?
No, not anymore.
-But our baby is in the ICU.
-What's the baby's name?
We haven't registered the birth.
But Cho-rong is the nickname.
I used to drink
vegetable juice every morning.
But I've been busy lately,
so I've been forgetting.
Sorry?
I want to order juice from you regularly.
Thank you, ma'am.
I'll deliver one to you
starting tomorrow--
It'd look cheap if I had it by myself,
so bring a few more.
Yes, ma'am. How many more do you want?
Well…
If all my employees were to get one,
then about 250.
Sorry?
Thank you, ma'am!
Thank you!
Sir, this is the blueprint
I've been telling you about.
It's the complex resort that will become
the palace of our Queens empire.
It includes two five-star hotels,
duty-free shops, casinos for foreigners,
an arena, a convention center,
a family waterpark--
And how much will it cost?
One trillion…
-And 700 to 900 billion won.
-Do it.
With your money.
Grandfather, I'm not asking
for your money.
We just need to secure a site,
and Eun-sung will invest in us.
Who?
Mr. Yoon Eun-sung.
We've gotten pretty close
since he moved in.
Are you saying he agreed to this?
We're still in the early stages,
but you could say so.
I'm embarrassed to say this,
but he's head over heels for me.
He's not as cold-hearted as I thought.
He's extremely affectionate
once you grow on him.
Is that so?
He must've taken a liking to you.
It's more than that.
He's eager to listen to what I want to do.
Is he?
Father, Mr. Yoon's funds
come from Middle Eastern oil money,
so he's reliable.
Is that so?
-In that case--
-Hold on.
I think we should do
a site validity check first.
We've had many feasibility studies done
on our sites in the past.
However, none of them
were settled due to several risks.
We need government licenses
for duty-free shops and casinos.
As for the licensing…
You know we have our person
in the Ministry of Land.
We can trust him
since he received our scholarships.
But people can change.
It's risky to rely on him and start
a business worth 1.9 trillion won.
That's a fair point, isn't it?
Yes, Father. He knows what's important.
Father?
Review the risks first.
There's nothing wrong
with reviewing, Soo-cheol.
Hyun-woo.
Hello, sir.
You told me to call
if I recalled anything.
A gas deliveryman came by that day.
The dashcam?
Yes, he had one.
I received it.
But its memory size is small,
so footage from that day is gone.
It's okay. I'll try to restore it.
I'll send a deliveryman over
to pick it up.
Thank you.
This is from a dashcam.
The old footage has been deleted.
How long will restoring it take?
Well, I'd say at least three to four days.
But no guarantees.
It's important footage,
so please restore it well.
Okay.
Doctor, our chairman has been interested
in sweet potatoes this past week
since that was
Lessie Brown's favorite food
until her death at 114.
I heard that he was interested in berries
last week because they were
Christina Wahara's favorite food
until her death at 102.
Correct.
But since Brown lived
12 years longer than Wahara--
Then dried sweet potatoes?
He likes sweet food.
No, he has high blood sugar.
You should boil them.
He won't like that.
It can't be helped.
Please serve him chicken breast,
beans, and egg whites for now.
Are you serious?
Egg whites, chicken breast,
and beans? Come on.
He chews ribs whenever he's upset.
He might as well die.
Watch what you say.
What's your department?
-Family medicine, ma'am.
-Mr. Jang.
My father's psychiatrist
should be here too,
so he can take
his mental state into consideration.
Yes, ma'am.
Also…
I can't entrust you
with preparing my father's meals.
I heard you make the condiments yourself.
He only wants the soy sauce that I make.
Exactly. Who knows what you put inside?
I want you to try all his food
in front of me before serving it to him.
Like those court ladies did.
No, you'd be his concubine.
That'll be all for today.
You may go.
What do we do?
What if Beom-ja hits her again?
Should I wait and treat her afterward?
Why are you locking it?
Planning to beg me or something?
What are you doing?
What was that?
Beom-ja.
"Beom-ja"?
You've been cheeky with me
for the past 20 years
and will continue to do so.
But guess what? I no longer find it cute.
Are you crazy?
How dare you talk to me like that?
"Cute"? Do you want more slipped discs?
Wait! That hurts!
I'm counting to three. One, two, three!
Clench your jaw.
-Why?
-Or you'll bite your tongue.
That bitch hit me!
In my stomach! Like this!
Damn it.
I bet you hit her.
No, I didn't!
I hit her.
I hit her out of rage.
-I'm sorry.
-See? You heard her!
Do you think I'd believe her?
Why not?
You may not believe me,
but you believe her.
Believe her!
A regular decaf
with an extra shot. Correct?
-You didn't forget.
-Of course not. You're our savior.
We were nothing but thugs 15 years ago.
But we quickly became
top secret affair professionals,
thanks to you.
You're right.
I saw how your office grew…
MZ DETECTIVE AGENCY
…every time I got a divorce.
We're no longer a simple detective agency.
We're licensed and even pay tax.
I know.
Your sign changed,
so I almost couldn't find you.
So what are you now?
We're a PIA that passed
the state-certified test.
A private investigation office.
Then what should I call you?
Can I keep calling you Mr. Park?
Call me Conan. Conan Park.
Conan, it is.
Do a background check on her.
Which category is it?
The investigation method differs
depending on what you want to look for.
I want to know everything about her.
I had only been hating her
for the past 20 years.
I finally came to my senses
after she hit me.
I need to know
who she is.
Damn it.
YOON EUN-SUNG
Are you ready?
Hercyna's Due Diligence Team
will be here in five.
Yes, my people are already there.
I'm leaving now.
I was waiting for you.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
We're running late.
Sorry, they must be waiting.
You don't look well.
Do you want to rest today?
We can reschedule.
No, there's no need.
Let's go.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Don't mind me.
Thanks.
Your face is still pale.
If you're sick--
I'm not.
But I wish I was, so I can rest.
Hello, everyone. Thank you for coming.
My name is Hong Hae-in.
Has Hae-in been getting
her medical checkups?
It's been a while
since she joined her family
with the checkups.
Maybe she's doing it elsewhere.
Please find out where.
Okay.
I think you should postpone
your trip to Germany.
Why? What for?
Your white blood cell count is too low.
They need to extract
and transform your cells
for the immune cell treatment.
But they can't do that
when your WBC is too low.
That laboratory in Germany
will refuse to do it with this result.
Are you telling me to give up then?
That's not what I mean.
You should wait until your WBC increases--
"Wait"?
I don't have time for that.
Wait, Ms. Hong.
Sir, I'm doing fine.
I barely feel any pain.
I would've found
this damn tumor sooner had I been in pain.
But…
I…
I came by for this cast.
By the way…
Why were you in there?
Do you know Mi-yeong?
Who's that?
My friend.
She also had a brain tumor.
It was about five years ago.
She called her friends over
and cried a river when she found out.
But what about her?
She's fine now.
She's the healthiest one among us.
She goes golfing all the time. She's well.
We have more than enough money.
Incurable illnesses don't exist anymore.
So don't you worry about a thing.
Aunt, I don't worry about getting better.
I'm just worried you'll tell others.
Does no one know?
Not even your husband?
Only he knows.
Really? I see.
Hey, it's fine as long as he knows.
It's nothing serious.
Exactly. It's not serious.
Aunt.
Yes?
I'm going to Germany.
Their lab found a new type
of treatment that can cure me.
That's why I came here today.
Really? Is that true?
So don't tell anyone.
Hey! I won't.
I don't want to cause a scene.
I'll trust you.
Yes, you can.
Aren't you leaving?
I should go now.
Hey.
I'm sure you were shocked.
I know it's nothing serious,
but I bet you were still shocked.
The number you dialed
is currently unavailable.
Suk-hui.
Did Mi-yeong change her number?
-Who?
-Mi-yeong. Jang Mi-yeong.
What? Didn't you hear?
Right. You were in jail.
Why? Did something happen to her?
She died.
She died?
Why?
What do you think? She relapsed.
I heard the surgery went well
and that she was fine.
I heard she golfed all the time,
so why did she die?
How would I know?
I guess it was a tough one to beat.
Why would she die?
Why would she?
Hey, are you crying?
Were you guys that close?
Why would she die?
In 2014, the royal family of Monaco
auctioned off their Napoleon relics
before repairing their palace.
This is the dress sword
Chairman Hong purchased at that auction.
Gosh.
This sword is worth
over three million dollars.
I've seen a similar sword
at a museum in London,
but not in a house.
Napoleon is my favorite figure.
Don't you think
it's a miracle that a country boy
from an island south of France
became an emperor?
I was dirt poor
and always hungry as a teenager.
That's when I came across
Napoleon's biography
and started dreaming.
He also overcame poverty
and achieved his dream.
You can do the same.
Dream big if you want
to become greatly successful.
Let's give him a hand.
I have Jacques-Louis David's portrait
of Napoleon
at my house in New York.
It's a painting of him
in his military uniform in 1813.
If I may, I'd like to gift it to you.
To me?
I feel like you deserve it.
You experienced a miracle
just like he did.
Right, when I first came to Seoul,
I was a shoeshiner
in front of a department store.
But now, I'm the owner
of that department store.
It's a miracle, isn't it?
Of course.
You're suddenly leaving
for Germany by yourself?
Why isn't Hyun-woo coming?
He's busy.
And this is nothing.
Should I come?
I just need my passport. I'll tag along.
-Aunt.
-Yes?
I prefer going alone.
I'll be fine.
Hyun-woo.
Why did Hae-in go to Germany by herself?
Sorry?
Didn't you know she left?
She said only you knew about her illness.
So why didn't you go?
She said only you had to know,
so why did she go alone?
Why did you let her go alone?
Cheers!
I know a great stream in Gapyeong.
The lodging is great,
with water sports activities.
So let's go and have a barbecue.
That sounds nice.
Hold on. Let me invite everyone.
Yes, you should.
-I'll post it on our group chat.
-Okay.
Seok-jun is coming.
Dae-ho is canceling
his golf plans to come.
Is Cheol-seung crazy?
He wants to bring his wife?
What an idiot.
Blocked.
Are you listening?
-Of course.
-Then why aren't you excited?
No, I'm excited. I can't wait.
Barbecue. Oh, yeah.
Water sports. Got it.
This isn't right.
Where's the old Hyun-woo
who used to down three cups of espresso
to stay up all night partying
when his wife went abroad?
I'm here.
No, you're not here.
You're in Germany.
Why are you checking their weather?
Are you worried about your wife?
Of course not.
Did you try so hard to pretend to like her
that you actually fell in love?
No.
I suspected you
ever since the peanut cake incident.
-You're wrong.
-Right?
No, right?
Yes, get a grip.
Don't get too into it.
Okay?
All right! Let's do that again!
Yes, honey.
It's not fun.
This isn't fun at all.
Of course not.
Anyway, he's been a romantic ever since.
That's how our love story began.
Here's my last question.
What is your dream?
I'd have to say
surpassing one trillion won in sales
at my department store.
I'm working on it, and it'll happen soon.
Congratulations in advance.
What's your next dream?
I guess I'll aim
for a higher number in sales.
What about
after you achieve all your goals?
I've never thought that far before.
By then…
I'd like to take a break.
I'd like to travel with my husband.
Our first and last trip was our honeymoon.
I'd like to go
on walks,
drink tea, eat, chat,
and do some catching up again.
That'd be nice.
I wish I could do that…
every day.
Why do they all want me to wait?
Why do they talk as if time is on my side?
I don't have time.
I don't.
"No worries"?
I'm already worried
about walking down these stairs.
Why are there so many of them?
Hong Hae-in!
What was that?
Am I hearing things now?
Didn't I tell you
to wear comfortable shoes?
You really don't listen.
How did you know I was here?
Your phone was off.
They said you left the hospital
after being rejected.
But Secretary Na said
you didn't catch a flight back.
So I thought long and hard.
And this place came to mind.
You enjoyed our honeymoon here.
You liked the name.
I never said that.
I said it was a lie.
"A place of no worries or tears."
They're just lying to lure tourists.
You're the one who lied.
-What did I do?
-Don't you remember?
What did you say to me when you proposed?
You promised not to make me cry.
You told me to trust you.
But guess what?
I cried a lot during our marriage.
I cried while driving,
washing my face,
and at the car wash.
I liked sleeping separately
since I could cry myself to sleep.
Back then,
I just said whatever so I could marry you.
And now, we're married.
So I should be…
by your side
at times like this.
Did I ever tell you not to?
I wanted you
to be by my side.
I didn't want to be alone.
Ever.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Let's go home.
I thought I'd find it here.
A miraculous way to live.
Or a place of no sadness.
But there was none.
All I wanted
was to go home with you.
I heard this is your lifeline.
Why is mine so short?
I'm offended.
Is this
short?
I guess…
it kind of is.
How about this much?
About this much.
QUEEN OF TEARS
I'm truly blessed with a good husband.
-Can I sleep in your room?
-Just sleep wherever you want.
Do as you want. Follow your heart.
Unbelievable.
Why would you
when she's already so strong?
Stop being greedy if you've had it
for that long, you scumbag!
Yongdu-ri has become famous.
A relationship
is bound to crumble with a secret.
-I just saw someone.
-Hae-in!
When you're about to die…
Maybe he came
because it's time.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim