=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 10=
When you raided the enemy camp
and dueled with Fifteen,
you were like an unfeeling spirit.
But now, you whine like a spoiled baby.
Simu.
What did you call me?
Your Grace,
can I call you Simu?
It makes me feel closer to you.
I'm nearly 400 years older than you.
Choose your words carefully.
I like it.
Like what?
Your name.
I'll make a wish now.
Every time we make a deal,
please allow me
to call you Simu.
You could have asked me
for a lot more things.
They'll help you achieve your wishes.
You shouldn't have wasted the chance.
This is my wish.
To get to know you.
To get to know He Simu.
Now, borrow my sense of touch.
You'll feel happy
and I'll feel well.
Do it.
Young general,
don't bother trying to know me.
You just need to stay alive
and make deals with me.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
Skin.
Breath.
Lip.
Pulse.
Heartbeat.
Bite me.
Bite you?
Bite me now.
It hurts.
Simu,
welcome to the Mortal World.
So this is what it feels like to live.
Simu,
have you ever
really lived?
My spirit power.
When you have my senses,
your power is gone?
The sense swap only lasts ten days.
If you dare do anything to me,
you'll be dead in ten days.
Ten days?
Then I'll only live for ten days.
What do you think?
What are you doing?
What feeling is this?
It's itching.
Itching?
I'll tell you a secret.
I'm extremely sensitive.
So, I'm very ticklish.
Every time you leaned
or you touched me,
I struggled to hold back.
I'll make you suffer
just as I did.
You're going to die in ten days.
Then I'll make the days worth.
Wa... Wait. Stop!
Stop that!
It doesn't hurt.
It really doesn't.
It was the same when I touched you.
So this is what the world
has always felt like to you.
Why do you want
to get to know me?
Like why you tried
to get to know me.
You're special.
You make me curious.
You're just a fragile mortal.
Too much curiosity
will get you killed.
I'm not afraid.
How did it
get this messy overnight?
I don't know.
Even the dirt and grass are torn up.
Come on, everybody. Let's clean it up.
- Why?
- Look.
Help me set this upright.
Let's tidy it up.
Come on.
What happened here?
No idea. Let's just clean. Come on.
How did this happen?
Let's move this over there.
What about this?
Oh, I almost forgot.
I have no sense of touch now.
Sweep over there.
General,
is the door bolt broken?
I'll have it repaired.
Clean up the soil
and the grass.
Thank you.
The rooms are cleaned.
What’s going on here?
This is really strange.
You, come over.
Move it over there.
Sorry to have woken you up, General.
No one knows what happened last night.
This morning,
it looks like thieves came.
(Fucui Chamber)
It's a mess everywhere.
A lot of things are damaged.
Looks like they were crushed.
Even groceries in the kitchen
were messed up.
Our chickens and ducks
got completely plucked.
Was anything stolen?
Nothing was stolen.
It's more like rats
than thieves.
But the rats
were pretty savage.
All right.
Oh, General.
Be careful, General.
Two more, come here.
Coming.
Yes.
- All right.
Simu.
Look.
Your Grace, did you stay up all night
experiencing this sense?
I was just looking around casually.
Suddenly, it was morning.
No wonder mortals always say,
"Time slips away so fast."
For mortals like you,
time is really a bit short.
It seems
you had a wonderful night.
Come on.
Wipe it.
I can't control my strength now.
You wipe it yourself.
Not here.
The left cheek.
And your forehead.
I guess you've explored
the entire residence.
Shall I take you to the market?
I can go myself.
You don't need to go.
I don't want to hear more stories
about rampaging rats.
What did you say?
(Ginger honey water,
Perilla tea, River water tea)
Ginger honey water.
Tasty ginger honey water.
Miss, would you like some?
Be careful, it's hot.
Are you all right?
Come take a look.
Big and sweet fruit.
Miss, look at the apples.
These are tangerines. Very sweet.
Miss, they're sweet. Buy some.
Chestnuts.
Miss, two wen each.
- Buy some.
- They're sweet.
Very tasty.
Miss, don't do this.
Unless you're buying.
Hey, Miss. Please don't.
No, Miss.
He'll pay.
I'll have to take them home.
My chestnuts are very sweet.
Would you like some?
Are you all right?
Be careful.
Freshly baked flatbread.
Excuse me. Make way, please.
Watch out.
Flatbread.
Come take a look.
Is this young man drunk?
What... What is wrong with him?
Sorry.
- Take a look.
- Chestnuts.
It's nicely made.
Come try some chestnuts.
You can try on these jewels.
Take a look.
Sorry, sir.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Why are you crying?
With no sense of touch,
you can't feel your own body.
So, your sense of space
gets thrown off.
At this time,
you must learn
to use your sight
to judge the distance
between your body...
And other objects.
Miss, you...
He'll pay.
Sir, these jewels...
They haven't been paid.
You need to pay.
Miss, it's...
It's for squeezing.
Look, you've ruined them.
You just love squeezing, huh?
Foxy,
come and pay.
Fine.
You've squeezed them,
and you'll pay.
Sir, you have to pay for all these.
Miss,
pinwheels for sale.
Here I am!
Look, she squeezed them all.
Sir.
How much?
Ten wen.
Fine.
Hey, gentleman.
You haven't paid me yet.
And me.
Look, it's crushed.
You owe me fifteen wen, too.
And you owe me thirty-five.
She crushed everything.
- Yeah.
- You have to pay for all.
- That's right.
- Yeah.
- I'll pay.
- Exactly.
That's right.
(Is this world)
(really this lovely?)
♪Touched memories linger like shadows♪
♪Scattered reflections
sink into my heart♪
♪If I could softly call you like this♪
♪As gentle as a fleeting embrace♪
♪Even if the day gives way to night♪
♪Grows dim and fades away♪
They say fingers speak the heart.
♪I care for no one but you♪
♪I'll come near and run to you♪
♪To heal the deepest wounds♪
So am I holding your heart?
♪Worth more than any barren land♪
♪I might as well
spend the rest of my life♪
♪Walking with you through eternity♪
(Shuozhou)
Marshal Qin,
we await your presence!
We await your presence, Marshal!
(Qin Huanda, Marshal of Great Liang)
I'm Fang Xianye,
the Censorial Counselor.
Welcome, Marshal.
Counselor,
no need for that.
You've just taken over
the city affairs.
How's it going?
Things are messy and yet to be sorted.
But the citizens
cooperate with the reforms.
So far, so good.
Glad to hear that.
I'm counting on you
to handle this.
Thank you for asking.
Why isn't Duan Xu here?
General Duan is severely injured.
So, he can't come to greet you.
Please forgive him.
What?
He has arranged
a welcome feast for all of you.
Everybody, please come.
(Shuozhou Yamen)
I'm Duan Xu of Tabai.
Greetings, Marshal.
Greetings, Generals.
I'm severely injured,
so I didn't meet you.
Please forgive me.
Marshal Qin had a long trip.
And this is where you settle him?
The battle in Shuozhou has just ended.
The Yamen
is actually the tidiest place.
I believe
Marshal Qin wouldn't mind.
General Duan,
you're truly a young talent.
In Shuozhou, you confronted
200,000 Chong soldiers
for over two months.
Then, you sneaked in
and killed Awo'erqi
to turn the tide.
I've reported
your achievements.
You'll surely be rewarded soon.
Thank you for entrusting me
with that mission.
I didn't fall short.
Now, the Chong court is in chaos.
It's the perfect time
when we can save the people
in the north.
We must press our advantage
and keep going north.
As for the target city...
Generals,
what are your opinions?
Youzhou, to the northeast,
is in a key location.
It's a strategic battleground.
I second that.
If we don't seize Youzhou
while our enemy is in chaos,
we may never get another chance.
Youzhou has offensive
and defensive advantages.
Once we occupy it,
Chong will never retake it.
General Duan,
any objections?
Youzhou is strategically vital.
However chaotic the Chong factions are,
they will unite against us,
regardless of their grudges.
So, in my opinion,
we should target
Yunzhou and Luozhou.
When I just walked in,
I noticed you were
quite interested in my armor.
Even my brother
who is 10 years old
can lift this armor.
But it's unbreakable
and impenetrable.
This armor is light and sturdy.
Very formidable, indeed.
This kind of armor
is forged from Tianluo Ore.
Very rare in our state.
It's abundant in Luozhou,
the city named after it.
Chong captured Luozhou
and ignorantly massacred its people.
Now they know nothing
about how to refine
this kind of ore.
As for Yunzhou,
it can be used for warhorses.
That would narrow the gap
between two armies.
The grasslands of Yunzhou
and ore veins of Luozhou
are indeed vital resources.
But the tides of battle
are ever-changing.
One battle
can bring years of peace.
So they believe
Youzhou is the best choice.
But Marshal...
General Duan,
I've heard
about an extraordinary lady in your army
who can read the stars
to predict the weather.
Youzhou happens to be
a place with changeable weather.
So, would you be willing
to lend this lady to me?
No.
We face a great crisis.
How could you keep her for yourself?
General Duan,
why don't we hear
what she herself
has to say?
What do you think?
Chenying,
go get her here.
But...
It's all right.
Just go.
Xiaoxiao.
General sent me to invite you.
(Clear-sighted and Astute)
Miss He,
this is Marshal Qin.
I heard General Duan's several victories
were attributed
to your marvelous predictions.
Marshal Qin wants to move you
up to our army.
Would you be willing?
No.
- What?
- Please understand.
Most things go against our wishes.
When trapped in Shuozhou,
we needed backup.
But no one ever came.
In this world,
not every desire
can be fulfilled.
Miss He,
are you blaming me
for not sending reinforcements?
I'm merely lamenting.
In such peril,
we were alone and helpless.
Therefore,
for the sake of merit,
I offer you this promotion.
Thank you, Marshal.
But I've divined
that General Duan is my destined one.
The secrets of fate I uncover
can only serve him.
If they serve another,
the consequences will be dire.
Orders are absolute!
Such nonsense won't be tolerated!
If I refuse,
what could you possibly do?
How dare you!
Duan Xu!
Marshal,
since she refuses,
no one can take away
my lady.
Thank you for understanding.
My army will still
be yours to command.
Marshal,
Duan Xu is deceitful and insolent.
And that woman.
They're two of a kind!
His family has connections to His Majesty.
We may not suppress him
as we wish.
In the Shuozhou campaign,
I meant to use him as bait.
Never expected this bait
to destroy the enemy instead.
Put me down.
No.
I won't repeat myself.
Don't struggle.
(Shuozhou Yamen)
We have eyes everywhere
watching us.
Let's play it to the end.
(Liang)
After getting the sense of touch,
you stayed up all night.
But a human needs to sleep.
Why don't you
get some sleep now?
No wonder I feel
my eyes are glazing over.
You're getting awfully bold.
Are you so confident
that I won't punish you
in ten days?
I wouldn't dare.
Like I said,
we should play it to the end.
Back in your room,
I will put you down.
♪Snow on sunny days♪
♪Countless wayfarers roam the world♪
♪Luckily, I share a fate with you♪
♪I hold a lantern to draw the moon♪
♪Light up the night that haunts you♪
♪I have simple wishes, but I fear♪
♪The world can't hold them♪
(Shuozhou Yamen)
♪See the world I've never seen♪
♪However the years may wind♪
♪I wish I could live in your heart♪
Simu,
have a sweet dream.
(Liang)
Greetings, Marshal.
No need for formalities.
Take a seat.
You visit me so late.
Anything urgent?
Shunzhou horse ranch lost its ledger.
A registrar is missing too.
Duke Pei is furious.
Horse administration?
Wouldn't that mean
Duke Pei could be implicated?
I'm afraid
Chancellor Du's faction is behind this.
The court is still unaware of this.
I'm going to Shunzhou soon
to investigate the ledger case.
When you're here, Marshal,
you'll surely suppress
Duan Xu's influence within the military.
Duke Pei had planned
to delay the war by attacking Youzhou.
As it seems now,
horse administration
must be the priority.
During the day, Duan Xu
showed intent to seize
Yunzhou and Luozhou.
I didn't want to support him.
But now,
I have no choice but to let him go.
Yunzhou has vast grasslands,
so it's great for horses.
If we capture Yunzhou,
it will make up the deficit
in the horse administration
and help Duke Pei out.
I will present this to him.
Whether Duan Xu captures the two cities,
the court's attention
will be diverted
until we solve the horse administration.
Duan Xu uses cunning tactics in battle.
But you're the one
to make battlefield decisions.
If he wins,
you'll be rewarded as well.
But if he dies in battle,
he'll be accused of reckless deployment.
The wind is so warm.
Father.
Mother.
Simu.
Come here.
Come over to us.
Mother.
Mother,
what's so great
about this tune?
I can't pick out the melody at all.
Neither can your father.
He just knows how to play it.
Your father plays music for me
because he loves me.
He knows
I can feel his love.
This is why
mortals love music.
Because there is love in it.
Simu,
mortals in this world
are sensitive and fragile,
yet passionate and vibrant.
Your power is overwhelming.
You must learn to understand them
and be gentle with them.
Because one day,
you'll protect this world
by balancing spirits and mortals
just as your father did.
(Mother's hands)
(are very warm.)
(Father's hands)
(are very soft, though.)
What's wrong?
I feel some wind inside my body.
Is there wind in every living person?
This is breath.
Breath?
Right.
The wind inside the body
is breath.
Just now, my parents were here.
Did you have a dream?
Dream?
Something mortals have?
Why are you here?
You're getting bolder.
What a waste to be a mortal!
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪