What are you doing here?
You're not gonna let me in?
I asked what you're here for.
You gonna mess with me again?
I pissed you off, and I brought all
this stuff. What do you call that, Jun?
What's the point of all this? You're nice just to
slap me in the face again? Doesn't help at all, man.
I admit I messed up, okay?
And I already said sorry. But since you're still
mad, I brought you this stuff as an apology.
Well?
Did you mess with my
little bro, you jerk, P'Sorn?
Champ told you?
What did Jun ever do to you? Why'd you mess with
him like that? Didn't you promise me you wouldn't?
Yeah, I get it. I was wrong. I already
apologized, what more do you want?
I just called him. He's
still mad at you, man.
If you want me to baby you like
the rest of them, I can't do that.
If you keep acting like this, I'll tell Dad to
send you to Vietnam so you won't see him again.
If you're gonna mentor him, stick to the line.
Don't mess with him until June has to yell at you.
Fine, fine. I'll make it up to your precious
little brother until he forgives me. Happy now Tai?
Yeah, I'm good now. Just
make sure you do it. That's all.
If this still isn't enough, I
don't know what else to do.
P'Sorn, if you think an apology
will magically fix everything, it won't.
But I'll take your apology. Just...
don't mess with me like that again.
Can we eat now? I'm starving.
I'm getting noodles from
the place at the corner.
So you're leaving me
to eat all this by myself?
Hey!
I'm heading out, Jun.
Um.
Jun.
Why you so pissed?
You're not even gonna talk to me?
I'm talking to you now.
When did I say I wouldn't?
Then give me a kiss.
Nope, Just go.
Leave.
You really not gonna talk to me?
Sorn told me yesterday's
meeting wasn't your fault.
He said he did it on
purpose to mess with you.
Oh… okay.
I'm sorry for scolding you yesterday.
It's totally fine. I get that meetings are important.
And I was kinda at fault too, barging in like that.
So, have you cleared things up with Sorn?
Yeah, all good. He called
me in for a chat yesterday.
Alright, good to hear. Go
ahead and get back to work.
Thank you.
Didn't get scolded—YESS!
Guys! Here—grilled
sticky rice for everyone!
Aww, Jun brought us sticky rice?
If P'Sorn sees, he'll get jealous!
Yeah, he's gonna sulk for sure.
Relax, guys. I had P'Sorn buy it.
Go ahead, eat!
Pick whichever one you want.
This one's gotta be banana. Smells amazing.
I bought it for you, you got the right one.
Then I'll return it, Jun. Not
eating anymore. Get back to work.
P'Put, what would you like?
Hey, can I get an iced
Americano, no sweetener?
And I'll have a latte.
That's one Americano and one latte, right?
Yep.
That'll be... 12,000 baht.
Whoa, kid! Are you this
friendly with everyone or just us?
Friendship?
More like a scammer. You
tryna sell me a house next?
Oops! My bad—120 baht.
120? Hang on—here's 200.
Here's your change.
Wow, that was fast!
You're quick at math. Super fast.
Hey, let me pay for you.
Nah, it's fine. I can buy
coffee for my little bro.
You're the real sugar daddy.
So touched. Just take it, bro.
Come on, no biggie.
Nope. Just take it already.
You dissing me, kid?
It's just one cup. Forget it.
Oh hey, Vee. When did you get
here? How come we didn't see you?
How would Put notice? You
two were too busy chatting.
What did I even do?
We just got carried away.
Oh, this is Jun—our beloved intern.
And this is Vee, my girlfriend.
Nice to meet you, P'Vee.
Wow, who'd think someone like
you could land a girl this pretty?
Yeah, she's pretty. Wait a sec—what
do you mean “someone like me”? Huh?
I mean you look... good! Totally
good-looking... not ugly at all.
Hmph!
Oh, that's P'Yoni.
Vee, chill. There's nothing
going on with her anymore.
Why don't you try dating her again?
Damn, P'Put!
There's nothing between us now! Ask Jun,
he knows everything—he's always with me.
Jun! Jun! Say something,
man! Help me out here!
Nothing's going on, P'Vee. I
always see P'Put working, that's all.
You better be telling the truth,
Put. Jun, I'm counting on you.
You almost got me in serious trouble.
Yeah, but I covered for you, didn't I?
Thanks a ton. Hey kid,
is the coffee ready yet?
It's coffee.
Damn it! What are you doing—you're
not a kid, stop fiddling with that.
I haven't tied this thing in forever.
So... how've you been? Long time no see.
I've been alright.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Really sure?
What?
Let's just go get that coffee already.
Hey there.
Oh hey!
Jun, coffee's all gone!
Didn't help much. I'm still
scared I'll pass out at work.
Forget him—hey beautiful,
could you make me a cup?
Make it yourself.
Sigh... people and their kindness, huh?
Gimme a sip.
Go ahead.
Hot!
Careful, man.
Hey kids.
P'Tai! I Hey.
Want some coffee, P'Tai?
Help yourself.
Yes sir.
Pae, Aey—come help me
set up the meeting room.
Damn, missed my shot again.
Got it!
I'll catch up with you guys.
So I'm not invited, huh?
I'm out.
You're back, Hia?
Yeah.
Hey.
You get any sleep at all?
They're fixing the road near my
dorm. Still came in early though.
What time?
4 a.m.
Four?!
Yeah, it's killing me, Hia.
When will they be done?
No clue. Probably forever.
Huh? Tai, your tie.
Smile and fix that tie, Hia.
I'm leaving it like this.
Why not look for a
dorm closer to the office?
I've been thinking about it, but
rent around here's crazy expensive.
Yeah, makes sense.
What're you guys talking
about? You look so serious.
Jun's dorm area—they're fixing
the road, and it's gonna take forever.
So what now?
Just stay at my place, dude.
It's empty anyway. Office
is only 15 minutes away.
And don't feel bad, you've
crashed there before.
Sounds good to me. At least someone will be looking
after Jun. Je Poey and Ko Nueng won't have to worry.
Yeah, I agree too.
Hey Jun, come check those
documents upstairs with me.
Wait—Jun stayed at P'Sorn's place
before? How come I didn't know?
Yeah, what the hell?
You sneaky little...
Thanks.
Jun.
Oh, I still owe Win a meal. Is he home?
Let's invite him over to Sorn's place.
I'll call him.
Great! Wanna go buy stuff to eat?
It's been ages since we had a party.
Yeah.
You guys go ahead. I'll
stay and help Jun tidy up first.
Shall we go?
Jun.
P'Sorn.
I'm in the middle of sorting stuff.
You can do that later.
But
I want to...
Hold up.
Hurry up, okay? I don't want Hia to see us.
P'Sorn, answer your phone.
No, not now. I'll lose the mood.
What if it's something important?
Yes, Hia?
Champ's out shopping—do you guys
have any sukiyaki sauce at home?
P'Sorn, do you have any sukiyaki sauce?
Nope.
No, we don't, Hia.
What about garlic and fresh
chili? I wanna make seafood dip.
Got garlic and chili?
Nope.
No, Hia.
And a mortar and pestle to grind it?
Hia...
No, man! Just buy
whatever the hell you need!
Then why the hell are you yelling at me?
P'Sorn, Open the door.
P'Sorn!, Open the door!
P'Sorn!!, Open the door!!
P'Sorn!!!, Open the door!!!
Stop—Win's coming!
Hold on, Jun's almost done.
P'Sorn!
P'Sorn, stop!
I'm hot, open the door!
P'Sorn!!!
Didn't you hear? Win's here!
Damn!
Hey P'Sorn
oh hey Hia!
What took you so long?
Where's Jun?
There he is.
Man, I waited forever!
It's freaking hot out.
Yeah, I was in the bathroom.
P'Sorn opened up already. Come on in.
So, how's it feel living at P'Sorn's?
Not bad.
Close the door, will you?
Whoa, look at the size of this shrimp!
Yeah, Hia stocked up. Looks delicious.
Seeing all this reminds me of
the beach trip. I wanna go again.
Win, let's go again next month.
Let's pick a date. I'll invite Pe and Aei too.
Nice. Deal!
Let's make it happen.
You guys only ever
think about going on trips.
Ever think about work?
Sorn.
He's just an intern.
Not a full-time staff like us.
Cut him some slack.
Yeah, alright.
Invite Piang too. The more the merrier.
I don't think Piang's free though.
She's been swamped with work.
You okay?
Ouch.
You alright? That looked bad.
I'm fine. Just a scratch.
You're bleeding though.
Hang on, I'll get you a band-aid.
Hey—wait, I can do it myself.
Be careful.
Thanks.
P'Champ.
Where's my seaweed salad?
Did you forget it?
I bought it—it's somewhere around here.
Where?
If it were a snake, you'd
be dead. Right here.
Ow!
Let me see.
Wait a sec, it hurts.
Your eyeball's not
gonna fall out, calm down.
Sorn, what the hell did you do to him now?
Can't you see your
beloved little bro's hurt?
All you think is I'm
messing with him again.
Come on, I'll rinse your eye.
If you wanna tell Tai I
messed with you, fine.
But the part where we slept
together—keep that between us.
What the hell are you saying?
Huh?
Hi! I'm Candy.
I live next door. I saw you just moved
in, so I brought you some sweets.
Thanks a lot.
Have you been here long?
Just moved in.
Hmm, and the guy who lives here?
Oh, P'Sorn? Let me get him for you.
Here he is—P'Sorn, the owner.
Hello.
He's busy with work.
Then I'll just leave the sweets
here. If you like them, I'll bring more.
Thanks.
Who do you live with?
With my mom.
Oh yeah?
Thanks!
Bye!
Bye-bye!
Oh, P'Penny. Hi there.
Hi sweetie.
Sorn.
Come see me in my office later.
Hey, I bet P'Sorn hasn't
gone to see her lately.
You really think P'Sorn has
something going on with Ms. Penny?
Come on, we both know
he's into older women.
Oops, I meant more mature
women. So little cuties like me lose out.
He's picky. Especially with people at
work—never seen him hook up with anyone here.
Ugh, Praew, don't argue
with me. Just wait and see.
Ahem! Back to work, you two.
Don't spread rumors unless
you're sure. It can ruin reputations.
Yes, P'.
Back to work, missy.
Yeah yeah, I'm on it.
Hey stop.
Kidding, chill. No need to look so serious.
Alright, I'll stop teasing.
Heard you're playing nanny these days?
Kid had to move dorms,
so I let him stay at my place.
You don't like kids. So Jun's an exception?
Why would Jun be?
Normally.
You never let anyone
near your personal space.
What are you trying to say?
Just thinking… maybe
someone's changed their mind.
Jun's like Hia Tai's little brother.
There's no special reason
except he's Tai's brother.
Then let's talk tonight, just us.
Mm-hmm.
Hey.
Where are you?
Why?
I've been waiting for you.
Didn't you say we'd go out for breakfast?
Yeah, wait there—I'll
swing by to pick you up.
Okay.
Jun.
Aren't you coming with?
Maybe next time.
Where are you going?
Hmph. See?
I knew it. Just like I thought.
Think what?
Oh come on, look at the signs!
Hah! Gonna say he's “running
errands”? It's after work. What errands?
Just wait—Khun Penny's
gonna be all smiles tonight.
Do you always have to suspect him?
Not suspecting—my
intuition never fails, okay?
I think he really does
have something to do.
What would you like to order?
I'll have this one, and
that one... that's all.
Please wait a moment for your food.
Oh—hey!
You are...?
I'm Jun. And you are...?
I'm Jom. Are you dining alone today?
Yeah.
Are you working here, P'Jom?
I thought you were some office guy.
This is actually my aunt's restaurant.
Anyway, enjoy your meal once it's ready.
If you need anything, just let me know.
Or you can leave a
comment on this card here.
Sure, will do.
Great.
Hey, P'Jom!
Yeah?
What's this?
That's “Joojai.”
For solo diners, we let “Joojai” sit with
them so they won't feel lonely. Cute, right?
Alright then, I'll leave you to it.
Thanks!
Oh—can I see the menu again?
Here you go.
I think I'll order something to take home.
This one, to go please.
No problem. Give me a moment.
Hey, can I get the bill?
And I've got a coupon.
Sure. Just a sec.
Thanks!
Heading out?
Yeah, P'Jom. The food was
amazing. No complaints at all.
And I even got a discount—bonus!
If you like it, come back again.
I'll give you more discounts.
You're too kind.
If I come again, I'll say I'm your
friend—get the insider treatment.
With pleasure. How are
you getting home today?
I'll probably just grab a bike from
here. My neighborhood's nearby.
Oh right, I've got to deliver food
near there anyway. I'll give you a lift.
Sure, thanks!
Your takeout's ready.
Perfect timing.
Here's your change.
Thanks a lot.
Thank youuuuu.
No problem.
Shall we go?
Yeah.
Here, let me carry that.
Thanks.
Hey! How'd that work talk go?
Pretty good. Smooth overall.
Nice.
Here.
Eat.
You okay?
I think
I don't feel so great.
Hey.
What's wrong? Lemme see!
I'm not feeling well... but I think
you know how to take care of me.
Jun close with the delivery
guy now? Seriously?
But Jun close with everyone anyway.
Yeah, but not with me.
Can you blame them?
Let me chip in for this meal.
You really think I can't cover
something this cheap for you?
Hey! Watch where you're walking!
Mind if Jujai joins us?
Who?
I went on a date with her the other day.