( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
STILL SHINING
MARCH 2021
Hello, sir.
You don't have to bow like that
with our team.
Okay.
Dawn is a good time for programming.
It's quiet.
As for Grandma and Grandpa,
they're so happy I got a job
that they're always picking up tabs
for people in town.
And Hui-seo…
He's even more thrilled.
He's always saying he's happy.
I've never seen someone
who says that out loud.
I thought it was just a word.
It's peculiar.
As for me…
Well…
Does it even matter?
STILL SHINING
The train is now approaching.
SEPTEMBER 2025
In position.
Doors opened. Screen doors opened.
The doors are closing.
The screen doors are closing.
TRAIN OPERATOR 231
YEON TAE-SEO
Hello.
-Tae-seo, over here.
-Hey.
-I'm off.
-Hey, Tae-seo. You're going?
-Last train?
-Yeah.
At least we saw each other. See you later.
-Good luck.
-Bye. Good luck.
-Ma'am, I…
-We ordered for you.
-Do you want a drink?
-I'm on the 6:01 a.m. train tomorrow.
I have to leave right after.
I know we eat fast for work,
but slow down, man.
When did you get here?
I was going to see Mi-ju after doing
errands for Dad, but she's busy.
Geez. I'm hungry.
Let's make some ramyeon.
I forgot to hook up the gas.
You know I don't cook at home.
You've forgotten for three years. Geez.
My goodness.
Sure. It happens.
It's whatever you want, after all.
This is too much.
Sure. I guess it's okay to live like this.
What is this?
It can be a bit loud.
It's too loud to do this at night.
Hey, why do you live like this?
See you later.
Quit looking at me like that.
-Don't point at me. Do this.
-Go.
Why are you telling me
to attend Mr. Mu's sister's wedding?
You should go.
You know I don't have weekends off.
Come on.
You always say you're busy
and never drop by.
Let me know if anything's broken.
I'll come right away to fix it.
Does something have to break
for you to come home?
Don't you feel sorry for me?
Honestly, I don't ever
bother you or anything
while I take care of Grandma and Grandpa.
Why are you always busy
whenever I call you?
Here it goes again.
If you were busy dating,
then it'd be fine.
But you need to see someone
to get married.
Then, I can have nieces and nephews.
That way, I can become an awesome uncle.
How about having three kids?
-I'm hanging up.
-What? Hello--
PLAYLIST
YOUR ACCOUNT IS CURRENTLY STREAMING
ON A DIFFERENT DEVICE
YOUR ACCOUNT IS STREAMING
STOP OTHER DEVICE
AND STREAM ON THIS DEVICE?
CANCEL
The train is now approaching.
It's Eun-a.
DONGJAK STATION
-Ms. Mo Eun-a?
-Yes.
Please come up this way.
Most of our guests are solo travelers.
Many of them are writers
who stay here for long periods.
You need to ask the long-term guests
for housekeeping hours.
And we outsource the cleaning
to another company.
This is our new manager.
-Here's the inventory list.
-Okay.
Make sure to clock out at 4:10 p.m. sharp.
Our boss said you were a veteran
and emphasized that I had to remind you
of when to clock out.
We inform guests on the booking page
that this is an unmanned hotel,
but there are always a few
who complain in reviews.
So please remind them when they check in.
Also,
you need to wear
white tops and black bottoms.
You just need to get the colors right.
Did you bring your clothes?
Yes. What about the manuals?
I put all of them up on the monitor.
-And the break room?
-This way.
This is the break room.
-I'll put this here for now.
-Okay.
I wanted to look around the area.
I heard you ran a guesthouse before.
Where was it?
What happened?
At least you got to run your own business.
-Have you found a place to live?
-I had to leave in a hurry, so…
My place is really nice.
My roommate is great too.
And I'm moving out in two weeks.
It's close by. I highly recommend it.
I'm telling you because you seem nice.
Could I get your number?
It's been a while.
Hey.
Eun-a.
How have you been?
Let's go.
Go.
I'm so happy.
What is it?
My dad's photo.
I came by to pick it up.
You can take these bed sheets.
They're new.
Luxury hotels use them.
You should use them.
You'll need them if you're settling here.
They look expensive.
I shipped these to give them to you.
I couldn't organize my things
since I left in a hurry.
These were all I could grab.
Are you hungry?
Yeah.
I didn't even get to visit Tongyeong.
How can things happen like that?
It's all over with.
I'm actually relieved.
When I closed down the guesthouse,
I was upset, dumbfounded,
and heartbroken for months.
But I'm relieved to let it go.
-Is this your mom's kimchi?
-Yeah.
It's delicious.
Eat up.
You can have all of it.
You can stay here
and take your time in finding a place.
Although it's a bit far,
you can commute from here.
No, I don't need to stay here.
-I can sleep at my workplace.
-Since when?
I'm pretty lucky.
I found a job in Seoul
within a couple hours.
My predecessor
connected me with her old place.
And my acquaintance will suddenly be away
for a week, so she said to stay there.
It's in Seoul.
Everything's been going smoothly
after I decided to come to Seoul.
Still,
if where you're staying isn't good,
you can come back here.
Seung-jun said you could too.
He's drunk again.
I told him to come home early today.
Why do you keep changing the passcode?
Eun-a! You don't have to come out!
Stay there, Eun-a! It's okay!
You're so loud!
-I told you to come home early.
-Eun-a.
Well…
Look how we've all made it!
Middle schoolers from the country
have reunited in Seoul.
This is Suwon.
Have you been well?
As if.
Eun-a, you're the one
I envy the most in the world.
Zip it and go away.
-Do you know why? I'll tell you.
-Hurry.
-Go wash your hands.
-You quit a job.
-You stink.
-Then, you get a new one.
You quit and get a new one.
You go to all the great spots
like Namhae and Tongyeong.
-Not to mention Hawaii, right?
-Go inside!
I want to live freely too now!
Geez, will you zip it?
It's been a while since we've seen her…
This stop is Dongjak.
The doors are on your right.
The doors are closing.
The train for Buramsan is now approaching.
May I have your attention, please?
We will stand momentarily to maintain
proper distance between trains.
SEONG-CHAN
The doors are closing.
Doors closed. Screen doors closed.
Train departing.
I'll be staying in Seoul
for a bit starting today,
just as you stayed
in Yeonwoo for a bit, Dad.
I'll be in Seoul.
Just for a moment too.
-What was our room number?
-It's the room at the end.
It's 13 millimeters.
Thirteen.
Hello?
Sure. Got it. I'll change it.
I forgot.
Okay, bye.
I had forgotten that I shared my account
and the reason for sharing it.
I had forgotten all about it.
-Hello.
-Stay Youngwon?
-Yes.
Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Sure. Have a nice day.
You too.
Thank you for your work, ma'am.
What's with the flowers?
It's to celebrate my first day of work.
Just for the first week.
It's a personal ritual.
This stop is Isu,
Chongshin University Station.
The doors are on your right.
In position.
-The screen doors are opening.
-The doors are opening.
Doors opened. Screen doors opened.
Please watch your step.
Train 4654, please stop
for an additional minute.
This is Train 4654.
Request for stop is loud and clear.
May I have your attention, please?
To maintain proper distance
with the train ahead,
we will be standing
for one minute before departing.
Tae-seo.
Train 4654, you may depart now.
The doors are closing.
Doors closed. Screen doors closed.
Train departing.
Please watch your step.
LAST TRAIN FOR OIDO
LAST TRAIN FOR ANSAN
UNIT 610
I'm on my way. I'm at Isu Station.
Hey, that Seong-chan guy
called me out of the blue.
After I told him
you were coming to my place today,
I realized we'd be in trouble
if he barges in here.
Na-yeong thinks we know each other
through Seong-chan.
I told him you'd call me
when you got to Isu Station
and we'd meet there.
I just rambled on and on.
He won't be waiting
for you there, will he?
I'll call you back.
What are you doing here?
Eun-a.
Let's go to Tongyeong.
No.
I told you I needed a break.
You disappeared after saying you'd go
and close down the guesthouse.
The doors are opening.
You have to know too!
Eun-a!
Eun-a.
Yeon Tae-seo.
SEONG-CHAN
We've been colleagues for ten years.
Why be on a break
when we weren't even a thing?
That way, you couldn't contact me
and deliver the bad news.
We worked as partners,
so we should share the closure.
Yes, we're colleagues. Happy now?
It's their typical move.
If business is good, they kick out
those running it and take over.
We were duped by malicious outsiders.
It wasn't your fault.
When we win the suit--
So what's in it for us?
We can't let them run…
We can't let them do business either.
It'll also be a loss for them
if the suit drags on.
I'll see this through to the end.
I really don't want to know.
I don't want to hear about it.
You've come so far.
Why Seoul?
I'll visit often.
Don't. I hate going back and forth
and matching schedules.
The job here is simple and easy.
It's great for passing the time.
I feel comfortable.
You've been through so much.
Get home safely.
Hello, Mr. Mu.
Hey, why did you send
so much wedding gift money?
It's nothing.
I should've been there.
You didn't have to come. You're busy.
And Hui-seo was very helpful.
He collected all the money at reception
and handed out the meal tickets.
More students came than expected,
so it was hectic.
But Hui-seo took care of everything.
Did my classmates come too?
To call them your classmates would be…
The ones you might actually know…
Eun-a…
You haven't heard from her, have you?
No. No one's heard anything from her.
You're not in touch
with her either, right?
No.
Was it last month?
A petition was filed under Eun-a's name.
I heard a document
was filed very clumsily,
requesting to tear down her house.
As you know,
my wife works at the town office.
Demolishing a vacant house
requires a lot of complicated documents,
but there was only one sheet of paper
with Eun-a's name on it.
It came in the mail.
This document is nonsense.
Demolishing a vacant house
creates truckloads of trash,
so it requires a delivery address.
They wrote down Eun-a's house.
So after demolishing the house,
did they want the trash piled there?
There's no phone number, so I'm at a loss.
Hey, Tae-seo!
What on earth?
That's my brother.
-I see.
-Hey, Tae-seo!
-He's the pride of Yeonwoo.
-Right.
What brings you here?
You should've told me.
He's the one I always talked about.
-My colleagues at the post office.
-Hello.
-This is my mentor.
-Hui-seo's told me a lot about you.
Why are you here?
Three years ago,
you suddenly showed up on a weekday
and dropped a bomb,
saying you quit that big company.
Damn it, I'm still traumatized.
You complain whether I come or not.
How's work?
The post office can't run without me.
Didn't I tell you that already?
Don't you worry about me.
That is true.
You'd been so responsible your whole life.
Why are you acting up now?
You only do whatever you want.
I never imagined
I'd worry about you when I grew up.
Hey. Eat first. Okay?
I couldn't prepare much
since you came without notice.
I'll take care of this since I'm here.
Is there anything else?
No. Just come and eat.
Let's put this here.
Grandpa is taking a while.
He was a hard worker
when he worked on others' farms.
Now that we have our own farm,
he basically lives there.
It's good having our own farm, you know.
We get to live in comfort at this age
thanks to our grandsons.
Goodness. I forgot the kimchi.
I'll go get it.
-I'll go put this in the storage then.
-Okay.
MART
Yes? What is it?
Gosh, look who it is.
How have you been?
Eun-a was here, right?
These vegetable drawings are hers.
She doesn't come here.
Excuse me.
Please give this to her.
010-0922-1109
YEON TAE-SEO
I ran into her by chance in Seoul.
Is Eun-a doing okay in Seoul?
I don't think so.
I only saw her by chance.
You're wrong. She's fine.
Here.
She sends me Christmas cards every year.
They were sent from hotels and hostels.
Those were places she worked.
This one.
It's from last year.
Grandma, how have you been?
I think I'll settle down here.
She's been well.
Stop.
Let's stop…
with the worries and everything else.
No more.
I'm attaching the photo
since it can be disclosed.
It's 5 by 7 inches.
No glass. With at least 10 cm of margin.
You can find Citizens' Cultural Heritage:
Old House online.
I'LL FIND THE MEANING IF THE WORLD WON'T
In order,
they're oak, cherry, walnut, and maple.
See how they would look.
You can either leave margins
or pull the frame in tighter.
This one.
Leaving margins would be nice.
Can we use traditional paper?
Yes, we can.
What's your day job?
I'm a train operator.
I see.
And you're not working today?
I work tomorrow afternoon.
It's a night shift.
A total of five. And your name?
Im A-sol.
Ms. Im A-sol.
The type of wood is oak.
By the third week…
of next month. Is that right?
What's good about being a train operator?
Well…
It's good because I can't bring work home.
That's awesome.
I have a question too.
What made you decide
to commission me for this job?
I've never done this for anyone
other than my colleagues.
It was at a restaurant.
A landscape photo had a frame worthy
of being in an art gallery, so I asked.
And I checked the social media account
written on the back.
Also, can I commission you
for another frame?
This one has no deadline.
It's for an oil painting.
How big is it?
Well, it's about…
About this big?
Or maybe this big?
Please give me five minutes.
Sorry?
What on earth?
-This is it.
-Do you live close by?
-Yes.
-I'll…
This is the first painting I ever bought.
It dropped on the floor
when its string broke,
and the frame was smashed.
I've never worked with a painting before.
It really is huge.
Good. I wanted a completely new frame.
Roughly, how big is it?
I don't have a measuring tape.
No, it's okay.
You can take actual measurements at home
and send them to me.
Okay.
Let me take a photo first.
Is that okay?
The restaurant's owner told me
the frame maker used to be a programmer.
You're him, right?
Which restaurant was it?
The one under the study center.
I see. Hyeong-seok's study center.
Then, I guess that is me.
So that was what you used to do. I see.
Why? Did something happen?
Well, as for me,
stuff happened at home,
and the frame that was fine for ten years
fell on the floor when its string snapped.
Isn't it strange?
I guess such a question
would be bewildering since we just met.
Well, nothing happened.
And I get asked that all the time,
so I don't mind.
I see. You get asked that all the time.
It was…
a strange day for me too.
It was as if moments of the past
were coming together and…
I'm not really good with words.
But there was a day like that.
Are you sure you don't need any help?
I'm sure.
REOPENING AFTER RENOVATION
MAEUM STUDY CAFÉ
Did you see that it's a study café now?
Yes, I did.
It looked very bright
after unblocking all the windows.
Back then, making it dark
made it better to focus.
But now, it's about openness.
They concentrate better
with people going back and forth.
Ma'am, it's me.
-Hey.
-Two spicy stir-fried pork.
It was that one.
You did that one.
So you were the one
who told the owner here about my old job.
What are you talking about
all of a sudden?
Do you want to drink?
This is rare.
You're getting a call.
No.
-It was an unknown number.
-Why did you answer it then?
-Ma'am, a rolled omelet too!
-Okay.
For ten years, I'd forgotten.
They were gone.
But can old worries come back?
If it's ten years ago,
that's after you got into college.
Then, it's likely not about your family.
You don't talk about the stuff
that really worries you.
You were really going through it
before you did your military duty.
It had to be about a girl,
but you just wouldn't talk about it
because you said it would remind you.
You said you'd die
if you spoke about it out loud.
So if you're talking about it,
it's not a problem.
If it's a real problem,
you never mention it.
You're afraid it would worry you.
Right.
Geez. That was it.
I've worked as the study center's
manager for ten years.
I'm at the peak of encouraging
and counseling the kids who don't study.
"You matter. It's up to you in the end."
"That guy lives his life
on his own terms."
"He can't hold his liquor,
but whenever he drinks,
he only thinks about what to do
and his direction in life."
"You should focus on that too."
"And he got into
Hanguk National University."
"He used to sit in Seat One."
I end with promoting the study center.
So, stop bringing back old worries.
Okay?
Did you already forget the kind of future
your mom wished for you?
"Something safe and peaceful."
I'm making that my family motto
when I get married.
Then, memorize it properly.
This sure is peaceful.
"Something safe and peaceful
where he can make a living
without struggle."
JANUARY 2022
Tae-seo.
Yes?
You've been dispatched
to the India branch.
We've worked with their research team,
so there will be familiar faces.
It's a good opportunity.
Yes, sir. I understand.
It's not a big deal.
But Grandpa fell
on his behind while weeding.
The village head said he fainted.
But he's just taking aspirin.
He should… He should go to the hospital.
Make him get a prescription for medicine.
I'll drop by this weekend.
Don't worry.
Just visit during Lunar New Year.
Busy people only come
on Lunar New Year and Chuseok.
Things are running well around here
thanks to me. But it won't last.
Enjoy your freedom.
I saw Auntie Suk-hui today.
Mom used to work with her at the station.
She told me that I resembled Mom
whenever she'd get off work and say,
"I love looking at the ocean."
-It was a strange day.
-I guess I resemble Mom.
In the morning, I received an opportunity.
I heard Hui-seo talk about Mom
when he usually doesn't.
And in the afternoon, I gave up
the opportunity I received in the morning.
You don't want me to look into that room?
Even though it's uphill,
it's a good price.
-Actually, I want you to look into it.
-The next stop is Dongjak.
-Hey, I'll call you back. Bye.
-The door is on…
-The doors are closing.
-Hey, Hyeong-seok.
-Could you look into that room for me?
I just got off the subway.
I couldn't hear a thing before.
Well, something came up in the morning.
Yeah.
Okay, bye.
At that moment,
I had a strong feeling that I knew
what was important to me.
Mom!
Tae-seo!
Compared to how much Mom cared for me…
Wait just a bit.
I didn't even care
a tiny fraction for myself.
"Where?"
In case something happens at home,
a distance that can be traveled in a day.
Later on one day,
I'll be doing what I want to do.
"With who?"
Myself.
The one momentarily free
thanks to Hui-seo.
With myself.
Will it be possible?
CHONGSHIN UNIV (ISU)
March.
Every time around the start
of the school year, I thought of you.
On the day of your parents' memorial,
I thought you'd be sad.
I would think,
"Should I call you?"
And then, April would come.
When summer comes, I can't do it.
When autumn comes, it gets even harder.
In the winter, I completely give up.
I've repeated this for several years.
But I'll stop now.
Because I saw you.
MESSAGE FROM CORNER STORE GRANNY
Tae-seo is worried about you.
010-0922-1109
YEON TAE-SEO
MISSED CALL
CALLS
Hello?
Sorry to call at this hour,
but I had a missed call.
It's me.
Why are you worried about me?
That's what
the corner store granny told me.
Are you outside?
Yeah.
Can I call you back in a little bit?
Okay.
Hey.
Hi.
You're a train operator, right?
The corner store granny told me
you were a train operator in Seoul.
Do you commute to Isu Station?
-I heard it's different for each operator.
-It's Dongjak Station.
I see.
Train Operator Yeon Tae-seo.
It suits you.
I called to tell you
not to worry about me.
My situation wasn't good,
so that might've made you worry.
What kind of situation was it?
He wants to apologize to me.
We had some stuff going on.
It's a long story.
He's your colleague from the hotel, right?
Be clear with him.
That way, he won't show up out of the blue
to apologize.
-If it's nothing to worry about--
-It's not.
Don't worry.
Okay. It's late.
-I'll hang up now.
-Okay.
NO ANSWERING THE PHONE AFTER WORK HOURS
Hello, sir.
You can't stay there.
Please stick to the contract.
It's supposed to be an unmanned hotel.
I'm sorry.
I came in a hurry, so…
I have a place to stay
starting from today.
It seems one of the customers saw you.
They asked me
if it really is an unmanned hotel.
Please follow the rules,
or you'll put me in a tough position.
Eun-a.
-I'm not late, am I?
-Not at all.
I heard you got to Isu Station that day
but had to go back because of work.
It would've been great
if we had dinner together then.
-Ho-sik, Eun-a's here!
-I'm coming.
-Did you bring the camera and batteries?
-Yeah.
-I got everything. We're good.
-Good.
Traveling is our job,
but our dog and plants
made it hard to go on long trips.
We're lucky to just have
the plants looked after.
We can be away for a while
thanks to Eun-a.
That's right.
It's nothing.
I'm the one who's truly grateful.
You saved me.
Come on. Let's go.
She was waiting to see you.
Hurry and get going.
Please enjoy your trip.
What was that?
You sound like a hotel manager.
Take care of our place for us.
-Have a good trip.
-Bye.
Let's go!
Let's go! We're late!
Dongjak Station.
The screen doors are opening.
The doors are closing.
The screen doors are closing.
Please stand back.
It's been a while.
STILL SHINING
You really haven't changed.
It's the same. My feelings are the same.
You're someone I liked ten years ago,
but I still feel the same way.
All the things you see every day in Seoul,
I want to see too.
Stay right by my side.
Granny!
You just take back what's yours
and go back to living your life.
Is he…
weighing on you a lot?
Subtitle translation by: Hye Won Yoon