=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 13=
(Liang)
(Duan Xu ambushed)
(Luozhou)
(the enemy in Luozhou,)
(using the terrain.)
(The elite Chong forces)
(held the Capital and Youzhou)
(and refused to help.)
(Luozhou)
(Luozhou was retaken.)
(Two months later,)
(Yunzhou)
(Yunzhou was also retaken.)
(Luozhou)
(North Chong was still mired
in the succession struggle,)
(unable to act.)
(For nearly half a year, Liang's war)
(Liang)
(shifted from defense to attack)
(and finally paused for a time.)
Meng.
Where is the General?
He said he'd return to Nandu.
So, he won't travel with us.
Meng, let us go now.
The General and Xiaoxiao
will take care of themselves.
The General is going to meet
some friends.
We'll meet again in Nandu.
In that case,
once we reach Nandu,
I'll drink
with some old friends too.
Thanks for the invitation.
I will be there on time.
As for your drinking capacity,
you should sit with Chenying.
- I can't drink.
- Compared with last time,
I can do much better now.
Then I shall look forward to it.
(Liang)
Simu.
Eat it.
Aren't you going to ask what it is?
You wouldn't harm me.
If you meant me harm,
there'd be nothing I could do.
What you swallowed
was the Spirits Lantern in sugar.
The Spirits Lantern?
An artifact of the Spirit World.
With it, one's spirit power
can grow over tenfold.
It represents the Sovereign.
All spirits crave it deeply,
each desperate to claim it first.
And now it's inside you.
Simu,
this is what a spirit is like.
Foxy,
welcome to the world of spirits.
From now on,
you can use Deliverance's power
to awaken the Spirits Lantern.
You feared that after the exchange,
you'd be a mortal
without spirit power,
so you
made me a spirit to protect you.
I suppose so.
Surely,
I won't fail you.
What are you doing?
Jade-like petals wet with dew
release a fragrant bloom.
Before spring, they await their prime.
Their scent leaves the soul spellbound.
A fragrant breeze
enthralls the passerby.
So, the things in my father's book
were all true.
Simu,
welcome back to the human world.
♪Falling down like snow♪
♪Joys and sorrows of the mortal world♪
♪Swept along by the daylight♪
♪The forms and hues of the mortal realm♪
♪Lingering for a fleeting moment♪
♪Was once touched by laughing tears♪
♪If I could live a simple life♪
♪For once♪
♪I'd be a guest in a sweet dream♪
♪Dawn and dusk rise and set♪
♪Longing to meet, yet parted by destiny♪
♪Let me wander through♪
♪Light and dark, without turning back♪
♪Wander to the other shore
with the lantern♪
♪Accompanied by eternity♪
♪As all things turn and flow♪
♪Whether I stay or go, I'm all alone♪
Simu.
♪Falling down like snow♪
What is that scent?
This is
agarwood,
amber,
storax,
mint leaves,
Bletilla,
and benzoin.
My sister loves fragrance.
She uses fragrance
to scent
my everyday robes.
Agarwood,
amber,
storax,
mint leaves, Bletilla,
and benzoin.
♪Light and dark, without turning back♪
It smells wonderful.
♪Wander to the other shore
with the lantern♪
♪Accompanied by eternity♪
♪As all things turn and flow♪
♪Whether I stay or go, I'm all alone♪
The army has returned to rest.
I happen to be free as well.
How about I travel
with you for a while?
Come with me to Youzhou
to meet an old friend.
I happen to know
a gifted fragrance maker
in Youzhou.
Do you want to learn
fragrance-making?
If you do,
start by blending
the scent on me.
Why must it be
the scent on you?
♪A lone lamp shines on the other shore♪
Because you like it.
How long will it take?
Until the day
our time is up.
What if
I fail by then?
I haven't picked the stakes yet.
You can owe me for now.
Don't be so sure you'll win.
Their mutton soup is excellent.
You should have a bowl.
Then I must try some.
(Fujian City, Youzhou)
Yili'er,
there's still no progress
on the royal order.
Are you unwilling
to serve the royals again?
This concerns the war with Great Liang.
The Royal Court needs you
to find a new gold mine
for military pay.
(Yili'er, Youzhou merchant)
In a week,
we'll come again.
I only hope that by then,
you can give us
a clear answer
and ease the Royal Court's burden.
Yes.
I won't fail the Royal Court.
(South Gate)
My kid will love it.
Youzhou has grown
so prosperous.
Tight defenses,
full granaries.
Luckily, we didn't attack Youzhou first.
(Fragrance)
Goodbye.
Thank you.
Miss, have a look around.
We have fresh fragrance balls today.
What a lovely scent.
This is it.
Let's choose this one.
Miss,
are you Liu Ruyu?
Where did this sachet come from?
Its owner said
you'll understand after this letter.
(To Liu Ruyu)
(My friend is interested in fragrance.)
(You're the expert. Please guide her.)
(Duan Shunxi)
Brat!
Stop running if you dare!
Stop!
You...
I just bought
this pellet drum for you.
Do you like it?
I do.
Thank you, Mother.
Good girl.
Mother,
I'm hungry.
All right.
I'll go home and make
some goodies for you.
My power has grown far too much.
I lost control.
Who are you?
Why slay a spirit here?
My apologies.
I didn't mean to.
Forget it.
It was a spirit marked for death.
I'll just report what happened.
Still,
how did you manage
with a spirit body
to wield a mortal spirit sword?
I've long since lost my memory.
When I'm conscious,
I've had this sword on me.
You must've
just become a spirit
from Spirit Aura.
No wonder you know so little.
Young fellow,
were you making an arrest?
That's right.
But don't call me young fellow.
In the Spirit World, rank isn't judged
by appearance.
I'm over 600 years old.
You look
quite young.
You ought to call me sir.
I see.
Please enlighten me, sir.
You were seizing that spirit.
What offense did he commit?
Killing without cause
in the 32 Golden-wall Decrees.
That is a grave offense.
I have hunted him for days by order.
(Li Renyi)
The 32 Golden-wall Decrees?
Please tell me about them.
Otherwise, I may break the law
without knowing it.
Your memory loss is thorough indeed.
Fine then.
You're pitiful.
I'll explain as we walk.
It was hard coming to the mortal world.
I should enjoy myself.
(Fragrance)
I have remained here,
awaiting news from Mr. Duan.
Youzhou is now
under North Chong's rule.
You must be extra cautious.
Please don't take offense.
(Foxy)
(has long placed)
(his own eyes in Youzhou.)
Mr. Duan said in his letter
that you wish to learn
fragrance-making.
But that's no easy craft.
If you can name
the aromatic ingredients
in this floral dew,
then I can teach you.
The ingredients for this floral dew
can all be found on these shelves,
right?
Of course.
Aren't you forbidden from coming here?
Coming here unapproved also breaks
the Golden-wall Decrees.
Miss, look.
Stop.
You can't do that.
If you take things directly,
to mortal eyes,
won't they just float in midair?
Look carefully.
When no one is looking,
wrap the item with spirit power,
make it unseen,
and then pick it up.
Let me take another look.
Alright.
Let's go.
The 32 Golden-wall Decrees
were agreed on
by the former Sovereign and the Lords.
But somehow,
they were never carried out then.
They were shelved.
Once the current Sovereign
took the throne,
she revived the decrees.
Any spirit that defies in secret
or rejects the law is annihilated.
You know nothing of spices,
yet you picked out
the matching ingredients
by scent alone.
You truly are gifted.
I owe it to him for lending me his nose.
What did you say?
Nothing.
So, may we begin learning
fragrance-making now?
You make
the current Sovereign sound impressive.
Of course.
Though these laws are restrictive,
they do have some merit.
Ever since she took charge
and enforced the decrees,
the Moral
and Spirit Worlds knew peace.
The evil spirits caught
by Starhaven Sect
will be sent
to the Spirit World for judgment.
Each does their own job.
It's no surprise.
The Sovereign's mother
was once a Starhaven sorcerer.
Her mother
was a Starhaven sorcerer.
What?
Have you ever seen
the current Sovereign?
I never have, actually.
But I heard
she's wrapped in malice,
with bloodthirsty eyes
and a ghostly face.
Do not laugh.
She's slain
many Lords.
She is even capable of wiping out
all evil spirits.
You came here without permission.
If the Sovereign knows it,
the Lord you serve
will be in trouble.
Perhaps
you will be utterly annihilated.
Today,
our meeting must be fate.
I won't breathe
a word of your secret.
Lend me your spirit sword
for a few days, okay?
This is a spirit sword.
It didn't choose you as its master.
You can't touch it.
Why can you touch it?
You got friendly
with a Spirit Official quite fast.
Spirit Official? A mortal girl.
In broad daylight,
how did she spot us?
How did your lessons go?
Not very well.
It's fine. We still have time.
Master Yili'er.
- Master.
- Master Yili'er.
This is my family heirloom.
Please take a look for me.
Master.
Master Yili'er.
A treasure.
Well, I have something to do.
Bye.
Please have a look.
It's ancestral and very fine.
(Grace Garden)
No entry.
- Master.
- You can't enter.
Everyone, go on back.
Stop pushing.
He can see me.
It looks that way.
Step back. Step back.
Master Yili'er.
Stop pushing.
Master.
Come back another day.
What are you doing?
Getting his attention.
That man
must be the most famous Yili'er
in Youzhou.
Let's go.
So, this is what mortals call
the bustle of mortal life.
It really is a mix of scents.
I can smell everything.
Tell me about that Yili'er.
It's rare for you
to be interested in mortals.
This Yili'er branch
is kin to the North Chong Royal Court,
though the tie is a distant one.
A fringe clan like this
had little wealth to its name.
But after coming to Youzhou,
somehow their luck turned.
They bought a hill
and found a gold mine.
Before long, he amassed
a sizable family fortune.
Even his son
was promoted in the Capital.
I heard Yili'er brought back
quite a few treasures
made for the Royal Court…
Be careful.
To his Treasure Vault
in Youzhou.
You just said
the Treasure Vault?
You want his riches too?
It's hot.
Why?
It has been two months,
and you still ignore me.
Lord of Jiling Temple.
I...
Exactly.
Treasures…
The Treasure Fair
will surely draw you out.
I'll change the question.
Why do you think
he is so lucky?
I heard
some trade for luck, fame, and gain
with spirits.
Is Yili'er also
dealing with spirits?
One day, I must treasure
your clever little skull.
What a unique way to praise someone.
Which one would you like?
You may have a taste.
Where did this copper coin come from?
Dear, come look.
What happened here?
A copper coin just fell
from nowhere.
Where did it come from?
What is going on here?
No idea.
Could that young lady have left it?
Could it be?
He got lucky
because he struck a deal with a spirit.
So, he'd offer a treasure
to that spirit.
Could that bell
be proof of the deal?
When a mortal has a deal with a spirit,
a token may be left
for them to connect.
Do you know who that spirit is?
Our long-missing Lord
of Jiling Temple,
Song Xingyu.
The Spirit Official you met today
is a Jiling,
also called a child spirit.
They've become spirits
for hundreds of years,
but they still look
like youths.
Did that Spirit Official
ask you for anything?
He wanted my Deliverance.
Most Jiling have
little worldly experience,
so they desire
everything in this world.
They want everything
but lose interest once they have it,
forever chasing
their next desire.
So,
they are the easiest to stir up,
never learning, and are used by others.
Is the Lord of Jiling Temple
the same?
He is even worse.
When I put down the chaos,
Song Xingyu fled the Spirit World
with the Glazed Pagoda
and the Lord Token.
Two months ago, when I was attacked,
I saw Song Xingyu's
unique Puppet Technique.
That is why I came here.
To take back the Glazed Pagoda
and the Lord Token?
Your Grace,
do you need shelter from the rain?
I may have no sense of taste now,
but I can smell.
I've long wanted to try
the scent of this brew.
(Wine)
It's raining.
What is that smell?
It's the smell of rain.
Rain carries the scent of the sky
and draws out the earth's scent
and the vitality of all living things.
So, Simu, look.
Even if you can't sense it,
you can still feel the weather.
How wonderful.
To tell scents apart,
there must be enough scent particles.
Moist air
helps your nose
catch scent particles.
When flowers and grain
are brewed into wine,
their aroma gains a charm.
This wine
is called Nü'erhong.
When a daughter is just born,
her family takes glutinous rice
to brew three jars and bury them
beneath the osmanthus tree.
When she marries at 18,
they're considered a gift.
It smells wonderful,
but it tastes rather faint.
This is grape wine.
It's made from grapes and sugar.
On the nose,
it has a fresh grape aroma.
And sweet rice wine.
Its rice aroma is rich and sweet.
Your Grace,
you are a mortal now.
You can't taste it,
but you may still get drunk.
What does that mean?
You shouldn't drink more.
I want to drink.
How dare you stop me?
I would not dare.
Still, this is your first time
drinking in a mortal body.
You shouldn't drink too much.
It's been 400 years.
This is the first time
I've smelled wine.
Yet, you're stopping me.
Foxy,
just let me have a taste.
(Wine)
Promise me.
This will be your last pot.
All right?
You feel no touch.
Isn't a bed wasted on you?
You've got quite the nerve.
Isn't it a shame you're a mortal?
Your brows stretch like hills.
Your waist sways like a willow.
Freshly adorned,
you face the spring wind.
One smile outshines a fortune.
Your Grace,
in your long life,
you must've made many men
fall for you.
♪Spring comes; ice and snow thaw♪
♪All things wake, with the east wind♪
♪In the season at its fullest♪
♪Light the lamps
to pierce the old night♪
♪Borrow mortal warmth to ease the cold♪
♪Warm winds bring fragrant blooms♪
You made the first move.
He Simu,
if I wanted to kiss you now,
would you say yes?
♪With light, carefree words,
still shining bright♪
♪A pot of wine in fleeting dreams♪
Your eyes are beautiful.
You want to keep them?
Eyes are best when they're living.
Is that so?
Then you'd better keep me alive.
♪Let me savor this fleeting joy♪
♪May I roam drunk in dreams
and never forget♪
♪Please ferry me once through this life♪
♪In the netherworld, I see a ray♪
♪To what home shall I return♪
Who hit me?
No one.
Someone did.
Who is there?
Show yourself.
What is that thing?
Thank you, Your Grace, for saving me.
This room is soiled.
I'll get you another room.
Miss,
my master awaits downstairs.
I truly apologize.
My inn failed
to care for you, Miss He.
Sorry to startle you.
Failed to care for me?
From what I can see,
you did quite well.
You sent so many here
to keep me company.
What a surprise.
You're traveling with spirit.
How could they
possibly harm you?
Is that so?
As I see it,
what you mean is this:
If they were to hurt me,
they'd only kill
a commoner at worst.
You'd settle it with ease.
But if they fail to hurt me,
you can sound out my true depth.
I overstepped.
I beg your pardon.
I'm simply very curious
how you made this evil spirit
obey you.
Your spirit won't obey?
I'd like to hear more.
I was discourteous tonight.
Tomorrow,
I'll hold a garden party
in my rear garden.
I hope you'll honor us
with your presence.
I can be your friend.
I do not make friends.
But I can pay
a visit to your garden.
Lord of Jiling Temple,
seeing you once
has not been easy.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪