GOOFY: Yeow-hoo-hooeee!
(CRASHING)
GIRL'S VOICE: Maa-ax!
(GASPS)
Maa-ax!
-(PANTING)
-Maa-ax!
Roxanne?
Mmm-mmm-mmm.
(SIGHS)
-Ahh.
-Oh!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(SIGHS)
(GASPS)
What's wrong?
Argh!
Argh! Ooo-ooo.
Aah! Oh!
-Argh! No!
-Look!
(SCREAMS)
-(COUGHING) Ayuk! O-O-Oh!
-(THUNDERCLAPS)
(SCREAMS, PANTING)
(SIGHS)
(PHONE RINGS)
Uh... Ahh! Hello? Ahem. Hello.
MALE VOICE:
Max, where the heck are you, man?
-P.J.?
-You should've been here an hour ago.
What? What are... Hold on.
Oh, no!
P.J.: Look, maybe we should just
call the whole thing off.
No way, man.
It's now or never. Oooh!
You better get a move on.
I'll meet you at my locker.
Ayuk! Mornin', son!
Dad!
Oops! I forgot.
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
Ayuk! Mornin', son!
Came to see if you had any...
dirty clothes.
Well, there they are. Help yourself.
Max, I thought we talked about this.
Look, I'm sorry, Dad.
I-I'll take care of it later. Ow!
-What's the big rush?
-I'm running late.
I could drive ya on my way to work.
Uh, no. No, thanks.
-I, uh, need the exercise.
-Aw, come on, Max. Huh?
Dad! No, don't do it!
Don't... No!
Oh, Dad, you ruined it.
Sorry 'bout that.
Who was he, anyway?
It's only Powerline, Dad.
The biggest rock star on the planet.
Ooh, not bigger than
Xavier Cugat, the Mambo King.
Everybody mambo!
Boom-boom-boom, boom-boom-boom
Dad, there's no time for this.
What if the neighbors see us?
Boom-boom-boom
Maxie, wait up!
You forgot your lunch.
-Have a good day!
-Duh... Ah!
-(LAUGHING)
-Huh.
(SINGS) They've been laughin'
Since I can remember
But they're not gonna laugh any more
No more "Maxie the Geek"
No more "Goof of the Week"
Like before
No more algebra tests 'til September
No more lookin' at losers like him
-No more havin' to cheat
-No more mystery meat
-No more gym
-Gonna move to the mall
-Gonna live in the pool
-Oh!
-Gonna talk to Roxanne
And not feel like a fool
'Cause after today I'm gonna be cruisin'
After today, she'll be mine
After today, my brains'll be snoozin'
-(LADIES GASP)
-If I don't faint, I'll be fine
I've got 40 more minutes of home economics
-Then down with the textbooks
-And up with the comics
Just think of all
The time I've been losin'
Finding the right thing to say
But things'll be goin' my way after today
She looked right through me
And who could blame her
I need a new me
Plus some positive proof
That I'm not just a goof
And after today, I'm gonna be cruisin'
No more pep rallies to cut
Yuck!
After today, our brains'll be snoozin'
I'm gonna sit on my butt
I've got less than an hour
And when this is ended
-I'll either be famous
-Or you'll be suspended
Just think of all the time
I've been losin'
Waiting until I could say
Gonna be on my own
Kiss the parents goodbye
Gonna party from now 'til the end of July
Things'll be going my way
After today
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
I wish that this was the day...
-After today
-(SONG ENDS)
Whoa! Dah! Argh!
(ALL LAUGHING)
-Are you all right?
-Yeah, yeah. I'm okay.
I just, uh... Dah... (STAMMERS)
-(CONTINUES STAMMERING)
-(GIGGLES)
(CHUCKLES) Ayuk!
Oh.
Argh!
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
I can't believe I did that!
Urgh! She finally says
"Hi" to me, and what do I do?
I... choke! Urgh!
Ayuk!
-Like a big spaz!
-Where have you been, buddy?
Uh. Hi, Peej. Did you get the camera?
Look, Max, if my dad catches me
with this, he'll kill me!
Are you sure we gotta do this?
It's my only chance, Peej.
To Roxanne, I'm... I'm just a nobody.
But after today...
Bobby!
(SLURPS)
Wow, look! All this is for us?
Mmm, slurpage!
Oh, this is gonna be so great, man!
Dude. Need fund-age, bro.
Oh, your fee. Yeah, yeah. Right here.
Ahhh!
Cheddar! Aah-ooh!
Cheddar whizzy!
Mmm. Mmm.
(COUGHS)
Mmm. It's pretty scrumptious.
Ha-ha! Let's do it, ladies!
(CROWD CHEERS)
As student body president,
I just wanna say like "yea"...
-to all of us for a really neat year.
-Yo, Stacey!
Talk to me, talk to me, talk to me, baby!
And also that I hope you can all attend
my totally amazing end-of-school party
next Saturday
to watch the Powerline concert
live on pay-per-view.
(CHEERING)
Thank you, thank you very much.
And now, without further ado,
Principal Mazur.
-(CROWD FALLS SILENT)
-(MICROPHONE FEEDBACK SCREECHES)
Thank you, Stacey.
And good morning, boys and girls.
You know, every year
on the last day of school
I have several youngsters
approach me and say,
"Principal Mazur, what can we do
to not waste our summer vacation?"
-(CROWD GROANS)
-"We don't want to waste our free time…
-(CROWD YAWNS)
-…sleeping or visiting friends. "
-(YAWNING)
-Say, Roxanne, about Stacey's party.
How you, uh...
How you doin' down there, Bobby?
Don't give me that attitude, you guys.
I'm doin' it all for you.
This is nuts.
I don't know why
I let you guys talk me into this.
If my dad finds out, he's gonna nuke
my entire existence... Ah!
...of the element, or...
Heh-heh-heh.
I hope this works.
How about... science slumber parties?
Huh?
(ROCK MUSIC BEGINS PLAYING)
Wha...
Hey!
I'm not gonna just... Aaah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-hah!
(SINGS) Some people setttle
For the typical things
Livin' all their lives
Waitin' in the wings
It ain't a question of "if"
It's just a matter of time
Before I move to the front of the line
Once you're watchin'
Every move that I make
You gotta believe that I got what it takes
-Whaaa!
-(THUD)
-To stand out above the crowd
-(WILD CHEERING)
Even if I've gotta shout out loud
'Til mine is the only face you'll see
Gonna stand out 'til you notice me, yeah
A little smoke-age! (HOWLS)
If I can make you stop
And take a look at me instead of just
(CHORUS) Walkin' by
There's nothin' that I wouldn't do
If it was gettin' you to notice
(CHORUS) I'm alive
All I need is half a chance
A second thought, a second glance
To prove I've got whatever it takes
It's a piece of cake.
To stand out above the crowd
Wow! Who's that guy?
'Til mine is the only face you'll see
Gonna stand out... (RECORD DRAGS)
(SONG STOPS)
BOY: Hey, it's the Goof boy!
We're busted!
Hmph.
Gaga-booja-boo boo-boo-boo.
Ayuk! Come on, smile!
Smiley-wiley!
Blaa-aa-aa. Ayuk!
Oh, come on, Kimmie. Gimme a big...
(GAGGING, GULPS)
-(SQUEAKS)
-Ahh!
Whee!
-(SQUEAKS)
-Ahh! Whee!
-Ahh.
-(SQUEAKS)
-Ahh!
-Stop goofin' around!
We got work to do!
Okay, Kimmie, back to Mommy now.
-Ayuk! Blaa-aa-aa.
-Ahh.
You're such a cute little girlie.
-Mmm.
-Oh, come back and see me.
Oh, you have such a way with children.
"You have such a way with children. "
Pah!
Okay, now. Who's next over here?
Step aside, Goof.
Let a pro show you how it's done.
Okay. Who's next over here? Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ooh, hello, precious...
-Oooh! Oooh!
-(GIRL GIGGLES)
You lucky woman. Heh.
Now, now, you come on here, honey.
-It's picture time. Come on.
-Peekaboo!
-She's so cute.
(GIGGLES)
Gosh, Pete, you sure are good with kids.
-Oh, yeah. Well, they love me.
-Argh!
Ha-ha. Why P.J., he's been beggin' me
to take him on vacation this summer.
Really? Where ya goin'?
Campin'!
Nothing like the great outdoors
to strengthen the bond
between a father and a son.
-Argh!
-Max'd never go for anything like that.
-I don't know, Goof.
-Ooh! Gimme, gimme.
Somethin's wrong when a kid
won't spend time with his parents.
Well, for all you know,
he's runnin' around with some gang,
and stealin' stuff,
and causin' riots and...
Waaa! Gimme!
Oh, Max is a good kid.
He'd never get mixed up
in somethin' like that.
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(SECRETARY HUMS)
-(HUMMING)
-(TYPEWRITER DINGS)
(SIGHS) I'm a failure.
Complete loser.
My one chance to impress Roxanne
and I blew it.
Uh-huh!
Max, look.
It's the Leaning Tower of Cheese-a. Huh.
(DOOR SQUEAKS OPEN)
Oh, man.
My dad is gonna smash me like a bug.
Hey, P.J., detention! (LAUGHS)
PRINCIPAL: Robert Zimuruski.
Okay. I'm comin'.
Max, here.
Guard this with your life, dude.
Hey, Maz-u-ur!
What's up, bro? All right.
Then my parents' air conditioner
went on the fritz.
I figured with all those kids in my house,
the place'd be like a sauna.
So I'm all freaked out,
but then I thought, like, use it.
So my theme's gonna be,
"Powerline Goes Rain Forest."
Too much?
Roxanne, are you listening?
Oh! (CLICKS TONGUE)
-Stacey, no! I don't wanna...
-Talk to him.
Ahem!
A-A-Ahem! Hmm.
Tap him.
(GASPS)
-Gosh, I'm sorry.
-It's okay... really.
Um, I liked your dance.
Yeah. (NERVOUS LAUGHTER)
Yeah?
Yeah, it's from Powerline's new video.
I know. H-He's totally a genius.
Yeah. He's doing a concert
next week in L.A.
Oh, yeah.
Stacey's showing it at her party.
-Yeah!
-Yeah.
Um, uh, Roxanne...
I was, uh, sorta, kinda
thinkin' that maybe I'd, um,
ask you to, uh, go with me,
that is to the... party.
Of course if you don't want to,
I'd completely understand.
Well, I was sorta, kind of
thinkin' that... I'd love to.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-Good.
-Great.
-Terrific.
-Wonderful.
-All right.
-Okay.
C'mon, Roxanne. We don't want
to belabor the moment now, do we?
Well, I'd better be going.
I'll, uh, call you later.
Okay.
Bye. Oh.
(NERVOUS LAUGHTER) Bye.
See, that wasn't so bad.
I told you men are easy to deal with.
Yes! She said yes!
Ya-ha-ha-hoo!
Everybody mambo! Rum-bum-bum-bum-dah
-Oooh!
-Rum-bum-bum-bum-dah
It's not my break yet! Ooh!
-Oooh!
-Rum-bum-bum-bum-dah
Yeah! Dance with her! Groove with her.
Rum-bum-bum-bum-dah
-Miss Maple!
-Yes, sir?
Get that boy's father
on the phone at once!
Right away, sir! Whoo!
Hello.
Ah, yes. Mr. Goof.
This is Principal Mazur.
I'm calling in regard
to your son Maximilian.
Max? Oh, my gosh! Is he hurt?
No, Mr. Goof.
He's in trouble!
Trouble? What kind of trouble?
-Dressed like a gang member...
-Gang member?
your son caused the entire student body
to break into a riotous frenzy!
-Riot? Couldn't be my...
-If I were you, Mr. Goof,
I'd seriously reevaluate the way
you're raising your child
before he ends up in the electric chair!
-(PHONE CLICKS DEAD)
-The electric chair?
Oh!
What am I gonna do?
P.A. SYSTEM:
Blue light special on aisle three.
Lake Destiny.
Okay, kiddo. Now, smile!
Lake Destiny, Idaho!
-Lake who-did-ho?
-You were right, Pete.
Nothin' like the great outdoors
to strengthen the bond
between father and son.
-You said so yourself.
-Well, yeah, but...
I'm goin' fishin'! Ayuk!
I'm goin' fishin' with my boy!
Yeah.
Okay, precious, gimme a big smi...
(GIRL LAUGHS)
Fishing! Fishing! (LAUGHS)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
-(KIDS CHEERING)
-Cool concert, lad.
-What?
-You wailed, bud!
-Hey, Max, wicked dance.
-Thanks.
Forget it, girl. He's Roxanne's.
Way to go, man!
I just heard about you and Roxanne.
Oh, Pete! Ow!
See, see? I told you our plan would work!
-Max! Max! Max!
-Peej, knock it off. Come on. Shh.
-Maximum! Maxi-mu-um!
-Max! Max!
Max! Max! Max! Max! Max!
Max! Max! Max! Yeah!
(SONG BEGINS) All I need is halfa chance
A second thought, a second glance
To prove I've got whatever it takes
It's a piece of cake.
To stand out above the crowd
Even if I gotta shout out loud
'Til mine is the only face you'll see
-Gonna stand out
-Stand out, heh
Stand out
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
'Til mine is the only face you'll see
Gonna stand out
'Til you notice me
Goin' somewhere, Pop?
-Sure are, pal-a-roony.
-Cool. Have a good time, Dad.
If you're gonna be gone
more than a month, drop me a line.
But, Max, this isn't just my vacation.
It's a vacation with me and my best buddy.
-Oh, Donald Duck?
-No, silly. With you!
-(BIRDS TWITTERING)
-Are you okay, Maxie?
Wh-What did you say?
That's right!
A vacation, son!
We'll spend some
real quality time together!
I think I'm gonna be sick.
Hey, got a present for ya!
Dad, stop that! What are you doing?
You look just like I did at your age.
Please don't say that, Dad.
Wait! I saved the best for last. Ayuk!
It's been handed down
from Goof to Goof to Goof.
And now, it's yours, son.
-A stick?
-No, silly.
A fishin' pole!
Fishing? We're going fishing?
Yep. Just like my dad and me did.
Two best buddies fishin' on Lake Destiny.
Away from it all!
I don't wanna be "away" from it all, Dad.
I like "it all"!
Look, Maxie, we're using
the same map me and my dad used.
We'll take the same route,
and make the same stops...
-and see the same sights.
-Ahh!
-But that trip would take weeks, Dad!
-Exactly!
Gettin' there is half the fun.
Put the map away, Dad.
-It's not gonna happen. I'm tellin' ya.
-Careful, son. You'll wrinkle my past.
Ayuk! And our future.
What the map says, Max, we will follow.
That's very mystical and everything, Dad,
but, uh, seriously, there's this party
I have to go to. And there's this girl...
There'll be plenty of time
for parties when you're older.
Why, when I was your age
I'd never even been invited to a party.
-Look at me now!
-Great, Dad.
-Hop in, Maxie.
-No.
All right, then.
Guess I'll just have to go...
all alone.
That's all.
Just sit in the boat all alone...
and talk to myself.
-All alone.
-I guess so.
-Oh, come on! Hop in!
-No, Dad.
-Just hop right in there.
-No.
-Come on, Maxie. Go for it!
-Argh! No.
Let's buckle you up!
And we're ready for takeoff! Ayuk.
Set for adventure, Maxie?
Why are you doing this to me, Dad?
'Cause I don't want ya
to end up in the electric chair.
Electric chair? What are you...
I'm not givin' up on ya, son.
Together, we're gonna work this out.
Work this out? But, Dad!
No buts about it, Maxie boy.
-Your ol' pop knows best.
-But...
(CAR ENGINE REVVING)
Goodbye, house. Goodbye, mailbox.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Goodbye, pile of broken wood.
Goodbye, hopes.
Goodbye, dreams.
Goodbye, Roxanne.
Roxanne!
Dad, I gotta stop somewhere first.
I have to talk to someone.
-Well...
-Turn here!
(CAR SCREECHES)
-D-Dad, watch out! Aaah!
-(YELLING)
Stop here. Here! Pull over!
Now, make it quick, Maxie boy.
We gotta put some road behind us.
You get and cancel your first date
in less than an hour.
-(DOORBELL RINGS)
-Must be some kind of lame-o record.
(DOOR OPENS)
(GROWLS)
Hi. Is Roxanne home?
-M-M-My name's Max.
-(GROWLS)
Does Roxanne live here?
-Does she even live on this block? Ha-ha.
-ROXANNE: Wait!
It's okay, Daddy.
Max is a friend from school.
Oh. (GROWLS)
Go on. Go on. Good Daddy.
-Hey, Max.
-Hi, there.
You wanna... uh, have a seat?
Hey. Uh... oh.
-(GROWLS)
-Daddy!
I promise, he'll be better behaved
when you pick me up for the party.
Yeah, that's, uh, sorta why I came by.
I'm really looking forward to it, Max.
-Yeah. I was too.
-Was?
You see, my dad's
on this stupid father-son kick and...
Don't worry about it, Max.
It's just a dumb party.
No, it's not. Roxanne,
I really wanted to go with you.
-Max, I understand. Really, it's okay.
-But my dad surprised me.
I don't wanna go, but I have no choice.
I'm sure I can find someone else.
Someone else?
-I'll just talk to you later.
-Uh, uh, Roxanne!
Uh, my dad is, uh...
My dad's taking me
to the Powerline concert in L.A.
Your dad's taking you clear across
the country just to see a concert?
Uh, well, you see, uh, my dad...
uh, knew... knows... knows Powerline.
They used to play together, in a band!
-Yeah!
-(CAR HORN TOOTS) Come on, son!
Let's get this show on the road!
Uh... (NERVOUS LAUGHTER) Just a minute!
You... party animal, you.
-You're really serious.
-Absolutely.
So, uh...
you aren't still thinkin'
of goin' with someone else, are you?
-Well, I guess...
-Because I was hopin'...
I could, uh, wave to you onstage
when we join Powerline
for the final number.
This is incredible.
Well, I wouldn't miss
our date for anything
that wasn't incredible, Roxanne.
Mwa.
Have a great time at the concert, Max.
-(MUMBLING)
-I'll see you on TV!
Ah. I'm in deep sludge.
(CAR ENGINE REVVING)
GOOFY: Day one.
Well, here we are,
out on the open road,
retracin' the steps of my boyhood.
And here's Maxie! Ayuk!
Say hi, Max.
-Well, how 'bout a wave?
-Not now, Dad.
Ayuk! What a kidder!
Hmm.
Fun games I used to play with my dad.
Road bingo. Twenty ques...
(GASPS) Hey, Maxie.
Let's play a game.
You think of a name,
and I'll try and guess who it is.
-Uh, man or woman?
-Oh, man.
A man, huh?
Hmm, that's a toughie.
Uh, let's see.
-Walt Disney!
-Right.
I'm good at this.
Now, uh, I'll think of one.
-Hmm.
-(ROCK MUSIC BLARING ON RADIO)
Oh! You wanna sing a song, huh?
Me and my dad used to sing this one
all the time.
-(SONG BEGINS)
-High hopes
GOOFY: (SINGING) He's got high hopes
He's got high apple pie
In the sky hopes
(HARD ROCK PLAYS)
-(ROCK STOPS)
-Oops, there goes another...
(HARD ROCK PLAYS)
-(ROCK STOPS)
-Oops, there goes...
-(HARD ROCK)
-Oops...
(CASSETTE TAPE WHIRS AND SCRATCHES)
Oh, g-great, Dad.
Now we don't have any music!
Oh, Maxie. It's not so bad.
We'll just have to entertain ourselves!
(DEEP SIGH)
(PERSISTENT JINGLING SOUND)
(JINGLING CONTINUES)
(KEYS JINGLING)
(EXHAUST PIPE SPUTTERS, POPS)
Putt-putt-poof!
-Ping-ping-ping.
-Putt-putt-poof!
-Ping-ping-ping. Ping-ping-ping.
-(JOLLY WHISTLING)
-Ping-ping-ping.
-Putt-putt-poof.
(SONG BEGINS)
(SINGS) Do ya need a break
from modern livin'?
Do you long to shed your weary load?
If your nerves are raw
And your brain is fried
Just grab a friend
And take a ride together
-On the open road
-(TIRES SCREECHING)
Come on, Maxie! Ayuk!
All in all, I'd rather have detention
All in all, I'd rather eat a toad
-Yuck!
-(HORNS HONKING)
Old man drives like such a klutz
That I'm about to hurl my guts directly...
Upon the open road
GOOFY: There's nothin' can upset me
'Cause now we're on our way
Our trusty map will guide us
Straight and true
Roxanne, please don't forget me
I will return someday
-(YELLS)
-Though I may be in traction when I do
-Me and Max relaxin' like the old days
-This is worse...
-... Than dragon breath and acne
-In a buddy-buddy kind of way
I'm so mad I think I may explode
-When I see that highway I could cry
-That's funny, so could I
(BOTH SINGING TOGETHER)
Just bein' out on the open road
(PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
Howdy, boys
Is this the way to Nashville?
-(TRUCK HONKS)
-Watch it, Mac!
Or you'll be gettin' towed
I'm in no hurry to arrive
'Cause I'll be turnin' sixty-five
The next time I sees the open road
-Just a week of rest and relaxation
-Yeah!
And the odd romantic episode
Very odd!
And it's Califor-ni-a or bust
Look out, you dirt-bags, eat my dust
From now on, I own the open road
It's me and little Maxie
My pip-squeak pioneer
They're partners forever, westward ho
-Yee-haw!
Could someone call a taxi
And get me outta here?
To Beverly Hills 90210
Oh, every day, another new adventure
Every mile, another new ZIP Code
And the cares we had are gone for good
And I'd go with them if I could
I got no strings on me
I'm feelin' fancy free
How wonderful to be
On the open ro-oad
Ro-oad
(CLANGING SOUND)
(GOOFY SINGING)
You'll all do-do-do-do
-Do-do-do bum-bum-bum
-(TRUCK HORN BLOWS)
GOOFY: Grandpa! Grandpa!
-(HORN BLARES)
-(MAX YELLS)
-(GOOFY HUMS)
-Dad, you're gonna get us killed!
-Why don't you just give me the map?
-Oh, no thanks, son.
Navigating's a big responsibility.
Besides, you wouldn't wanna
spoil the big surprise!
I'm takin' you someplace pretty special.
Gosh! It's even better than I remembered.
No, Mommy! I don't wanna go! (SOBBING)
Yeah, fun. Tell you what...
-I'm just gonna wait here in the car.
-Ayuk!
You party pooper! Come on.
This is gonna be fun!
Oh, howdy there, folks.
Lester's is proud to present
the Possum Posse Jamboree.
Here it is.
(CROWD CHEERS)
Oh, boy! Just in time.
(FIDDLE MUSIC PLAYS)
Howdy, folks.
Who's your favorite possum?
Lester!
(KIDS LAUGH AND CLAP)
Got us a seat right up front.
LESTER: Let me introduce you to the posse.
Here's Beuford, Beulah, and Mordachai.
(ELECTRONIC SCREECHING)
Hey, Lester, ready for yodelin'? Ha-ha-ha.
Sure am, Beuford!
(SINGS) Now gather 'round my possum pals
Join the jamboree
Come hoot and howl
And holler from the heart...
This is pathetic.
-Here in Lester's Possum Park
-LESTER: Join in, folks.
This is yodelin' time!
Yodel-lay-ee, yodel-ee-oo
Yodel-ee-oo, ooo-ooo-ooo
Lester's Possum Park
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Ayuk! Yodel-lay-ee, ooo-ooo-ooo
-LESTER: Don't you wanna be
-ALL: Mm-hmm.
-A-hangin' from a tree?
-ALL: Uh-huh.
We're mighty glad to see ya
And the parking's always free
Here at Lester's Po-Po
Po-Possum Park
Doodle-do, diddle-do
(CROWD LAUGHS)
Hey, that's the ticket!
I'll be right back, my little possum pal.
(SIGHS) My life's a living...
Hello, little buddy!
Who's your favorite possum?
Don't touch me.
Aww. Why such a long face?
You're so sad. (CRIES)
I know! You need a big hug from Lester.
-Don't even think about it! No!
-See?
Now you feel all good inside.
Beat it, doofus!
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
-Oh, no. No, Dad. Not that. Please.
-Here you go, sport.
What say we get our picture taken?
(WAILING)
-You have got to be kidding.
-Oh, all right.
But you're missin' out.
-Urgh. Huh?
-(CROWD LAUGHS)
Hiya, son!
(CROWD HOWLS WITH LAUGHTER)
Hey, everyone! Check out the dork!
Say "sassafras."
Sassy-frass!
-(POSSUM SCREECHES)
-Argh!
-(CROWD LAUGHS)
-Ahh! Get it! Get it!
(BANJO MUSIC STARTS UP)
That's the spirit, Maxie!
Whoa! No!
Dad, stop! Please! No!
Dad, look, this is embarrassing.
No, no, no!
Let go! Dad!
-Ta-da! Ayuk.
-(APPLAUSE)
(CROWD SIGHS)
It's Dork and Dork Junior! Hah-hah-hah!
(CROWD HOWLS WITH LAUGHTER)
(THUNDERCLAPS)
(EXASPERATED GRUNTING)
-Argh!
-Max!
Hey, what the heck you tryin' to do?
-Trying to get away from you!
-Me?
-What'd I do?
-Forget it!
I thought we was having fun.
What's the matter?
Nothin'. Let's just go.
Well, come on!
(JINGLING OF CAR KEYS)
(SLAMS DOOR)
Hey, you dropped your hat.
Ah! This is the stupidest vacation!
You drag me from home,
you jam me in this dumb car,
then drive me a million miles away
to see some stupid rat show!
Call me when the trip's over.
(THUNDERCLAPS)
(CAR ENGINE REVS UP)
(HAMMERING)
Hey, Max.
You wanna get in some fishin' practice?
Just a couple of days
'til we get to Lake Destiny.
Maybe later.
(SPLASH)
(RUMBLING)
(SAWING)
Whoa!
Now that's camping.
Did you say somethin', Max? Ow!
-Pete?
-Goofy?
Oh-ho! What a serendipity doo-dah!
Who'd've thunk it, huh? (LAUGHS)
-Is P.J. here?
-Who? Oh, yeah.
I'm sure he's loafin'
around here somewhere.
-(SONG PLAYING)
-It ain't a question of how
Just a matter of when
You get the message
That I'm trying to sing
I'm under a spell, I'm in over my head
And you know I'm goin'
All of the way to the end
What a goob!
-To stand out above the crowd
-(SONG STOPS)
(CONTINUES SINGING)
Even if you got to shout out loud
No matter what the look is
It's Max, I get...
-Max!
-H-H-Hey!
Whoa! Small wilderness, dude.
-Didn't expect to run into you.
-Apparently not.
You're just jealous, man,
'cause you ain't got the moves!
MAX: Yeah, you can keep the moves.
But I wouldn't mind havin' this RV. Oh!
-You are so lucky, man.
-Me? Oh, come on. You're the star.
-Wh-What do you...
-Going to the Powerline concert.
-Ah! It's unbelievable, man.
-Who told you about that?
Hey, come on. Everybody in town
knows about it, Max.
You are gonna be famous, buddy.
Especially with Roxanne.
There's, uh, only one person
who doesn't know about it yet, Peej.
-Who?
-My dad.
So tell me, Goof.
Is that kid of yours
still givin' you guff?
Oh, I don't know what's wrong.
Just seems like everything I try
only drives Max further away.
Maybe I oughta just back off,
I don't know.
Wrong, Goof. (SIGHS)
Look, if you keep 'em under your thumb,
they'll never end up in the gutter.
Too bad, Pete. Almost.
Almost? Hah!
Watch this.
P.J.!
(P.J. PANTS)
Here, sir. Comin', sir. Yes, sir.
Whoo-hoo! Strike-ola!
Yee-haw! Thank you. Thank you. Yes!
And the crowd goes wild! Ahh-ha-ha-ha!
High five, son!
Psych! Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Say, Goof, why don't
you two stay for dinner?
-Cool!
-Oh, no thanks, Pete.
-Max and I have some fish to catch.
-Dad, we can do that tomorrow.
So, uh, what're we havin'?
-But, Max, I thought...
-Ahem! Under your thumb, Goof.
-Maximilian!
-What?
Get your gear, little man.
We're goin' fishin'!
And I mean now!
(SIGHS)
Dad, I don't even know how to fish.
Oh, now come on. That never stopped me!
Let me show you a little family secret,
handed down through
about 12 or 13 Goof generations.
The perfect cast!
The perfect what?
The perfect cast.
My dad taught it to me
when I was about your age.
Okay now, watch carefully.
You gotta be I-I-loose.
Relaxed, with your feet apart.
And... ten o'clock, two o'clock...
Quarter to three, tour jeté.
Twist, over, pas de deux.
I'm a little teapot and the windup!
Huh?
And let her fly!
The perfect cast.
(THUD)
(RUMBLING FOOTSTEPS)
(DEEP GROWLS)
Huh? (SNIFFS, GROWLS)
And now we reel her in.
Grrr. Ah! Ooh!
Oof! Grrr!
(GROWLS)
-Whoa!
-Grrr!
Quick, get the camera!
(GURGLING)
Must be over three pounds.
I don't wanna miss this!
Look, Max!
A... duh, D-Dad?
It's Bigfoot!
Could you back up a bit, Mr. Foot?
You're out of focus.
(ROARS)
-What's the idea?
-(GROWLING)
-(YELLING)
-(ROARING)
Bigfoot!
Behold the legendary Bigfoot!
Fabled, but seldom... Yeow-hoo-hoo!
-It's locked!
-Quick! The sunroof!
(BIGFOOT SNARLS)
Hurry up!
(SNARLS)
Huh?
MAX: Whoa!
I can't believe it!
Bigfoot!
And I got the only video!
We're gonna be famous!
(HAPPY GROWLS)
Huh? Grrr.
Let's just get outta here.
(KEYS JINGLING)
Ha-ha!
(SNIFFS) Ooh.
(CHUCKLES)
Is he gone yet?
Mm-mm-mm-mm?
-Nnn. Bb-fftt.
-Bb-bbb-bbb.
(SNARLING, GROWLING)
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Nope. He's still here.
(GROWLING)
Gee, Max, was that Bigfoot
or your stomach?
Man, I'm starving.
Ayuk! Alphabet Soup comin' up.
(DOOR SQUEAKS OPEN)
Huh?
-(GROWLS)
-Uh, Dad?
(GROWLING CONTINUES)
Dad!
Stop playing around! He's coming!
-(MUSIC PLAYS THROUGH EARPHONES)
-(BIGFOOT MUTTERS)
You can tell by the way
I use my walk I'm a woman's man
No time to talk
(BIGFOOT CHUCKLES)
I've been kicked around since I was born
But then it's all right, it's okay
Well, it's nice to know
this thing's good for somethin'.
(MUFFLED MUSIC PLAYS IN BACKGROUND)
(PLAYS OVER RADIO) Ah, ah, ah, ah
Stayin' alive, stayin' alive
Ah, ah, ah, ah, stayin' alive...
(LAUGHS)
What's so funny?
"Hi, Dad" Soup.
Huh?
Don't tell me you don't remember
"Hi, Dad" Soup!
Oh, come on. Sure you do.
You used to spell things out
using the letters, like, uh, "Hi, Dad,"
-Or Maxie, or...
-Ambidextrous?
Yeah! That's... Huh?
No! Little words like...
-Hasta la vista?
-Like "Bye-bye. "
-Or "I pledge allegiance"...
-Ayuk-ayuk. Or "I love you. "
Is, uh... is it soup yet?
Oh, oh. I almost forgot.
Whoa! Where'd you learn to do that?
Your granddad taught me that
when we went to Yosemite.
You two did a lot together, huh?
Yep.
-Max, you and I...
-Dad, I'm sorry...
Um, um... how's the soup?
Not bad. Um, not... Ahem.
-What?
-N-nothin'.
(BIGFOOT SNARLS AND GRUNTS)
Well, we might as well get some shuteye.
I don't think
we're goin' anywhere tonight.
Hi, Maxie.
(BIGFOOT GROANS, SUCK THUMB)
(SNORING)
(LOUD SNORING)
(SNORING CONTINUES)
"Dear Roxanne,
I couldn't sleep...
so I thought I'd drop you a line.
Dad and I are having a great time!
We're only days away from L.A.
and I can hardly wait
for the big concert."
(GOOFY YAWNS)
More "Hi, Dad" Soup, please.
(SIGHS)
"Dear Roxanne, sorry I lied,
but I'm not really going
to the Powerline concert.
You may never want to see me again..."
Oh, man.
I'm dead no matter what I do!
(SNORING CONTINUES)
(PENCIL SNAPS)
(GOOFY YAWNS)
How many cups of sugar
does it take to get to the moon?
Ah... three and a half?
(GOOFY SNORES)
(COUNTRY AND WESTERN MUSIC PLAYS)
(BELL RINGS)
-Pickup!
-Hold your horses.
-Short stack?
-Right here.
Here you go, hun. Eggs?
Eggs?
-Eggs!
-Oh, yeah, yeah. Right here. Sorry.
Here you go, cutie.
-Max, I think we need to talk about this.
-Huh?
Seems to me you need to start
taking some responsibility around here.
Excuse me.
Can I have your attention, please?
(GOOFY CLEARS THROAT)
I, Goofy, hereby dub my son Maximilian...
Official Navigator and Head "Which-Wayer"
of this here road trip.
-Isn't that nice?
-Hee-haw!
Seriously?
GOOFY: I'm not even lookin'
at the map any more.
As a matter of fact, you can pick all
the stops from here to Lake Destiny.
I trust you wholeheartedly, son.
To the open road!
To the... open road!
Wha-hoo! Wha-hoo!
(TIRE BURSTS)
-Ooh!
-Ow!
-Ya-hoo!
-Woo-hoo!
-(MAX CHEERS)
-(GOOFY GULPS)
(CROWD CHEERS)
Oh boy!
(BOTH WHISTLE)
-(MAX GRUNTS)
-Whoa!
(CAMERA CLICKS)
(BATS SQUEAKING)
(MAX AND GOOFY SCREAM)
-(CROWD CHEERS)
-Oo-oo-waah!
-Wah-ha-hoo!
-Oof!
(CRASHING)
Gosh!
MAX: Whoa-ho-ho!
-Check out the bed!
-(WATER SLOSHING)
Check out the dresser!
Coral!
Nice lamp.
-Classy choice there, Navigator.
-(POUNDING ON DOOR)
-MALE VOICE: This is the police!
-Huh?
We've got the place surrounded, see?
You Goofs come out with your hands up.
(IMITATING MACHINE GUN FIRE)
(LAUGHS)
You should've seen the look on your face!
(PETE LAUGHS)
-Ayuk! You really had him fooled, Pete!
-Me?
You jumped outta your skin!
-I was just pretendin' for your sake.
-All right, sure!
-GOOFY: Did too!
-MAX: Did not!
Oh, ain't this sweet?
(PETE LAUGHS)
Don't let him fool you
with that buddy-buddy act now.
Under your thumb!
So... since we're all
bein' palsy-walsy here,
-how 'bout lettin' me hook up the RV?
-Well...
Oh, it's just a tiny extension cord.
You'll hardly even notice it.
-Okay.
-Great! P.J.!
(P.J. GRUNTS)
Hey, Goof, why don't you order us a pizza?
This might take a while.
-No, I mean it... Ahh!
-Here you go, kids.
I'm gonna check out the hot tub.
-Okay, sir.
-All right.
I can't believe you, man.
Whatever made you think your dad
would fall for a stupid idea like that?
-It wasn't stupid!
-Come on! It was really stupid.
P.J.: Changing the map?
MAX: I didn't know what I was doin',
all right? I-I was panicked.
(HOT TUB BUBBLING)
Oof-oof-oof.
Oh-oh-ah-ah!
Ah!
Taking a break from
the MTV generation, huh?
Can't say I blame ya.
(SPLASH)
People are always puttin'
too much water in these things.
So, um...
you and your son seem to be, uh,
gettin' along just hunky-dory, huh?
Yeah, it's been great!
You know, it's funny, but none
of your techniques worked for me.
The harder I tried, the worse it got.
-Once I eased up, things just clicked!
-Oh, that's swell.
So, there's no problems then, huh?
Not a one!
That's, uh... (SIGHS)
I just hate to be the bearer
of bad news, but uh...
What is it, Pete?
-Your kid's dupin' ya.
-What do you mean?
Well, I heard the little mutant tellin'
P.J. that he changed the map,
so you're headin' straight to L.A., pal.
-What?
-Oh, you tried, Goof.
He's just a bad kid, that's all.
I don't believe you.
-What?
-I don't believe ya, Pete!
Well, hey, don't take my word for it.
Check your map.
I don't need to check the map.
I trust my son.
You know, maybe Max isn't all the things
that you think a son should be.
But... he loves me.
Hey, my son respects me!
Yeah.
Check the map, Goof!
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
Hi, Dad.
Sorry about the mess. I-I'll clean it up.
(WATER SLOSHES)
-Me think I better go.
-See ya, Peej.
-P.J.: Don't forget... Powerline!
-MAX: Shh!
Well, here you go, Navigator.
Just follow my route on the map, son.
Okay.
Um, huh...
Here comes our junction.
Okay, Max, now this is it. Left or right?
Uh...
Come on, Max!
Uh, left!
(SIGH OF RELIEF)
Uh... how 'bout a song, Dad?
Uh... a game?
A game. Yeah! Yeah, a game. Okay.
Uh... a man or woman?
A man? Man, okay. Uh... Walt Disney!
(CAR SCREECHES TO A HALT)
(GOOFY GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
Dad...
Listen, about my directions...
Will you listen to me?
I gotta tell you somethin', Dad.
Why bother? I'm probably too stupid
to understand anyway.
Right?
Ah, forget it.
H-H-Hey, the car!
-What? Now you want to drive, too?
-No, Dad.
The car! Look!
The car!
(METAL SCREECHING)
What'd you do now, Max?
I didn't do anything, Dad.
I only touched it.
W-W-Whoa!
You locked it!
I locked it? It's your door.
You locked it.
Well, you distracted me.
Whoa!
-You should've put the brake on.
-(METAL SCREECHING)
Why don't you just put it on yourself?
See? You ruin everything.
(CLANKING)
W-well, y-you r-ruined the vacation.
-MAX: I ruined it?
-(CRASHING)
-(CRASHING CONTINUES)
-I never... wanted to go...
on this stupid...
vacation!
Ah! Ah!
-Now look where you've got us, Dad!
-Where I got us?
-You should've let me stay at home.
-Why?
So you'd end up in prison?
Prison? What are you talkin' about?
-Your principal called me.
-It's not what you think.
-You even lied to me!
-(CRASH)
I had to! You were ruining my life.
I was only tryin'
to take my boy fishin', okay?
I'm not your little boy any more, Dad!
I've grown up.
I've got my own life now.
I know that!
I just wanted to be part of it.
You're my son, Max.
No matter how big you get,
you'll always be my son.
(SPLASH)
(SONG BEGINS)
MAX: (SINGS) There are times you drive me
Shall we say, bananas
And your mind is missin'
No offense, a screw
None taken.
Still, whatever mess I land in
Who is always understandin'?
Nobody else but you
Oh, your moodiness is
Now and then bewilderin'
And your values may be, so to speak, askew
-Gesundheit.
-Thanks.
Who deserves a hero's trophy
As we face each catastro-phee?
Nobody else but you
MAX AND GOOFY: (SINGING)
It's just our luck
We're stuck together
Nobody else but you
It's crazy enough to believe
We'll come through
So your jokes are all
Let's face it, prehistoric
And your music sounds
Like monkeys in a zoo
But when life becomes distressin'
Who will I be SOS-in'?
If you're havin' trouble guessing
Here's a clue
Though he seems intoxicated
He's just highly animated
And he's nobody else but
Nobody else but you
We've turned into
A true-blue duo
Hard times, we've had a few
Like we're thrown in the drink
Like we're tossed out of town
But when I start to sink
Hey, I'd rather go down
With nobody else
But Y-O-U
-(KISSES)
-Aw, Dad!
(SONG ENDS)
MAX: Anyway, I figure she's never
gonna want to talk to me again,
much less go out with me.
-What a dumb lie, huh?
-What do you know?
My Maxie... in love.
Gosh, you're really growin' up.
It happened so fast...
I guess I sort of missed it.
Well, I think the only thing
for us to do now
is to get you up onstage
with this Powerline feller.
(MAX CHUCKLES)
Uh, how are we gonna do that?
-Well, you just leave that up to me.
-No, Dad, really,
I-I think we should just,
you know, forget it.
Now how come you always think I'm gonna
lead you into some sort of calamity?
Uh, uh, Dad? Dad?
-What's wrong now?
-Look!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Ayuk! A waterfall.
Waterfall!
(BOTH GASP)
(BOTH YELL)
Dad!
Max!
(GRUNTS, COUGHS)
Grab ahold, Max!
(GRUNTS)
-No!
-(GASPS)
No! Ah! (GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
Whoa!
(GASPS IN FEAR)
(CRIES OUT)
Aaaaaaaaaah!
Dad!
(GRUNTS)
Aaaaaaah!
Ten o'clock, two o'clock,
quarter to three. Tour jeté.
Twist. I'm a little teapot
Let her fly!
(GOOFY SCREAMS)
Huh? (GRUNTS)
Aaah! Aah! Aah!
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
(RELIEVED CHUCKLE)
(RELIEVED SIGH)
The perfect cast.
Boy, this has been one crazy vacation.
And it's not over yet!
-(RIOTOUS CHEERING)
-(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
(THUDS)
-(WHISPERS) Dad.
-(SONG BEGINS)
Oof. We made it!
Come on, Max. Let's get you onstage.
Uh, maybe this isn't such a good idea.
(SINGING) Yeah, yeah
Oh, then again...
Dad? Dad!
POWERLINE: (SINGING) Heyyeah
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(SINGS) I got myself a notion
(CROWD CHEERS)
One I know that you'll understand
We set the world in motion
By reaching out for each other's hand
-Dad?
-Maybe we'll discover
What we should have known all along
-What are you doin' here? Hey!
-Yeah
-One way or another
-Max? Max?
-Together's where we both belong
-(SCREAMS)
If we listen to each other's heart
We'll find we're never too far apart
And maybe love is the reason why
For the first time ever
We're seein' it I-2-I
That Goof kid ain't there.
Don't worry, he'll be there.
-Seein' it I-2-I
-(GRUNTS)
Seein' it I-2-I
Excuse me. Uh...
-I think we're seein' it
-Max?
Yeow-ee! Yeow-ee!
(YOWLS)
Hey, Dad. Dad!
Do the perfect cast!
(CROWD CHEERS)
If you're ever lonely
Stop, you don't have to be
Whoa! Whoaaa!
After all, it's only a beat away
From you to me
-Take a look inside to see
-Yeah
If we listen to each other's heart
Yeah! Max is on the tube!
That's Max. I know him...
And maybe love is the reason why
For the first time ever
We're seein' it I-2-I
-He did it!
-(CHOKES, COUGHS)
Seein' it I-2-I
Seein' it I-2-I, baby
-WOMAN: For the first time
-For the first time
-Seein' it, seein' it, baby
-Yeah!
-Yeah, yeah
-(LAUGHS)
For the first time ever, yeah, yeah, yeah
Come on, baby
-I-2-I
I-2-I
Yeah, I-2-I
(CROWD CHEERS)
(CAR ENGINE SPUTTERS)
(CAR BACKFIRES)
(CLANGS)
You're doin' the right thing, son.
Yeah, I know.
But she'll probably
never talk to me again.
Well, if she doesn't...
maybe she's just not the one for you.
That's what I'm afraid of.
(DEEP SIGH)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(GROWLS)
Ah, hi! Remember me?
-(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
-ROXANNE: Daddy!
Max, I saw you on TV.
You were great!
Yeah? I mean, no, no.
I mean, uh...
Roxanne, I lied to you.
I don't even know Powerline.
What are you talking about?
A billion people saw you dance with him.
Yeah, well...
I never met him before...
the concert, that is.
You mean that story
about Powerline and your dad...
Why would you make up something like that?
I don't know.
I guess I just... wanted you to like me.
I already liked you, Max.
From the very first time
I heard you laugh.
"Ayuk. " (CHUCKLES)
So, you wanna do something tonight?
Definitely! Oh! Oh, no, I can't. I can't.
What?
Well, I'm kinda doin' somethin'
with my dad.
Honest!
-How 'bout tomorrow?
-Deal.
(GIGGLES)
Ayuk! Ha-ha-ha-ha-yuk!
(CHUCKLES)
(CLANKING)
(GOOFY HUMS)
(LOUD EXPLOSION)
-(WHISTLING)
-Yeow-hoo-hoo-hooee!
(LOUD CRASH)
(CHUCKLES)
Roxanne, I'd like you to meet my dad.
Enchanté, mademoiselle.
(ALL LAUGH)
(SONG BEGINS)
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I got myself a notion
And one I know that you'll understand
We'll set the world in motion
By reaching out for each other's hand
Maybe we'll discover
What we should have known all along
Yeah
One way or another
Together's where we both belong
If we listen to each other's heart
We'll find we're never too far apart
And maybe love is the reason why
For the first time ever
We're seein' it I-2-I
If a wall should come between us
Too high to climb
Too hard to break through
I know that love will lead us
And find a way to bring me to you
So don't be in a hurry
Think before you count us out
Oh, you don't have to worry
-I will never let you down
-Nothin's gonna stop us now
If we listen to each other's heart
We'll find we're never too far apart
And maybe love is the reason why
For the first time ever
We're seein' it I-2-I
Yes, we're seein' it I-2-I
Yes, we are
Seein' it I-2-I
I guess we're seein' it I-2-I, yeah
I-2-I
If you're ever lonely, stop
You don't have to be
After all it's only
A beat away from you to me
Take a look inside to see, yeah
If we listen to each other's heart
We'll find we're never too far apart
And maybe love is the reason why
For the first time ever
We're seein' it I-2-I
If we listen to each other's heart
We'll find we're never too far apart
And maybe love is the reason why
For the first time ever
We're seein' it I-2-I
Seein' it I-2-I
Seein' it I-2-I, baby
For the first time
Seein' it, seein' it, baby
Seein' it I-2-I, yeah
For the first time ever, yeah, yeah, yeah
Seein' it, baby, we're seein' it I-2-I
I-2-I, yeah
Come on, baby, I-2-I
I-2-I, I-2-I
Yeah, I-2-I
GOOFY: Yeow-hoo-hoo-hooee!