RTNNJ
GLORY
Are you always so selfish?
We've all been waiting for you.
It's not right for you to study here alone.
Will you come with us?
Well yes. Dong-eun.
You wanted to study architecture.
If you have any questions, contact me.
I am well versed in construction.
It is said "I understand".
That's what I said, crazy bitch.
You said "I'm sorry", dumbass.
Don't correct me, tuko.
Don't rush, don't hurry
Be a dude when you come for me
My heart is burning with love
I want to feel her tonight
Sing me a love song
Until you and I become one
Your feet that were happy to inflict pain
and those who followed them.
Your lips that laughed at other people's suffering
and those who laughed with them.
Those evil eyes
and all eyes
who looked at them with love.
I want to dance with you tonight
Your hand that mocked and broke others
and the hands of helpers.
And your soul
who looked forward to every moment.
That's how far I intend to go, Yeon-jin.
There will be no forgiveness.
And there will be no glory either.
Crazy bastard!
- Let me go.
- You act like a high school girl.
Let me go!
Did you achieve your dreams?
Looks like you have a good job.
Like young and beautiful
you married a desirable guy.
Do you have a happy life?
I'm sure you have. Right, Yeon-jin?
For God's sake!
-Carefully!
- When did you organize it?
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Yeon-jin
What do you want?
You must have read about my marriage.
What the hell do you want?
Stop if you don't want to kill her.
There are a lot of students outside.
Be a better person.
Yeon-jin is still a kid
who has anger issues.
You haven't changed at all.
And neither is your friendship. I envy you.
You have changed.
You were black and white at school,
but now you are colorful.
You think?
I have to go.
I can't wait for the forecast, Yeon-jin.
Can I post on your channel's forum?
I was glad to see you.
By the way, Jae-jun,
you have no idea
which means "colorful".
CEREMONY FOR GRADUATES
Here's the purse.
You didn't come to work
and you don't answer all day.
I'm confused.
I drive my car more than you do.
Why are you even getting paid?
Sorry.
Drunkenness killed me.
Do you need me to do anything else?
Find out what Moon Dong-eun has been up to.
Moon Dong-eun?
Oh, a girl from high school?
The one whose mouth you covered.
How much will you need?
Let me ask you something.
Did you sleep with Dong-eun?
Do you have a child with her?
Are you high?
Are you normal?
You decided to be a jerk?
- Bathing together?
-Not.
He doesn't buy me purses.
At night, the view is wonderful.
Should I move in with you?
What's your name?
Ha-na.
My dear Ha-na,
you're not exactly the brightest, are you?
Ha-na, do I look drugged to you?
You don't even want to tell me your real name,
and you have big dreams.
That makes me sad.
Ha-na.
Is your hair red?
It's red.
Can't you see?
Ha-na.
Do you know which two bastards I hate?
Anna of the Green Gables and Little Red Riding Hood.
Since you are also a redhead,
to make your life lonely and sad
to harden?
Call me if the doctor comes
for consultation because of Mr. Yoon.
I'm sorry, Yeo-jeong. I have a question.
Ask me. He has to go.
I'll take care of everything. Go.
I'm going because I trust you. Call me.
I'll be back.
What are you interested in?
Is Yeo-jeong the principal's son?
Seriously? He's the principal's son?
I thought she was her daughter.
Pink suits him well.
So, it's true.
I found out yesterday.
Jong-heon,
that means he is Yeo-jeong's father
the former principal who passed away, right?
Want to go that far?
Look it up on the internet.
The patient really killed him
who did he save?
Today is the anniversary of his father's death.
That's why he went home early.
Remember the anniversary of your death?
Yeo-jeong's mother is my cousin.
I understand.
What?!
It is bad for doctors to smoke.
The house is full of heart surgeons.
Did you eat before coming?
Will you be able to drink?
Your uncles are already drunk.
- Have you written a message to your father?
- I will now.
Here you go.
It belonged to dad.
It's yours now.
Let's go. Your father is waiting.
JOIN US, FATHER TEACHER
-Spirit from the past.
-She came on purpose.
She knew what she was doing.
Nobody knows what he's up to?
Myeong-o, look into it.
Who will pay me and how much?
I need something first.
God, the color is a little...
Hey, you.
Show me that one.
Yeon-jin, are you okay?
What if on the forum
spread a strange rumor?
What if they throw eggs at you?
Moon Dong-eun is a badass.
Sad smiley face.
Fucking scumbag.
MY crumb
Love! How was lunch?
I'm just about to head home.
I spilled milk on my slippers.
They got wet.
Now I'm barefoot.
Are you barefoot?
That's dangerous!
Did you tell the teacher?
Mr. Yang Wu-gyeong is no longer our class teacher.
What do you mean?
We will get a new classroom.
He will come soon.
Seriously?
They didn't tell me about…
I will come to school tomorrow.
You will be happy. She is your friend.
That? Who is that?
New teacher.
Miss Moon Dong-eun.
What is your teacher's name?
We are glad.
Tell her everything she needs to know about school.
Mr. Director.
Take good care of Miss Moon.
Of course.
I'm Moon Dong-eun.
I will be your new class teacher,
instead of Mr. Yang.
From now on, the following three things will do
to be irrelevant in this classroom.
what do your parents do
how much money they have
and who they know.
Please follow these three rules.
Don't bully others
because you have better clothes,
because you drive in a better car
or live in a better house.
If you bully someone,
I will make your family
to ask for forgiveness:
your mom who bought you clothes,
your dad in whose car you drive
and the grandparents who bought you the house.
Let's have fun together.
Good!
Let's brush our teeth.
Give me the brush.
I wonder how he knows the director.
He introduced her.
Maybe she's his cousin.
Mr. Kang, do you feel like a good person
when you play innocent?
Are you proud?
Sorry.
She probably sleeps with him.
Or once was.
There is no doubt about that.
Ye-sola's classmate.
Is that really you?
She is barefoot because she spilled milk.
Her feet are so tiny and soft.
This is not a coincidence.
Of course not.
Nothing in my journey is by chance.
I walked right into your trap.
Incredibly.
I thought you'd find some asshole,
give birth to a bunch of crappy kids
and lead a crappy life. I am amazed.
How long are you planning this?
I'm disappointed that you don't know.
Yeon-jin, you are my dream.
I told you I'd see you.
I bet you do every day
was fun on that trip.
The road was difficult.
I thought I was going to die.
But now it's a lot of fun.
You should have died then!
For whom?
Even a scumbag like you lives a nice life.
Why should I die?
We met again because I survived.
Today was particularly fun.
Welcome to my hall, Yeon-jin.
Okay, this is understandable.
Since you came here on purpose,
you are capable of coming up with something so fucked up.
Even a poor bastard like you
can be irritating.
Good. Do your best.
Good luck.
HYE-JEONG: REMEMBER GRADE CLASS?
HIS WIFE CALLED ME.
JAE-JUN: YOU MAKE FRIENDS WITH EVERYONE.
HYE-JEONG: HE'S DEAD.
He's dead.
You became a teacher?
Did you go to college?
I am, Mr. Kim.
Thanks to you.
Thank you, Mr. Kim.
I'll take this.
My father has asthma.
It must not be near the lilies.
Let that bouquet be your congratulations.
Congratulations.
You passed for school inspector.
How did you find out about it?
I came as soon as I heard.
I passed the first part of the exam.
The oral part remains.
I'm worried about that.
There's nothing to worry about.
You come from a family of teachers.
When I wanted to print,
you took off your watch...
Shut the fuck up!
Dad?
Damn you!
Rubbish one!
You!
-Dad!
-You!
You think you'll be fine
after you ruin my life?
If I expected this...
- I should have killed you then!
-Dad!
Were you thinking of me?
when you ruined my life?
Dong-eun, you need to calm down too.
Dad, come in the house.
People are watching. Come on!
Gadura is just lying! Don't listen to her!
Dong-eun.
Tell me.
What's going on?
I came to you before the announcement
on the web page of the Office of Education.
Office of Education?
I know very well that you are innocent.
But...
I was also innocent then.
You're all grown up now, Soo-han. I was...
I was only 16 years old.
You did that?
That's what you did to Mr. Kim?
What exactly are you talking about?
About his death
or his punishment?
Dad!
Congratulatory bouquets have already started arriving.
I'm going to be a dad too, dad.
A father can do anything for his child.
What's that about...
What are you talking about?
All I have left is an estimate.
In a little while, I'll be an inspector.
I will do my best to help you.
I may be retired, but...
Soo-hane, open the window.
Not.
Don't be like that.
You know that in our business
rumors spread quickly.
Your reputation becomes rumours,
and rumors about your reputation.
I'm returning your watch.
Good.
Soo-hane, open the window, please.
There is one more thing left...
which you can do.
Remain an exemplary father
who received the Service Award.
Do it for me, please.
Soo-han, please. Window.
Dad!
For what happened to Mr. Kim
he himself is to blame, not me.
If you're looking for another culprit,
then it's you, not me.
Fucking bastard!
It's better that way.
I'm glad you stayed the same.
You know what?
Let's move on to what interests you.
Like a mother.
Your daughter Ye-sol is pure and tender-hearted.
He is a good person.
She will be your punishment.
I will kill you.
Just try Ye-sol to get a hair off your head,
so you will see.
I'm interested.
What will I see?
You've already broken my body and crushed my soul.
What else can you do for me?
Are you going to transfer her to another school?
Don't even think about it.
Will you move me? Don't even think about it.
You will have to suffer from now on.
As am I.
Fuck it!
How much money do I have to give for condolences?
Damn it, his wife is writing to me again.
For a schoolmate 100,000,
500,000 for a friend
a million won for a pet dog,
and 50,000 for the class teacher.
How much will you give me for the wedding?
A hundred.
My God!
Vona.
Fuck it.
Excuse me, would you mind a moment
holding an umbrella?
I picked up the wine from the secretary.
He's in the passenger seat.
It is sent by Mr. Shin from Hanjinmaru.
You drink it.
If it's from Mr. Shin, it's worth a million won.
Please?
I can't, sir.
My hands are full.
I can't take something that expensive.
I wouldn't even know how to drink it, sir.
It's okay.
I speak when something is right.
And I've said it before.
I don't know what the problem is.
Sir?
Then buy a 10,000 won wine
on the way home.
And some cheese.
First drink the 10,000 won wine,
and then this.
That's how you'll learn how to drink it.
See you tomorrow.
You know what I once wanted?
Dad!
Dad's vitamin! Daddy's darling!
I wanted to one day
I forget your name and your face.
If I met you somewhere, I would wonder...
who are you.
I hoped I wouldn't remember you anymore.
If you think about it, it's horrible.
My life revolves around you.
And because of that fact
the world your daughter lives in
it will revolve around me.
I will take responsibility
for her resentment.
That is the price of revenge.
FOR YEON-JIN
What was it? Who did it?
I received a photo,
as well as a photo of Soo-hee.
Thank you, ma'am.
I had to do it.
I was young then.
You were close with So-hee?
Pads, please. The ones with wings.
Just a moment.
These are hydrogen peroxide
and ointment for burns.
4700 won please.
I didn't.
When she was mistreated,
I was
just an observer.
And then I became a victim.
And now...
Now I will be the perpetrator.
it's late
but I will no longer be just an observer.
In other words,
Is this the start of a great battle?
That's right.
I can tell you only one thing.
Win.
For 16-year-old Dong-eun
and for 36-year-old Dong-eun.
I'm rooting for you.
Good.
I…
I'll do my best.
There you are. I was afraid you wouldn't come.
Why wouldn't I?
You met them.
And you didn't tell them that we met.
Why would I tell them?
I invested everything I have in you.
I'm going all the way.
Remember one thing.
You're dead if you get me into some shit.
have you eaten
I'll cut the story short.
Let it last. We'll talk over food.
What do you like?
Sorry!
A bottle of soju, please.
Why don't you eat?
I already ate.
What about what I asked for?
Do you want a drink?
I already drank it.
Information about Sarah's drug
and about the guy Hye-jeong is obsessed with.
And the hairs I gave you?
They match.
Seriously? Jae-jun has a child?
- Where is he?
- I will play that card.
Take this.
Morgue? What's there?
- Is this a better card?
- Yes, if you want money.
You will see for yourself who is there.
I will make money from this.
Isn't it?
D-3. It's here.
YOON SO-HEE
ARRIVED 15. 12. 2004.
So,
Yoon So-hee lies here
more than a decade?
That's right.
The bill is over 100 million won.
The police concluded that she had killed herself.
Parents did not believe.
They don't contact us.
We can't remove the body
without the consent of the family.
May I…
May I see her? That is, a corpse?
I don't think I should…
- You are not a family member?
- I didn't.
We are friends. We know each other from high school.
You must be accompanied by a family member.
It's a problem for us too.
Try to convince someone from the family.
It's fine if they don't want to claim the body.
You want to know what I want?
Do I want Myeong-o's wings
cause a hurricane?
Myeong-o has no wings, Yeon-jin.
He doesn't deserve to have something so beautiful.
Myeong-o is my SD card.
I'll put it in the camera
and record whatever I want.
That will be worth a lot of money.
Dong-eun, you've become an interesting curmudgeon.
ROOM 701
PATIENT: YOON JEONG-HWAN
Where is 701's Yoon Jeong-hwan?
Didn't you hear? He went into shock this morning.
are you ok
Isn't she hot?
I'm fine.
Ye-sol, did anyone bully you at school?
- Did anyone hit you?
- What is it, mom?
If your teacher does something to punish you,
that's not right.
Has anyone put it on you?
something hot on the body?
Why would anyone do that?
That's mean.
They should be scolded.
I will play Among Us with my friends.
Ye-sol!
He always comes on Fridays.
Three out of five photos I take
they are sharpened.
GO CLUB PAGODA
I learned it very quickly, Yeon-jin.
I had a clear purpose.
You win if you win houses
that your opponent built.
It's beautiful.
You were gone for a long time.
Yes, I had to work.
What do you do?
I fooled the naive and made them cry.
Are you making good money?
And not really.
I'm a good person.
Where did you learn to play?
In the park.
Your answers are unexpected.
For 20,000 per lot?
Last move.
There is no going back.
Will you pay in cash?
What?
It was fun.
Let's play for 50,000.
Another party?
Yeon-jin,
you want me to tell you the real reason
why do I love him?
That would be gambling.
Is it?
When you play go,
in silence you show what you long for.
You quarrel and you are misled.
The opponent and you expose each other.
Maybe your opponent doesn't fight back.
In that case…
it's just a game of goa.
I want that. Gamble.
Subtitle translation: Davor Fröbe