(Lee Jae In, Kim Woo Seok, Choi Ye Bin)
(Cha Woo Min, An Ji Ho, Jung So Ri)
(Night Has Come)
(All people, organizations, locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Cha Yu Jun is a Doctor.)
What's this?
- I'm a Citizen. What about you? - I'm...
(You can select 1 participant and use your Heal Skill.)
(The selected participant will be protected from Mafia's attack.)
Oh, no.
(Will you use it on Cha Yu Jun? Yes)
(Heal Skill used on Cha Yu Jun.)
Ji Soo.
(The selected participant will be protected from Mafia's attack.)
(You can revive someone who was voted for and executed.)
No.
(Will you use it on Park Ji Soo? Yes)
(48 hours have not yet passed since you last used Heal.)
(Adhere to the cooling time.)
What's this?
Ji Soo.
I don't want to die.
You won't die.
I'll never let you die.
We should go home.
Don't you want to go home?
I do.
It's me.
I'm Mafia.
It's not you.
It's really not you.
Don't.
It's not him. Don't do it.
(Heal Skill used on Kim Jun Hee.)
Hey.
Take it back. Say you're not Mafia.
Did you find the photo album?
It's not on the first floor.
No.
I swear it was here.
It must be somewhere. Let's keep looking.
Cha Yu Jun...
- has died. - Yu Jun?
- Cha Yu Jun was... - Why?
the Doctor.
All participants,
identify the Mafia and begin to vote.
He didn't break any rules.
So why did he...
Did he fall?
He didn't fall.
Someone killed him.
There are lots of signs of a struggle,
and there are wounds on his head.
Someone attacked him.
I bet it was the Mafia.
I don't know.
Even if it was, this is wrong.
How could they kill during the day?
What will you do now?
Find out who did it.
Why do you think Yu Jun was here?
Yoon Seo.
The Mafia has gone insane.
They're killing during the day now?
Even if Yu Jun was the Doctor,
this is too much.
Let's just catch the darn Mafia.
Who on earth is it? Darn it.
- Hey, guys. - What?
- Come over here. - What the heck for?
What's this?
What is it?
(Jun Hee is Mafia. Da Bum is Mafia. From Police)
Jun Hee...
and you are Mafia?
No. I'm really not Mafia.
Guys, I'm not Mafia. I'm a Citizen.
Who wrote this and why? It's really not me.
Police used their Skill twice.
I think two people makes sense.
But earlier it said Jun Hee was a Citizen.
I'm not Mafia either.
Don't lie.
I bet the Police wrote this because the last one was a lie.
Yes. The real Police would name the Mafia.
Why would they name a Citizen?
No.
This could be fake.
It's weird how it appeared right after Yu Jun died.
The person who killed him...
could've written this to frame them as Mafia.
You guys. Why did you get here so late?
Didn't you write this?
If so, Yoon Seo wouldn't have said what she just did.
What the heck is this anyway?
(Jun Hee is a Citizen. From Police)
Police.
Quit this crap and show yourself.
Show your phones. Let's see your Skills.
There's no need to do that.
The person who killed Yu Jun.
I think I know who it is.
You said you'd tell us who did it.
Why did you bring us here?
In the warehouse...
I found a footprint.
And this was next to it.
I think it's from the shoe of Yu Jun's killer.
This is the same one.
It stood out because I found it weird there was a blank.
I think this explains it.
This is an accessory lots of basketball shoes have.
Basketball shoes?
Why? What?
Is this yours?
Why would you say that, you witch?
Show us your shoes so we can check.
I don't use that, okay?
Let's see and find out.
Screw it. Take a look then.
It's not his.
I told you so.
What?
It's really not me. Why the heck do you suspect me?
If you're innocent, show us, then.
- Yes, let's see. - No. It's not me.
Screw you guys. It's not me.
Will you stop it?
Darn you.
Who bit you?
It really was you.
Why did you do it?
It wasn't me. I didn't kill him.
We found the weapons you used. Don't try to lie.
Darn it.
Shall I tell the truth?
Ko Kyung Jun killed him. It wasn't me!
What are you saying, psycho?
The shoe and brick says it's you!
How do you know that?
We never mentioned a brick. How did you know about it?
What?
Jin Ha was with someone else in the warehouse.
We found another identical footprint but without the heel pad.
It was you, wasn't it?
Ko Kyung Jun.
Guys. It really wasn't me.
He killed Yu Jun.
He killed Seung Bin too.
You have the effing ax too.
You lunatic. Darn you.
- Screw you. - Hey!
- Darn you. - Stop it!
- Will you stop! - Get your hands off me!
You killed him, you dirtbag.
Let go. I said let go of me.
Kyung Jun!
Will you all get off me?
You lunatic!
Hey.
Let go. Stay away from me.
You scumbag!
Jun Hee!
Come at me! I'll take you on!
Get off me! Come and get me, you!
Darn you!
I'm cool.
Hey.
What's that?
What a mess.
Did you write it with this?
And you still say he's not Mafia?
When he wrote the sign?
What's this? Did you name them as Mafia?
No. I didn't write that sign.
Hey. Guys, wait.
Wait. Don't do anything.
I don't know what's going on!
- Honestly. - We have the answer.
Vote already.
Hey, Jun Hee. It wasn't me.
You're class president!
I don't know what's happening.
Hey, wait. Please, Jung Won. Don't.
What a joke.
I'm innocent.
He's a hundred percent Mafia! Let's vote and be done with it!
Will you stop it?
You killed Yu Jun too.
We'll vote at 11pm.
You two should wait in a room.
Don't leave the room.
This is an effing prison cell.
What?
- Hand over the keys. - Why?
What if you get out?
How are we to know you won't kill again?
We'll all use the cafeteria now. Hand over the keys.
They're gone. I lost them.
Don't lie. Hand them over already.
I don't have them, okay?
Then give me your phone. I'll keep that as collateral.
You can't go anywhere without your phone.
You murdered someone.
It's the least you can do to make us trust you.
What the heck, Da Bum?
You'll get it back at voting time.
Guys.
I really am not Mafia.
I didn't kill Seung Bin.
Don't vote for me, okay?
I really am not Mafia.
I'm a Citizen.
I must live if you're to live.
This is the men's room.
I know that.
- What? - Where do you think...
is the safest place here?
What do you mean?
Speak up.
Where is it?
I don't know.
What a moron.
It's the cafeteria.
- The cafeteria? - Yes.
No ax can get through the shutters.
So what?
What do you mean "so what?"
Kyung Jun's keys. Let's take them from him.
We'll let you in.
Join us.
- Did it hurt? - I'm fine.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
Thanks.
If you're done, let's go.
They'll suspect us of being late again.
Okay.
Yes. Let's go.
Let's go.
(Povidone)
(From Police)
(Kim Jun Hee is Mafia. Jin Da Bum is Mafia. From Police)
Now we really have to vote.
What do you want to do?
Anyway,
Kyung Jun seems to be a Citizen.
But we don't know about Jin Ha yet.
Then...
it's right to save Kyung Jun.
But Kyung Jun is weird too.
Why did he kill the Doctor if he were a Citizen?
Right.
He had an axe too.
Are you stupid?
He had the key. Why would he break the door?
Do you have a hole in your head?
He must've broken it not to be suspected.
You dumbhead know nothing.
No.
Jin Ha is weirder.
He wrote the others' names as if he were a Police.
I know.
Jin Ha often borrowed money from Ju Won...
to buy lottery tickets too.
He might've killed him because he didn't want to pay him back.
That must be the reason.
Yoon Seo.
Who do you think is the Mafia?
Actually, something is bothering me.
What is it?
When the Mafia kills someone, it says they're "executed."
But why did it say Yu Jun has "died?"
It's probably because he died in the daytime.
But what if...
both Jin Ha and Kyung Jun are Citizens?
What are you going to do then?
Why do you make it so complicated?
The two killed Yu Jun together.
Just...
tell them not to vote.
No.
If we kill everyone like that,
we're no different from them.
Yes. Stop saying nonsense.
The Police should use their Skill.
Then out of the two, we can save the one who is a Citizen.
Right.
That's a safe way to do it.
No.
After the Doctor died,
the Police would be under even bigger pressure now.
Don't force them.
There is that message too.
That's why it became more complicated.
That's enough.
Let's decide who to vote for first.
Then all of us...
agree with it,
right?
But...
what do we do about this?
We should bring it to them.
We should tell them about the result of the voting as well.
Then...
who should go?
Are we all going?
I'll go.
You guys should hide after voting.
When everyone is hiding,
I'll give the phones to them.
I'll go with you.
We should give these to each of them.
Take it.
Ko Kyung Jun, you scumbag.
(Will you vote for Ko Kyung Jun?)
(Kim Jin Ha voted for Ko Kyung Jun.)
How about you?
Did you vote?
Please.
(Jun Hee, So Mi, Mi Na, Eun Chan, Yeon Woo, Jung Won, Da Bum,)
(Na Hee, Yoon Seo voted for Jin Ha. Jin Ha voted for Kyung Jun.)
Please.
Jun Hee.
I...
I'm really not.
I'm really a Citizen.
Please save me just once.
I really don't want to die.
- Jun Hee, please. - Jin Ha.
Yu Jun must've wanted to live too.
Please.
(Kim Jun Hee)
(Kim Jun Hee is Mafia. Jin Da Bum is Mafia. From Police)
(From Police)
This is why you should've gotten insurance.
What did you say?
Never mind.
Tell them to bring my phone.
We didn't bring your phone.
Tell us where the keys are.
I'll give it to you then.
You scumbag. Have you lost your mind?
You will never find it by yourself.
You know what happens when you can't vote.
Where are the keys?
Da Bum, you've grown a lot.
Right?
You know how to threaten me now.
Follow me. We don't have time.
Go.
What? It's not here.
Are you happy now?
Give me my phone now.
You should've told me you needed the keys.
You scared me for no reason.
Where is it?
Over there.
You bring it.
How would I know if it's real or not?
Do whatever you want. I'm leaving.
I told you to bring it, you scumbag.
We don't have time. Will you be okay?
Darn it.
Is it fun? You piece of trash.
Hey. Open it.
Open it, you scumbag.
Open the freaking door.
Open it, you jerk.
Hey, open it.
Open it. Open the freaking door.
You piece of trash.
I'll kill you when I go out, you rascal.
Open the freaking door.
Darn it.
Jin Da Bum.
Open the freaking door.
Darn it.
Open it, you scumbag.
Voting is over.
Kim Jin Ha who got the most votes will be executed.
Darn it.
(Cleaning Tools)
No.
Kim Jin Ha was a Citizen.
What? Jin Ha was a Citizen.
He was a Citizen?
Darn it. We're doomed.
I'm going to kill those darn Mafias tomorrow.
I'll kill you, you piece of trash.
What does it feel like to be fooled by a loser?
It sucks, doesn't it?
Kyung Jun.
Mafias...
choose a target by unanimous consent.
They're all coming.
You scumbag.
Gosh.
You jerk.
You're a piece of trash.
Just freaking die.
Darn it. The time is up, you idiot.
It freaking hurts. You piece of trash.
What the heck?
What the... Get lost!
Darn it.
It scared the heck out of me.
Kyung Jun.
They say when people die,
hearing is the last sense to go.
Think about me while listening to this.
(Night Has Come)
(Gwangju Information and Content Agency)
(This content was produced through Gwangju Information and...)
(Content Agency's 2022 OTT Platform Content Production Business.)