(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
[Episode 7]
- You...
You go first.
I was originally planning to go out of town.
Just a little later.
What did you want to say?
When I kissed you that day,
were you awake?
Liu Yi.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have used you
to test my emotional perception.
Even though I have a lot of confusion,
no matter how lost or how painful it feels,
I still shouldn't have taken advantage of you.
Have you ever heard of
Jandamon latent cognitive disorder?
It means my emotional perception
became distorted while I was growing up.
So, it made me very scared,
and I didn't dare tell anyone else.
Even my dad doesn't know.
So, you kissed me because...
I don't want to run away anymore.
The doctor said if I want to change,
I need to take testosterone injections
for forced correction.
You can't just take injections like that!
That's ridiculous.
But I don't have any other way.
Don't you want to be more manly?
I'm very professional. I'll help you.
I've got your back.
Professional.
A man should take up such a competitive sport.
A real man never holds back.
You figure out a way to knock me down.
Come on.
Pretty impressive, right?
Next one.
Jump.
Stop, stop, stop.
Get down.
Watch me jump.
Too scared to jump.
All right.
Here, push your hips down,
then use your thighs for power,
tighten your core,
then go up.
Swing twice.
Uncle, you've got to give
Xiao Ma a handsome haircut.
Don't worry.
Don't move.
What are you laughing at?
Do it.
A hundred reps. The most basic ones.
Hurry up.
One.
Two.
Two point zero.
Two point zero one.
Two point zero two.
Two point zero three.
Two point zero four.
Liu Yi, I'm thirsty.
Drink some water.
Liu Yi.
Do you want some?
I'm starving.
Let's eat.
Do you like the fish balls that much?
They're good.
I didn't expect it.
You're pretty manly today.
How do you figure out who you like?
Have you ever felt your heart race for someone?
Like that kind of sexual impulse.
Liu Yi, why don't you go find a woman?
Every day, aside from work,
you just come hang out with me.
You...
really don't have those kinds of thoughts?
I'm helping you with your treatment,
not just hanging out with you.
It's not that I don't want to.
I just choose not to.
- Qi.
Qi.
Qi, you're here.
Sit over there.
Boss.
Xia Liu Yi.
What do you want?
- What do you want?
- What's the matter?
You killed my men and stole my goods.
You dare bring these lackeys onto my turf?
- So what?
- This will soon be our turf.
Shut up.
My boss hasn't even spoken yet.
Shut up, did you hear me?
Why are you pushing?
- Come on.
- Bring it on.
Here.
- Hit me.
- I'll hit you.
What?
- Hit me.
- Trying to fight, huh?
Go ahead, hit me.
Go ahead.
Asking for death?
You think I'm scared of you?
I'll hit you if I want.
- Watch closely.
- Come on, come on.
Xia Liu Yi.
Do you believe I'll kill you right now?
If you dare make a move, just shoot me.
Otherwise, tell your men
to put their weapons away.
Don't disturb the neighbors.
Xia Liu Yi.
Don't push me too far.
If you're in this game,
how can you not bully others?
Shoot me.
I'm trampling all over you.
Qi, Xia Liu Yi is not the same as before.
He's been focused on
avenging Qing Long these past years.
It's hard to say
if we'll be able to handle him.
Afraid to shoot?
He Chu San, let's go.
Get out of the way.
Xia Liu Yi.
I'll kill you sooner or later.
Don't let me see you.
Come on.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
Inspector Xie, why don't you arrest them?
The forces of Hesheng and Kowloon
are so deeply rooted in Kowloon.
This small conflict won't do anything to them.
But the evidence we found a while ago
shows they're helping
Inspector Hua with money laundering.
The latest summary.
His daughter received
a huge sum of five million.
Do you have evidence?
The five million was claimed
by Hesheng and Xiaoqi.
They claimed it was an investment
in his daughter's film companies.
Because of an operational mistake,
it was transferred under personal names,
and deposited into the company account.
An operational mistake?
Only a fool would believe that.
So, what can you do about it?
They have witnesses.
The fine has been paid.
What can you do?
Xiaoqi Hall paid a fine of 200,000.
It was on May 15th.
The day after we checked Inspector Hua's file.
Inspector Xie.
We must investigate
Kowloon's Senior Inspector Hua.
It's him.
He specifically led me
to investigate Inspector Hua.
Inspector Xie.
What a coincidence.
You're here to join the fun too?
[He Family Clinic]
We've arrived.
Here, have a candy.
Your whole face is bruised.
Don't go back and tell Uncle He
that following me makes you starve.
That little scene scared you?
Don't worry.
With me around,
no one will dare to touch you.
Fat Qi, that damn fatty,
- I wasn't scared of him.
- I'm not afraid of losing my life.
What I'm afraid of is...
how you have to face
such people and situations every day.
I've read many books on gang conflicts before
to write my script.
There were many
powerful figures in those books,
but the underworld itself
is a path of no return.
How many people can walk it
peacefully till the end?
To be honest, not a single one.
Books are just books.
Reality is reality.
Reality.
How did Xu Ying die?
When have you not narrowly escaped death?
Your brother and sister, too.
He Chu San.
- Have you said enough?
- No, I haven't!
I can ignore what happens with other gangsters.
But not you.
I don't want to see you like this.
And I definitely don't want to see you hurt.
All right.
You've been through a lot today.
Fine, I won't take you to such places again.
It's late.
You should go back and rest.
Don't overthink things.
Take this walkie-talkie.
Make sure I can find you.
Xia Liu Yi.
My childhood dream was that one day,
I would lead my dad
out of this filthy, murky water.
And now...
I want to take you with me.
Sir, your order is here.
Why are so many big shots visiting today?
Inspector Xie.
Why aren't you eating?
It's on me.
Why are you treating me to a meal?
Thanks to you,
I'm now an official investigator.
You led me to investigate
Inspector Hua's stolen money,
then used me to gather information about him,
and got yourself promoted.
Pretty smart.
No wonder you're an elite inspector.
Quick-witted and quick on your feet.
You just got promoted to official investigator.
Aren't you scared?
Of course I'm scared.
I'm very afraid of dying.
But compared to my small rank,
I'm more afraid of your grand ambitions,
which may never be realized in this lifetime.
What a waste of time.
Inspector Xie.
Actually, you know better than anyone,
you can only catch Xia Liu Yi,
Sha Jia Jun, Fei Qi,
and these so-called big bosses.
Someone like Inspector Hua,
as long as the forces behind him remain,
you won't be able to touch him.
As long as I have evidence of someone's crime,
I'll arrest them.
If I have evidence of organized crime,
I'll arrest the gangsters.
If I have evidence of police misconduct,
I'll arrest the cops.
As for evidence against Inspector Hua,
you've lost it.
Do you think those few million in stolen money
is enough evidence
to bring down a police commissioner?
Even without me,
there will be countless people
with countless reasons
and even more hidden methods
to prove he was wronged.
But this time, with the two of us teaming up,
we caught Inspector Hua off guard.
And you've uncovered
his network with the triads.
It's a win-win.
A win-win.
Sophistry will be re-judged.
Perjury will also be re-judged.
Your recorder seems to be out of battery.
If you really recorded it,
you wouldn't need to say so much to me here.
Even if you really recorded it,
you still can't bring me down.
In fact, I can make Inspector Hua
respect me even more.
That would be a good thing for me.
You're quite shameless.
Inspector Xie.
Please stop pretending to be the righteous one.
I feel like throwing up every time I see you.
In fact, you're just a useless cop.
You can't save anyone.
You only make those
who believe in you die faster.
Lu Guang Ming, do you want to die now?
Inspector Xie.
Please calm down.
Police officers fighting is against the rules.
I'm the kind of person
who believes in reciprocation.
You've helped me so much,
So, I'll help you once.
Don't you love catching the triads?
Then I'll help you catch
the most powerful triad leader, Xia Liu Yi.
How about that?
My treat.
Inspector Xie.
In fact, you're just a useless cop.
You can't save anyone.
You only make those
who believe in you die faster.
Congratulations.
You've officially become
an officer of the ICAC.
Jia Hua, don't worry.
I will definitely be a good officer
who upholds justice like you.
All the best.
Boss!
Call for you.
Damn.
Great gun, boss.
Heavy bleeding.
This gun is hard to handle.
For He Chu San.
I'll take him to the shooting range today.
Let him be bolder.
Is the place ready?
It's clean.
Not a single fly can get in.
- Dong Dong.
- What is it?
Have you ever tried
letting someone worry about you?
Who?
Worried about me?
There are plenty who want to cut me down.
That idiot He Chu San.
He says he's worried about me.
I, Xia Liu Yi, Dual Blades Xia.
Do I need a university student
to worry about me?
A student?
A student should just be holding a lollipop.
Why?
Why have a gun?
Forget it.
It would be good
to teach him some self-defense.
So, he won't worry in the future.
I heard he was parachuted in.
[Gangcheng Bank]
What kind of guy is he?
He's related to both you and me.
The Hang Seng Index has gone up again.
Let's work.
Let's get to work.
Do you need me to go over the details again?
No worries.
I'll just find someone.
I want him.
Please have him contact me directly
so that we can get started.
Sam.
Hello, I'm Jason.
Nice to see you.
Hello, Jason. Nice to meet you, too.
I just got back to Hong Kong.
And I'm not familiar with many things.
I may need a local guy
to help me with some personal stuff.
I think...
Sam.
Sam will be a great choice.
Okay, Sam.
You'll be in charge of Jason during this time.
- Okay.
- Great.
The Hang Seng Index
has broken the 1,000 point mark.
Passion.
Are you kidding me?
Did he get that big phone as a decoration?
The whole building's power is out.
Still not off work.
Jason.
This is our project plan.
- Let's leave together.
- Okay.
Sam.
You're so talented.
It's a bit beneath you to be here.
They just said you're the hardest working one.
Why?
I...
A gun, for you.
Sorry.
Same time tonight, I'll pick you up.
Tonight?
I have an important guest to entertain tonight.
I might not be able to make it.
A guest to entertain?
I'll hang up now.
How dare you hang up on me!
What kind of job is so important?
I'll make you resign sooner or later.
I haven't eaten yet.
Your girlfriend?
She sounds like she has quite a temper.
No, no, no.
Just a friend.
They're a good person.
Seems like it's not just a regular friendship.
You've known each other a long time?
Let's continue.
He drew a little dog.
11.3%.
The expected growth
for this year is 26.51 million.
I thought you were working overtime here.
Turns out you're flirting with someone here.
You misunderstood.
We're working.
Sam.
Is he... your friend?
Hi.
I'm Jason.
Nice to meet you.
Don't speak English here.
Shut it. Shut up.
Did you hear me?
What are you doing? We really are working.
He Chu San.
You...
You're always like this.
You really misunderstood.
Sorry, Jason.
You misunderstood.
Let's see how I'll deal with you.
I guess I do feel a little reluctant.
He Chu San.
Are you using the phone as decoration?
Why didn't you answer my call?
Have you eaten?
Just right.
Recently, there have been
some investment reports.
Are you kidding me?
- Liu Yi.
- Shut up.
Why did you bring me here?
I told you it was a misunderstanding.
He Chu San, stop talking to me.
Come with me.
Don't you have some gender
and emotional awareness disorder?
I think you're just messing with me.
You like men, don't you?
You bastard, you're fooling me.
- Messing with me, huh?
- I'm not messing with you.
You aren't?
If I must say,
I'll find a woman to sleep with you,
and after you sleep with her,
you'll be cured of all your issues.
I don't need to prove anything to you.
I would never do something like that.
I would never come to this kind of mess...
This place.
This kind of place?
Is this kind of place beneath you now?
Does this place tarnish your reputation
as a university graduate?
I'm the owner of this place.
I hang out here every day.
Since you look down on this place,
why do you follow me here every day?
You're not that kind of person.
Where's Mei?
Get Mei here.
Liu Yi.
It takes a thousand days to raise an army.
But a moment to use them.
One thousand, solved.
Did you see that?
A pure, pristine girl.
Liu Yi, take it easy.
I've only slept with her once.
Just the right match for you, the chaste guy.
Let her teach you what it means to be a man.
Liu Yi!
I'm leaving.
Stop.
Is this a place where you can
just come and go as you please?
Do you think this is a public restroom?
Didn't you bring me here?
But I didn't tell you to leave.
He Chu San, I'm telling you,
if you don't sleep with her today,
I'll strip her immediately,
and throw her to the dogs on the streets.
Sir, save me.
Save me.
Save me, mister.
You wouldn't do that.
Someone!
- Where are they?
- Liu Yi, what do you need?
Take off her clothes.
No problem.
Come on, come on.
She's so fierce.
Are you crazy?
- Come here.
- Save me!
- Come here!
Come here!
Always misbehaving.
I'll beat you to death.
Mister, save me.
You won't listen to Liu Yi, huh?
I'll beat you to death.
Sir, save me.
Be quiet!
I'll beat you to death.
Mister, save me.
- Will you listen?
- Save me! Save me!
You're the one I'm beating.
- Save me!
- Will you listen?
Stop hitting me.
Don't hit me anymore.
Save me!
Okay.
I'll do as you say.
Sir, you're here.
Come over here.
Make sure to keep Miao company, okay?
Be smart. Have fun.
Smile.
Ma'am, I'm leaving.
Where is she going?
Chu San.
I understand.
They're even holding hands.
This guy is really in love.
He dares to steal the big boss's woman.
No way.
What are you doing?
Get back to work.
What are you looking at?
Mommy, I want that, too.
You want your head cut off?
Do you want the money or not? Go back to work.
Back to work.
What are you doing? Go inside.
Be smart.
Hold hands.
A date.
Date, hold hands.
Are you boxing or torturing yourself?
I heard you spent 20,000
buying a woman for the student.
Are you crazy?
What does my money have to do with you?
He likes you.
You sleep with him.
Then you can save 20,000.
Cui Dong Dong.
What are you talking about?
I'm just talking nonsense.
He risked his life to save you back then.
He almost died delivering a message for you.
A top university student skipped class
and came to join the underworld.
If he doesn't like you,
could he be an undercover?
I treat him as...
I treat him as a friend.
I treat him as a brother.
So, a brother goes on dates with a girl.
Why are you jealous and punching the sandbag?
I'm not jealous.
Xia Liu Yi.
I don't care whether
you two sleep together or not.
But that He Chu San...
Every day, he's looking all handsome,
taking that girl away from me,
and then sweetly bringing her back.
Girls are getting all wild at heart
and don't even want to do business anymore.
I don't care about all that.
Just get him away from me.
Whatever loss you have, I'll cover it for you.
Xia Liu Yi.
You're just asking for trouble.
Chu San.
- Dong Dong.
- So early.
College student.
Waiting for Mei?
So sweet.
When are you planning to take her away from me?
Mei belongs to Xia Liu Yi.
He'll be upset.
You're really adaptable.
A real talent.
No, wait.
Xia Liu Yi, this eternal virgin,
actually told you that Mei has been with him?
That's hilarious.
That's what he said.
His personality is really awkward.
He talks tough,
but when it comes to someone he likes,
he doesn't dare to even glance at them twice.
So, after all these years,
no one has paid him any attention.
Xia Liu Yi is in the hospital.
What?
Not sure what triggered it.
A single sneeze landed him in the hospital.
Are you going to see him?
Which hospital is he at?
College student.
Are you serious about Xia Liu Yi?
Yes.
Xia Liu Yi is like a stone,
smelly and hard in a cesspit.
Your passion alone won't do anything.
You have to let him figure it out himself.
Maybe Mei is your trump card.
Dong Dong.
Why are you helping me?
I'm not helping you.
I'm helping Xia Liu Yi.
Ever since Xiao Man and Qing Long died,
he's lived every day in regret.
It wasn't until he met you
that he started acting like a human again.
So, I hope you can help him
move on to a new life.
What's going on?
He hit me!
Get out here!
Don't you know this is my turf?
Boss, your food is here.
I... He...
Go explain it yourself.
I heard you're sick.
I came to check on you.
Which one do you want?
This one.
Put your leg down.
Here's plain congee and century egg
with lean pork congee.
What would you like to have?
And these.
This is salted radish made by Dad.
It doesn't look very appealing,
but it smells amazing.
Try it.
No.
Find a place to sit.
Your foot.
Liu Yi.
I'm sorry about that night.
I shouldn't have made you angry.
I know you meant well.
Mei is really nice.
I'm happy when I'm with her.
Thank you.
Liu Yi.
I want to show you something.
What is it?
Look.
A rose.
I got it tattooed just for Mei.
Do you like it?
Have you lost your mind!
It's just a relationship! Why get a tattoo?
Don't you know a tattoo lasts a lifetime?
It's about to fade.
What are you doing?
You really care about me.
Care about what?
I'm just afraid...
I'm afraid Uncle He would hit you
if he knew about your tattoo.
Dad wouldn't do that.
Besides...
To me...
Loving someone is a lifetime commitment.
Don't you agree?
How would I know?
Liu Yi.
Do you want to watch
a new movie together next week?
No.
Go with your girlfriend.
Fine.
Then I'll watch it with her first.
If it's good, I'll tell you.
Forget it.
I've been busy lately.
You won't be busy during the New Year, right?
Dad asked whether
we should celebrate the New Year together.
He Chu San.
My whole squad from Xiaoqi Hall...
They're all lined up
waiting to celebrate with me.
Why would I celebrate New Year at your place?
I'm not going.
Here it comes, the dishes are served.
Wishing you wealth in the new year.
Liu Yi, I didn't expect you
to take the time to celebrate New Year with us.
I also want to celebrate with you guys.
Son, I'm not blaming you,
but Liu Yi is our guest.
You shouldn't make him do it himself, really.
Uncle He, it's nothing major.
You don't know.
Lately, he's been neglecting family matters.
Whenever he's free, he goes chasing girls.
I almost forgot.
I mean, really...
It's fine that you're chasing girls.
- But you don't even bring them home.
- Exactly.
My wine is meant for my future daughter-in-law.
That's right.
Liu Yi.
Home-brewed glutinous rice wine.
- Have a glass.
- No, no, thanks.
Just try it.
Glutinous rice wine
won't make you drunk quickly.
Don't be shy.
Chu San, why are you tugging me?
I haven't even finished talking.
Am I such a narrow-minded father?
If I'm getting a daughter-in-law,
shouldn't you bring her home?
Let me see her first.
That's all I'm saying.
- Come on, come on.
- Dad, our fortunes aren't even matched yet.
Let him drink a little less.
Drinking glutinous rice wine...
That's how you celebrate the New Year.
Without glutinous rice wine,
it doesn't count as the New Year.
Drinking it warms your heart
for the coming year.
Exactly, exactly.
And you said our fortunes aren't even matched.
Fei said they all went to her shop.
Yes, hear me out.
That day, he brought a girl over
to eat beef offal at the shop.
She's a very pretty girl with long hair.
She looks so beautiful.
- Fei.
- They look perfect together.
Fei, eat something.
Eat first.
All right, let's eat.
But when chasing girls,
he's all calculative and deliberate.
Dad, don't speak. Eat.
I really want to have a grandson.
Me, too.
Next New Year, you must bring her home.
Yes, the more the merrier at home.
I'd be so happy to have a chubby grandson.
Come on, come on.
You guys eat first.
I'm going to the bathroom.
All right, go ahead.
Liu Yi.
You're upset?
No, not at all.
I'm leaving.
Where are you going?