This is a work of fiction.
Underage drinking is strongly prohibited and illegal.
Scenes involving alcohol with forceful consumption and shameful acts are not encouraged. Please view this as a comedy. Furthermore, all characters appearing in this work are of legal age.
This work is an original copyrighted material
of the Content Provider. Unauthorized reproduction
or distribution of this work in any form or manner is prohibited. Some viewers might find this work disturbing as it may contain strong language, a degree of violence or adult situations. Viewer discretion is advised. Please watch it at your own risk.
The story, names, characters and incidents portrayed
in this work are fictitious. No identification with actual
persons, organizations, religions, places and products is intended. The Content Provider, the producers and related parties shall have no liability, as to the accuracy, legality, safety or suitability for any purpose of the information provided in this work. The views and opinions expressed herein do not reflect the views and opinions of the Content Provider, or any of its affiliates, partners, subsidiaries, or Licensee.
This is Iori-chan! She's new here!
She just started college this spring!
Welcome! Thanks for requesting me today!
It was just a dream...
What a nightmare!
I would never wear a high school girl's uniform.
Good morning.
No!
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
Grand Blue Dreaming
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
An expanding ocean of possibilities
Summer is our amore
We'll swear to the crystal clear sky
Summer is in our hands
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
With a cheerful heart
Don't mess with me
Keep going even if you fall
And let summer take it all
I didn't know you guys were into that sort of thing...
What are you talking about, Iori?
That uniform...
I like uniforms, but why did you give me
a boy's uniform?
I thought we'd focus on our club activities today.
Good morning. Huh?
Uniforms...
Perverts.
-It's not what you think, Chisa!
-They told us they're for diving!
Diving? Oh.
So it's that time of year again...
That's right.
Chisa just accepted it...
So, we really do need uniforms for diving?
But how are we going to use these?
Maybe they repel sharks.
What are those two talking about?
Who knows...
Let me explain.
This is the equipment we need for diving.
WEIGHTS / SUIT / FINS, MASK, & SNORKEL
BCD / REGULATOR / DIVING COMPUTER, ETC.
Then we don't need the uniforms!
You lied to us!
Be quiet and listen.
In other words, diving...
Is expensive.
You understand what I'm trying to say, right?
This is where those come in.
Their imaginations are running wild.
Have you guys heard of the Izu Spring Festival?
It's our school festival, held in May.
There's an event called the
"Inter-Club Men's Beauty Pageant."
The winning club gets some prize money.
I see. You want us to enter?
-Correct!
-No!
-Also called the male beauty pageant.
-Or, male pageant.
That's terrible!
Did you know about this?
Well, yeah. I watched it last year.
I'm not participating.
Wearing an outfit like that and getting laughed at?
No way.
Hey, Kohei.
You're a pretty boy.
What?!
If you enter, you'd probably win.
Use your charm to help our club.
I'm sorry, but...
-So, you guys don't need me.
-Why not?
You have Kohei.
Hey, Iori.
What?
-You'll enter in the joke category.
-I'll kill you.
-Put those on, you guys.
-Huh?
We're going to the ocean today.
How is the size?
It's a little tight.
As long as there're no gaps, it's fine.
Let's go.
Okay.
The ocean...
Aren't you going, Chisa?
I'm watching the store.
I see. Well, then...
THE OCEAN, US, AND BLUE
Hey, Iori.
Were you excited when you started college life?
-Huh?
-How did you feel?
Now that you mention it, I did...
feel excited...
Then I'm sure
you'll have fun.
Iori will team up with me for practice.
Then I'll practice with Kohei.
This is really simple.
You'll simulate what it's like
to breathe underwater.
Okay...
Put the regulator in your mouth and breathe in.
Okay.
How was it?
It feels really different from breathing normally.
Correct. It's as if the air flows in
all at once when you breathe in.
That's true.
You have to use force to breathe in.
Yeah. You might have a hard time
breathing until you get used to it.
-Okay.
-Let's try actually diving underwater.
Okay...
Iori...
Hey, Iori.
What?
Why are you out of breath?
Because I can't breathe.
Then why are you carrying
that tank on your back?
I'm scared of breathing underwater.
-Scared?
-Yes.
I see. Well, you might feel confused at first,
but you'll get used to it.
Then I'll try it one more time.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Water leaked into my mask...
Maybe it's too loose. Let me see.
Thank you very much!
-Who are those customers?
-Wait up!
Oh. They came to dive before their business trip.
That looks rough.
They look really busy,
but they even brought their suits.
-It's reassuring, right?
-Reassuring?
It's true, right?
They're spending their
precious money and time on diving.
In other words...
it proves just how alluring this place is!
You said it's scary underwater, right?
-Sorry.
-You don't have to apologize.
Even I get scared when I think about what would happen
if I run out of air.
Do you know what this is?
-Uh...
-This is called an octopus.
It's a spare regulator.
You give it to your buddy if they run out of air.
And the weight belt always faces the same way.
There's a reason for that too.
It's so you can remove it quickly
if something happens.
It's not only for your own safety.
It's so you can help the friends you dive with.
We did a thorough safety check.
You're not here alone. I'm here too.
You'll be fine, so be tough and go dive.
I'll help you, no matter what.
All right!
-Here I go!
-Yeah.
Huh? I did it!?
It's not tough at all!
I did it!
So this is...
what it's like underwater.
A new world...
I didn't know about.
-Chisa!
-Iori?
I understand what you were trying to say now!
It's amazing to be able to breathe underwater!
-And I can't even swim!
-Oh, really...
So, this is what it means to experience
a new world!
So, this is how it feels to go to outer space
and experience zero gravity!
-Iori, I know. Now go change...
-I wonder if it feels like
-you're floating when you really get into diving...
-People
who only choose what they know
will never experience that joy.
What do you mean?
-You don't understand?
-I'm talking about this, of course!
It's the joy of learning how to do
something you couldn't do before.
Cheers!
-That was good!
-It burns.
Have some food with your drinks.
Thanks!
That was great, Iori.
You conquered your fear.
I'm still not great in the water.
But you learned how fun it is
to step into a new world!
Yeah! Thank you.
No, you don't have to thank us.
Right. Now...
There's no reason for you
to say no to this new world either!
No!
I drank too much again...
Water...
What are you doing?
Let's stay in bed a bit longer.
Huh? Uh... Huh?
This can't be real.
Getting drunk and waking up to
someone half-naked sleeping next to me...
Is a normal thing now..
I mean... Who is she?
-Oh. This is the first time you guys met.
-Whoa!
You know that our club
is an intercollegiate club, right?
INTERCOLLEGIATE CLUB:
A CLUB WITH MEMBERS FROM DIFFERENT COLLEGES
So, she's from another school?
She's Azusa Hamaoka from Oumi Women's University.
Why is she sleeping here?
Maybe because there was a futon.
I was sleeping in that futon first...
She's not the type of girl to care about that.
Whoa.
Who would take off their clothes
and sleep in a room with naked guys?
That's what I mean.
If you treat her like a girl,
you'll make a fool out of yourself.
You're wearing clothes? That's unusual.
We have something to do outside today.
That's why we invited Azusa.
-Let's wake her up then.
-Wait.
There's something we have to tell you first.
Something important about the Izu Spring Festival.
Okay, done!
You're really good.
Not really!
We'll be selling okonomiyaki
at the Izu Spring Festival?
-It's delicious!
-It has to be!
The sales will go to fund our club.
Today, we're going to have the freshmen
learn how to make these.
What about you, Tokki and Bukki?
-Oh, we're...
-Tokita! Kotobuki!
-Let's go!
-Okay.
We're going to prep the equipment.
When we're done,
we'll eat with everyone.
So, make a lot of them.
Okay.
-Then let's begin!
-Okay.
Let's do it, Kohei!
Leave it to me, Kitahara!
Something about the Izu Spring Festival?
It's not about the male pageant?
Actually, it is related to that...
We want you to convince Chisa.
What do you mean?
There's an Izu Spring Festival
women's beauty pageant.
We want Chisa to enter so that
we can get more funds for our club.
-You want us to convince her to enter!?
-That's impossible!
But if she wins,
you guys don't have to enter
the male pageant anymore.
All right! Let's do it!
Normally, Chisa would never agree
to enter the women's beauty pageant.
Then we just have to put her
in an abnormal condition.
We'll get her drunk, she'll loosen up,
and we'll get her to enter the pageant!
It's hot today, Kohei!
Right, Kitahara!
It's so hot I'm going to get heatstroke!
We have to stay hydrated!
I'll go bring something to drink!
VODKA + WHISKEY
OOLONG TEA
-Here's some oolong tea.
-Oh, thanks.
Kitahara, got it?
The alcohol is in my right hand.
The right hand is for Chisa.
The left hand is for me.
Hey, Chisa. Have a drink.
I can't stop right now.
I'll have some later.
Then I'll take it.
Huh?
VODKA + WHISKEY
-Aren't you going to drink?
-Well...
What? Is there something weird in it?
Of course not!
Come on, drink up, Kitahara!
Yeah! You're right!
What's wrong, Iori?
Oh, nothing.
You bastard! Look what you did!
It was unavoidable!
Let's switch!
I'll do it this time.
I'll bring some drinks!
What are you making?
Chisa!? This isn't--
You guys sure are pathetic.
You're trying to get Imamura to drink that, right?
Kohei. Here's some tea.
Oh. Thanks.
Sorry. It was unavoidable.
How was this unavoidable!?
Good job!
I'm not as good as you, though.
It's okay!
It's just for the school festival.
In a setting like this...
What?
-Don't you feel like having a beer?
-I knew you'd say that! So I brought some!
I don't want any.
Can I have some?
You two are really considerate!
Well, well...
We're extremely delighted.
Just like I heard from Nanaka. You're cute.
-From Nanaka?
-Are you guys close?
We talk on the phone sometimes.
That's why I know a lot about you,
-Iori.
-Oh.
She told me lots of things.
Nanaka...
I have to go call my friend...
Iori. That's disgusting.
What are you doing?
That porn and that gay porn...
It's all a misunderstanding!
It's okay!
No, it's not okay...
Actually,
I'm okay with both too.
It's nice to meet someone who's into the same stuff!
Let's talk someday, okay?
-Into the same stuff?
-She's talking about diving, right?
Hey, Kitahara!
There's no time for meaningless conversation!
This is pretty important...
Is something wrong?
-No! Nothing!
-I'm going to get some drinks!
I didn't want it to come down to this...
I'll have to give everyone this...
-Here's some oolong tea!
-Here!
-I still have some. I'm fine.
-Me too.
There's more!
Shaved ice is perfect for the sea!
It has special syrup!
I'm full.
You guys can have it.
What are you guys doing?
Can I ask you something?
Why are you trying to get Chii-chan drunk?
What you're talking about!?
That's a pretty extreme accusation!
If you're trying to get her drunk, then I have an idea.
No! That's not what we're doing!
Then what were you trying to do?
It can't be helped!
No more tricks! Chisa!
What?
-Enter the women's beauty pageant!
-No.
He'll kneel down naked and beg you! Please!
Want me to step on him?
Just answer yes or no!
-Please!
-We're begging you!
I said no!
That won't work. If you're going
to ask her for something,
you should tell her your reason.
You don't have a reason?
Well...
If Chisa enters, we can get the prize money.
Then we don't have to enter
the male pageant.
I see. Now I understand.
What about it, Chii-chan?
No way.
I was expecting this...
You shouldn't have asked in the first place.
What? She said no?
We didn't even have a chance.
So, now we have to enter the male pageant...
It can't be helped.
Who entered the pageant when it was your turn?
Azusa entered the women's pageant.
She is pretty.
-She lost in the preliminaries though.
-Huh? Why?
She forgot her swimsuit and competed in her underwear,
so she was disqualified.
That's amazing.
She wasn't embarrassed?
She's that type of girl.
No, that can't...
Well, you'll find out soon.
Take it off!
If you lose, you have to spread your legs!
All right! I'm going to go join them.
Go ahead.
Azusa likes that kind of stuff.
Let me join!
Okay! Huh!?
-Really?
-Yeah.
It's naked rock paper scissors!
You'll strip?
Are you okay with that?
If you lose, you strip!
It's naked rock paper scissors!
I'm not going to get totally naked though.
I'm a young girl, you know.
-Oh, yeah.
-You're right.
That's why...
I've stuck band-aids on.
I'll go first.
But, Kitahara...
You have nothing left to take off.
There's nothing to worry about, Kohei.
Just once.
I'm going to bet everything on just one chance.
HAIRPIN
Tokki! Bukki! This guy is great!
I'm glad you like him.
He's talented, right?
Let's compete on speed!
I'm going to take this one standing.
You stay back, Kohei.
No, you stay back.
That was fun!
-They're nice, right?
-Yeah.
What's nice about them?
I like them, though.
-Hey, Chii-chan.
-Yes?
Why don't you enter the women's beauty pageant?
No.
-It's part of the joy of being born a woman.
-What do you mean?
You know...
Those guys never doubted
that you'd win, right?
It's because they think
you're the cutest one, Chii-chan.
If Chisa enters, we can get the prize money.
What do you think?
-Well...
-Huh?
It's not that I won't do it no matter what...
I just don't like how
they're trying to embarrass only me.
HEARTTHROB
LEMON SOUR
-What?
-You're right.
That's not very manly.
Then let's do this.
Thanks to Iori and Kohei,
Chisa decided to enter the women's beauty pageant.
-Really?
-She changed her mind overnight?
So, there's something we want to give you.
Here. Take this.
Why?!
Chisa said she'd enter the women's beauty pageant
under one condition.
You guys have to enter the male pageant.
Then why did we even...
It was all for nothing!
-You wear the girl's uniform!
-You're the one entering the joke category!
They look like they're having fun.
I'm glad they're close.
-Everything's okay now, right?
-Yes.
Well, I feel a little better now.
DEEP BLUE AL FINE
KAYA MIZUKI
Here's your mic, Kitahara.
Me, too...? All right, let's do this!
-Yeah, sing your heart out.
-You guys seem to be having fun.
A fairytale whispers
In a fake world
Hiding in the complete darkness
I reach for the forbidden fruit
In my last days
Now I know the meaning of the song about hope
A broken gear will never stop again
Even if I were to lose everything
I'd still want you to know
Trapped in the sky so far away
I'm praying with ripped off wings
Because we span together
The vows of areppegio
If life sparkles only to the beat
of the resonating stars
I'll sacrifice everything
Till death do us apart
Cheers!
We're very sorry!
Izu Spring Festival! Yay!
I'm Chisa Kotegawa
from Peek-a-Boo!
Take this!
A ghost!
NEXT EPISODE
"THE MALE BEAUTY PAGEANT"