♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 20=
Storm the city!
Attack!
Sweetie.
This pot looks pretty heavy.
If the Wutuo forces really break in,
can you even swing it?
No, I can't.
But I'll throw it
at them.
Killing one enemy is good.
Killing two
is better.
With enemies coming,
we must stand united.
Jiyang is my home.
If home is gone,
what's the point of living?
Exactly.
My brother and father are
on the battlefield.
I want to cheer them in victory.
You're right.
Women
should also be tough.
If officials' families only
want self-preservation,
how can we expect soldiers
to fight on the front lines?
Let's fight enemies!
- Sure!
- Let's fight them!
(Compassionate Salvation)
(Radiant Illumination)
Who are you?
That's not important. Attack!
Charge!
(Three Passes)
Fire arrows!
Feinu.
You lead the vanguard out of the city.
Muyi will lead Jiyang troops
to guard the gate.
Not a single Wutuo man
shall enter Jiyang!
- Understood!
Once the gate opens,
lead the main force
against the Wutuo army first.
Then I'll take an elite squad
to divert Huyate
and his heavy armor troops,
luring them away
from the main battlefield.
The remaining Wutuo forces
will be leaderless.
Commander.
Let me lead the elite squad
to lure away Huyate and his heavy armor.
No.
To divert Huyate,
we need someone of high standing.
The Wutuo loathe me.
Therefore,
I'm the right one.
Actually, in Jiyang, there is someone
of higher standing
than you.
Quick!
You want to impersonate Princess Mengji?
Yes.
Do you understand the risks?
I do,
so I can't let you go.
As our commander-in-chief,
the entire army's fate relies on you.
You can't take unnecessary risks.
I know you are
worried about my safety.
But you must realize
that once I wear this armor,
I become a soldier,
fearless of death.
Medic!
Come quickly!
There's another one!
Hurry!
Move faster!
He Yan, receive orders!
Come back alive.
Yes!
Quickly!
Medic!
Hurry!
He's dying!
Let me check.
Faster!
This will hurt.
Bear with it.
Alright.
Prepare the horses!
Yes!
Charge!
- Attack!
Whoever captures Xiao Jue alive
will be handsomely rewarded.
- Attack!
Attack!
Mu Hongjin is trying to escape.
Heavy infantry! Capture her alive!
(He Yan.)
(You must return safely.)
Seize Mu Hongjin!
Don't let her escape!
(Wutuo forces)
(are accustomed to land battles.)
(Horses aren't water-adept.)
There's a riverbank east of the city.
It's a risky move.
Destroy the leader first.
Capture Huyate,
and the battle can turn around.
You're not Mu Hongjin.
Trash like you
isn't worth Her Highness' effort.
You're courting death.
You're seeking death!
I'm killing you at any cost.
(Chai Anxi?)
I just spotted Chai Anxi.
But he vanished.
You must find him.
Yes.
(Dear sister,)
(I gave you mercy.)
(Yet you rejected it.)
(You let me down.)
(Bring honor to our family?)
(You don't deserve to do that.)
(My family needs only one heir.)
(Prepare to die!)
(Our family doesn't need you.)
(Your death)
(will ensure our family's peace.)
Commander.
Commander, have we won?
Listen.
We've won.
- We've won!
Great!
We've won.
Indeed.
- We won!
We won!
Splendid!
- We won!
We won!
Brilliant!
- We won!
We've won!
Your Highness.
We've won.
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
What's on your mind?
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
Nothing.
Let's report to Her Highness.
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
Hold my hand.
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
You've all worked hard.
On behalf of Jiyang's people,
I thank you all.
My pleasure.
Protecting the nation
and people
is our duty.
That's an honor.
Congratulations, General Fengyun.
I'm glad you're safe.
I appreciate your concern.
Your Highness.
I found Mr. Liu's body near the mansion.
There were many Wutuo men's bodies
surrounding him.
Their weapons were poisonous.
Mr. Liu was fatally poisoned.
Enemies outnumbered him.
He died of exhaustion.
My master?
That's not true.
My master couldn't have...
(This pair of bracelets
is called Joyful Hearts.)
Lovers wearing them
will never be parted.
Is this your beloved?
(Buy a pair for the lady.)
You two will be together forever.
Did you hear that?
Aren't you buying me this?
She's not my beloved.
Liar.
You liar.
What's wrong?
Are you upset?
None of your business.
Did I upset you?
Liu Buwang.
Why didn't you buy me the bracelets?
If it were anything else,
I'd promise you.
Really?
Don't trick me again.
I mean it.
Well,
go outside the city with me?
I'll share a secret.
In a temple
lies a passage leading out of the city.
A passage?
You already promised me.
Keep your word.
Let's go.
(Radiant Illumination)
Here we are.
Alright.
♪Through endless nights, I walk alone♪
♪Heartache swirls like ceaseless winds♪
♪Yet I yearn to stand opposed to you♪
♪Seeking fleeting clarity♪
♪Imprisoned within memories♪
♪Upon towering fortress walls♪
♪Brooding over lamented pasts♪
♪Where shall light be found♪
♪Once♪
♪I had an unbreakable faith♪
Jiyang
is safe now.
That's good.
♪I'm shrouded in darkness♪
♪Resent old dreams like drifting clouds♪
♪Heartache♪
♪Resenting the lonely years♪
♪Why♪
♪Not let it go♪
♪Tears crystallize to frost♪
♪Clutching stubborn obsessions♪
♪Yet falling into folly♪
♪Fading into oblivion♪
♪Yet memories surge everywhere♪
♪After the separation♪
♪Who will be with you♪
Hongjin.
♪You are my light♪
I wish you peace.
♪Get lost♪
Live
well.
♪Mournful through night skies♪
♪How dare I hope♪
♪That twilight outshines vastness♪
♪Ultimately♪
♪Await ancients
to bid farewell to the past♪
♪After parting♪
♪My heart feels adrift♪
Maybe I should go check on them.
No.
This is not something
you and I can fix.
Leave them alone for a moment.
Commander.
Thanks for guarding the door.
Why are you staring at me?
Is there something on my face?
Ugly.
What?
It makes you ugly
when you lie.
I've told you.
Just cry or laugh
if you want to.
Just be yourself.
You don't have to act.
It looks unnatural.
I'm not acting.
It's just
that I can't help.
What do you mean?
Commander.
In this world, only a few people
who treated me well.
Less than five people.
Now, one of them is gone.
(Tomb of Hermit Yunlin Liu Buwang)
Yan.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Miss He.
I'm so sorry.
We're all mere mortals.
Who can truly remain detached?
If we don't force ourselves
to let it go,
what else can we do?
Mr. Liu was
free and unrestrained.
If he saw you grieving like this,
he would worry about you.
The living
must move on.
They say
that the deceased
would cross the River of Forgetfulness
to reach the other shore.
But what's it like
across the river?
Master.
According to Jiyang's customs,
tonight,
the family should prepare food
to send off the departed.
I have
prepared your favorite dishes.
Jiyang
is now recovering steadily.
All is well.
And everyone is safe.
Master.
May you rest in peace.
Let me
toast you.
Your Highness.
I brought some dishes for your master.
After all these years,
your master's taste in food
remains unchanged.
Sweet and sour fish.
You didn't put any sugar
in this dish?
My master
loved sugarless sweet and sour fish.
He never put sugar in it.
I used to tease him
that it was sweet and sour fish
without sugar,
and he could eat sour fish.
Only later did I know
it was because the one
my master had been missing
liked
to eat sugarless sweet and sour fish.
I always knew
he liked me.
I refused to meet him
because he broke his promise.
But the bracelet
made me realize
he must have had his reasons.
Thinking about it now,
what difference would it make?
I'm Mu Hongjin of the Mengji Mansion.
I'm Mu Hongjin of Jiyang.
I could never
be his Mu Hongjin.
He Yan.
Fate didn't bind me to your master,
but I've genuinely
come to regard you as family.
My greatest regret
is that I didn't go out
to meet him that night.
Even just a glimpse from afar
would be better.
Cherish the one you like.
Don't repeat the mistake
your master and I made.
It's lucky
to meet the one you love
in your life.
Once you find the right one,
don't let him go.
Give him a chance
and trust him.
It also means a chance for you.
I see, Your Highness.
Commander.
Why are you here?
Once you returned,
you went to restaurants,
preparing food for Mr. Liu.
But you eat nothing.
Let's eat together.
Sir.
Xiao Jue has taken Chai Anxi back.
Chai Anxi is now unconscious.
He's now at the Cui Mansion.
Cheng Lisu and Song Taotao
are treating him.
Chancellor Xu sent a letter,
urging you to act quickly.
Should I go kill Chai Anxi now?
I suspect
Chai Anxi holds crucial information.
So, I need to verify details with him.
Have you noticed something?
Chai Anxi
was Xiao Zhongwu's deputy general.
He faked his death
after the Mingshui Battle.
Xiao Jue's search for him
is understandable.
But to kill him,
Chancellor Xu sent me
and even contacted Wutuo.
It makes me realize
that he and Chai Anxi must
share a dark history.
Are you suspecting
Chancellor Xu is related
to the Mingshui Battle's defeat?
We'll know the answer
when Chai Anxi wakes.
Chai Anxi knows you.
If he wakes,
will he implicate you?
No.
Chai Anxi values loyalty.
He'd never
betray his lifesaver.
Moreover,
even if he says something,
I have contingency plans.
Now that Chai Anxi's at the Cui Mansion,
as an Inspector,
I should pay a visit.
Though Chai Anxi's life is stabilized,
his injuries are severe.
Song Taotao is preparing medicine.
I'll leave it to you.
Chu Zhao?
What brings you here?
Commander Xiao.
I heard General Fengyun
found a soldier
who supposedly died
at the Mingshui Battle.
I wonder why a dead man
came back to life.
It's pretty strange.
As an Inspector,
I must figure this out.
It made sense.
I just found this man
and wanted to inform you.
But unexpectedly,
you came.
You are
so well-informed.
I have to be alert
as His Majesty's courtier.
He remains unconscious,
so we can't question him.
However,
Cheng Lisu and Song Taotao
are trying to treat him.
When he wakes,
you'll be informed.
Thanks, Commander Xiao.
I'll take my leave.
See you.
Commander.
Why share details with him?
He's Xu Jingfu's disciple.
He's up to no good.
His official position
grants him authority.
Avoidance won't work.
Post more guards
around the courtyard.
Prevent the opponents
from breaking in.
Yes.
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪