( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(Lee Na Young)
(Jung Eun Chae)
(Lee Chung Ah)
(Honour)
(Supported by the Culture Ministry and Korea's Creative Content Agency)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
I see it. Have you told Shin Jae?
(Hyun Jin)
Ra Young! Yoon Ra Young!
Hey, Ra Young, open the door!
Hey, what happened?
I'm okay. I'm okay now.
Let me see where you're hurt.
What kind of jerk did this?
Did you see their face?
Did you call the police?
- Not yet. - Let's get you to a hospital first.
Can you walk?
(Episode 3)
Still, don't you think you should stay in the hospital today?
Are you sure it wasn't that stalker who used to follow you around?
It wasn't the stalker.
It wasn't a robbery. Then what was it?
A fan of Kang Eun Seok?
It could've been an online hater. The backlash has been worse lately.
It's Do Jun.
Yes. What have you got?
I'm sorry.
You're telling me nothing was caught on any CCTVs or dashcams?
It seems they used the emergency exit to get out the back,
and it seems the whole route was planned out beforehand.
Who would go to such lengths and why?
(Husband)
I was worried. The house is a wreck, and you were gone.
- You went out like that? - Sorry.
I was completely out of it.
Is Ra Young okay?
Yes.
Her injuries aren't serious, but she seems really shaken up.
Was it that stalker again? Or just some other psycho?
We're not exactly sure yet.
Do you really have to keep doing this work?
I don't mean being a lawyer. I mean LnJ.
There are other cases besides crimes against women. You have options.
I see about five bodies a month.
Over 70 percent of them are women.
In a world like this, how could I not worry about you?
In a world like this, how could I not do this work?
Hyun Jin, I hate that...
you're constantly attacked by strangers.
And I hate that you'll be targeted for revenge.
You used to admire me fighting back and never let anyone get to me.
Why is something you used to admire now something you want me to stop?
Are you worried about me, or just for yourself for having to?
I ran into Ra Young at the hospital earlier.
She said you stepped back from representing Jo Yoo Jeong.
That's true, right?
I was, until a little while ago.
But not anymore.
You're taking Jo Yoo Jeong's case?
You know who the lead detective is, don't you?
I'll be gathering evidence to put Jo Yoo Jeong away,
and you're helping her get away? While we sleep in the same bed?
Maybe she didn't do it.
What?
The person who killed Jun Hyeok...
It might not have been Yoo Jeong.
How can you even say that? We have her confession and evidence.
The real killer could've framed her, you know.
Do you have anything to back that up?
Why? You can't bring yourself to believe it?
What Lee Jun Hyeok did to Jo Yoo Jeong?
It's not that...
Honey!
I'm just going to crash here.
You don't have to trouble yourself. I'm fine, really.
Who said this was for you?
I'm the one who can't sleep.
This is nice.
This brings back memories.
Back at Hyun Jin's place in college.
Remember how the three of us slept on one mattress in that tiny place?
How did the three of us even fit in there?
Tell me about it. You were a wild sleeper back then.
- I still am. Want to find out? - In a space this big? I'll pass.
You should cut back on your shows.
And lay low from the press for a while.
Shin Jae.
Yes.
I can't stop.
I don't care who stabbed me today. A stalker, a hater, whoever.
If I stop,
I might as well be dead, Shin Jae.
Fine. Keep going.
I'll handle the consequences.
I said I'm just here to meet someone!
I'm sorry, but we have a dress code. We can't let you in.
Who said anything about eating here?
Darn, let go of me!
What, you're just gonna ignore me?
Min Seo!
See? What did I tell you? I said my daughter was in here.
Why haven't you answered my calls?
I was worried, so I came to find you.
I'm so sorry. I am so, so sorry.
How much do you make here? You're not cut out for this place.
Are you crazy? What are you doing here?
Is that any way to talk to your mother?
Maybe you should've picked up and read my texts then.
Those jerks have started hitting me in the face now.
I guess that means I'm of no value now.
They'll probably sell me off for parts or worse.
- What's that got to do with me? - Give me your phone.
- Darn it, where did you hide it? - What do you think you're doing?
Fine. Let's make it a win-win.
I have a way to get us some money.
I thought they were cheap lawyers,
but I looked them up, and it turns out...
Haeil's daughter is a lawyer there.
- So what? - Connect.
If we leak some info on that, I think we can score a huge payday.
Just throw them a few scraps of what you know.
Come on, sweetie.
Don't be like that. You're disappointing me.
Enough already. I'm still paying off...
the debt you racked up in my name.
How else will you exploit me? How much more can you sell me out?
You wench. You think you paid it all off yourself?
I chipped in five grand, you know.
Don't come looking for me ever again.
Forget Connect and all that nonsense.
Stay there, and you'll end up dead, you wench.
This is all stuff we already know.
What did Dong Je say?
He dug through forums, social media, and databases,
and said no prostitution link has come up on that app.
Yes?
Ms. Hwang, your husband is here to see you.
Seon Kyu's here?
We had a little fight yesterday. I wonder if that's why he's here.
Still in the honeymoon phase?
You couldn't even wait for her to get off work.
I heard you got hurt. Are you okay?
It was nothing. Coffee? Tea?
Coffee, please.
What brings you all the way out here?
About yesterday...
I shouldn't have said it like that.
I'm sorry.
I was a little on edge too.
Look.
I still have that dream.
The one where you leave me for Lee Jun Hyeok.
Even though you're right here with me.
I'm so pathetic, Hyun Jin.
I shouldn't feel this way about someone who died so tragically,
but I guess that's just how much I love you.
No, I'm the one who's sorry.
For making you feel so insecure.
I'm so sorry.
- Should I have left you two alone? - We're done.
We'll finish the rest at home.
A little more information than I needed.
Thanks.
I just need to pack up. Do you want to wait?
Shall we hit the gym before we head home? It's been a while.
No. I have to hurry back. I actually just stopped by for work.
Work?
I'm here to collect DNA samples. From both you and Ra Young.
What are you talking about? Our DNA? Why?
We found some unidentified DNA at Lee Jun Hyeok's place.
It was on a woman's accessory, but it's not Jo Yoo Jeong's.
We can't even identify the person.
What does that have to do with our DNA?
We need to compare them to rule out those close to her.
Since you were all in contact with Jo Yoo Jeong very recently,
there could have been some transfer.
So, who's first?
(DNA Collection Room)
- Detective Gu. - Yes, Chief.
Are you here to drop off evidence for analysis?
Yes. It's from the victim's house. We're trying to rule out associates.
That must be the case Attorney Yoon is working on.
- You know Attorney Yoon? - We go back. I'll let you work.
Yes, ma'am.
My hair could have been left at Jun Hyeok's place, right?
It could've gotten on Yoo Jeong,
but my earring...
getting on her and ending up stuck in his bed?
Hey, does that sound plausible to you at all?
No.
Should I beg? Cry? Just throw myself at his feet?
Hwang Hyun Jin, what have you done?
That's not the problem right now.
If the police find out that earring is yours,
you'll be brought in for questioning.
From their point of view, your actions are suspicious enough,
and then if, by some chance, the police...
run your DNA against the cold case database...
No way.
But what if they do?
If...
that comes to light...
The police can't get...
their hands on your DNA.
He went to collect your DNA?
All right. I'm on my way.
No, wait.
There might be...
another way.
(Hong Yeon Hui, Chief Forensic Medical Examiner)
Yes?
Thank you for agreeing to join our Task Force.
I should be thanking you.
It's been ages since I've handled corporate law,
but you insisted on bringing me on board.
Please have a seat.
Why me? That's what I came here to find out.
Shall I venture a guess?
It's no secret my mother wants me to succeed her,
and you know if you rope me in, she'll go all in on this project.
I simply needed you, Attorney Kang Shin Jae.
The one who created deal structures no one else could even imagine...
And pulled off a last-minute upset in the K-Finance acquisition.
Named by a prominent legal journal as one of Asia's attorneys to watch.
The ace corporate advisor, Kang Shin Jae.
That's the person I chose as my partner.
That's a shame. My specialty is sex crimes now.
So if you're ever a victim, be sure to call me.
I'll be a much better partner to you then.
How are your ex-husbands doing?
I doubt they're doing very well.
Thanks to the alimony my mother wrung out of them.
You'd best be careful too, Mr. Baek. Stay off my mother's radar.
(New Free Support Program)
There.
Are you satisfied now?
I told you, I always get what I want.
And just so you know, don't bother making room for me at Haeil.
The view from my office is much better, anyway.
I told you you'd change your mind.
After just one autopsy, the smell clings to all of my hair.
Cigarette smoke is nauseating, but this covers it up pretty well.
Want to try some?
Let me get straight to the point.
You're more interesting...
than I gave you credit for, Yoon Ra Young.
That's the most audacious request I've ever heard.
It's not a request. It's a deal. Either take the deal, or forget it.
But you have to decide right here, right now.
If you refuse, I have to move on to my next option.
All right.
You do understand exactly what I'm asking, don't you?
I'm not drunk.
If I swap the DNA samples for you,
you'll take on my divorce case. Right?
You're a lawyer, though.
Doesn't this request... No, this deal.
Doesn't it weigh on your conscience?
I'm not exactly planning on going to heaven.
What about you?
My life is already a living hell.
Child custody, division of assets...
I'll get you everything you want, Hong Yeon Hui.
But do you even know who my husband is?
He's a sitting prosecutor.
I don't care who he is.
All right, then.
Then let's say we have a deal.
I'll choose the celebratory drinks.
Wasn't the crime scene reenactment scheduled for next week?
How should I know? We just do as we're told.
Hey, he's here! He's here!
- Just a moment... - He's here.
Come on, guys.
Is it true you murdered the victim because he sexually assaulted you?
Was it really sexual assault this time?
Weren't you trying to intentionally approach the victim again?
How did you know the victim?
Why go to the victim's house?
Don't you feel any remorse toward the victim's family? Say something!
- Let's see your face! - Hey, why hide your face? Come on!
There's no need to be nervous.
Just reenact what you told us. Exactly what happened that day.
Do you remember what you said in your statement?
Want me to recite it for you?
So you don't get confused about your own statement.
It's all a lie, isn't it?
I told you to stay away.
It was Connect, wasn't it?
How you met Kang Eun Seok, and how you killed Reporter Lee...
It was all through Connect In, the sex trade app.
(Suspect)
Seon Kyu.
I need to speak with you for a moment.
Sure.
(Suspect)
I don't know what you're talking about.
Connect In? What's that? I've never heard of it.
This is Reporter Lee's phone, the one you said you threw away.
And on it, I found...
who really killed Reporter Lee.
So what? This doesn't mean I didn't kill him.
The phone...
- The detectives kept asking, so... - This is as far as I go.
This is all I can do for you.
If you take one more step, there's no turning back.
We're all set. Let's begin.
The choice is yours.
Are you going to turn back with me?
Or walk off that cliff alone?
You went into the living room.
Okay, you got the knife from the kitchen.
And then what?
What did you say you did next?
Yoo Jeong, run! Get out of here!
And then?
Then what?
I can't do this.
It wasn't me.
I didn't do it.
What do you mean? Are you saying you didn't kill him?
They made me do it.
- I didn't kill him. - Who's "they"?
- I really didn't do it! - Hey!
Are you messing with us right now?
You think this is some kind of a joke?
- Let's get this right. Hurry up. - Are you getting all of this?
Excuse me?
Despite the right to recant anytime during the investigation,
the police are coercing a suspect who is doing just that.
Are you getting all of that on camera?
Did you murder Reporter Lee here on that day?
It wasn't me.
I didn't kill him.
So...
is there any need to continue?
Darn it.
All right, everyone out.
Come on, let's move!
Let's go. Come with me.
Is this a strategy, or do you really believe her?
We'll see, won't we?
You know how solid the physical evidence is.
Everything is so conclusive.
Don't you find that a little strange?
Do you have any evidence besides her testimony...
You of all people should understand why I can't say more.
- I knew it was too good to be true. - Sir.
What?
The unknown DNA from Lee's place. Did you run it against his contacts?
What, you're hoping it's a match for the real killer?
What's gotten into you? You're not a rookie, are you?
Suspects always flip their stories. It's common before the prosecution.
Gosh.
Hello, Detective Gu Seon Kyu, Mujin Police.
The sample I submitted yesterday. Can I get a rush on the analysis?
Connect In is a secret app for sex trafficking.
Reporter Lee was writing and expose on it. That day...
That's enough for now.
You've been through enough today.
Attorney Yoon.
Those people are very dangerous. They won't just let this go.
Nothing's going to happen to you.
I won't let them.
We have a long road ahead of us. So we need to keep our strength up.
What do you want? Korean, Chinese, Western?
- Korean. - Korean it is. What about dessert?
Ice cream.
I'll get us the biggest and most expensive kind.
So you have that to look forward to.
The suspect, Ms. Jo, who surrendered for the murder of Reporter Lee...
has reportedly denied all charges...
during a crime scene reenactment conducted by police this morning.
While the police focus their inquiry...
on why Ms. Jo recanted her testimony,
they also plan to conduct further investigation.
They will also analyse the evidence and the confession's credibility...
to ensure the investigation proceeds without...
Excuse me. We need your cooperation.
Please lower your mask.
(Kim Mi Jeong, Cleaner at Hankuk University Hospital)
- Thank you for your cooperation. - For goodness' sake.
Am I free to go now?
Yes, Attorney Yoon.
Everything's clear so far.
Thanks, Do Jun.
I need you for a few more days until she's moved to detention.
You sent Do Jun to the hospital?
I had to take precautions.
These are Reporter Lee's murderers we're talking about.
Good call. What's the word from the police?
They seem to think she's just backing out of her confession.
We need evidence to turn the tables. Evidence against Connect.
If only we could use that photo from Jun Hyeok's phone as evidence.
Even so, that doesn't prove Connect was behind Lee's murder.
Now Yoo Jeong has changed her mind, we'll soon learn about Connect.
If we can find out what that app is and shove it in their faces,
the police will have no choice but to act.
Yes?
Attorney Hwang, you have a visitor.
I don't have any meetings scheduled. Who is it?
She said you'd know her. Her name is Lee Seon Hwa.
Ms. Lee Seon Hwa.
This place is really nice.
Do you really help people like me here?
If you need our help, we do.
I don't know.. I think you ladies need my help more than I need yours.
I know a girl who works for Connect.
How much will you give me if I put you in touch with her?
What's your price?
- Three. - Three grand?
Are you kidding me?
Thirty grand.
But why are you here alone?
Is your contact on board with cooperating with us?
The 30 grand is just for her phone number.
Persuading her is your job.
What? Thirty grand for just a phone number?
- That's ridiculous. - Take it or leave it.
I'll pay it. Thirty grand.
Write down your account number. I'll wire it right now.
Now here's someone who gets it.
No way! How can you trust her?
Here.
- Shin Jae, 30 grand is too much... - It's sent. Go ahead and check.
(Deposit from Kang Shin Jae: 30,000 dollars)
Here.
Gosh, I've never met a cool girl like her before.
Pleasure doing business with you all.
Just so we're clear,
that 30 grand I just gave you isn't for the phone number.
It's to buy your silence.
You leaked your source's number to us.
What's to stop you from selling them our information for more money?
What kind of person do you take me for?
I don't care what kind of person you are.
What's important is that this money is our insurance policy.
So if you ever feel tempted to side with Connect, remember this.
I have a complete record of the money you took from me.
From what I've seen, they go crazy if anyone leaks their secrets.
Welcome aboard. You're in the same boat as us now.
- The number's unavailable... - She's not picking up?
Let's just leave a message for now.
Contact her by any means necessary. Tell her we'll meet her demands.
(Hankuk University Hospital)
(Nurses' station)
Do Jun.
No one's been in or near the room except for the medical staff.
Just as you instructed, we brought in her meals separately.
Thank you.
Yoo Jeong, are you asleep?
Wake up. I have good news.
We might have someone who's willing to testify for us.
They might even have info about Connect that you don't.
And look. A big tub of fancy ice cream.
We won't leave a bite. We're going to finish it all, just us two.
Yoo Jeong?
Come on, wake up.
Yoo Jeong, let's wake up.
Yoo Jeong.
Yoo Jeong?
Yoo Jeong!
Yoo Jeong, please wake up.
Yoo Jeong! Yoo Jeong!
A doctor! Please, get a doctor...
Oh, Yoo Jeong...
Are you the next of kin?
- Yes. - Please confirm her identity.
Oh, Yoo Jeong!
Yoo Jeong...
Yoo Jeong... Oh, Yoo Jeong...
Yoo Jeong, please wake up...
Those jerks did this.
This is definitely Connect's work. She recanted, so they silenced her.
Are you positive no outsiders had access to her?
I don't know. I'm not sure.
Did you check the CCTV footage?
It looks like...
the drugs in the treatment room were tampered with.
The culprit?
Jo Yoo Jeong herself.
- Are you saying it was suicide? - What? That's ridiculous.
She had a procedure this afternoon. We'll need the autopsy,
but the missing medication matches what was found by her bed.
Motive?
She had no reason to kill herself all of a sudden.
You would think.
The pressure of what happened today must've been immense.
Whether her story was true or not,
that's a lot for anyone to handle.
All of you, please just go.
Go. Please, just go. I said get out!
Yoo Jeong never wanted to report it in the first place.
She said she didn't want the lawyers involved anymore.
Her lawyers and I... We're the ones who killed her.
We're the ones who killed her.
We killed her...
Tomorrow will be mostly clear nationwide.
It'll be chilly in the morning, with a big temperature swing.
- That was the weather forecast. - We have some breaking news.
The suspect in Reporter Lee's murder identified as Ms. Jo,
has reportedly died by suicide.
Police say Ms. Jo was a patient at the hospital,
and was found dead in her hospital room this afternoon.
Reporting from the hospital where suspect Ms. Jo was being treated.
Ms. Jo reportedly evaded the watch of police and staff this afternoon.
And it's been confirmed that she obtained a controlled substance.
During a crime scene reenactment this morning,
Ms. Jo had completely denied the charges against her.
It appears she couldn't handle the resulting psychological pressure...
and resorted to this drastic measure.
This was Oh Min Young for SMBS.
And now for our next story.
(Violent Crimes Unit 2)
(The suspect denied the murder, changing her story...)
(However, at 8:10pm, at the hospital, )
(she was found dead.)
The lab results are in.
Thanks.
(Exhibit 1 DNA doesn't match 3 or 4.)
(Exhibit 1 and Exhibit 3, Yoon Ra Young: DNA mismatch)
(Exhibit 1 and Exhibit 4, Hwang Hyun Jin: DNA mismatch)
Oh, about that unidentified DNA from Lee Jun Hyeok's place.
It was his junior reporter's.
So there's no evidence, not a hair, to back up Jo Yoo Jeong's story.
She's just a kid, but she told such a big lie.
She must have panicked under pressure.
So, stop with the pointless theories and just close the case, you idiot.
(We recommend dropping the charges under "no right to prosecute.")
(No right to prosecute)
(Prosecutor Park Je Yeol)
I'm so sorry.
I...
I made things so hard for Yoo Jeong.
On the anniversary day, why do you think Yoo Jeong...
came looking for all of you?
I kept wondering about that.
A girl who hated trials and lawyers, and was acting out...
If she was turning herself in, she would've gone to the police.
So why did she go to that hotel?
The truth is,
I think she was relying on you, on all of you lawyers.
She was just a kid who couldn't rely on adults.
I guess it was her only way to ask.
For you to save her, to help her.
It's Yoo Jeong's suicide note.
She left it for you.
(Inpatient guide)
(To Attorney Yoon Ra Young)
To Attorney Yoon Ra Young.
From the very beginning until now,
I've actually been very grateful.
Since you were always on my side, I have one last favour to ask.
Please protect my sister.
It wasn't suicide. She was driven to it.
Those jerks changed their target to Yoo Jeong's sister.
To make sure Yoo Jeong would break.
We even had someone watching her since the reenactment.
So how on earth did they get to her?
We underestimated them.
I told her nothing bad would happen.
That I wouldn't let it.
On the day of the crime scene reenactment,
she was terrified of what Connect might do...
and that's what I told Yoo Jeong.
Ra Young.
I'm the one who failed Yoo Jeong.
Your sister's a real beauty.
Right.
You need to protect your sister. What if she ends up like you?
Your sister's life is in your hands.
Don't you get it?
I was wrong. Please, just spare me this once.
(Park Je Yeol)
That's up to you, isn't it?
Do you not understand...
what I'm saying?
What are you guys doing here at this hour?
I had a feeling you'd be here.
See? What did I tell you? It was obvious.
There has to be something we missed about Connect.
Whether she meant to or not,
Yoo Jeong must've let something slip.
I can't let her go down like this.
I...
wanted to be the kind of person that we so desperately needed.
To people like us back then, I'd say,
"It's not your fault. You don't believe me?"
"Then we'll fight for you. We'll win."
"No matter what,"
we'll be on your side."
"And that you too..."
"deserve to be happy."
That's what I wanted to tell them.
But why is it that back then, and even now,
it feels like nothing's changed at all?
I can't forgive them!
I'm going to make those jerks pay.
No, I can't let them get away with this.
Connect? What a joke.
Just you watch.
I'll follow those scumbags to the depths of the fiery pit.
Okay, let's be rational about this.
We don't have a client for this case anymore.
On top of that, we have no intel on Connect.
The one thing we do know is that these guys are extremely dangerous.
So, no one could blame us if we were to walk away right now.
Realistically speaking.
So, what's it going to be?
Do we keep going?
Or do we stop?
All right. Then I guess we'll see this through.
You said we don't have any intel,
but if we can't get to them,
we just make them come to us.
What are you planning?
If they want to kill me, I say bring it on.
I'm not going down alone.
When did you get home?
Just a little while ago.
You should've woken me up.
What's all this?
(Sunchang Meju Eel)
You've just seemed so worn out lately.
It's about Jo Yoo Jeong, isn't it?
I just can't seem to shake it.
I figured as much.
I brought you something fortifying before you left.
But you just got off your shift.
You must be tired too.
I just had to grill it. It was no trouble at all.
Thank you. I'll enjoy it.
Hey, I've been thinking.
Maybe we should go back to the clinic?
Let's try to have a baby again.
IVF, whatever it takes,
let's give it another try.
Thank you.
- And I'm sorry. - For what?
(Mujin Memorial Park)
(The Late Jo Yoo Jeong)
(Incoming Call)
Han Min Seo's still not picking up?
No. She's not picking up for you either.
I can't even try convincing her if I can't get a hold of her.
Try calling Lee Seon Hwa. Ask her for an address or something.
Yes, got it.
What time is Ra Young on?
At seven, in a bit.
But I don't think we can watch it together.
I have a doctor's appointment.
All right. I'm on my way now. Okay.
- I'm taking off. - Okay, good luck.
This is Detective Gu Seon Kyu with Violent Crimes Unit Two.
Detective Gu Seon Kyu?
This is Park Je Yeol from the Mujin Prosecutor's Office.
We've met before, haven't we?
- Yes. - About the Jo Yoo Jeong case.
There's something missing from your report.
The identity of the initial caller who reported the case to 911.
Okay, I'll look into it and get back to you.
Please do.
- That was Prosecutor Park, right? - Yes.
Actually, I already got the file from 911.
Turns out it was from a payphone. And there's no CCTV nearby.
We could've just closed this case, but he's making us run in circles.
I think someone's hurt. I heard a scream.
It's a house in front of the park on Seongil-gu, Jungam-ro.
- Why bother identifying them? - Play it again.
What?
I think someone's hurt. I heard a scream.
It's a house in front of the park on Seongil-gu, Jungam-ro.
The person you called is unavailable.
Leave a message after the tone.
(Honey, are you okay? If you can't make it, let me know.)
Ms. Hwang Hyun Jin?
Yes.
Your husband isn't here yet?
I'm so sorry, but I'll have to reschedule.
A public interest firm specialising in representing sex crime victims.
Joining us is Attorney Yoon Ra Young of LnJ.
- Welcome. - Hello. I'm Yoon Ra Young of LnJ.
I heard the three of you at the firm went to college together.
I'm curious how you all decided to start a firm helping victims.
Would you mind doing a quick search for "sex crime law firm"?
This is a first for me, using my phone on a live broadcast.
But since she asked, I hope our viewers will understand.
(Juvenile crime acquittal, Yes, you can.)
- What do you see? - It's mostly ads and promotions.
That's right. Most promise favourable results..
For the perpetrators.
They boast about how many times they've gotten charges dropped...
and how much they've gotten sentences reduced.
So when victims go online for help,
the first thing they see are ads like that.
That's why we saw a desperate need for a firm that helps only victims.
We wanted victims to know we'd fight for them, not the perpetrators.
We knew we had to get that message out there.
So that's why you created LnJ, a firm dedicated to victims.
Yes. We wanted victims to know that no matter what happened,
they are absolutely not alone.
Because what victims truly want is to have someone on their side,
to listen to their story, and to fight alongside them.
That's why we named our firm LnJ,
which stands for "Listen and Join."
To listen to victims and join their cause.
This is Attorney Hwang Hyun Jin from LnJ.
Lee Seon Hwa gave me your contact information.
I want to help you.
Now, we have to talk about your most recent case.
The case was closed when the suspect suddenly died,
but many questions still remain.
In this case, during the crime scene reenactment,
the suspect recanted her confession, saying she didn't kill the victim.
The investigators saw it as her simply changing her story,
but I believe that's the most crucial part of this case.
What specifically makes you think so?
Because the voice the suspect tried to raise until the very end...
was ultimately never truly heard.
I believe this is still happening to others as we speak.
Even at this very moment, there are people who are too scared...
and are suffering all on their own.
That's why, through this broadcast,
I have a message for every single one of them.
We are waiting to hear your stories.
So we can fight alongside you.
There's only one thing we need.
And what would that be?
Connect.
Connect? As in a connection?
Yes. We're weak when we're alone,
but we find strength when we connect with one another.
Our goal going forward is clear.
It's to connect, to form a connection.
If we can't get to them, we just make them come to us.
Hey, Do Jun. From this moment on,
don't let Ra Young out of your sight.
Connect. A connection.
It sounds like you're referring to solidarity among victims,
What kind of victims are you referring to, specifically?
Like victims of sexual assault, harassment, domestic abuse, and...
those exploited by large-scale sex trafficking rings.
(Han Min Seo)
- Hello? - This is Han Min Seo.
I'm so glad you finally called.
Can we meet and talk in person?
I heard from Han Min Seo. She said she's coming by tomorrow.
We have only one goal. To connect.
- Are you all right? - Our real fight begins now.
If you're watching this right now,
please reach out to us.
We will take your hand.
(Honour)
This is a warning. A warning that they know about it.
You know what gives me this kind of feeling?
That green hoodie?
This all started when we got close to Connect.
You wouldn't happen to know anything about the seal, would you?
Who could've sent us this card?
Han Min Seo is our only way into Connect.
Should we try tracing the server first?
- I'm in. - I saw one of the VIPs.
A Connect user.