♪Wandering alone♪
♪Walking far by dusk-lit streets♪
♪Your eyes are as cold as clouds♪
♪Faintly coming into view♪
♪The city lights♪
♪Lit up that single moment♪
♪I can't hide or stop missing you♪
♪I can't forget those moments♪
♪Losing you♪
♪Like the seasons in my memory♪
♪Without winter♪
♪Walking down the long, dark street♪
♪Snow will never fall again♪
♪Our old story was torn♪
♪Into scattered pieces♪
♪Replaying every single scene♪
♪After you left♪
♪As if our documentary♪
♪Lost winter♪
♪The breeze speaks of good times♪
♪Pure white devotion♪
♪Send out a letter♪
♪Carrying my longing♪
=The Double Game=
=Episode 8=
Land reclamation...
(Post)
Should I tell Lu Tingxiao
before posting?
Forget it.
I did what I was supposed to do.
Why be afraid of him?
Tingxiao,
how's it going with the investors
pulling out?
It's settled now.
That was a huge mess.
How did you fix it?
I refunded all their money.
Refunded?
Who said you could do that?
I worked so hard to raise that money.
You just refunded it so easily?
If it could be refunded,
wouldn't I have done it myself?
Do you know how much that was?
You've drained
the company's working capital.
If I don't refund it,
once this blows up,
the company will be done for.
Do I need you to teach me business?
This whole thing
shouldn't have been left to you.
Jianchuan,
look.
Lianxin Island is under seizure.
- What?
- Look.
(Lianxin Island placed under seizure
over illegal reclamation)
- Hey.
- Sis.
Did you see the big news alert?
Let me see.
(Lianxin Island placed under seizure
over illegal reclamation)
What?
This isn't right.
I just posted the video.
I just hit post.
How did it
get officially seized already?
Someone must've reported it.
What do we do now?
(Jin Chanchan exposes
Lianxin Island reclamation)
Jin Chanchan did it.
(Jin Chanchan?)
(Wen Yan?)
Lu Jianchuan,
what is going on?
The island was seized!
What did you promise me?
Leave us.
(Chairman of Linhai Group)
It's seized.
(Lin Youqiang)
What about my money?
Will you pay it back?
How much money have I made you?
Without me,
would you be where you are today?
Cut the act with me.
You've dragged the development out
for years.
Then let's go
our separate ways.
Is that your plan to keep
the best part?
I'm asking you.
Did you bring in Jin Chanchan?
Did you supply the report?
Then you leaked some dirt for show.
You think I don't know that?
What Jin Chanchan?
I've never heard of them.
Don't make things up
and pin this mess on me.
You're not behind it?
Then prove it to me.
Jerk.
I'm the scapegoat now?
Today,
I'll drag that Jin Chanchan out
and tear them apart.
Lu Jianchuan,
don't forget.
Lianxin Island
was mine to begin with.
Don't think
some tourist add-ons and fake papers
make you the boss.
If you push me too far,
I'll expose everything.
Then we're done for good.
Yan.
Go, now. Go.
Lin Youqiang's inside waiting for you.
Go, now!
Don't be scared.
I know his daughter.
He won't do anything to me.
Don't worry.
Yan.
Lin Youqiang.
Is violence the only way
you solve things?
So, you're Jin Chanchan.
You're the one who's been
spreading lies to smear me.
Lies?
Are they really lies?
All these years on Lianxin Island,
you've conned money, land, and hearts.
You even drove people to death.
Do you think trashing this place
can cover up what you've done?
What proof do you have?
Lin Youqiang,
all these years,
you've lived well off blood money.
Haven't you had nightmares?
The people you ruined
are all watching you.
What are you talking about?
I don't get a word of it.
You lied to outsiders
and even to your own family.
Your own child
was sent to the Lu family for gain.
You could've been a decent man,
but you chose Lu Jianchuan's pawn.
You...
Who are you?
I'm one of the people you ruined.
Long time no see.
Dad.
Zhi'er?
So, you're Jin Chanchan.
That's right.
Oh, Jin Chanchan is you.
Then I can relax.
Zhi'er,
what you just said was a joke, right?
I wasn't joking with you.
My dear girl.
Hear me out, okay?
I'm not your daughter.
I'm just a tool for your marriage deal.
A puppet that you used
and can be tossed aside anytime.
Do you know how I've lived
all these years in the Lu family?
Silly girl.
Yes.
I've failed you all these years.
Tell me what I can do to make up for it.
I'll agree to anything.
I want you in prison.
Zhi'er,
if I found you today,
the Lus can find you tomorrow.
Fine.
At that time,
I'll stick to one story:
You were behind all of this.
Let's see if Lu Jianchuan
starts doubting your loyalty.
I really underestimated you.
I didn't expect you to be behind this.
It looks like your alliance is fragile.
You're right.
It is fragile.
So,
I have to make
some extra preparations.
Chairman Lin.
Tingxiao,
you found this place too.
Perfect timing.
This girl
was actually Jin Chanchan.
She's been trying to set us up.
This voice recorder is the proof.
Is that so?
That's really low.
Then what will you do?
I know right from wrong.
Zhi'er is my daughter,
but she's bad for both our families.
So, I'll do what has to be done.
Lin Youqiang,
you're such a beast.
Tingxiao,
you saw it yourself.
This girl still won't change.
Handle this
however you want.
Handle it however I want?
Yeah.
It's all up to you.
This...
♪This door♪
♪Lets in the sky outside♪
♪With a voice even lighter♪
♪Than how you just greeted me♪
♪I know now♪
♪What the chill in my body means♪
♪The moment salt hits the wound♪
♪My heart still beats so naively♪
♪To complete♪
♪A joy that needs no brave pretense♪
♪How cruel sincerity can be♪
♪Like a door with no key♪
♪Maybe you just passed by♪
♪The tears in my eyes♪
♪You looked like you had nothing to say♪
♪Then got so good at being cold♪
♪That's why a smile feels so precious♪
♪Maybe you just passed by♪
♪The tears burned into my heart♪
♪Let's say silence was just for show♪
♪Even if I've grown another year♪