Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.xyz or dramacool.club
Previously on
Seducing Drake Palma.
I’m really sorry, Alys.
I’m here now.
I’m already here, see?
You don’t understand.
I’m done.
I heard you and Drake broke up.
I’m so sorry to hear…for you.
Definitely happy for me.
Aunt, Daddy, don’t tell me…
Oh my gosh, it’s in
19th floor, too.
I really insisted that
Cy should buy you this unit.
Lord, I knew it. Be careful what
you wish for ‘cause you just might get it.
Alys?
Will you eat breakfast with me?
Good morning, Zy!
Tripp!
What’s your passcode?
Come on, let’s eat.
Come here,
I’ll whisper it to you.
What?
1131?
Why did you shout it out?
Ouch.
Drake…
I changed my mind.
I can’t let you hate me.
I’ll make you love me again.
I know we broke up, but I
feel like kissing you right now.
I feel like kissing you right
now, but I won’t force you.
Lord, is this a test to
see if I’ve moved on?
Because if it is, my standing
might already be failing.
I won’t kiss you if
you don’t want me to...
or not.
Lord, did You know already?
I failed.
Is there a retake?
What do I do?
Someone else might slip.
Here.
Lord, that was
a fast retake.
Why are You
testing me like this?
This is too much.
It’s fine, you can use my shirt.
Tss.
Let’s go.
Is he really my ex?
Why does it feel like he’s still
my boyfriend from the way we act?
Alys!
Coming.
I love you, Drake Palma!
It’s almost a month
since I last came here.
It looks better.
I like it simpler.
Is your family mad at me?
Huh?
Please tell them that I’m sorry.
No.
I’ll tell them personally
that I’m sorry.
No, Drake. That’s over.
Past is past, right?
I know.
- I know, but?
- But...
It’s over, Drake.
The damage has been done.
Even if you’re sorry,
you already did it.
So let’s just leave it, okay?
And besides, a lot
has changed.
Those things that changed,
does that include
your feelings, then?
Drake!
Um…I’ll just get some water.
You still haven’t answered
my question, Alys.
Answer me.
Huh?
What question?
I said –
do you still feel the
same way about me,
or have you forgotten how it
feels like to be in love with me?
Huh?
Alys Zyril, I have all
the time in the world.
Are you gonna answer me or not?
Uh…it’s just that, Drake…
What?
Of course I still love
you, but I’m tired.
Don’t you get it?
I just want to be honest with you,
because you deserve honesty.
I don’t want to hurt you.
Is it Tripp?
No, Drake.
Tripp and I are just friends.
Like I told you—
you’re the one I
still love, okay?
I just don’t want this anymore.
The reason, Drake—
the real reason, Drake—
I got tired of you.
Oh no, Drake.
Alys, I’m gonna ask
you one last time.
Do you still want me or not?
I know that I’m not the most
patient person in the world.
So Alys, if you don’t want
me anymore, I’ll quit on you.
Tss.
Forget it.
You know, Alys…
I really love you.
But like you,
I also get tired.
What have I done?
Hey.
Hmm?
I’ve been talking here for a
while, and you’re not even listening.
Sorry, I was just thinking.
About?
My cousin?
Yes.
That took a while, huh?
Looks like you’ve been replaying
your memories with Drake since day one.
Stop it.
You know, Alys,
Drake is one complicated man.
Even I...
don’t understand him
most of the time.
I know.
I know very well how
complicated Drake is.
But why is it like that?
Even if I know how
complicated he is,
the feeling is still there.
I still love him so much.
We dated for months.
And I know I can’t just
easily forget what we had.
But then, what’s the
sense of a relationship
if you can’t even
understand each other, right?
You knew after all.
But what’s your decision?
Decision about what?
Alys, Drake is my cousin.
We talk.
And I know
he wants you back.
What can you say about that?
I’m tired, and so is he.
So I guess that means
we both have to move on.
Maybe.
Right?
Are you sure about that?
Maybe this is right.
Like they say, “if it’s
meant to be, it will be.”
Maybe it’s better not to force
something that’s not meant to happen.
Let’s go.
Let’s go where?
You’ll see. Stand up.
Where exactly?
You trust me, right?
Let’s go.
Tripp, why are we even here?
Come on.
You’re so mean.
Zyril, let’s go, hurry!
Why won’t you just tell me?
Just say it.
Trust me on this, alright?
You’re so annoying.
Tripp, what kind
of trip is this, hmm?
Didn’t you say
you’re tired of Drake?
So?
What does that
have to do with this?
Since you’re tired of Drake,
I can start courting you.
Tripp!
Hey!
Hey, you, Tripp!
You’re really talking nonsense!
Oh no, Drake’s here.
Lord, what’s happening?
My God!
St. Collette, I know I’ve
been a bad best friend to Aya,
but why are you
punishing me like this?
Drake.
I’m going to court Alys.
That’s fine with you, right?
You like her?
Good luck.
She likes breaking hearts.
Maybe she won’t break mine.
Alys...
Don’t mind him, okay?
Come on.
Let’s go.
Don’t mind him.
“She likes breaking hearts.”
Wow. Is it me?
Me, of all people?
Don’t mind him.
Come on.
Me?
Let’s just go.
Zy...
Are you okay?
Why?
What does he even know?
Does he know how many
times he’s made me cry?
He doesn’t even have a clue.
Here.
You’ve been crying nonstop,
I thought you said you
were tired of Drake?
Then why are you still crying?
I don’t even know.
The truth is, I’m hurt because
the person I love is mad at me.
But of course, it’s not
like I can tell that to Tripp.
Zyril, don’t cry over
him anymore, okay?
I’m already here.
You’re right.
I don’t know anymore.
But thanks, Tripp.
It’s nothing.
So, you want to eat something?
My treat.
Really? Your treat?
Yes.
Why are you surprised?
Because you rarely treat anyone.
You’re such a cheapskate.
Really?
For real.
Don’t you want it?
No, I do.
Wow, Tripp’s treating me.
There.
You finally smiled.
Wow, so all it
takes is a treat.
You’re so cheap.
Oh.
Hey, how dare you!
Who wouldn’t be happy
when you’re stingy?
You rarely treat anyone.
Wow!
“Zyril, get me this!”
“Zyril, get me that!”
Well, don’t cry anymore.
Let’s wipe your tears.
- There’s still some tears here.
- There’s nothing.
There’s nothing.
It’s just eye gunk now.
There’s still some. Right there.
Sigh.
How many times have you
cried this month already?
Haven’t you reached
your quota yet?
Gosh, I already went over.
I can’t blame Drake.
Maybe that’s just how I am.
What now, Zy? My treat has
a deadline, you know.
Fine.
Seriously, Tripp?
It’s hot outside and
you still want coffee?
Right, Tripp?
Don’t you want it?
They’ve got cold drinks.
Well, you’re right.
- Good afternoon.
- What can I get for you?
Uhm...
How about you?
What’s your order?
- Hey...
- Hmm.
I rarely treat. So if I were
you, I’d make the most of it.
For sure.
Miss, what’s your most
expensive food item?
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.xyz or dramacool.club
Wow!
You can check down here.
Okay, I will.
You said make the
most of it, so I will.
This might be the last time
because of your stinginess.
Geez, I just wanted
to make you happy.
Really?
So I have to be sad
so you’ll always treat me?
Wow!
Miss, one strawberry shortcake,
and a large strawberry
frappe, please.
Okay.
And then…
Hey, that’s enough! You’re
getting way too much!
You told me to make
the most of it, right?
Fine, go ahead.
- Order what you want.
- Alright.
And then this one,
and this one, too.
Okay.
- Thank you!
- Welcome, ma’am.
Thank you.
Why didn’t you order anything?
Are you full, or are you holding back
since I went all out with expensive orders?
I’m already full…
just by looking at you.
There you go again
with your pick-up lines.
No, I’m still thinking about
what to get, but I’ll order.
Tripp!
Oh, why do you look so
surprised to see me?
Who wouldn’t be surprised
seeing a walking octopus?
Oh, you’re also here, Alys.
Obviously.
Gosh, maybe Shaira has
a secret crush on Tripp.
I can feel it.
Tripp, why don’t you join us?
Like old times.
Uh, I’ll pass.
But why? It’s been so long
since we bonded.
I’ll pass for now.
Come on, please?
For old times’ sake.
Um, maybe next time, Shai.
Alys and I have somewhere to go.
Yes, we need to go somewhere.
- Drake.
- Drake!
They don’t want to come with us.
Let’s just go?
Wait!
We’ll just join you.
I forgot, we already ordered
but it hasn’t arrived yet.
Right, Tripp?
Oh, yes.
Where are you seated, Shai?
Over there. Let’s go!
Shall we?
How about Sir Cruz,
do you still remember him?
The long-haired teacher?
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.xyz or dramacool.club
Yeah!
Who’s balding now?
I saw him last time.
No way!
- He’s still at Brenford High?
- Yeah.
Oh, my gosh!
What was I thinking,
joining them here?
Their topic is making
me feel out of place.
Anyway, remember, he’d do
recitations, and if you got it right,
he’d give you candy
from Thailand?
Yes, that’s right.
What was our favorite
flavor again, Drake?
- Taro.
- Taro?
Maybe Shaira really is
a better match for Drake.
They definitely have similarities.
Are you okay?
Of course, I’m fine.
Oh, by the way, how
was your debut, Alys?
You didn’t invite me.
I thought we were friends.
Huh?
Well, it was fine.
Aww, just “fine”?
Maybe because Drake
didn’t arrive on time, huh?
I’m sorry. He had to
attend to my needs.
So he really went to see Shaira,
that’s why he left me on my debut.
All along, my suspicion
was right.
Hope everything went well despite
Drake not being there to escort you.
It’s fine.
It’s over, anyway.
There’s nothing we can do.
And besides, it turned out okay.
I was happy.
See? Past is past,
so move on already.
And am I right, you
and Drake broke up?
Yes.
See, Drake?
I told you, we’re really
meant to be.
Tss.
Well, anyway, since
you and Drake are done,
we can be friends now.
Huh?
Yeah!
You know,
I didn’t like you before because
you were still with Drake,
but now that you’re not,
we can be friends.
I’m Shaira Silos.
And I’m only mean to people who
are a threat to me and my hubby.
Um, I’m Alys.
And I’m not a threat
to you and Drake.
Not anymore.
Well, that’s great news.
I don’t really have friends here
aside from Tripp and Drake.
All the girls hate me since
I’m close to these two Palmas.
But we’re friends now, okay?
Okay.
See, Drake?
You don’t have to be
so grumpy anymore.
We can be friends with your ex.
Tss.
Are you okay, Alys?
Of course, I’m fine.
Are you sure? Look at your
cake, it’s all squished.
Oh no.
You’re so cute!
Oh my gosh!
Here, you can have my cake.
I haven’t touched it, anyway.
Good thing I ordered it.
Thanks, Tripp!
Of course, anything for you.
I’m trying to impress you.
Since I’m courting you.
Oh, you’re such a suck-up!
Oh my gosh!
You’re so cute!
Aren’t they cute, Drake?
Anyway, I’m having a barbecue
party later. Wanna come?
Huh?
It’s just a barbecue party.
And we can go swimming, too.
Sure.
Oh no, why did I say yes?
Am I becoming a masochist?
Do I really want to see
Shaira and Drake together?
Yehey, so exciting!
Where do you live?
Antipolo Heights.
In Antipolo?
Yeah. I only stayed in the
condo because of Drake.
But I really miss my house,
so I’m going home later.
You’ll come, okay?
Minus the overacting, being all posh,
and being territorial with Drake,
Shaira actually seems nice.
Oh no, sorry, I really don’t
know how to go to Antipolo.
What are you talking about?
Tripp knows my house.
You’ll fetch her, right?
Fine.
You’re really grumpy, Tripp.
Just move on already.
How many times do I have
to tell you, I don’t like you.
How am I supposed to forget
when you keep reminding me?
And besides, you were
just a puppy love.
Alys is my true love.
Come on, Zy, let’s
head back to Brenford.
Bye, Shaira. Bye, Drake.
Don’t forget later, okay?
I’ll be expecting you.
Are you really okay with this?
Even if you don’t come,
I’ll just make an excuse.
It’s fine. I don’t have
plans later, anyway.
Alys, I know your IQ’s
a little on the edge.
But don’t lower your pride, too.
- Wow, you’re really something, huh!
- Ouch!
- Of course, I know!
- That hurts!
Whatever, okay? That’s it.
Oh, Sir is here.
I’m heading in now.
Later, at my place, okay?
Don’t be late!
- Bye.
- Don’t make me wait later.
- Thanks for the treat.
- Bye.
Mom, I’m here at the house,
but I’ll sleep at the condo.
I’m going out with Tripp.
Nanny, if Mom looks for
me, tell her I’m with Tripp.
She knows. Okay?
Alright.
Tripp arrived early.
- Okay, Nanny, I’ll go ahead.
- Okay.
Tripp!
Drake, what are you doing here?
I don’t wanna see you
flirting with my cousin.
Have some decency, Alys.
Drake!
Are you mad at me?
Why would I?
What makes you think
I’m mad at you?
Because you haven’t
looked at me all this time.
Get over yourself, Alys.
We’re over.
You said it yourself.
Where’s that Tripp, anyway?
What time is it?
- Hey, Alys!
- Ahh! Son of a–!
You get startled too easily.
Sorry, I went inside already.
Your gate was open.
So, shall we?
Are you good?
My God, what is it
with these Palmas?
They’re way too hot.
So, let’s go?
Okay. Hold on.
- Ouch!
- What?
What happened to you?
Are you okay?
My leg’s cramped, it went numb.
This one?
Here?
Better?
Hop on.
Alys!
Are you hopping on or
do I have to drag you?
Hold on.
- You’re so agitated.
- Ouch.
Fine, I’m getting on.
Hop on.
Ouch.
Don’t choke me!
Forget it, just walk.
- Tripp?
- Mmm?
Can I ask you about
you and Shaira?
Huh?
I said I wanna know
more about Shaira.
That’s so random.
Why are you asking me about her?
Nothing. I’m just curious.
What else do you want to know?
Didn’t I tell you I
courted her before?
So what?
What else happened?
You’re so nosy!
Do you know that?
You’re so grumpy!
I’m just asking.
Here, get off for a second.
What else?
This is annoying. I don’t want to think
about it, and you keep bringing it up.
But why?
Do you still love Shaira,
that’s why you’re hurting?
You know what, Zyril Perez,
Shaira dumped me
ages ago. That’s over.
And at someone this handsome?
Do you think I would sulk
that long for something like that?
So what, that’s it?
You didn’t even
take her seriously.
- You really are such a playboy!
- Ouch.
Would I still be a playboy if you’re
the only one I’m serious about?
Come on, hop on.
Hurry up!
Ugh.
Hold on.
Let’s go.
Go, hubby.
Wow. You’re so good
in swimming, my hubby.
Drakey, are you having fun?
Gosh.
- Tripp…
- What?
Should I have brought…
two-piece?
I didn’t know we were
supposed to have a swimming attire.
Yes. Didn’t Shaira say
we’ll go swimming?
Oh no, I’ll just go home!
Hey, Zy, wait!
Your outfit is fine. That will do.
It looks nice.
Really? But how do
I go home like this?
I can’t just head
home soaking wet, right?
Hold on, I’ve got
an extra shirt here.
Here.
Wear this.
Just wear this when
you go home.
- Okay, fine.
- Good evening, Sir Tripp.
Oh, good evening.
Thank you.
Hey, Tripp! Feeling
right at home!
At least pretend to be shy.
Come on, it’s fine.
No big deal.
Go on, get changed.
Tripp?
Yes?
Is Shaira an only child?
She was supposed to have a
sibling, but it was a miscarriage.
So, Shai is an only child.
You know what, she’s nice.
Promise.
Just a little bratty sometimes.
Anyway, go get changed.
Go in, then turn right.
- Okay!
- Go on.
Fine!
- Alright, I’m going!
- Turn on the light.
Got it!
Tripp.
Why?
Come here.
Thanks, Zyril.
It’s always been my dream to
have the girl I like wear my shirt.
Cheesy, right?
Cheesy, huh?
I’m sorry.
It’s fine.
I’m used to your cheesiness
and your life drama.
You’re ruining the moment.
Fine. I’ll get changed, too.
I’ll just change.
Hurry up.
Mmm, okay.
Hey, Alys!
Hello, Shaira!
Hey, I know that shirt.
That’s Tripp’s, right?
Yes. I forgot to
bring swimwear.
OMG!
You two are so perfect together!
And for letting
you wear his shirt.
Where's my towel?
It’s over there.
I’ll get it for you.
You know, it’s better
you see them like this.
Maybe now you’ll realize
he’s for someone else.
And you…
are meant for me.
You know,
you shouldn’t be serious.
It doesn’t suit you.
The one time I get
serious, you’ll just laugh at me.
You’re really something, huh?
Sorry, it was just funny.
Sorry, I’ll stop.
Are you going to swim?
If you are, go ahead.
I’ll just stay here.
Why? Are you not
going to swim?
I don’t want to anymore.
So if you’re swimming,
go ahead. I’ll just stay here.
Okay.
Tripp...
whatever it is you’re thinking,
whatever it is you’re planning,
don’t do it.
Tripp...Tripp!
Tripp, I’m warning you!
Hey, Tripp!
Tripp, I said –
Ahh!
Ugh, you’re so annoying!
- You’re the worst!
- Ma’am, phone for you.
Your dad wants to talk to you.
Oh, I forgot my phone.
I’ll just talk to my Dad
real quick, I’ll be back.
You’re really mean!
Zy, wait, someone’s calling.
I’ll be back for you.
Hello?
Tripp is so annoying.
Where can I get a towel?
Well, maybe he brought a towel.
Drake!
Hey, what are you doing?
What is your problem?
You told me that you
don’t like me anymore.
So I’m trying to forget you.
But why are you making
it so damn impossible?
- No –
- Shut up!
Drake?
Hubby?
- It’s Shai–
- Shut up!
But Shaira...
What’s this?
My phone, obviously.
I know, of course.
But it’s the first time
you’ve given me your phone.
What am I supposed
to do with it?
Your brother’s been sending me a
lot of nonsense since we broke up.
Could you please tell
him to shut the hell up?
Because he’s slowly
getting into my nerves.
Oh, Dane.
He’s really got my back.
Here.
I’ll talk to him.
Sorry about that.
Alys.
Drake, what do you want?
Alys…
I thought that being mad at you
would make me forget about you.
But why is that every
time I see you,
all I remember is that
I love you?
Drake, what are you doing?
We broke up, didn’t we?
We broke up, right?
Tripp’s courting me now.
You’re good with
Shaira, but why this?
Alys!
Let me go. Drake, please.
Alys…
Let me go.
- Alys…
- Let me go.
Let me go.
Alys…
I know I’m not the best
boyfriend in the world.
Maybe I’m the worst.
But I love you so much, Alys.
I’m so stupid for letting you go.
Please take me back, Alys.
I love you so much.
I lay myself bare here.
Please, come back.
Take me again, Alys.
Drake…we’re fine now, aren’t we?
We’re fine now, right?
We’ve always been like this.
We don’t talk, we
ignore each other.
Even before I presented to be your
girlfriend, we were already like this.
Can’t you just think
we never happened?
Alys…
When I hear your name,
I remember that I love you.
When I see your face,
I remember how much I love you.
When I kiss your lips,
I realize that I couldn’t
live without you.
Alys, let’s get back together.
Please.
Drake, you know
I love you so much, right?
Don’t you know that
I love you?
Because you’re
always hurting me.
I’m confused if you
really love me or not.
Drake,
I love you so much.
[In French] Only you.
But now, there’s
Tripp and Shaira.
So?
What do you mean “so”?
There are others
we’ll end up hurting.
Would you rather hurt me, then?
No.
No, Drake.
It’s not like that.
I don’t want anyone to get hurt.
I’d rather get hurt than you.
Why do you care too much, Alys?
If you really love me, I
sure as hell love you back.
Why do complicate
things, Miss Perez?
That’s just how
it is, Mr. Palma.
We’re not the only ones
involved here anymore.
Is it not because
I’m always hurting you?
No.
Believe it or not, I’m used to it.
I’ve been through the worst
when I was with you.
But that’s not the
reason anymore.
There’s Tripp and Shaira.
Do you like my cousin?
What’s not to like?
He’s a pain in the ass.
Well, it takes one to know one.
Touché.
You’re getting smarter
and smarter, Alys.
But you’re always
going to be my noob.
Can you not call me that?
Tripp’s looking for me.
I’m leaving.
Wait.
What?
If you don’t want anybody
to get hurt, date me again.
What?
Date me again, Alys.
Secretly date me this time.
I’m going to court Alys.
It’s fine with you, right?
You like her?
Good luck.
She likes breaking hearts.
Maybe she won’t break mine.
Is she really that serious?
She’s really letting
my cousin court her?
Why are you hurting
me this much, Alys?
Hubby!
My husband!
Where are you going?
Wait, where are we going?
Drake, where are we going?
Are we going on a date?
We’re going on a date?
We’re going on a date!
Go ahead, I’ll just order.
Okay.
And one strawberry shortcake,
and then a large
strawberries and cream.
- And then—
- Hey, you’re ordering so much!
- You said make the most of it.
- You’re abusive.
- Oh?
- Oh, fine, just order it.
And this one, too.
That’s it!
I don’t know why it hurts
seeing you with him like that.
Maybe I really love you, Alys.
Because in my heart,
you’re supposed to be mine.
It’s my biggest mistake to let you go.
On the last episode of
Seducing Drake Palma.
Drake, the one I’m
always with at night.
Are you hiding from me?
Of course not!
And Tripp, the one I’m
always with in the morning.
You ignored me
for days after that…
Wow, you have shifting schedule?
Are you a nurse?
Every girl always wants Drake.
Should I act mean too,
so you’ll want me instead?
Tripp.
What?
Stop going after Alys.
I love Alys, Drake.
Just be honest, Zy.
If you like someone,
then go for him.
You’re not the same
Drake I knew anymore.
Alys Zyril Perez,
I’m crazy for you.
Alys?
What if Alys leaves me?
I don’t know if I can handle it.
I love you, Alys Zyril Perez.
I love you so much too,
Drake Sebastian Palma.