Subtitle by Kisskh.Asia Translator [ Admin Qari ]
May I be like the stars
and you like the moon.
As long as the world remains,
so shall we.
I only wish to stay with the one I love,
watching every sunrise and sunset.
I want to be with you forever.
Eternals and demons walk different paths.
You and she are ultimately different.
Have you ever
truly cared for me?
No.
Never.
In this life and the next, through all lifetimes…
May we live and die together,
and share life and death as one.
[Moonlight Mystique]
[Episode 8]
Master.
I found the tomb of Qian Yin.
I found that he died
two days before my parents died.
If my parents hadn't been killed by Qian Yin,
they could still be alive, right?
Back then, I went deep into the Demon Race to kill Qian Yin,
only to learn he'd died in an internal power struggle.
I didn't even find where he was buried.
How did you find it?
Fu Ling told me.
Fu Ling from Cold Spring Palace?
Why did you get involved with a demon?
In Ning'an City, I thought she was a human.
I saved her life, so…
You fool!
How can you believe what a demon said?
Moreover, it's just a tombstone.
She must be on
something else.
Chong Zhao,
I know
you've never gotten over
your parents' deaths.
But as a disciple of Lanling,
you should know
once the soul lamp goes out,
there's no chance of living.
It's irreversible.
Besides,
if they were still alive,
why would they have left you
and never come back?
You should let it go.
West sun mountain.
East moon river.
A snake slithers across the grass.
A fish leaps above the sandy sea.
The earth knows, but the sky does not.
Only by stepping in can you find the way.
This is a nursery rhyme from the Desireless Stone?
I don't understand a single line of it.
"West sun mountain"
means the sun
is about to set from the west of the mountain.
"East moon river"
means the moon
is about to rise from the east of the sea.
The sun and the moon
are both visible at twilight.
What unusual sights might appear
in the desert at twilight?
A mirage?
That's what I thought too.
If it's a mirage,
then the snake and fish
should be just illusions.
What does it mean by a snake slithering across the grass?
You don't live among humans,
so you don't know about it.
It's a riddle of the Human Race.
A riddle?
In the human culture,
we have the zodiac.
The snake in the zodiac
corresponds to the "Si" in the Earthly Branches.
A snake slithering across the grass means "Si" slithering across the grass.
The character "Si," combined with the grass radical,
becomes the character "Yi," as in Yi City.
The Desireless Stone is telling me
this nursery rhyme is the key to finding Yi City.
Master,
if only we knew better about the human culture.
It's not surprising to find a snake in the desert,
but how do we explain a fish leaping above the sandy sea?
How could there be fish in the desert?
I still haven't figured that out.
Looks like
we need to see this mirage
for ourselves.
Turns out it's the city walls blocking the view.
People mistook the snake's tail for a fish's tail.
Just looking at the tail,
it looks like a giant fish leaping into the sandy sea.
Then what do the last two lines mean?
The earth knows, but the sky does not.
Only by stepping in can you find the way.
Maybe we can only find a clue
by going to the mirage site.
This is just the illusion of Yi City.
Where is the real Yi City?
What's wrong?
I can't explain it, but it feels strange.
Everything just seems too easy.
Oh no!
It's a sand formation!
Don't let go.
Hold on tight!
Hold on tight.
The suction is too strong.
I can't hold on much longer!
Don't worry.
I won't let anything happen to you.
♫No matter if I'm drunk or not, I just want to be reckless once♫
♫Because love is thrilling♫
♫If you tear open my heart♫
♫I can hold you a little tighter♫
♫This pain will gradually fade♫
Bai Shuo.
♫Time withers the moonlight♫
A snake slithers across the grass.
A fish leaps above the sandy sea.
♫All that's left is pitch darkness♫
The earth knows, but the sky does not.
♫I want to tear apart♫
Only by stepping in can you find the way.
♫This sky for you♫
Fan Yue.
I understand.
♫A lifetime of guarding everything with you♫
Bai Shuo!
♫Crossing the abyss to fulfill our vow♫
♫I'll leap without a thought for tomorrow♫
♫This moment feels like forever♫
♫I've missed too much time in my life♫
♫I'll throw myself into this flame for you♫
Who allowed you to let go of my hand?
It's because I found…
I don't care!
♫Even if I'll perish♫
Do you know that one wrong judgment
♫At least I can still kiss your face♫
could cost you your life?
♫Burn out my waning moon♫
But you still followed me in.
Did you trust my judgment,
♫In exchange for a lifetime of passion♫
or were you afraid I'd die?
It's because I've said before
that I won't let you die.
Your arm.
What are you going to do?
♫No matter if I'm drunk or not, I just want to be reckless once♫
I believe you.
I believe you won't let me die.
I always keep my word.
♫Because love is thrilling♫
Don't worry.
I won't let myself die.
Do you remember the last two lines of that rhyme?
♫If you tear open my heart♫
The earth knows, but the sky does not.
Only by stepping in can you find the way.
They hint that
♫I can hold you a little tighter♫
the answer is underground.
Only if we go with the wind
♫This pain will gradually fade♫
to the underground
can we find the entrance.
That's still no reason for you to let go of my hand.
♫Time withers the moonlight♫
Your life
is mine.
♫All that's left is pitch darkness♫
Fan Yue.
Although you came down because of me,
♫I want to tear apart♫
I still have to correct you.
♫This sky for you♫
My life
has always been my own.
Thank you for following me,
risking your life without hesitation.
But without you,
I'd still save myself.
This must be the core of the sand formation.
I feel
the entrance to the city is right here.
Hold on to me.
Hold on to my sleeve.
Stick close to me.
Don't go anywhere or act rashly.
There may be other formations.
[Hua Lin, King of Yi]
I didn't expect the Master of Bright Moon Palace to visit.
I apologize for not welcoming you properly.
Yi City has been locked down for seven years,
yet you recognize me.
Seven years of locking the city
doesn't mean we're out of touch with the world.
You're famous far and wide.
I've long
heard of your name.
In that case,
that sand formation earlier
was your way of welcoming me?
Yi City has been oppressed
by Eternals and demons for a thousand years.
The sand formation
is just for defensive purposes.
This young lady
is very smart.
Your courage is commendable.
In the face of life and death,
you remained calm
and saw through the pattern of the formation.
I must say, I'm impressed.
I'm not particularly smart or wise,
and I'm not fearless either.
I just know
there's another way to live in this world.
It's called "live after death."
No wonder Master Fan Yue
risked his own life to save you.
I've come here to tell you
that within three days,
you should send invitations
to all Eternals and demons
for the Wutong Martial Arts Contest.
Why?
You should know
Bright Moon Palace
is a place no one dares to trespass in the Polar Region.
King of Yi, if you agree,
I'll allow Yi City to move into the Polar Region
under my protection.
But if not,
I doubt you have time
to move the city within three days.
The easy way
and the hard one
are both in front of you.
You choose.
Your Majesty,
back then,
the first King of Yi
agreed to host the Wutong Martial Arts Contest
to earn the respect of Eternals and demons
for peaceful coexistence.
We've held the Contest for a thousand years
and put in a lot of effort,
but they still look down on us.
If we hold the Contest again,
the people in the city
[Wu Zhao, Deputy General of Yi City]
will complain more.
Although the protection
the Master of Bright Moon Palace
offers seems tempting,
we don't truly know
his real intentions.
We must not trust him so easily.
I know that.
But now, Yi City is exposed.
Moving the city in three days
is simply impossible.
If the Eternals and demons
discover Yi City's location,
the secrets of the city
can no longer be hidden.
Whether I agree or not,
it will be troublesome.
King of Yi.
Zhen Yu?
Long time no see.
Is this how you welcome your guests?
Zhen Yu.
How did you find this place?
Was it difficult?
If Fan Yue could find it,
it would be
a piece of cake for me.
What do you want?
Why are you so vigilant?
I came here today
to help Yi City.
I can help you keep the secrets
you wish to keep
and solve
the problems
you want to solve.
Every deal
has its price.
What do you want?
Straight to the point.
You must have heard of
the Desireless Stone.
Sect Leader,
are we about to attack Bright Moon Palace?
I've decided on the moves. Look.
Calm down.
Sit down first.
Alright.
Today,
I've gathered everyone here to discuss another matter.
King of Yi has sent an invitation.
He's invited all Eternals and demons
to go to Yi City
[and strengthen the bonds between the three races. We invite the esteemed guests of Lanling to join us in Yi City.]
[On the 15th of this month, the Wutong Martial Arts Contest will be held to test the abilities of Eternals and demons]
for the Wutong Martial Arts Contest.
He wants to ease
[and strengthen the bonds between the three races. We invite the esteemed guests of Lanling to join us in Yi City.]
[On the 15th of this month, the Wutong Martial Arts Contest will be held to test the abilities of Eternals and demons]
the relationship between the Yi citizens and the two races.
The Contest hasn't been held for seven years.
They just hold it and cancel it
as they please.
Are we fools in their eyes?
I won't go!
That's right.
Seven years ago, King of Yi suddenly canceled the Contest,
which led to more fighting between the Eternals and demons.
If Eternals enter Yi City,
they'll surely get into fights with demons.
Lanling
doesn't need to get into that mess.
Don't rush to object.
Let me finish.
The winner of the Contest
will get the Wutong Spirit Pill.
How could I forget that?
If that's the case,
maybe we should reconsider.
The Wutong Spirit Pill is a rare spiritual treasure.
It can greatly enhance cultivation.
Even if we don't need it,
we can sell it to other Eternal sects.
It'd be enough to support us for three years.
Three years?
It would last us ten years!
Since no one has any objections,
then
Chong Zhao will lead the team.
Yes, Master.
But...
Don't worry,
I haven't forgotten about the Desireless Stone.
The Contest this time
is not only for the Eternals.
Bright Moon Palace, Jingyou Mountain, and other demon clans
are also invited.
Bai Shuo, eager to grow stronger,
will likely attend it as well.
We can wait for her in Yi City
instead of searching for her in the Polar Region.
Isn't that much easier?
Then I'll go!
Calm down.
Yi City has a restriction formation.
Even the strongest Eternals and demons
can't use their magic there.
They can only rely on physical strength.
So whether you go or Chong Zhao goes,
it makes no difference.
Chong Zhao,
the Wutong Contest
is not just a simple martial arts competition.
It's a comprehensive test
of strength, intelligence,
temperament, and character.
So, going to Yi City
will certainly be dangerous.
Remember,
bringing Bai Shuo back is secondary.
The most important thing is to protect your fellow disciples.
Understood, Master.
This is my Cangxuan Sword.
It has a century-old sword spirit
and will be useful at a crucial moment.
Thank you, Master.
I never said I was giving it to you.
But if it's useful,
then take it.
Thank you, Master.
[and strengthen the bonds between the three races. We invite the esteemed guests of Lanling to join us in Yi City.]
[On the 15th of this month, the Wutong Martial Arts Contest will be held to test the abilities of Eternals and demons]
King of Yi knows how to read the room.
Knowing there's no escape,
he's agreed to hold the Contest.
King of Yi is shrewd
and has always despised Eternals and demons.
Master has figured out Yi City's location,
but he's agreed to our terms too easily.
Once the city gates are open,
whether it's a conspiracy or something else,
I'll be right there to see it through.
Grand Master,
King of Yi has already sent out invitations
to all Eternals and demons for the Wutong Contest.
When there's more fish than food,
we've got to fight
to get what we want.
Yi City reopening
only means it's all but over.
Even if they fight to the death,
what difference will it make?
In the end,
they'll all fall into my hands.
But...
they'll all be dead by then.
[Yi City, home to Yi citizens]
Who are they?
Alright, alright, alright.
No more fooling around!
Go home!
I'll teach you a lesson after we get back!
This is Yi City, huh?
It really looks different.
These Yi citizens
are surprisingly
strong.
They don't seem to welcome us.
Yi citizens have been at loggerheads with Eternals and demons for over 1,000 years.
Eternals and demons look down on them,
and they despise
Eternals and demons.
When we're in Yi City,
don't leave my sight.
If you die, the Desireless Stone will be useless.
Just take care of yourself.
The city gates have opened.
The Eternals will arrive soon.
You took their Desireless Stone.
They can't wait to kill you.
The Eternals will come, so what?
Their power will be restricted too.
Even if it wasn't,
Bright Moon Palace
wouldn't be afraid of those Eternals.
Restricted?
In Yi City,
Eternals and demons can't use their magic.
Then why the Contest?
With punches, kicks, swords,
and clubs,
we can still fight.
So in Yi City,
one can only rely on weapons and physical strength.
Neither Eternals nor demons can use magic.
That gives me a better chance of winning.
Stop dreaming.
Even without magic,
I can still easily
hold you in my palm.
You're overthinking it.
Shuo.
Why are you here?
She's with Bright Moon Palace.
Where she is
is none of your business.
Shuo.
You shouldn't stay with demons,
and you shouldn't have come here.
Who I stay with
and where I go
are my decisions to make.
Demons can't be trusted.
We're not here to fight.
We?
Since there's a "we,"
don't pick the wrong side.
Think carefully about
who you should trust
and who you should choose.
I have my own plans.
The Eternals can't give me what I want.
We're destined to be on different paths.
Let's go.
Great!
All the Eternals and demons
have fallen into the trap.
Everyone who needs to be there
has already arrived.
The grand Wutong Martial Arts Contest
wouldn't be complete without
us from Cold Spring Palace.
Fu Ling.
Go to Yi City
and carry out the plan.
Remember,
keep a close eye on Bai Shuo.
She must not
leave Yi City.
Understood.
Grand Master.
Why send Fu Ling?
Aren't you worried that Chong Zhao could mess things up
and ruin your plan?
No plan can be foolproof.
I just need to have backup plans.
In Yi City,
you've got other people in place?
People are simple.
As long as they're properly used,
anyone
can become my pawn.
[Sihai Inn]
Come on.
Bring it on!
I'll teach you a hard lesson!
Bring it on! You want the room?
Who do you think you are?
Exactly.
Demon, you're dead!
How dare you act up in front of me?
You good?
Stop fighting.
I'm not afraid of you. Bring it on!
Looks like
the prophecy from the Desireless Stone has come true again.
Could this Contemplation
be related to the conflict between the two races?
[Nan Wan, Eternal Race, Yunxiao Sect]
That's my room!
-Enough. Calm down.
-You deserve a good beating!
You want to die?
-Bring it on!
-What are you talking about?
Everyone.
The top-tier rooms
should naturally be the Eternals'.
Look at you,
a bunch of furry beasts,
wandering around like street rats.
[Xiao Kan, Demon Race, a wolf demon]
Second-tier rooms suit you the best, unless…
you prefer the bathrooms.
What are you saying?
Listen up!
I'm talking about you guys,
a bunch of stinky foxes.
Bei Chen.
[Bei Chen, Eternal Race, Kunlun Sect]
Say something!
Aren't Kunlun
and the Fox Clan sworn enemies?
Why are you
so quiet today?
Let me say something.
Stop.
I insist.
We Eternals believe that
from one breath, three purities are born.
As…
As Eternals, we should restrain our evil desires,
clear out the bad energy,
(Watch on www.kisskh.la or www.kisskh.co to support Admin)
and make it pure again.
My Eternal friends,
stop arguing.
Come on.
Let's recite
the Scripture of Forgetting Emotions.
-Forgetting emotions…
-Shut up!
I can't stand you Eternals and your scriptures!
All you do
is waste time!
-Exactly.
-You…
We're all here for the Wutong Martial Arts Contest,
so why fight over something pointless?
Bah!
The Eternals from Kunlun
are the most hypocritical.
You guys
are cruel and bloodthirsty.
Since Eternals and demons can't get along,
why do they have to stay in the same inn?
It's the tradition of the Contest.
The former King of Yi wanted to help the three races reconcile
and set the rules with the heads of the other two races
for Eternals, demons, and Yi citizens to stay together.
But I think this rule is just for show.
Once sides are taken,
right or wrong doesn't matter,
and the fighting never ends.
Nonsense!
It's your Saintess…
Eternals and demons
are not nobler than one another.
You can't insult the Saint!
Everyone, stop arguing!
What's the point of fighting over the rooms?
Lanling has old ties with many sects.
Please listen to me.
Look who's here.
Isn't that
Chong Zhao, the Eternal who couldn't even
guard Ning'an City?
They call you the head disciple of Lanling.
But you're weak and incompetent,
causing chaos in the whole city.
If I were you,
I'd have already buried myself in a hole.
You don't deserve to come here
and fight with us for the Wutong Spirit Pill.
Nan Wan!
That's nonsense!
If Chong Zhao doesn't deserve to be here,
then do you?
You guys are Eternals,
but instead of protecting the people,
you're here fighting
and arguing.
Is that what Eternals do?
You're just a human.
How dare you lecture me?
You're dead!
Senior!
Senior.
You know where to seek protection, don't you?
With someone like you around,
if I don't make use of it,
it'd be an ungodly waste.
Are you alright?
Senior.
Who are you?
Tell me your name!
Forgot to mention.
The top-tier rooms
are all mine.
Who do you think you are?
Senior, calm down.
He's so powerful.
Forget it.
The second-tier rooms will do too.
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
It just feels good to boss around
under your wings.
I'll do it more often.
Not anyone can stay by my side.
Kill them! Kill them!
Go!
Kill those Eternals and demons!
Yes, kill them!
Kill them!
Hey, bro,
what are you...
Bah!
Don't call me bro.
Eternals, demons—
none of you guys are any good.
[Hu's mother, a Yi citizen]
You brought this disease
into the city.
You all deserve to die!
Kill them!
Kill them! Kill them! Kill them!
Disease?
[Hu, a Yi citizen]
Chong Zhao.
What's wrong with this kid?
It doesn't look like an ordinary illness.
Cut the crap!
These Eternals and demons
never cared about the lives of Yi citizens.
If we kill them,
the kid can be saved!
Right, kill them! Kill them!
Please, calm down.
Enough.
Yi citizens
are all lowlifes.
How dare you talk like that?
Their king
invited us to the Contest.
Not only did they fail to host us properly,
but now they're actually
messing with us.
Fine.
Bring it on.
I'd like to see
what you can do
with us today!
Watch your mouth!
Come on. Bring it on!
We'll kill you all!
I'm actually with him on this one.
I was just getting started.
I can't wait to see which one of you has a death wish
and wants to try your luck with me.
Come on!
Hu.
Hu, wake up!
Hu!
Listen.
Take her away.
If she dies here,
we can't stay in this inn anymore.
The situation is not clear yet.
It's no good for you to be kind now.
Hu.
Hu!
Kunlun is skilled in medicine.
Do you know how to treat him?
I've never seen a disease like this before.
Why are you still there?
Take her away!
Don't bring bad luck to us.
I knew it.
None of you Eternals and demons are any good.
Get out!
Get out! Get out!
Hu.
Hu, hang in there!
Don't sleep.
Don't sleep!
Hu, wake up!
Hang in there!
Hu.
Hu, wake up!
Hu, don't sleep.
Hu!
Wake up, Hu!
What's that?
I'm a human,
not an Eternal or a demon.
This pill can save her.
Even if you're a human,
you came here with Eternals and demons,
so you're definitely with them.
You can believe me or not.
For me,
whether I save her or not,
it's no loss either way.
What's more important,
your child's life or hatred?
You choose.
Mom.
-It worked.
-She's awake.
Hu.
Bai Shuo
did learn something from Old Turtle.
Her pills are great,
but she's still
too soft-hearted.
Thanks
for the pill.
Earlier,
I was wrong about you.
It's fine.
I don't care.
Take her home for some rest.
Look.
Heart flame. That's the heart flame.
The first heart flame has appeared.
I've never seen one before.
Why did it appear?
Why is it landing on her?
-Yeah.
-Why?
Wait.
What are you doing?
That's the heart flame!
I can see it.
Chong Zhao.
Look.
Maybe after Bai Shuo saved the Yi child,
the heart flame sensed it and responded.
That's nonsense!
Maybe this human planned it
with those Yi citizens from the start.
How could she get the heart flame with just a pill?
That's cheating.
Cheating, cheating!
That's the first heart flame.
Whether it's taken by the Eternals
or the demons,
it can't
be taken
by a human!
Exactly!
Why can't a human
have the heart flame?
This Contest is for Eternals and demons.
The Human Race doesn't even have the right to attend it!
Is that so?
I'm here in Yi City with her.
That gives her the right!
Not convinced?
Come fight me.
You...
Senior.
Why are you sticking up for her?
Why?
You just got to Yi City.
Why are you already at each other's throats?
I'm Wu Zhao.
I'm the deputy general under King of Yi.
Welcome to Yi City
to attend
the Wutong Martial Arts Contest.
You've come at the right time.
I've got one question.
What gives her, a human,
the right to take the heart flame?
Before the Master of Bright Moon Palace came,
he'd notified the King
that a human would contend in the competition.
The King gave his approval.
Isn't that right,
Master?
-Master?
He's the Master of Bright Moon Palace?
He's come to Yi City in person.
We don't stand a chance.
The Wutong Contest
has already begun the moment
you entered the city.
There are three heart flames.
The first gives rise to the second,
the second to the third.
The first two heart flames
are naturally generated
and choose their owners themselves.
But the third heart flame
must be kindled by the King
along with the Eternals and demons
by burning Wutong branches
at the Fenlan Banquet.
The one who collects all three heart flames
will be the victor of the Wutong Contest
and receive the Wutong Spirit Pill.
This has been the rule for the past thousand years.
I hope I've answered
your question.
The heart flame chooses its owner.
No one can interfere.
Magic is forbidden in Yi City.
Eternals and demons are equals here.
I wish
you all
a victorious start
and an enjoyable return.
Come up.
Shuo.
Chong Zhao.
Let's settle down too.
Okay.
Brother,
among the Three Kings of the Demon Race,
the Master of Bright Moon Palace is the most powerful.
What do you think we should do?
If we don't show some goodwill,
we may offend him.
But if we do show goodwill,
we may upset the heads of Jingyou Mountain
and Cold Spring Palace.
Let's stay neutral.
The more neutral, the better.
After all,
we're here for the Contest,
right?
Yeah.
We just
won't ask questions
or get involved.
Right.
No questions. No involvement.
But why has the Master of Bright Moon Palace
brought a human with him?
What did I just say?
No questions!
Got it?
Yes.
No questions.
Let's go.
Go.
Don't you think everything
is going a bit too smoothly?
Eternals and demons just entered the city.
Before they even got to grab a bite,
a kid fell ill,
and a bunch of Yi citizens rushed over, throwing accusations.
It happened so fast,
almost like someone planned it beforehand.
Go on.
Then I saved that kid
and got the first heart flame.
It's said the heart flame chooses its owner,
but why do I feel like
someone's intentionally
given this heart flame to me?
You've gotten smarter.
What I want to hear isn't praise.
Giving the first heart flame to you
would make you the target of both Eternals and demons.
Everyone will have their eyes on you.
No matter who's pulling the strings behind the scenes,
the game has already begun.
And,
it's more interesting than I expected.
This isn't a conspiracy.
It's a blatant scheme.
Bai Shuo,
they're coming for you.
But to be exact,
they're after the Desireless Stone.
It's the Desireless Stone again.
Looks like
I'll have to turn defense into offense.
If someone's targeting me,
they'll definitely make moves behind my back.
[Sihai Inn]
I saved your life once.
Is this how you treat someone who saved your life?
You're a demon, and I'm an Eternal.
We're on different paths.
The truth about my parents' deaths,
I'll find it out myself.
If I worked with a demon
to uncover the truth,
my parents would turn in their graves!
Chong Zhao,
remember what you said today.
From now on,
whatever you want,
I'll take it from you.
You refuse to work with me.
Then let's see how long you can hold out.
Get out!
Don't make me fight you.
You're the one who should leave.
What do you mean?
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Yi City is dangerous.
Don't let those old fools from Lanling
end up holding your funeral.
Chong Zhao,
it's me.
Get out.
What?
Are you worried
Bai Shuo will see me?
Or
are you afraid you won't be able to explain things to her?
Get lost!
What's that sound?
A cat.
Shuo.
Have you changed your mind?
You're willing to go back with me?
I came to ask
what happened to Old Turtle after I left.
He's fine.
He was just punished to make
an extra hundred pills every month.
Nothing else?
No.
I'm glad he's fine.
Shuo.
There's nothing else you want to say to me?
What more
can I say?
I've said it before,
we're no longer on the same path.
If that's true,
why did you speak up for me just now?
We spent ten years together.
To hide your identity,
you always pretended to be weak.
Helping you
seems to have become a habit of mine.
I forgot again just now.
You're an Eternal from Lanling.
You don't need me to stand up for you.
Shuo.
While I was in Lanling, I heard some things.
I know you did all that back in Ning'an City to protect me,
and I know you endured 300 lashes.
But Chong Zhao,
I can't thank you.
Then,
do you hate me?
No.
The demon poison wasn't your doing,
nor did you cause my father's death.
You were just wrong
in taking my life too seriously.
To protect me, you almost ruined a whole city.
Have you ever thought
even if I survived,
how would I live with all of this
after knowing the truth?
It was all my fault.
I was too confident,
and the demons made use of it.
I'm sorry.
But I…
I really didn't expect things
to end up like that.
I know you didn't mean it,
so I don't want to blame you anymore.
Can we
go back to the way we used to be?
♫That year, that year♫
Everything in Ning'an City is over now.
♫The leaves fell unnoticed after the flowers bloomed♫
You're no longer that steamed bun boy,
♫I'm afraid the autumn wind will stir up memories♫
and I'm no longer that
devil-may-care girl.
♫They unfold, one page after another♫
♫That year, that year♫
I'll walk my own way.
♫The flowers flew under the moon, filling the sky♫
You too.
Shuo.
♫Falling to the mud, burying the memories♫
What about you and Fan Yue?
♫Layer after layer♫
What exactly…
♫Another year passed♫
is your relationship now?
Both of us need the power of the Desireless Stone.
It's just cooperation.
♫Another year passed♫
He's been protecting you.
What he's been protecting
is the Desireless Stone.
You chatted for a long time.
You're a Demon King,
yet you eavesdrop?
I wouldn't stoop to something like that.
What you wanted to ask him
and what you'd say,
I don't need to listen to know.
You think you know me very well?
At least better than he does.
Since you're on different paths,
don't waste time on all this sentimentality.
The night has fallen.
It's time to explore the city.