LOVE NEXT DOOR
Wow, look at this.
Honey, did they install
a moving walkway in our neighborhood?
My legs are moving on their own.
You fool! Stand up straight.
- Straight!
- Goodness.
Why are you so heavy? Jeez.
Just how much tteokbokki did you eat?
I had some deep-fried food.
I have high cholesterol.
- But how could I pass up good food?
- It's plant-based.
Why on earth
did you have to go this way?
Excuse me.
Does all of Hyereung-dong belong to you?
I wish I could, but I can't afford it.
Jeez, it's always about money with you.
Aunt Hye-suk.
Mom…
Seung-hyo. Seok-ryu.
What are you two doing here?
What's going on here?
I was mistaken, right?
You two brats always fight!
Now, you're ramming your bodies
up against each other!
What's the meaning of this?
So what happened was…
- We're dating.
- What?
You're… dating.
Are you talking about some old 80s song?
Wait, hold on.
- We…
- What?
We're in a serious relationship.
Yes, we're sorry
we didn't tell you earlier.
We thought it over
for a while before doing this.
So we had to be careful.
We know you're very shocked.
We know you'll be worried too. But…
Our feelings for each other
aren't shallow or superficial.
So you're telling me
they're not shaking hands right now?
My goodness.
Hey…
Let's go home.
Okay, Aunt Mi-suk. I'll go with you
and explain everything.
No, Seung-hyo. You go home.
- Seok-ryu, let's go.
- Just me?
No. You can't.
You can't take just her. I'll go too.
Don't you have something
you need to tell me?
Yes, but I'll go
to Seok-ryu's house first--
But I'd like to hear it now!
I'm sorry. But first…
Hey, you goddamn idiot!
You must think
very little of me, don't you?
Enough with the nonsense
and come here right now!
If you don't I'll kill you!
What did she say?
It's better if you didn't know.
It always sounds so beautiful
when you speak French.
Yeah, okay.
- She's being pretentious again.
- Wait.
Hey, it's better than pretending
to be a lifelong friend like you.
You wouldn't have had
any friends if I didn't do that.
You were so cold
people called you the Ice Princess.
That's a personal attack!
Mom, why are you
being like that to Aunt Hye-suk?
Did you two get into a fight?
They did. It was bad.
Seok-ryu, come with me.
Bye, Gyeong-jong.
- No, you can't.
- Seung-hyo!
What's wrong with you?
Hey!
Choisseung! There's a Spanish proverb.
"All sunshine makes a desert."
"Rain and wind make the land fertile."
We're going through this hardship
to become stronger.
- No, we can't!
- You understand, right?
I can't let you go by yourself.
- My goodness.
- We have to be together no matter what.
Don't worry.
- I'll never let you go now.
- No. All right.
- Don't worry.
- No.
- You deserve a beating.
- Choisseung! You trust me, right?
- Don't worry!
- Mom!
I think your mom is upset.
Let's go home for now. Okay?
Dad, wait.
No! Don't hit her, Aunt Mi-suk!
How could you hit her?
Shut your mouth!
UNDERSTANDING KINEMATICS
- Mom.
- Be quiet!
No, wait. Just listen…
Seok-ryu, what did you do this time?
Hey, getting in trouble is my specialty.
You keep stealing my shtick.
Just butt out.
- Explain yourself.
- Go ahead.
What's going on between you and Seung-hyo?
It's like we said earlier.
We're dating and it's serious.
Is that funny to you?
- You find that funny?
- Stop lying.
Did you drug him? Why would he date you?
I told you to butt out.
You two are dating. That's it?
He wanted to ask for permission first,
but I stopped him.
You and Aunt Hye-suk are friends.
And honestly, I wasn't confident then.
But I can tell you for certain now.
I really like Seung-hyo a lot.
What? You're serious?
It's not just a casual relationship.
Does that mean
you're considering marriage?
- No.
- What?
Whatever the case may be,
it can't be Seung-hyo.
Why not?
You like Seung-hyo.
In any case, you can't.
I'll never allow it.
- I've made myself clear.
- Mom.
Mom.
Your mom had a fight
with Aunt Hye-suk.
Honey, you should drink a lot of water.
You need it when you're angry.
It's gaslighting.
What?
I'm sure he was brainwashed by you.
If not, why on earth would he…
Come on.
You used to beat him up all the time.
And you dragged him around
like a rag doll.
I told you to butt out, didn't I?
- Didn't I?
- I'll butt out! I'm sorry!
Damn it, my hair!
- That damn temper of hers!
- What did you say?
For someone who told us
he wanted to share a meal with us,
I wondered where you went every night.
I guess you were busy dating.
We still have breakfast together.
Yes, I've been actively taking part.
When did you and Seok-ryu
start dating and how?
Who initiated it?
I'm sure Seok-ryu
said she liked you first.
You're perfect in every way,
and you're right beside her.
So how could she not develop
feelings for him? My word.
I liked her first.
- What?
- I've liked her since we were kids.
My feelings only grew after we met again.
Honestly, Seok-ryu told me no
and rejected me several times.
But I persisted.
Wait. Wait a second.
So she turned you down?
Well… At first, but now--
She is ridiculous!
Goodness, I really adored her,
but is she out of her mind?
Why? What's wrong with my son?
- I know!
- Why?
What is he, chopped liver?
- Why would she reject him?
- Hilarious.
I'm not saying this because you're my son,
but you don't deserve that treatment.
Exactly!
Well… What I meant was…
It was only like that at first,
but we're dating now.
She's even accepted my proposal.
You proposed to her too?
Did you make it a special event too?
- What?
- Look at him. He did.
He did do it!
Did you put flowers
in your car with balloons
and rent out an entire restaurant too?
Mom, did you stick
a listening device on me?
- For crying out loud.
- What is it?
Sit down.
Take a seat.
There's no point in raising a son.
No wonder why it's a saying.
Hey!
Remember this necklace
you got me for my birthday?
I already had the same one.
I didn't know. You should've told me then.
- How could I be so petty and tell you?
- You're doing it right now.
Want me to buy you a necklace?
Let's go shopping tomorrow.
Forget it! I don't need any of it!
Dad, I…
Don't even think of trying to convince me!
I'm on your mom's side!
- Dad, if you can talk to her…
- Hey.
My hands are already full.
Let's fight our own battles.
Honey, do you want a foot massage?
Honey, can I ask you something?
- No.
- Okay.
It's about Seok-ryu and Seung-hyo.
Why can't they date?
It's not anything personal
because of your fight with Hye-suk, right?
I said don't ask,
so why do you keep asking?
I know blood's thicker than water,
but who'd be a better son-in-law than him?
He's handsome, he has a great job,
and he has good character.
- We've known him since he was a kid.
- That's why they can't.
- We've known him for too long.
- What?
Hye-suk knows everything too.
Seok-ryu's canceled engagement
and illness. She knows it all.
I don't want that to become
a weakness for my child.
I don't want her to be
at a disadvantage, and above all…
and I don't want her to get hurt!
If they hurt Seok-ryu…
I don't care who it is.
I'll make them pay.
Friend or not.
What are you thinking about?
It's just…
In the past,
when we were busy…
I wonder about how Seung-hyo had felt.
Things like that.
We were terrible to him.
If I could turn back time,
I would go back to that day
when Seung-hyo was seven,
standing behind the door alone,
and I'd give him a hug.
Still, back then…
since Seok-ryu was by Seung-hyo's side,
we were so fortunate.
Honey.
What's the survival rate
for stomach cancer?
Never mind.
Pretend you didn't hear that.
Let's sleep.
CHOISSEUNG
The person you dialed is unavailable…
Hey!
- Hey…
- Jeez!
Help me.
- Come here.
- I almost died.
What are you doing?
Why did you climb through the window?
You could've been hurt!
But…
I missed you so much.
What else could I do?
So I did my best impression of you.
Your wrist isn't fully healed yet.
Let me see.
Doing this will make it better.
Your parents are really upset,
aren't they?
No.
They're just a bit flustered.
- What about your parents?
- What?
They're a little surprised.
They're just…
They're flustered too.
- Liar.
- You lied too, babe.
But it's funny when you think about it.
What did we do that was so bad?
Why do we have to be so scared?
What did you just say?
"Babe"?
Well, yeah.
What happened to the person
who wanted to keep things secret?
Well, we've already been caught.
I don't care!
So if my mom doesn't approve,
you're not going to see me, babe?
That would never happen.
Can't you tell from how I climbed up here?
My instinct to fight back is kicking in.
Should I wear a protest headband
saying, "Seung-hyo's mine"?
Not a headband.
Instead…
let's put this on you.
It's beautiful.
I know why people wear wedding rings now.
This gives me a strong sense of unity.
Do you like it?
Yeah, I love it.
But I'm curious. Why did you get
a bracelet instead of a ring?
Because…
Don't come to my workplace
and spread rumors about me.
I should sue you
for spreading false information.
What an ungrateful jerk.
You should repay me instead of suing me.
You even remembered what we said in jest?
It wasn't on purpose.
I guess my mind saved
everything you did
and every word you said.
And I'll continue to do so.
I'll listen closely
to the things you say.
And I won't waste
our time together.
I'll hold onto you
and everything you are.
I'll hold on tightly forever.
So Seok-ryu,
will you…
marry me?
I'd be a fool
to refuse a proposal like this.
CLOSING AFTER SEPTEMBER 13
This one.
Hey, my mom found out
Seung-hyo and I are dating.
Well, you did well to hide it
as long as you did.
My dad and Seung-hyo's parents
caught us too.
Taking your lumps all at once
isn't that bad of a thing.
Why aren't you surprised?
Because I got my mom's approval.
Really? How?
There's a method for everything.
So what is it? Tell me!
Well…
Share bowls of jajangmyeon
and jjamppong with everyone.
Get the japchae rice too.
What are you talking about?
Do it with sincerity.
That's the only answer.
Are you fanning the flames right now?
You don't work
for Korea Fire Service, do you?
I'm off duty today.
What are you doing?
This isn't like you at all.
Well…
I'm adding some oil to my hair.
Jeez, you're the worst.
Your friend is in shambles right now,
and you're here
sitting pretty by yourself?
I have a date today.
Hi, Dan-ho.
Hi, Mo-eum.
Did you wait a long time?
No, I was happy waiting for you too.
Don't be ridiculous. Come on.
- You look pretty today.
- What?
Hello. How are you?
Hi, I'm fine.
But don't mind me. I'll let you continue.
I'm going home.
Just a moment.
Hello, Mr. Choi.
- It's not Choi Seung-hyo, is it?
- It is.
Yes, go ahead.
- Is that Choisseung?
- Go.
I see.
Right now?
Yes, I can.
Right about now, I would be
on a Wolmido Island amusement ride
or having chicken and beer
by the Han River.
But why am I here?
You dreamed a lot
about going on dates, didn't you?
Hey, are you going to handle
your boyfriend right or what?
Sorry.
We can hear you, you know.
So what?
I'm sorry.
We're remodeling
an elderly lady's house next week.
- An elderly lady?
- Yes.
There's an elderly lady
in the neighborhood we know.
She lives alone.
Mr. Choi took time
out of his busy schedule to help.
That's such a good deed.
It's so good you can't complain.
It's more serious than I thought.
They're plywood walls, which are weak
for soundproofing or insulation.
Essential amenities are nonexistent.
They could've made a kitchen
or a bathroom in this leftover space.
If the owners had that kind of money,
they would've made more rooms like this.
More units mean
more rent they can collect.
Why would they go this far?
For money.
Recently, there have been rumors
of redevelopment.
My mom's been getting
a lot of calls about that at work.
But I like how Hyereung-dong is now.
- Me too.
Yes, me too.
By the way, why do you two
still speak formally with each other?
When are you going to speak casually?
- Sorry?
- What?
You're right.
We live in the same neighborhood.
We're friends of the same age.
You should drop formalities.
- It's fine.
- It's okay.
This is more comfortable for us.
Trust us.
An appropriate distance
is the key to friendship.
I see.
Right.
- What was that?
- They seem close.
And at times, they don't.
Hey! Why has it been so hard
to reach you these days?
Hye-suk didn't come by here, did she?
She's been out of touch too.
The group text has been so quiet.
Wait, did you make
a new group text without me?
I'm glad you said that.
If you know how, create a new group.
Leave Hye-suk out.
It'll be just you, me, and In-suk.
What?
- Did you two fight again?
- I've decided to never see her again.
Is it serious?
From now on,
Hye-suk doesn't exist in my life.
Still, you've been friends for 40 years.
You may have your differences,
but if you cut ties with her,
it would be sad to see
all those years become a waste.
Hey, I have a lot of years ahead of me.
I can make new friends.
Like shoes, old friends are always
more comfortable than new ones.
You have a long ways to go,
so don't hurt yourself with new shoes.
Were you always this good of a talker?
It's because I have
a lot on my mind these days.
I've almost attained nirvana
by letting everything go.
What? Is something going on with you too?
Mo-eum is dating Mr. Kang.
Mr. Kang?
Your next-door neighbor?
- Yeon-du's dad?
- Yeah.
So what did you do?
You didn't give them permission, did you?
They like each other,
so what can I do?
Break her legs
and keep her at home?
Shave her head
and send her to a temple?
Seok-ryu and Seung-hyo are dating too.
That's hot! I mean, it's cold!
What?
Hey, Hye-suk.
Sorry, Jae-suk. I'll come back later.
- I'm off, Jae-suk.
- I said I'm leaving!
Jae-suk, can you tell her I'm going
because it's time to go
and not because of her?
She must think
the world revolves around her.
- That little brat.
- Why are you two being so childish?
She's the one who always starts it.
Mi-suk! Goodness.
Where are you going?
Gosh! She's just leaving.
I had something to ask her though.
Hye-suk! It's been a while!
- How are you?
- Good.
What were you going to ask?
Well, on my way here,
I saw on the snack shop's door.
What was it?
It was a sign saying they're closing.
What?
- Really?
- Yeah.
What's going on?
Yeon-du.
There's actually something
I have to tell you today.
The thing is…
I'll do it.
I want to do it.
Yeon-du.
I need to ask
your permission for something.
What is it?
Can you give me…
the chance to become your mom?
I know I can't be your real mom,
but I can promise you a few things.
I won't force you
to eat spinach and carrots.
I promise to win the parents' relay race
at your kindergarten's sports day.
Also…
When you're sick,
and when things are hard,
I promise to be by your side.
But if…
by any chance, if you'd hate that--
I don't hate it.
I mean… to be honest, I would love it.
- Really?
- Yes.
I've been waiting for this day.
This is a secret,
but I've dreamt about it too.
Did you sleep well?
Any dreams about being an alien's friend?
No, I dreamt of something else.
What was it?
It's a secret. I'll tell you later.
I went to the moon in my dream,
and you and Dad got married there.
We were wearing spacesuits
and floating around.
What?
Mo-eum,
you're my best friend in the whole world.
So please be
a good friend to my dad too.
Of course.
Dad, are you crying?
I'm not crying.
I didn't get much sleep last night.
- I was just yawning.
- What? I don't think so.
You're obviously crying
because you're touched.
We made your dad cry!
No, I wasn't crying.
- Are there any tissues?
- Tissues?
I wonder if they have any tissues.
I'm currently sick, and I saw your video
while searching for healthy food.
It looks so good.
But I don't have the energy to cook,
so I can't make it.
It'd be nice if I could try your food.
What are you thinking so hard about?
What? It's nothing.
Hey, you can't talk to me though.
We agreed to take an hour to work.
Don't talk to me.
Yeah, I'm working really hard too.
- I can't take this. I'll move a seat over.
- No!
Then, you'll want to move
two seats over and get even closer.
Then, you'll want to sit beside me
and hold hands.
No, you can't.
We're an ideal couple that can manage
successful careers and love.
What do I do?
I'm already done with work.
It's time for something else now.
No, not yet!
I still have a lot to do!
I'm not finished yet!
I'm still not done!
I came to work on a Saturday night
to pursue wealth and honor.
And I end up seeing something like that.
SHANTY TOWN
BEFORE AND AFTER
- What's this?
- A gift.
Open it.
Honey, am I dreaming right now?
Did I fall asleep with my eyes open?
You damn punk, did you mess up again?
What is it this time? What did you do?
- You little punk, you're dead!
- What?
What is it? Did you make another mess?
No, I didn't.
I got my paycheck,
so I bought this for Mom and Dad.
That makes no sense, you punk!
The last thing I ever got from you
was a colored paper flower
you made in school!
Wait, hold on.
I must've been a scumbag.
Take a look. It's a health supplement.
You're right.
I know what this is.
You and Dad are older now.
I got something nice
to help your blood sugar.
Since it's opened now,
each of you take one.
Here's yours, Dad.
Is this really that good?
Yeah. This is for you, Mom.
This is too precious to drink.
Hey.
What does that make me
if you say that? I drank all…
Yeah, Mom. That's like a chronic disease.
Be happy when your kids
give you something.
- Yeah.
- Okay?
And use those beauty products I got you.
All right, I'll drink it.
I need to be healthy
so I don't trouble you.
I thought this punk
was trying to sell this to us.
Dong-jin, you've finally grown up.
You don't get any.
You still have a ways to go.
There you go being rude to me again.
Seok-ryu, Dong-jin.
Mom, we weren't fighting.
Our conversation
just got intense for a second.
It's not that.
- I have something to tell you two.
- Can I have two at once?
- Honey?
- Yeah?
I see.
Well…
I've decided to close the shop.
- What?
- Why?
Why do you think?
I'm at the age for retirement now.
The FIRE movement. Don't you know?
- What's that?
- You don't?
What is that?
Dad.
If you're here to get permission
to see Seung-hyo,
I have no power.
Talk it out with your mom.
Honestly, it's about that too,
but let's put him aside for now
and talk about you first.
What? What about me?
I'm worried about you.
Are you really okay
with closing the shop?
Of course, I'm okay.
You know I had a hard time.
I almost got scammed by those jerks too.
Gosh, the thought of being liberated
makes me so relieved.
It's like putting
a bunch of ice in your mouth
and crunching it on a hot day.
Then, that's a relief.
Still, if you become uneasy
or troubled by any chance,
you have to let me know.
What's our family's new motto?
"No more keeping troubles to yourself."
Yeah, that's it.
Good job, Dad.
Then, in that case,
are you going to hang out
with me more when I don't have work?
I am a little busy.
What?
So you're going to put me aside
and only hang out with Seung-hyo?
You little…
Don't even think of getting my approval.
Okay, I've persuaded you.
What?
What do I do about Mom?
Hey, I'm going to be
against it until the end.
Gosh, no way!
You're too precious to give up.
Honestly, it's true.
I have pretty eyes.
Jeez… I agree.
What was that?
You have pretty eyes,
but your nose is even prettier.
- Really?
- Let me see.
Look at that bridge.
It's as high as Mount Everest.
Come on. That's an exaggeration.
- It's unique. My nose takes after yours.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
- I have Mom's eyes.
Eyes? What are you talking about?
If I grow my hair out,
I'd look exactly like you.
Hi, Mr. Choi.
Hello.
- Am I late?
- Of course not.
We're here too. Hi!
What? Why are you two on-scene so early?
I'm more of an expert
on being on-scene than you.
I'll be responsible for your safety today.
In that case, I can write articles
and add wallpaper.
And I don't mean desktop wallpaper.
I mean actual wallpaper.
I'm in charge of the food.
You can't work on an empty stomach.
- Wow.
- Don't you need more skilled personnel?
- Hello.
- Myeong-u.
I mean, your intentions are good,
but as it stands, Seung-hyo will do
all the work by himself.
So you're here to help me?
Did you forget? I introduced you
to this volunteer group.
Okay, let's go! We must be quick
if we want to finish before sunset!
- Yes, sir.
- I'll sit in the back.
- I'll sit in the middle.
- Wow.
Okay.
Goodness.
Goodness, the walls are covered in mold.
We'll have to rip them out.
Goodness gracious.
There's no kitchen.
Does she cook with this portable stove?
The area out front is too dangerous.
The stairs are cracked too.
There's not enough space.
Will this be possible?
We'll have to try.
- It won't withstand it. It's too old.
- Really?
It'll be better if we put it here.
- Here?
- Yeah.
Wow.
Great job.
Dan-ho…
Keep holding that.
- Just a bit. Good, right?
- Yes.
- We can move over a bit more.
- Okay.
Hold on.
Who wants to put up wallpaper with me?
No one?
Me!
Fill the gaps. Yeah.
- Great job.
- Let's do our best.
Good, right?
There.
Goodness.
Is this really my house?
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Choi renovated your home.
I thought you'd need it
in your daily life.
We made you a mini kitchen.
You'll be able to cook here now.
There's a window here.
It was the first thing I thought
when I saw this house.
I wanted to give you a window.
Now, when you come home after work,
open the window first.
You can look at the sky
and take a deep breath.
Whenever I'd come home
after collecting scrap paper all day,
it would feel so suffocating.
I couldn't enjoy life
and spent each day just waiting to die.
I felt so trapped.
But I can truly live life now.
Ma'am.
If you look out front,
we made your stairway safer
and installed handrails.
That was Mr. Yoon's idea.
Yes, well…
It seemed a bit dangerous,
so always be careful.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Thank you so much.
- It's all right.
Hey, Jae-suk.
I called to see what you were up to.
What do you think?
I cleaned up after dinner.
If you're not doing anything,
want to come by the office?
- Right now?
- Yeah.
I got a bottle of wine as a gift today.
They said it's really nice.
Okay.
Since we're drinking expensive wine,
I put on a wine-colored lipstick…
- What are you doing here?
- Jae-suk called me here.
Did she call you too?
- What's going on?
- What?
What's going on?
What on earth? Was that the sound
of the door locking?
But we're still inside.
You brats! Listen up!
Jae-suk, what are you doing?
- We're the Suk Sisters…
- Hey! It's Lavender!
Right.
Lavender, formerly known as Suk Sisters.
The four of us met at 17,
and for 40 years,
we've been inseparable friends.
But you suddenly want to cut ties
and go your separate ways,
so how can we just sit back
and let that happen?
Yeah! That's not what friends do!
So we created an opportunity
for you to reconcile.
I didn't want you to get drunk and fight,
so I put grape juice
in the fridge instead of wine.
Hey, open the door. Open it now!
Hey, are you insane?
This is confinement, you know!
I'll open it in one hour,
so play nice until then.
Hey, wait! The bathroom!
What if we have to pee?
Hey, don't worry.
Look over there.
There's a chamber pot under the table.
My goodness, it really is there.
You crazy brat!
- Hey.
- Anyway, have a good time!
- Let's go!
- Open the door! Hey!
What do you take us for?
How can we pee in a chamber pot?
- Hey! Those little…
- Come on! Seriously…
I don't believe this.
I swear.
- Jeez.
- Come on!
I'm sorry about that day.
I think I spoke without thinking.
You probably said what you were thinking.
You didn't hold back anything at all.
Don't you see I'm apologizing first?
- Who asked you to?
- My heart did. What?
I mean…
We can't face Seung-hyo
and Seok-ryu like this.
We're being petty and immature.
I'm thirsty.
- Do you want some juice?
- No.
What if I need to pee?
You can use that.
Hey, can I have a sip too?
Have you ever thought about it?
About Seok-ryu and Seung-hyo
being together?
No, I never even imagined it.
I was so flustered.
What were you so flustered about?
It wasn't something expected.
So? What do you want to do?
What's there for us to do?
After hearing about it,
it seems they just started to date.
- Is that what Seung-hyo said?
- No.
It's not that.
What I mean is, let's wait
and respect what they choose to do.
Wait?
It sounds like you want them to break up.
So what I mean is
we shouldn't make
hasty judgments or decisions.
- Seok-ryu's been through a lot too.
- Like what?
Her canceled engagement? Or…
Her cancer?
Hey.
It seems you're trying
to find fault in Seok-ryu with that.
Forget it. I'm against it too.
I have no desire
to make him my son-in-law at all.
Hey, Mi-suk!
What on earth do you take me for?
Also, what's wrong with my son?
There's nothing wrong with him.
You're the problem!
You for a mother-in-law?
Wow, I'd be crazy to let
my daughter marry into that.
Hey! Are you done?
No, I have more to say!
If you can't fix that personality of yours
in this day and age,
Seung-hyo's going to be
on the fast track to die a bachelor.
Hey!
HYEREUNG REALTY
It should be over by now, right?
Let's open up and see.
Hey, I swear if I ever talk to you again,
I'll change my name.
Instead of Na Mi-suk, I'll be Ga Mi-suk.
Fine, change it. Go ahead.
Sure. Why don't you
go with Da Mi-suk then?
If I ever end up talking to you,
I'll bark. Woof, woof!
I'll become a dog.
Our plan failed.
Let's go.
Those darn brats.
Goodness!
STIR-FRIED TOMATO AND ACORN JELLY
She's gotten more views.
I'm currently sick, and I saw your video
while searching for healthy food.
It looks so good.
But I don't have the energy to cook,
so I can't make it.
It'd be nice if I could try your food.
Seung-hyo, come on out!
Professor Kim Chi-hun recommended us?
Yes, he said you were
the top architect these days
and praised you so much that I came here.
Coming from Gangnam,
the traffic was so bad.
Is there a reason why you built
your office outside of Seoul?
This is where I grew up.
A good location became available
while I was looking for a site.
Well…
There were rumors
of redevelopment in Hyereung-dong.
Do you know anything by any chance?
Sorry?
These days, finding trendy things
in run-down areas is all the rage.
I thought you may have heard
some premium information.
Well, we've heard about it too,
but it's just a rumor.
Nothing's really happening.
Yes, we didn't come here for that.
Then, that's disappointing.
I mean, I was hoping
you had a good feel for making money.
But it's surprising to hear you came here
simply because you liked the place.
I'm planning to put up a building.
I need someone who can deliver
as much value as I invest.
But if you're this out of touch
with reality, it'll be a problem.
On my way here,
the commercial area looked tiny.
And there was a shanty town off that way.
This area looked lousy.
I think it's best if you look
for a different architecture firm.
- Hey.
- Is that so?
You were right.
I don't think we're equipped
to meet what you're looking for.
It seems you're being like this
because I was a bit blunt.
Still,
you're going to refuse a referral?
- Yes, sir.
Turning down a project
won't really impact
our livelihood that much.
- Right?
- What?
We aim to work with clients
who align with our goals
and avoid those who don't.
How was that?
- Myeong-u, is this really okay?
- About what?
I mean, it's a building after all.
Won't it be a shame to turn it down?
You're the one who said
you wouldn't do it first.
Well, I wouldn't say that.
Still, how could you end things like that?
I mean, I've always been like this,
but you…
What about me?
What, am I someone who has a knack
for finding ways to make money?
Am I some monster born from capitalism,
always crunching numbers on a calculator?
Yeah.
But you're a rational pragmatist.
But what am I going to do?
I mean, I'm becoming more and more
of a romantic these days.
What are you talking about?
After the retirement community project
and the renovated shanty town house,
I started to think a lot.
How can I put it?
Working on something flashy
and extravagant
didn't make my heart feel as full.
That's right.
- Me too.
- Yeah.
Sometimes, I think this is why
I went into architecture.
You little punk.
Is this why you wanted
to build our office here?
You wanted to slowly change me,
didn't you?
Let's say I was looking
at the big picture.
But I need to enroll the twins
to an English academy.
And I want to buy
an apartment in Gangnam.
- Seok-ryu can teach them English.
- Yeah?
- And I'll build you a house.
- What?
Really? Okay, you promised.
A verbal contract is still a contract.
Go and write it down.
- I'll sign it.
- Hey! You reminded me.
I went to the district office
to turn in some documents. Look.
They had this.
"Our Neighborhood's Architect."
What's this?
It's a program at the district office.
They provide free consultations
for residents.
They also improve living conditions
for neglected spaces.
Like how you renovated
the shanty town house?
Yeah.
A lot of shops are closing
and old alleys are being abandoned.
They preserve neighborhood culture too.
Wow.
You'll become the protector
of Hyereung-dong.
I have to be selected first.
Of course, they'll select you.
What do you mean?
I heard construction for the pool
and gym will start soon.
That's pretty cool, Choisseung.
You're like the architect
in charge of Hyereung-dong.
Everyone calls me an architect,
but I'm actually a licensed architect.
The difference between the two is--
I should work harder too.
What?
Seeing you venture out like this
makes me want to do the same.
All I can do is make videos right now,
but I want to actually serve people
my food one day.
I want to cook pots of happiness for them.
I had no idea sitting with you like this
would become so awkward.
Did you want to see me
about Seok-ryu and Seung-hyo?
It's about our wives.
Right.
It's a full-scale war they're having.
I wouldn't be surprised
if nuclear bombs started falling.
As the neutral party,
shouldn't we try to settle them down?
Yes, you're right.
Then…
Yes, in situations like this,
instead of being so serious and sober,
we need a slightly more relaxed,
peaceful atmosphere.
Regardless of the time or place,
we always need this
for these types of conversations.
They say the truth
comes out when you drink.
Exactly!
Click, clack!
I guess we're having soju
instead of kaoliang today.
We can't always drink the expensive stuff!
Come on! My shop's closing!
We're shutting down and you ask for…
Or bring in something nice
to drink too then.
- Hey, did you hear?
- What?
Root Diner is closing.
Business was never good there.
They rarely had customers.
I know.
Flies didn't even touch their food.
Good grief!
Not only is her daughter jobless
but her husband's shop closed too.
- Goodness.
- I can't believe her luck.
- I know.
- Goodness.
- What's wrong with my luck?
M-Mi-suk!
I put kimchi in the ground the other day.
Today, I'll put you in the dirt!
You can bad-mouth me.
But my daughter and husband?
If you mess with my family, you'll pay!
- Goodness!
- Wait!
Hey, why aren't you budging? Darn it!
- What are you going to do about it?
- Goodness!
Hey!
What do you think you're doing? Well?
- Mi-suk, are you okay?
- Hey.
- Are you insane?
- Goodness.
- Hey!
- Jeez, why are you butting in?
- My goodness!
- You little… How dare you?
- Hey! I'm okay.
You're dead!
Let me go!
- What's with you?
- Jeez, stop it!
- What?
- You!
- Let go!
- Get out!
Are you insane?
Jeez, all she's good at is studying!
Now, this feels more like it!
- Hey!
- What on earth?
- Let go!
- Hey!
Hey!
HYEREUNG POLICE STATION
I mean, they're the ones…
- Hye-suk!
- Mi-suk!
Mi-suk, who did this?
- What's going on?
- Why did you two come together?
They reek of alcohol.
Wait, were you two together again?
No, not at all.
- No way. Where were you?
- Mom!
- Aunt Hye-suk!
- Hey!
- Are you two okay?
- Jeez, they keep coming in pairs.
Were you together too?
- Were you?
- You two pairs should be embarrassed.
You two are in no position
to talk that way.
It's not them, is it?
Hello. What are you doing here?
- Wait…
- Is that blood?
Are you okay? My goodness.
Why did you settle?
They were in the wrong first.
Just think of it as paying
for their treatment.
They were clearly the ones
who got badly beaten up.
That's right.
It'll take them two weeks to recover.
Honey, find a lawyer.
We're going to sue them for slander.
Still, seeing some action
after all this time was so refreshing.
Hey, you remember?
When that bully was shaking me down
in that back alley?
- You came.
- Yeah!
- And you saved me.
- That's right!
I took my backpack and lunchbox
and ran in swinging them at her.
That's what I did today.
- Yeah, you copied me.
- I remembered.
You hit the scariest lady
with the green onion.
- Her eye got so swollen.
- So swollen!
- She said she'd kill us.
- Mom, Aunt Mi-suk.
Have you two made up now?
What?
They have.
- Something's on my face?
- Yeah.
What is that?
What's with that basket?
I've never seen you carry
anything like that around before.
I have a lot of time now.
I should try to cook more at home.
It looks like you'll be wasting
ingredients for no reason.
Then, teach me.
I bought some bracken,
but I don't know how to cook it.
There's a bunch of good cookbooks.
Why learn from me?
The food you make tastes the best.
You can't teach the feel for cooking.
I'll cook it tomorrow, so just take it.
I swear…
I didn't think I'd ever get
to eat it again after we fought.
Goodness.
That's such a relief.
All you could think about
after we cut ties was bracken?
Of course. That dish is important to me.
You'd always make that dish first
for me whenever I came to Korea
and every time I left for work.
You'd always pack
a bunch of it in ice for me.
Gosh, when did I ever do that?
Whenever I opened a food container,
it overflowed with your friendship.
How could I ever forget that?
Why do you…
keep making me feel so small?
Fine, I'll be honest. I felt inferior.
You can speak English and French.
You communicated with locals
and earned a living abroad.
But I got paid to look after Seung-hyo.
It would've been nice to have looked after
your son without taking money.
Are you insane?
Why would you not take pay
for such priceless work?
Seung-hyo grew up well all thanks to you.
Raising a human being
is an incredible feat.
Not anyone can do it.
You did the same for me.
When I was eating lunch alone
after starting school,
you came over to me and said,
"I heard your name's Seo Hye-suk."
"We're short a Suk Sister member.
Want to join?"
That's why I'm not going to
be formal when we're in-laws.
- Hye-suk.
- Yeah, just call me by my name.
I'm going to call you by your name too.
That's what I'll do.
Even if our kids get married,
our friendship comes first.
Are you giving them your blessing?
Jeez.
I was never against them
in the first place.
Yeah, right! You looked so displeased.
Be honest.
It bothers you that Seok-ryu was sick.
Of course, it does!
Seok-ryu was sick,
so how could I not be worried?
She's your precious child.
The apple of your eye.
She's the daughter of my best friend.
You know how much I adore her.
How could I not care about her?
Goodness.
I didn't know you felt that way.
I was afraid
she'd be devastated if you said no.
After she was sick and alone
in a foreign land, I had to protect her.
Mi-suk.
I'll protect her with you.
Just like how you raised Seung-hyo,
I'll love and take care of Seok-ryu too.
Thanks.
I'm so grateful.
I'm more grateful.
- No, I am.
- You brat.
I'm so sorry I hit you back then.
It hurt.
You silly brat.
- Goodness.
- What are they doing?
Hey, we know you're there.
Come on out.
Seriously.
- How long have you been back there?
- Goodness, Seok-ryu.
You've always been so smart
and dependable since you were young.
Maybe we were meant to be.
Take care of Seung-hyo for me.
Okay, I will.
- Seung-hyo.
- Goodness.
You know you're half my son, right?
Of course.
If Seok-ryu hits and bothers you,
you can tell me.
- I'll punish her.
- You can tell on him too.
- Okay.
- Got it? Tell me everything.
They say as men age,
there's an increase in estrogen,
and they cry more too.
Is it true, Gyeong-jong?
To be precise, testosterone decreases.
The ratio of estrogen
increases relatively.
I can't look at them.
Do you have any meds?
I can't stand them!
What's wrong with those two?
What happened?
They're always hanging out
and drinking together these days.
- Yeah, they're weird.
- Sit down.
Honey, snap out of it. Stop crying.
Poor Dad.
Hey. Where are the kids?
I think they're still sleeping.
I see.
- I'm off.
- Okay.
How does it feel to go
to work for the last time?
Well, it feels the same.
Close up and come home early today.
Let's have some soju.
Okay.
Bye.
Great work.
Ms. Jung,
the director's looking for you.
- Me?
- Yes.
Congratulations.
For what?
Goodness.
How will you adapt in such a far-off place
if you're that clueless?
- What?
- Ms. Jung.
You've been selected as the safety officer
for the South Pole research station.
- Wow!
Me? Really?
I just got the official letter.
You're the first-ever woman selected.
Wow.
In two weeks,
on-site adaptation training will start.
- Job training and orientation too.
- Yes, sir.
After that, you'll leave
at the start of next month.
What? That quickly?
Yeah, get ready.
Now, let's give her a round of applause.
Thank you.
Jeez, my last day's a bust too.
Goodness!
- Are you open?
- Of course.
You can sit wherever you'd like.
Okay, here you go.
I didn't order the fish cakes.
What?
It's on the house.
Enjoy.
You gave me an extra fish cake
in the past too.
What?
I lived in this neighborhood
ten years ago.
Is that so?
I came to eat tteokbokki
after bombing my finals.
You gave me fish cakes
and told me to cheer up.
Really? I did that?
I came to meet a friend and stopped by.
You and the fish cakes haven't changed.
- Have one more.
- No, that's okay.
- Do you want some sundae?
- No, it's fine.
I want to give you some.
To be honest, today's my last day.
CLOSING AFTER SEPTEMBER 13
I see.
I would've regretted it if I didn't come.
Thank you for the food.
- Honey.
- Dad, we're here.
What brings you here?
What do you think?
We're here to eat your tteokbokki.
I don't think we're the only customers.
What? You're all here?
We came for some deep-fried food.
Honey, what did you say was good?
The deep-fried peppers.
You still have some left, right?
Gosh, what on earth is going on? Goodness.
- Hello!
- The shop's too small.
- Where will you sit?
- We're here too!
- Goodness.
- Sit down.
Yeon-du, you haven't had
tteokbokki yet, right?
That's right!
Yeon-du, you're so lucky.
The first tteokbokki you'll ever have
will be from Root Diner!
If you put the tables together,
move them back when you leave.
- All right, already!
- Fine!
Stop it, Mom!
I'll do it.
That's why I have these muscles.
There we go!
He takes after me.
What's going on?
Are we the last ones here?
- We came right after work.
- Hello.
And you are?
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Kang Dan-ho from The Chungwoo Daily.
What's a reporter doing here?
Well…
He's my boyfriend.
- Gross.
- Goodness.
Who knew she was such a cute fool?
She's so adorable.
- Thank you for coming.
- No, it's fine.
I'm preparing a special article
on retirement.
If it's okay with you,
could I interview you?
Me?
Goodness.
This is my first time.
- Cheers!
First…
You're about to retire,
so how does it feel?
Well…
I don't really know.
I cut vegetables and make broth.
Then, I soak the rice cakes.
I did that every morning.
Once I stop and become comfortable,
maybe it'll start to sink in then.
I'm sure it will.
So now that you're about to retire,
what do you regret the most?
Also, what are you looking forward
to the most?
Regret?
To be honest, what I regret is…
I don't think I regret anything.
Honestly… Goodness.
So many things didn't go my way.
But that's life, you know?
Yeah.
Rather,
I have more happy memories of this place.
Gosh.
"It tastes good."
I loved hearing that.
Also, what I look forward to is…
My family.
I've been busy my whole life
and used that as an excuse.
Finally,
it feels like
I can return
to my family now.
What would you like to tell yourself
after all the hard work you've done?
Well…
"Great job."
"You worked hard,
Bae Geun-sik."
ROOT DINER
My goodness!
Hey.
Why are you still here?
Did you think we'd leave you?
We said we'd clean up with you.
I needed some time to myself.
Yeah, Mom.
Respect a man's need for solitude.
Dad, did you say farewell
to your beloved shop?
Yeah, it was a passionate goodbye.
Great. Let's go home now.
Let's go!
And we're off!
You're really unemployed now.
- Yeah.
- What will you do tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Hey, son. Let's go play billiards.
I have to study for my exam tomorrow.
You punk. One day won't decide
if you pass or fail.
Hey!
Seriously? He wants to study.
Don't interfere with that!
Dong-jin hasn't studied in so long.
Look at this.
Did you see your mom, Seok-ryu?
She's already looking down on me
for being unemployed.
Stop. Let them have each other.
Let's play badminton tomorrow.
- Badminton? I don't want to play with you.
- Yeah, I get it.
You're going to keep playing
until you win!
- That's right!
- No, I don't.
Dad, don't do it. I got stuck playing
board games with her for seven hours once.
Hey, that was because
you kept buying the best spot!
Gosh, I'm exhausted
from staying up this late.
Hold on. Don't be rude
to your sister like that!
- That's right, you punk!
- What did I do?
- What?
- You punk!
- You too!
- Don't say that to your kid brother.
- Yeah.
- Don't call him a punk.
- He's my child too.
- Yeah, but…
Okay, fine. Hey, you wimp!
Seok-ryu.
Choisseung!
Why are you here alone? It's dangerous.
I was waiting for you.
I thought being with family was
the right thing tonight, so I didn't call.
How's your dad? Is he okay?
He took some soju
to the rooftop with my mom.
That's nice.
Having someone
by your side on a day like this…
I have something for you.
What? What is it?
It's sanjeok.
I tried to give this to you before,
but I couldn't.
I can't believe I didn't eat it back then.
I ruined my own luck.
- Can I try one?
- Yeah.
Wow.
It's so good.
Of course.
I prepared and cooked the tree onions,
bellflowers, carrots, and beef one by one.
I put them on skewers
and covered them in egg wash.
It was a lot of work.
It looks like it.
And it smelled like oil so much.
I thought I had become
one with cooking oil.
Gosh, you worked so hard.
Yeah.
But still,
despite that,
I'll always make it for you.
Unless you tell me you're sick of them,
I'll make sanjeok for you forever.
I'm so lucky.
This is my proposal.
I mean, I thought
being proposed to twice was a bit much.
So I wanted to balance it out.
Does that mean
I can eat rainbows forever?
Yeah, all colors of the rainbow.
Whatever color you want
and as much as you want.
That's the sweetest proposal in the world.
So, is that a yes?
Yes. Gladly.
Thank you.
For what?
For everything.
For back then and now.
Everything.
LOVE NEXT DOOR
- My eyes!
- It's not weird stuff.
We legitimately have official approval
from both families now.
There's no time to waste if we want to
catch up on 30 years of romance.
Let's go on a date. Don't worry.
You'll be safe next to me.
Why won't she be around?
She was assigned to the South Pole.
Seung-hyo.
Help me out, Myeong-u.
I want to get married too.
You two are becoming in-laws?
Let's have the wedding next spring.
Why? Strike while the iron's hot.
Just do it before the year's end.
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce