NO TAIL TO TELL
Anyway…
I WILL GRANT YOUR WISH
…what's this?
Oh, that.
Hey, Woo-seok.
By any chance,
do you have a wish?
A wish?
Why? Are you going to grant it?
No, it's not that. Actually--
It's fine.
It's my life, so I'll handle it myself.
I should get going now, Si-yeol.
By the way…
Congrats on the contract renewal.
Hey…
- Hey, Yeon-su.
- Si-yeol, we've got a problem.
Now what?
What's all the fuss about?
Thames FC is facing relegation.
What on earth are you talking about?
Relegation? We won the league last season.
They're voiding last season's title,
stripping us of our Champions League spot,
and relegating us to the Championship.
Is it April Fools' Day?
I'm serious.
Apparently, Thames violated
Financial Fair Play regulations,
so UEFA just slapped them with sanctions.
Explain it in simple terms.
What exactly is "Financial Fair Play"?
It's a UEFA rule stating
that a club can't spend more than
a certain percentage of its revenue.
I still don't get it.
Basically, the club
committed accounting fraud
to cover your transfer fee
and massive salary.
So what am I supposed to do now?
Will you play in the second division?
Are you crazy? I'm Kang Si-yeol.
Then there's only one option left.
What the…
KANG SI-YEOL
THAMES FC REFUSES TRANSFER
KANG SI-YEOL FACES A MAJOR CRISIS
SECOND DIVISION NEXT FOR KANG SI-YEOL?
THAMES FC CHARGED
WITH VIOLATING FFP REGULATIONS
This won't do.
Your passport's at home, right?
I'll have someone bring it over.
Let's head to the airport right now.
I don't think staying in Korea
will solve anything.
Okay, find the earliest flight
available right now.
What are you doing? Let's hurry.
Yeah, I'm coming.
NOVEMBER 20TH
ANNIVERSARY OF GRANDMA'S DEATH
DEACON KIM BOK-SUN
MAY SHE REST IN PEACE
Ms. Kim.
It didn't look like Si-yeol would make it
again this year, so I came instead.
Gosh, you know how busy he is.
Still, seeing how he timed his return,
it seems like he really meant
to come this year.
But something came up,
so he's probably
out of the country right now.
Hey, you…
Grandma, I'm here.
Looks like Woo-seok's been coming
to see you, Grandma.
He won't even see me these days.
GARDEN OF PEACE MEMORIAL PARK
I know
you looked after my grandma for me,
visiting her every holiday
and taking her to the hospital.
That's because you were abroad.
You were there when she passed too.
And you've been bringing her flowers
every year on her anniversary.
Hey, why are you getting all sappy?
That's the kind of friend you are to me.
You can tell me anything, okay?
If you ever need help, I've got your back.
If you need money, I can give you--
That's why I'm avoiding you right now.
I don't want…
to ask you for favors
or borrow money from you.
I want us to stay friends.
Even if you're a Premier League player,
no matter how famous you are,
I want us to be friends for who we are.
But if I start asking you for things
or relying on you for help,
I wouldn't be able to see you
as a friend anymore.
- Woo-seok--
- Let's stop talking about this.
Just think of it
as giving me some space for now.
But seriously,
is it really okay for you to be here?
Actually, my agent's already in the UK.
I said I'd stop by my grandma's grave,
then head there right away.
Do you think things will work out?
It doesn't look good right now.
The only option is to meet
and convince them,
but neither the chairman
nor the coach will see my agent.
Jeez, another reporter.
I'd better go.
I should go see what I can do.
Hey, wait.
You dropped this.
What is this?
I WILL GRANT YOUR WISH
Are you into this kind of stuff lately?
Isn't this like a cult or something?
Oh, right.
Woo-seok.
I think…
there might be a way.
The player is determined to transfer.
But Thames FC is refusing
to negotiate at all.
We offered
a 180 million euro transfer fee,
but they reiterated
that he isn't for sale.
I WILL GRANT YOUR WISH
Hey, what are you doing? That's dangerous.
I'm pretty sure
this is how I was told to do it.
Are you okay?
Why isn't it working?
You summoned me sooner
than I expected, Si-yeol.
Then again, the more humans have,
the greedier they get,
and the bigger their worries become.
That's why they always end up
needing beings like me.
So, tell me.
What's this great wish of yours?
EPISODE 3
THE RISE AND FALL
THAMES FC, LONDON, UK
That's none of your business.
I heard there's a nice pub nearby.
If you're done for the day,
why don't you stop by?
I couldn't even get him to see me,
and now I just run into him here?
So,
the real reason the Geumsu Group heir
turned himself in nine years ago
was because of that person… I mean…
Nine-tailed fox.
Right.
It was because of that nine-tailed fox?
Yeah.
I can't believe it,
but I can't say I don't believe it either.
But still,
she said she'd grant your wish,
and that's it?
She just listened and disappeared.
I know.
I'm not sure what's going on either.
RECENT WITHDRAWALS
What the…
What is it?
Did she really fix things?
No, but money was taken out of my account.
Out of the blue? How much?
- One hundred million won.
- What?
What the hell?
Hey, is your account
still getting drained?
Could it be a phone scam?
Hello?
Si-yeol, it's all settled.
You're clear for the transfer.
Really?
Yeah. I just ran into the chairman,
and it was like he was possessed.
He agreed to your transfer
and wants to know your preferred team.
He said he'll give
your negotiations top priority.
What did she say?
So can you transfer?
Really?
It's settled? Just like that?
Yeah.
Just like that.
- Hey, that's Kang Si-yeol.
- Hello.
Hello.
Si-yeol!
Hey, Woo-seok.
What are you doing here?
Si-yeol, can I really
ask you for a favor?
Of course.
The truth is,
I don't want to quit like this.
I want to play professionally,
and I want to play
for the national team too.
I really want
to live my life differently, just once.
Do you think…
that if I made a wish like you did,
it could come true?
I don't think so.
Why not?
Wishes always come with a price.
The bigger the wish,
the greater the price.
But your friend here
has nothing to offer.
Does that price have to be money?
What, are you thinking
of offering up your soul?
If that's what it takes, then yes.
Really? What use would that be to me?
Typical humans.
Always falling for tired clichés.
Is there really no other way?
I'll do whatever it takes.
You clearly have this all wrong.
You're not qualified to be my client.
Do you understand?
That means that you have nothing
of any value to me.
And you.
You think I'm a charity or something?
Don't ever summon me
for something this petty.
How insolent.
Don't go. We're not finished yet.
What?
You talk a big game,
but it all comes down to money in the end.
What are you getting at?
I'll pay for him.
That should settle it, right?
- No.
- Why not?
You have to pay the price
for your own wish.
But if you pay for him,
you're basically giving him your wish.
What's wrong with that?
What's wrong is that it's a good deed.
Maybe I forgot to tell you,
but I have only one principle.
I avoid doing even the smallest good deed
and only avoid doing major misdeeds.
I'd hate to cultivate more virtue
and end up becoming human.
Come on, stop making excuses.
- Excuses?
- That sure sounds like one.
You came to me first
to help catch that hit-and-run driver.
If that's not a good deed, then what is?
You know,
I think you'll need to make a wish.
Wish for it. I'll grant it for you.
What kind of principle is that, anyway?
Well, that was--
Just do it.
Unless it's beyond your capability.
"Beyond my capability"?
Come to think of it,
our first meeting was way too friendly.
That's why you're being so reckless
and pushing your luck.
Fine. I'll grant the wish.
But how I choose to grant it is up to me.
And of course, you'll pay the price.
Any problems with that?
I AM KANG SI-YEOL
Ladies and gentlemen.
We are experiencing sudden turbulence.
All passengers, please remain seated
until further notice.
DRIVEN BY YOUR TRUST
BEYOND SATISFACTION
Wake up, you bastard!
Hey!
What the…
Where am I?
FOREVER CARE NURSING HOME
What is this?
Did you sleep well, Si-yeol?
What's going on right now?
What happened?
Why am I suddenly here?
You made a wish, so a price must be paid.
What?
Wait, what does Woo-seok's wish
have to do--
Didn't I tell you?
I can grant the wish,
but how I do it is up to me.
Once again, your wish has been granted.
What do you mean,
my wish has been granted?
Where is Woo-seok right now?
What?
What the…
Here.
You dropped this, Mr. Hyeon.
Oh, I see.
But how do you know my name?
Of course I know you.
Everyone in Korea knows who you are.
Right.
Wait, what?
What do you mean…
Excuse me?
What is this?
"Hyeon Woo-seok."
Why am I…
Fine. I'll grant the wish.
But how I choose to grant it is up to me.
Well, let's see.
Your friend is probably
where you're supposed to be right now.
Oh, come on.
Stop talking in riddles.
You're not making any sense.
What does Woo-seok's wish have to do
with me being here?
I guess it hasn't sunk in yet.
That's understandable.
But you know…
I'm a bit busy right now.
I have another client waiting.
Sadly, I don't have the time
to explain everything.
Are you kidding me? I was on a plane to--
You'll understand exactly
what's going on soon enough.
So, we'll finish this later.
Jeez, what now?
Wait.
Where'd she go?
Seriously?
Hey, Si-yeol. I know you're in there!
Si-yeol, open the door.
- Si-yeol!
- What the hell?
I know you're in there.
- Open the door, Si-yeol.
- Si-yeol!
See, I told you he was here.
- Open the door already. Jeez.
- What took you so long?
Hey, have you been drinking?
- What?
- No way.
You know Si-yeol doesn't drink.
He's really disciplined.
Look. There are empty bottles everywhere.
This place is a mess.
He must've been having a rough time.
Hey.
This is why I told you
not to let soccer consume your life.
Who are you people? What is this?
Do we know each other?
Of course, and that's exactly why
we're here to pick you up.
I've got all his things.
Good. Let's go now.
Go where? I'm not going anywhere!
Who the hell are you guys?
Why won't anyone
give me a straight answer?
Si-yeol, come on. Let's go.
Just apologize to the coach.
Apologize for what? To whom?
Just apologize.
You're such a hothead.
Lift him up.
- One, two, three!
- Wait, hold on!
- Let's go.
- Let go of me! I said let go!
Let go. Stop it!
Hey, that hurts! Let me go!
I'm not going anywhere!
Hey.
Welcome.
I was wondering who it was.
It's been a while.
I had this specially ordered
from the hotel patisserie.
They say this is all the rage
with young people these days.
I hope you like it.
Gosh, you didn't have to bring anything,
especially considering
how much you brought.
Not bad.
This is why I like familiar faces.
It's just a shame
they keep dying of old age.
I hope you live a long life, Chairman Kim.
I guess you were taming a new client.
Yes.
This client is clueless and rude,
so I'm taking extra care
to tame him properly.
I like the scent.
That fellow must be suffering quite a bit.
- My gosh.
- Anyway, Chairman Kim.
You've lived a long life
and have everything.
And yet, you want more?
You've grown greedy with age.
Actually,
I didn't come to see you
because I have a wish.
You didn't?
Then what do you want from me?
Seriously.
Who are you guys?
I've asked you so many times.
What's with you today?
Knock it off, already.
You fought with the coach, not us.
You can't just dump us
like a bad investment.
You're not really quitting soccer
like this, are you?
What are you talking about?
Why would I quit?
I'm Kang Si-yeol.
I know you're Kang Si-yeol.
That's why we came to pick you up.
What does he think he is, royalty?
You'd never see a player
throw a water bottle at their coach,
even in the Premier League.
He didn't actually throw it at the coach.
He threw it nearby,
but it just bounced off the wall
and hit him, right?
No way.
When this jerk threw the bottle
at the coach,
I saw it in his eyes. He lost it.
He was aiming right at him.
Come on, Si-yeol isn't that crazy.
Hey! He is crazy!
This is driving me crazy.
Hey.
Are you guys on the national team?
I've never even seen any of you before.
Did Coach Gonzalez tell you
to bring me in?
Wow, I think he really has gone crazy.
- Si-yeol.
- I told you he's crazy.
Whatever, forget it.
Whoever you are,
I need to get to London now.
- So take me to the airport.
- London? Why?
Jeez, don't you guys even watch the news?
I'm in the middle
of transfer negotiations.
Really?
And where exactly are you transferring to?
To a Sunday league team?
Hey, Beom, that's a bit harsh.
Si-yeol,
don't let your pride get in the way.
Just go to the coach
and beg for forgiveness.
- Jeez!
- Seriously!
Who am I even supposed to beg,
and for what?
- Oh, come on!
- Just beg.
- Who am I supposed to beg?
- Knock it off.
- I'm getting out!
- Hold on tight!
- Stay still!
- Hold on to him!
Last night,
the wooden-handled dagger
that was here disappeared.
I remembered you'd come by
from time to time and just stare at it.
I felt it was only right to let you know.
There's a story behind this object,
isn't there?
Yes, there is.
Do you have a family, Chairman Kim?
Yes, I have a wife and children.
I had an older sister.
We weren't related by blood, but…
Grandma.
We spent a thousand years together,
cultivating ourselves.
We were like family.
Be happy, Geum-ho.
My lady!
My lady, something terrible has happened!
There are people outside--
Open the gates at once!
- Oh no!
- Oh my!
This is the house of a traitor!
Capture every single one of them!
That way!
Chun-sim!
I can't let you in.
The swordsmith is occupied at the moment.
If you have business at the forge,
try somewhere else.
What are you planning to do?
Are you forging the Sajin Ritual Blade?
What are you planning to use it for?
I guess I came to the right place, then.
You ignored me when I asked for your help
even though I told you
I saw a miserable future for Geum-ho.
But look, you chased me down like this.
It's a human life.
A life that Geum-ho
has to endure on her own.
This isn't something you should meddle in.
Don't make me laugh.
It's been a thousand years.
She spent a thousand years
cultivating herself and doing good deeds.
Is it right for the human life
she was rewarded with
to be nothing but misery and misfortune?
Is that Heaven's so-called will?
So making her commit a sin
and undoing a thousand years
of spiritual training
was the solution you came up with?
Yes. Her family was branded as traitors
and condemned to live as slaves.
Her husband will be beaten to death,
and her children will starve,
sicken, and die.
And she will grow old
having to watch it all happen.
Anything would be better than that.
Geum-ho.
THE SAJIN RITUAL BLADE
Stab him with this. You have to.
- "Him"?
- I'm talking about your husband.
You're not happy at all living as a human.
You're miserable.
If you kill the one you love
with that dagger,
they say you can return
to being a nine-tailed fox.
Eun-ho.
I have a wish. Could you grant it for me?
Of course. What is it?
Promise me that you'll grant it.
Very well. Go on.
Don't ever
appear before me again.
That dagger
was the last thing I gave Geum-ho.
It's also one of the very few
sacred objects that can kill me.
DAEHEUNG CITIZENS FC
FIRST HOME GAME OF THE SEASON
- Jeez.
- Damn it.
Hurry up!
- Who is it?
- Good afternoon, Coach.
Wait, why should I beg…
K4 LEAGUE DAEHEUNG CITIZENS FC
EMBLEM CONTEST
Just stay in here already! Damn it!
Wait…
DAEHEUNG CITIZENS FC
For crying out loud.
What do you want?
Hey, Yong-gil!
"Yong-gil"?
What are you doing here? And…
A black eye…
"Black eye"?
Where's Coach Gonzalez?
Why on earth
are you looking
for the national team coach?
I don't know. You tell me.
A bunch of weirdos showed up earlier
and kept telling me
to apologize to the coach.
So you're saying the coach
you need to apologize to
is Gonzalez and not me?
What are you talking about?
Why would I apologize to you?
Where even am I?
Hey, Yong-gil,
it's been a while. Aren't you
even going to offer me some coffee?
This little…
He's lost his mind.
Listen, Si-yeol.
What do you think you're doing?
Is this some kind of protest?
What's your problem?
Is this because I called you by name?
Don't you remember?
You said I could call you
by your name and not "Coach."
Hey!
Why are you yelling at me?
Why would
a fourth-division player like you
be looking for the national team coach?
"Fourth division"?
Me?
But I'm Kang Si-yeol.
I was ready to give you a second chance
if you came here
and begged for forgiveness.
But never mind. You're off the team!
This is ridiculous.
Anyone would think you were my coach.
Fine, kick me off the team!
Fine, you… No. You know what?
I'm going to ban you
from the sport, you punk!
You? Ban me? There's no way.
Do whatever you want!
Kick me off the team. Ban me for life.
That black eye
really knocked something loose.
Unbelievable!
What's wrong with him?
That little…
- Hey, did you apologize?
- Did he say you can return to training?
You didn't cause more trouble, did you?
Be honest with me.
Is this a hidden camera prank?
What?
This is for YouTube, right?
Whose channel is it?
You shouldn't be doing this
just for views. I'm Kang Si-yeol.
What's with him today?
You can't do this.
Even if you're desperate for views,
you need to ask first.
- I'm borrowing this.
- Wait…
- What…
- What's going on?
It wasn't just the cameras.
The whole security system
went down briefly.
Do you have any idea
what might have happened?
It doesn't make any sense, sir.
Everything was normal
during our last patrol.
Looks like your memory was erased.
Pardon?
You really didn't notice anything unusual?
No, ma'am. We patrol in pairs--
Look me in the eye.
Are you sure you didn't notice
anything unusual?
Well…
Actually, there was someone.
It was a man.
- Sir!
- Stay out of this.
A man?
Was he alone?
Yes. I tried to stop him
and asked how he got in--
He's under a binding spell.
I didn't realize there were still humans
who could use techniques like that.
A human?
Can a human do such a thing?
It's not something just anyone can do.
A mere human
mimicking the powers of a deity
will pay a steep price.
Why would someone like that
need the wooden-handled dagger?
Could they be…
trying to harm you?
Do you really think a human
who's learned a few cheap tricks like this
could actually harm me?
Sure, I'd die if I were stabbed.
But how would he even do that?
I'd like to see him try.
That's a relief then.
So what should we do?
I'm not sure.
But let me take a look at him first.
ADVANCING CORRECTIONS FOR THE FUTURE
HUMAN-CENTERED CORRECTIONS
MINISTRY OF JUSTICE
It's been a while.
Seeing you out here,
you look like a different person.
TWO YEARS AGO
There's no need to search
this cell so thoroughly.
- Excuse me?
- Jeez, come with me.
Inmate 478, anything to report?
Inmate 133 has
cigarettes stashed in his cell.
Inmate 2759 is making flower cards
out of cardboard.
And as for Inmate 1614…
You little piece of shit!
- You little bastard!
- Why did this jerk end up in our cell?
Damn it!
You crazy bastard.
Hey, I heard your father disowned you.
You're nothing now, you piece of shit.
Hey, look at me when I'm talking to you.
- I should poke your eyes out!
- That's enough.
What did you just say, old man?
Hey, you just got here,
so you clearly don't know how things work.
- Mind your own damn business.
- I said, that's enough.
I've got business with this guy.
Is he out of his mind?
What's going on?
What the…
We need to talk.
Who the hell are you?
It's a bit cramped in here.
Why don't we go for a walk?
So you're not human either?
I'm human.
That doesn't make sense. How…
How could a human…
Why wouldn't a human
be able to do what a mere fox can do?
It's just a little tricky, that's all.
Take this.
What is it?
A warding sigil.
It's a talisman to ward off evil.
As long as you have this on you,
the nine-tailed fox's spell
won't affect you.
No need to thank me.
But when you get out,
let's do a job together.
Jeez.
Where are we going?
I told you before.
I said let's do a job together
once you get out.
What exactly is this "job"?
It's nothing difficult.
You just need to act as bait.
- What?
- Starting now,
I'm going on a fox hunt.
JOSEON-ERA INK-WASH PAINTING
DEPICTING COMMERCIAL ACTIVITY
You there, painter.
I was thinking of commissioning something.
I don't have anything to offer,
but I can buy you a drink.
I heard someone took the dagger
from over there last night.
Could you do a quick sketch of him for me?
Why isn't Woo-seok picking up?
I don't think you're a resident here.
Oh, it's me.
I've never seen you before.
Which unit are you visiting?
- Pardon?
- What?
Come on now.
What?
Who are you?
I'm sorry. I thought this was my home.
Wait, this is my home.
What a weirdo.
Oh my goodness!
- Wait.
- What are you doing?
Who are you? Why are you in my--
What is wrong with you? Are you crazy?
Excuse me.
- Sir, this woman--
- Sir, this man--
This guy's really asking for trouble.
- Who are you?
- What's wrong with you?
Don't you recognize me?
How on earth would I know who you are?
- Come on, get out.
- Wait a second!
That's enough. Out!
Wait…
Oh my goodness!
What's going on?
Excuse me!
- This is my home.
- Do something!
- Yes, ma'am.
- My gosh!
- Excuse me.
- This really is my home.
He's just…
This isn't possible.
What's wrong with him? Hey!
- Are you out of your mind?
- Oh my!
No, this seriously isn't possible.
Come on! I told you to get out!
I'm very sorry about this.
Come on, let's go!
What is all this?
It's a trap.
I told you, I'm going on a fox hunt.
You can catch a nine-tailed fox with this?
All you have to do is set the right bait.
A wicked creature like that
can never escape
once it's trapped in this sacred rope.
Why are you doing all this?
Do you have a grudge
against the nine-tailed fox too?
A hunter doesn't hunt
because of a personal grudge.
What are you doing?
Shut your mouth and stay still.
We don't want to jinx it.
What is this?
You.
Food's here. Go on and stuff your face!
What is that?
It's the vengeful spirit
of a starved wild dog.
What?
- Roll up your sleeve.
- Pardon?
- Are you crazy? What are you doing?
- Roll it up.
Damn it.
Stay still.
That dog needs to pick up
the fox scent all over you.
The protective talisman you have
masks the fox's scent.
If you're done stuffing your face,
it's time to earn your keep.
This guy is under the fox's spell.
Don't move a muscle
unless you want to be torn to pieces.
Here.
Now, go and find out where that fox is.
SOLLENFORD AIRPORT, LONDON, UK
ONLY WOO-SEOK!
LOVE YOU FOREVER
WOO-SEOK
Woo-seok.
Dad?
Why are you here, Dad?
What do you mean?
Where else would I be?
I see.
Right.
Wait, listen to me. I'm not some weirdo.
I'm telling you that really is my home.
Hey, wait…
But do you seriously not know me?
Don't you watch soccer?
Don't you know Kang Si-yeol,
the world's best athlete?
What did you do
to get yourself thrown in here already?
You!
Perfect timing. Hold on a moment.
- Hey, you.
- Yes?
Find someone who looks like this.
Use any means necessary.
Yes, ma'am.
Do you understand what's going on now?
Damn it.
What did you do to me?
I guess not yet.
All right. I'll fill you in now.
I switched your fates.
What?
So, in this world,
the Kang Si-yeol you knew is gone.
Because your fate has changed.
Just tell me what's going on!
What does no one recognizing me
have to do with Woo-seok's wish?
And what happened to my house?
That's the price you paid
for your friend's wish.
For every rise, there must be a fall.
For someone to take the throne,
someone else
must be stripped of their crown.
That's the law of the world.
Not even I can change that.
So,
when you say
our fates have been switched…
Since someone became
a world-class soccer player,
someone else had to step down.
That's the only way
to maintain the balance.
Then…
it wasn't just a dream?
The past was rewritten.
Naturally, the present followed suit.
No way in hell.
So I really am a fourth-division player?
Are you kidding me? You…
What's the problem?
I made your friend a world-class player
who plays in the European leagues
and for the national team.
Isn't that enough?
That's what you both wished for.
"Enough"? The hell it is! I'm literally…
Whatever. Just put everything back
the way it was. Right now.
- I'm afraid I can't do that.
- Why the hell not?
Because you have nothing left
to pay for a wish.
You have no money,
and the life you built is gone.
Then…
I have to keep living like this?
Well, there is a way.
What is it?
What's going on?
This is my place in London.
Gosh.
This is our house? For real?
- Woo-seok.
- Oh gosh.
What has he been going on about?
Of course this is our house.
It's simple.
All your friend needs to do
is make a wish, just like you did.
A wish to switch your fates back.
What?
Woo-seok.
Have you thought about it?
About what?
Your transfer. Where do you want to go?
They said they'll match
any contract terms we want.
So,
you just have to make the final call.
I can go…
anywhere I want?
Of course, you're Hyeon Woo-seok.
But I wonder
if your friend
would actually make that wish?
For your sake?
He finally has the life
he's always dreamed of.
He's only just started living it.
Why…
are you doing this to me?
I can't stand humans
who get cocky with me.
To be my client,
I needed to teach you some manners first.
That's it?
Do you think it's okay
to toy with people's lives like this?
Why are you getting so worked up?
Everything can be easily fixed
if your friend makes the wish.
What's wrong?
You don't trust your friend either?
Actually, I'm curious too.
Let's see how your friend
decides to play this.
NO TAIL TO TELL
Si-yeol, just one month.
Let's switch back in a month.
Hyeon Woo-seok! Oh, come on!
No, no.
Are you saying
I have to keep living like this?
I'm going to burn this place down!
Put me down!
I can't live like that. I won't, damn it!
Have you learned your lesson?
Put me back! Please.
Well, that should do it.
I guess I've tamed you enough.
Shall we end this here?
Is it good?
Where to?
I'm sorry. I thought this was a taxi.
You have the wish-granting
business card, don't you?
I have some business with that fox.
Get up, Kang Si-yeol.
Subtitle translation by Susanna Kim