Characters, actions, places,
occupations, and events in this series
are fictional and created for
entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any
behavior in the series. Viewer discretion is advised.
If I knew Bambi's mom owns this brand,
I wouldn't take this job.
I didn't want to put you in a tough spot.
I can handle it. Don't worry.
Prim, I don't want her
to be in the room anymore.
Those who have good taste
always fall for me.
Sorry.
So I'll choose to be
a person with bad taste tonight.
Are you crying for that jerk?
You are so wasted.
I'm your client.
But it doesn't seem to work.
I guess I have to come up with a new plan.
6 MONTHS EARLIER
Off keeps changing his mind.
My shoot keeps getting delayed.
I have an appointment after this.
Be patient.
Off is a renowned photographer.
Even if he's a renowned photographer,
he should respect other people's time.
Okay, okay. I'll tell him to speed up.
Okay.
Come here.
Yes.
What is this?
This doesn't match the concept.
You approved it in the meeting.
I did that?
Did you bring the wrong outfit?
This is not what you presented
in the meeting.
I didn't bring the wrong one.
The color, the size, and the design
are exactly what you have approved.
I don't like it. I want to change it.
Young stylists are not professional
and prepared.
I'm not prepared?
The color, the size, and the design
are exactly what you have ordered me.
Do you forget what you've ordered?
Watch your mouth
if you don't want to lose your job.
Do as you want.
If I lose my job here,
I'll just go home and sell noodles.
It'll be better than working with a
renowned photographer with goldfish memory
who shows no respect to his coworkers.
Damn.
She's got the guts.
No one dares to talk back to him.
Who is the stylist?
Her name is Gorya.
Excuse me. I've got to go.
I've been waiting for over two hours.
I have an appointment.
Sha.
Shasha.
Damn it.
Gorya.
We keep running into each other.
I guess our tastes are more similar
than you think.
I don't think so.
This shop is viral on social media.
Everyone comes here.
I never thought a model like you
would like vintage stuff.
I like many kinds of things.
I like both new items
from luxurious brands
and used items that no one wants.
When they are in my hand,
their value will go up.
Those who hide behind a fake shell…
Will never get honesty from anyone.
What you are looking for
is a casual relationship.
Maybe you should follow your heart.
Follow my heart?
The same way you're still waiting for
your talented director?
Are you going to wait for her
to break up with her ex again?
While you're waiting for her,
you can be with me to kill time.
It's okay.
I'd rather spend time sewing.
It would be more useful.
If that's what you want.
I guess you still have some hope left.
When your hope on her is gone,
I still live in the same condo.
When did you take this photo?
When you were drunk,
and Prim asked me to stay with you.
You cuddled me like a kitten.
Really? I can't remember it.
I didn't do anything embarrassing, right?
It was not embarrassing.
It was cute.
Thank you for the photo.
I looked pretty but a bit sad.
You can look prettier.
Min.
Do you want to be my model?
I asked you about it before.
Do you remember?
A back model?
I've never done anything like that.
I have to decline.
Come on, Min.
Min.
You mustered the courage
to break up with your boyfriend.
Why don't you try something new?
Trust me. You can do it.
I've got to go.
It looks great. I like it.
It's different from my main brand.
It shows its own identity.
Thank you for giving me a chance
to work on this project.
You should thank me.
Because
I'm the one who chose you
to work on the project.
I hope you see
the project through this time.
Do you have any plans
for the brand opening event?
Don't worry.
I have a plan for it.
Prim will be helping me.
Okay.
Prim, please take care of it.
Also, take care of Bambi.
Make sure she gets the work done for once.
Sure.
Miss, Nin. It's time for a meeting.
This way.
Brace yourself for lots of work.
You know my mom barely compliments anyone.
I won't do it.
The brand opening event.
I can't do it.
Working with you on the video
gave me enough headaches.
Why?
Are you afraid that
you can't help yourself to kiss me again?
No.
You initiated the kiss.
It means nothing. It was only ten seconds.
Whatever.
You can say whatever you want.
But your body tells all
that you miss me.
What classes did you take
while studying abroad?
How did you have such high confidence?
I don't remember the classes that I took.
If it's about you,
I don't need to study.
I already know everything.
Thank you.
Are you going to the after-party
hosted by the sunscreen brand?
No.
I'd rather go home
to work on ideas for a new project.
You should go to the party
to build your network.
There are many potential clients there.
You talk like an expert.
But I don't need your advice.
I know how I do my job.
I don't know.
Maybe I'll go.
I'll add you as my plus one.
I'm a VIP guest.
It's okay.
I'll ask Prim.
She worked with this brand before.
I think she got the invitation.
Okay.
Keep trying.
One day, it might be your day.
I'm rooting for you.
(Don't you think
your outfit is too revealing?)
You're going to work.
It's not that revealing.
There are only women in my office.
A lot of them are lesbians.
Are you dressing like this to seduce them?
You mustered the courage
to break up with your boyfriend.
Don't take the jacket off.
Why don't you try something new?
Trust me. You can do it.
Praew.
Do you still want a model?
Why did you take me to this gallery?
I'm thinking about
holding a fashion show here.
Will it match the concept of your event?
I chose this place
because I have a good memory here.
Don't you remember?
You asked me to be your girlfriend here?
I guess I forgot it.
It matches my dress.
Can you take a photo for me?
I didn't come here to take photos for you.
Is it that hard to do?
You used to love taking my video.
When we were dating,
I was modeling for you.
I never complained about it.
You've come this far because
I helped you by being your model.
Please take photos for me.
Please.
Fine.
Stand here. This angle looks good.
You are the only one
who knows my best angle well.
Hello, Gorya.
Will you go to the after-party tonight?
The party hosted by the sunscreen brand
you've worked with.
I don't think so.
I don't want to be
around people these days.
You can just hang out with me.
Go have drinks and talk to me only.
I'll go there to build my network.
I get it.
But I have many errands to run.
I'm going to visit my mom.
I'll see you.
Okay.
Bambi, let's go…
Gorya, she keeps pestering you.
Why don't you tell her
that your heart belongs to someone else?
Let's take pictures.
Can you smile?
You look grumpy in every picture.
I'll go take pictures there.
You're asking for money again.
I just gave you a large sum
in less than a month.
I need the money.
What for?
You already used the 50,000 baht
I gave you half a month ago?
Why don't you tell her
that you will give the money to Dad?
What?
Baipor.
Is it true?
Why are you giving him money?
I told you not to give him money.
Does his new family leave him?
Is that why he asks for your help?
It's not like that.
He's having a problem.
I'm just helping him to get on his feet.
No matter what, he's still your father.
Don't tell me
that you two are getting back together?
I'm against it.
I won't welcome the man
who left me to take care of you and her.
Get back together?
Though we broke up, I still wish him well.
But he's probably more interested
in your money.
Why are you mad at me?
Don't worry.
She can't stay mad at you for long.
Soon she will cook a meal for you.
She never learned her lesson.
How are you?
Did you find a job?
I'm still looking.
But I'm not hurry.
I'm still tired from studying.
I want to take a break.
Don't take a break too long.
You should help me earn money.
I'm not as talented as you.
You don't need to be talented.
Just find a job that makes you happy.
I can support my own sister.
I'll sleep here tonight. I'm tired.
Min.
No need to feel nervous.
Just relax and make yourself comfortable.
It's hard to feel comfortable.
I'm nervous.
I've never done anything like this before.
Everyone has their first time.
How do you want me to pose for the camera?
Just go with the mood and the music.
Enjoy it. Okay?
Ready? Okay.
I'll need to check the pictures.
Can I have a beer?
I'll loosen up when I'm tipsy.
Sure.
Min, easy.
We can't finish the shoot
if you are drunk.
Let's do it.
Ready?
Don't forget to call me.
I can work on all kinds of projects,
series, movies, and events.
I can deliver exactly what you brief.
You're working hard.
Sure, I'll call you.
- Don't forget to call me.
- Sure.
- See you.
- Thank you.
You're at the party.
Why are you still working, Gorya?
Hello, Bambi.
I need to build my network.
It's too bad I wasn't born on third base.
Born on third base?
What does it mean?
It means trust fund babies
who live off their parents' privilege.
They have never had to work.
They have everything handed to them.
You can't blame them.
They are just lucky.
It's too bad
that Prim didn't come to the party.
I heard that she went to visit her mom.
When you called her, I was with her.
She took a video for me today.
It looks good.
There's a chance…
That we will get back together.
We had a brief kiss.
You're okay with it, right?
Can you still work with us?
Of course.
I have to work for a living.
I don't have time
to pry into other people's business.
Excuse me.
Bye.
So?
Do you want to go to
an after-party with me?
Where?
At my condo.
But there will be only two of us.
Didn't you say I'm not your type?
You can be my type for one night.
I usually don't steal someone else's girl.
But can I have her for tonight?
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
When did you know
that you are attracted to women?
When did I know for sure?
When I was in junior high,
a guy expressed that he liked me.
But I didn't like him.
When I turned him down,
he accused me of
following the trend of liking women.
He thought I would go back
to liking men anyway.
Do you think
you can go back to liking men?
No way.
I will always be attracted to women.
Okay.
I think I'm drunk.
Let's shoot the last set of photos.
Sure.
Besides my ex,
I've never shown this to anyone.
Thank you, Min,
for choosing me to be the lucky one.
I'll arrange your top.
Bambi.
It's me, Pae.
You get the wrong person.
Bambi.
(You wanted to keep a promise?)
(The promise you gave to your ex?)
(Why the f♪ck you need to do that?)
Prim.
When did you shoot this video of Shasha?
Last month. Why?
It's airing?
Are you still having a crush on her?
Yes.
But not as much as before.
I came to terms with it.
I know that she just led me on.
Back then.
She agreed to be a model
for my faculty's project.
She was so kind.
She did it for free.
CAN I TAKE A PICTURE WITH YOU?
SURE.
DO YOU HAVE A GIRLFRIEND?
(I fell for her first.)
NO.
(I was into her.)
I HAVEN'T FOUND ANYONE I LIKE.
(She only saw me as a sister.)
(But I wanted to be more than that.)
BUT I FOUND HER.
(A top model like her
would never choose me.)
No one could help but fall for her.
She was so cool.
That's why I don't like her.
She played with your heart.
I also allowed her to do that.
Don't blame her.
And stop being mad at her.
You also have someone
having a crush on you, don't you?
It's different.
If someone hits on you,
they need to pass my screening first.
I'm protective of you.
Do you understand?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Why don't you come to the party with me?
It's really fun.
No. I'm at my mom's house.
I'm watching a movie with my sister.
I want you to come to take care of me.
Please, please, please.
You decided to drink yourself.
Then you need to take care of yourself.
Fine, Mom.
You're so boring.
You are drunk. You should go home.
If you want me to go home,
you need to pick me up.
What?
You can go if you want.
Aren't you worried about her?
Who is worried about her?
She's just seeking attention.
I won't fall for her trick.
I hope that's true.
I'll wait and see.
Are you sure you want to do it?
I'm practically throwing myself at you.
Are you still hesitant?
I'm not hesitant.
I just don't want to
take advantage of a drunk woman.
I know you did that to spite someone.
Don't act like you are a saint.
I'm an adult.
I can make my own decision.
You don't want it?
Bye.
Don't regret it later.
I'm worried that you might get hooked.
Don't worry.
I don't expect anything anyway.
I just want to have fun.
You moved from Chiang Mai.
Where do you live?
I'm living with my friend.
My parents passed away when I was young.
So I moved to live with my older sister.
But I couldn't stand her husband.
He kept making advances on me.
So I moved out to live alone.
I'd rather work to support myself.
Wow, you're tough.
You went through a lot in life.
I'm surprised you're still this bright.
Anyone can change their lives.
If they want to.
Excuse me.
I've been watching you for a while.
I think you are cute.
Can I know your Instagram account?
Sorry. But no, thank you.
We can just talk.
I'm not going to ask you out soon.
She said no.
Don't you hear it?
Aren't you sick of it?
Men who don't know
how to take no for an answer
when women already say it clearly.
Do all lesbians hate men?
It's not about their gender.
It's about their manners.
You are so protective of me.
Do you want to keep me for yourself?
It's so obvious.
Can't you tell?
Yes, but I'll play hard to get.
Does it mean
you also have some feelings for me?
No.
You know that I'm not a lesbian, right?
Yes, I know.
But…
But what?
I'm Gen Z. I believe in gender fluidity.
Who knows?
You may be bisexual.
Maybe.
Sometimes,
I get butterflies around cute girls.
A cute girl like me?
I don't know.
But right now, I only see you as a sister.
I know.
I get it.
Can I wait for you?
But I like you.
You are my type.
It's up to you.
But I can't tell
how long you will have to wait.
Does it mean I still have a chance?
Excuse me.
Bambi.
You are so drunk. Let's go home.
Come on.
Prim.
My baby.
My beautiful angel.
You finally came to see me.
I called a dozen times,
but you didn't answer my calls.
Hey, it's not that hard to say
you are worried about me.
Can you say it?
That's enough, Bambi.
Let's go home.
Why are you in such a hurry?
I still have energy left to dance.
Your mom is worried about you.
What?
Do you know that
your mom is worried about you?
She'd rather have me live away from her.
Let's go home and talk.
No.
Can we stay until 4 am?
Let's stay until 4 am.
What time is it now?
Come on. Let's go home.
- 4 am.
- I'll take care of you, Bambi.
What?
I'll take care of you. Let's go.
Why are you so nice to me, Prim?
Let's go.
Excuse me.
- Excuse me.
- Bambi, you are leaving?
Bye. See you again.
Come in.
Bambi, walk.
She came home drunk again.
Hello, Nin.
I'm taking Bambi to her room.
You took care of her
when she was in college.
What is this?
Are you back together?
We are just friends.
It's too bad…
That she let a great person
like you slip away.
But I'm not surprised.
If you want to have a bright future,
you shouldn't get back with her.
Let's go.
Walk.
Wait a sec, Bambi.
Go. It's almost your bed.
Prim.
What?
Where am I?
You're at your house.
You are drunk. So I took you home.
Why don't you sleep over here?
No. I need to go home.
Home? This is also a home.
Didn't you notice
that your shoelace came undone?
You could trip over it.
You always take good care of me.
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
We are friends.
Of course, I should take care of you.
You take care of me like this,
I think it's more than friends.
You said you have work to do today.
But you came to the gallery with me.
I didn't cancel it for you.
An actress got sick.
Hey.
Is it that hard to say you love me first?
If I do that,
Will you be my girlfriend?
From now on, you can take care of me
as your girlfriend.
What?
Let's sleep over here.
No, I need to go home.
I'm scared.
Scared of what?
I'm scared that I will lose you.
Why are you leaving so soon?
Why don't you have breakfast with me?
No.
I usually don't have breakfast.
It's an important meal.
We used a lot of energy last night.
Do you remember what happened?
Yes.
I told you I wasn't that drunk.
How was it?
Was it good?
It's fine.
It's not bad.
It's fine. It's not bad.
Then I need to do better next time.
Anyway.
Thanks for my first and only
one-night stand.
It's my honor.
But I can be more than one night stand.
I don't mind if it will be two nights,
three nights, or a week.
No.
I told you.
You can be my type for only one night.
I'm at the studio. Where are you?
Aren't you coming to the studio?
I'm running an errand. I'll go in later.
(Can you handle it alone?)
Yes.
They are just my troubled ex
and the model that I can't stand.
I can handle them.
(Fine. I'll get there as soon as I'm done.)
Don't worry.
I won't be high-maintenance today.
Even though
we both can't stand each other,
I'll focus on work today.
Good.
We are both professionals.
Won't you give me a chance
to explain myself?
I think it will be an excuse
rather than an explanation.
It's up to you.
It's too bad.
We both are smart, pretty, and talented.
I think we can be friends.
I'll take that as a compliment.
Thank you for thinking
I'm in the same league as you.
Prim.
Gorya.
Sorry, you have to handle
many outfits today.
No problem.
I have something to talk to you about.
Sure.
Is it about work?
It's about you.
Did you get back with Bambi?
That…
Not yet.
Did you kiss her?
She's your ex.
It's not easy for you to cut ties with her.
She and I went through
many things together.
You understand me, right?
I don't know how things
between me and her will turn out.
But you are still like a sister to me.
We shouldn't have kissed that night.
Now, it's hard to see you as just a sister.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know that she would come back.
If she didn't come to see you that night,
I would get to be
more than your sister, right?
Or you would never give me a chance,
no matter what?
Whether it's back then or now,
she is the only one in your heart.
Gorya, I didn't mean it
to turn out this way.
The timing is really off.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I need to get back to work.
See you.
See?
It's exactly what I've predicted.
In the end, she only sees you as a sister.
Now you know…
Who should be the one to move on.
Don't hurt Prim's feelings again.
The pictures look great.
I never saw this side of me before.
Thank you, Praew.
Min, you have many good things about you.
But they were suppressed somehow.
No one can suppress me
unless I let them.
It was my fault.
But I've walked away from him.
Now, this is the new me.
Is the new Min ready to try new things?
Why don't you give them a try?
What are the new things
you're talking about?
For example, kiss a girl.
I told you I've dated only men all my life.
You never know until you try.
Are you saying I should try it with you?
I don't mind helping you experiment.
What if it doesn't work?
If it doesn't work,
then you need to try it again and again
until it works.
You really want me to do it, right?
I like your guts and honesty.
I'm just rambling on.
I don't have the guts to do it.
I'm just throwing it out there.
Maybe you'll get flustered,
and it might give me a little hope.
I was flustered at first.
But lately, I want to do it for real.
How is it?
It's good.
I've never felt this way before.
Did you tell Gorya that we kissed?
Why can't I do that?
It's true.
Why do you care about Gorya?
You don't have feelings for her.
Stop leading her on.
Did you come back to stop me
from starting a new relationship?
What makes you think that?
I came back to start over with you.
We will have a fresh start together.
The bad and terrible things that happened,
let's forget them.
Is that so?
Is it that easy to get over it?
You'd disappeared and never contacted me
for over a year.
Tell me.
Tell me what happened.
Explain yourself so I can understand you.
I'll tell you the truth.
The truth is…
You still love
and miss me so much.
You are the only one who accepts me,
no matter how messed up I am.
You have to admit
that I'm the only one for you.
Other girls,
you just use them to kill time.
I'll make you happy again, Prim.
But this doesn't mean
we get back together.
You have a lot to prove yourself.
I'm ready to prove it now.
Hello, Woon.
About my appearance fees,
they are not what we agreed on.
The number is much lower.
Did you deduct your fee
in the ratio we agreed on?
(Of course. It's the same ratio.)
(Don't you trust me?)
No, no.
My accountant might get it wrong.
I'll talk to her.
Sorry for asking you.
Are you still interested in
being more than a one-night stand?
What do you want me to be?
Anything is fine.
How about friends with benefits?
Who will gain benefits from it?
Both of us.
No string attached.
No feelings involved.
I sleep with you.
You sleep with me.
We sleep together.
That's it.
Have you thought this through?
Do you want to do it or not?
If you don't want to, I'll leave.
♪ Don't cross the line ♪
♪ Not really friends ♪
♪ But nothing more ♪
♪ Just a connection ♪
♪ Not a real bond ♪
♪ When we lie side by side ♪
♪ I'm in someone's place, aren't I? ♪
♪ Tell me what is on your mind ♪
Excuse me.
Yes.
Do you know Bambi?
Aren't you going to the after-party?
No.
If it makes you feel better,
you can use whatever excuse you want
to deny that you have a thing for me.
It's fine by me.
You kissed me.
Aren't you going to give me your answer?
Give me some time.
I want to be sure…
That I'm not doing this
because I feel lonely
or I have a moment of weakness.
You've never done anything for me, Bambi.
You did everything for your own benefit.
Like always.