♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Whether you're light or a lie,
I can't pull myself away ♪
♪ In this game,
truth or lie no longer matters ♪
[Queen of Darkness]
[Episode 24]
You sneaky woman.
How dare you hurt me!
Call an ambulance now!
Otherwise,
I'll make you pay dearly!
That An Ning who swallowed her pride
is long gone.
You're not Ye Ying.
Stop imitating her.
You know what?
You're nothing but a complete copy.
What's wrong?
Think a tiny knife is enough
to scare me?
You'll never
never become Ye Ying!
You're right, I'm not her.
But Ye Ying
gave me a chance to survive.
She helped me break free and start over.
The Song family pushed me to the edge.
You cheated and abused me.
Mom is cruel and petty.
I hid in the shadows, living like a ghost.
All for this moment
to take revenge on you!
You
you wouldn't
really kill me, right?
Letting you die
would be too easy.
Every slap you gave me.
Every ounce of pain.
Today,
you'll taste it all back!
Go to hell!
Gather all officers in the station now.
Find Ye Ying and Song Pa's location.
Legal or illegal,
just use any means necessary.
I'll take full responsibility.
Boss.
I know you worry about Miss Ye.
But this is overstepping your authority.
It'll cause a huge stir.
If anything happens to her,
I'll stake my life on it.
Everything else,
I don't care.
Inspector Huo.
We've received a report.
[Immediate suspension] Accusing you of
[pending investigation]
corruption and misconduct.
You are hereby suspended
for investigation.
Please come with us.
Suspending me just because of
an unconfirmed report?
How much did Song Pa pay you?
We're just following orders.
You can appeal
if you think there's a mistake.
What are you doing?
Does this feel familiar?
We're back here again.
Now Jiang Meng is dead.
And the evidence is gone too.
Honestly, I can't imagine
what else
can you do to fight back?
You've done so many shady things.
There'll always be traces left behind.
Even if I die,
Huo Xiao will keep digging for the truth.
Huo Xiao has been suspended
for investigation.
He can barely save himself.
How could he help you with the case?
I was being merciful
not to kill you right away.
You better worry about
how you're going to die.
Huo Xiao...
What did you do to him?
Don't rush.
Soon,
you'll meet him again
on the road to the afterlife.
Boss.
The doctor bandaged Ti Cha.
He's awake now.
Okay.
Let him come down.
Dad!
Dad, dad.
I don't want to live anymore.
I'm not a man anymore!
Dad, dad.
Alright, tell me who did this to you.
It was An Ning.
An Ning did this!
She's back.
Dad.
Dad!
It's you.
You must've teamed up with An Ning.
And set Ti Cha up, right?
Didn't expect karma to come this fast.
Since you've done so many evil things,
someone will help me
make your family end with no heirs.
So what if I've done evil?
Huo Xiao's father never knew
what was good for him
and got in the way of my money.
Ye Hong refused the merger
and even threatened me with.
Longxing Group's gang crime business.
The An family was even stupider.
Clinging to those group shares.
Thinking they could take the company
back from me.
But in the end?
All those who opposed me
ended up with
no proper burial.
Huo Xiao has transferred
all his shares to An Ning.
Even if we all die,
you'll never get Longxing Group.
Longxing Group?
That's just a cover.
The global illegal business group
I control
is the real big business.
I've bribed all systems,
including the police force.
With those systems clearing my path,
my way to profit
is completely unobstructed.
Just for gain,
you've killed so many innocent lives.
You're nothing but a heartless monster!
Being a monster
is still better than
being weak.
I've run out of patience.
You
should take your final walk.
Go find your so-called justice
in the afterlife.
I'll remember your face clearly.
Even as a ghost, I won't let you go.
Good.
Let's see
how exactly you won't let me go.
Kill her.
You...
Huo Xiao.
I thought you were already...
You'll never know
who the real winner is
until the end.
All the crimes you just confessed to
have been livestreamed
across the internet.
Turn around.
I heard them report to Song Pa
that they caught you.
Okay.
Don't let anyone know
I left the station yet.
We can't alert them too soon.
Got it.
[An Ning]
Song Pa sent Ti Cha a message,
saying he caught Ye Ying
and is on his way
back to the Song mansion.
Ye Ying.
Huo Xiao?
Why are you here?
- Are you okay?
- Are you alright?
What do we do now?
All the evidence is gone.
Only Song Pa's confession
can bring him to justice.
I've already
set up cameras in advance.
I know what you're trying to do.
Leave it to me.
Police?
How did it end up like this?
An Ning!
Take him down!
You okay?
Looks like today
we might not make it out alive.
Scared?
Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
No.
I'll never lose you again.
Out of bullets, huh?
At death's door
and still being lovey-dovey?
Don't move!
Put down your weapon!
An Ning has submitted
evidence of your crimes.
The chief has signed the arrest warrant.
Resisting will only lead to death!
Don't move!
If anyone moves, I'll shoot them.
You hired killers to
murder my father Ye Hong.
I've waited too long
to settle this blood debt.
Today is the day you pay for it.
You seized group interests.
Stay back!
You're completely out of your mind.
You staged accidents to silence people.
I endured in the darkness.
All for this very moment
to tear you apart completely.
Now, meet your end!
♪ Keep watching me ♪
♪ Run out of strength,
staring fixedly on me ♪
♪ Don't look away, keep watching me ♪
♪ Keep watching me ♪
Welcome back, Chairman An.
Let me make a statement.
It's about our group's ten-year plan.
Ying, thank you.
You've carried too much for me.
I'll do everything I can
to make it up to you.
Sis,
back then human traffickers targeted us.
You lured them away alone to save me,
and we were separated for years.
Now that Father has passed away,
we went through so much.
I never thought
we'd meet again.
And even stay by each other's side.
That's already healed so many regrets.
Sis.
It's time for me to find my own path.
Dad.
Song Pa has finally faced justice.
Now,
you can rest in peace.
Boss.
Thanks to all your trust.
I officially take over as the new Leader.
From this day on,
Qingyun Gang will never
engage in illegal activities.
If I, Ye Ying, ever break this vow,
may heaven and earth destroy me.
A major gang crime case was recently
solved in the city.
The crime group led by Song Pa
has been completely wiped out.
Why not sleep a bit longer?
It's already morning.
What are you up to again?
Getting my breakfast.
Stop messing around.
Some people
burn their bridges
once they've crossed them.
Not answering calls.
Nowhere to be found.
I have no choice
but to seize every second.
I was just busy.
Then when Leader Ye
finally has some free time,
maybe pay a bit more attention to me?
Is this enough?
What about this?
How about…
How about what?
How about letting the night
fall once more?
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Whether you're light or a lie,
I can't pull myself away ♪
♪ In this game,
truth or lie no longer matters ♪
[The End]
♪ Mist coils around the sleeping forest ♪
♪ Memories scattered
through cracks of darkness ♪
♪ How to escape this real-feeling dream ♪
♪ Lies reflect in water's gleam ♪
♪ Traces of existence
can never be erased ♪
♪ How to find the self I can't reclaim ♪
♪ Fly away, hear she says ♪
♪ She'll fly out from
thorns of woven lies ♪
♪ Pierce the fog,
shatter this dream tonight ♪
♪ Burn like fire ♪
♪ Just burn like fire ♪
♪ The maze in the abyss starts to clear ♪
♪ Yet night keep on whispering ♪
♪ Surrender to fate,
no clear direction ahead ♪
♪ She will rise as the dawn
that breaks the darkness ♪
♪ Never slowing down,
for tomorrow cannot be stopped ♪
♪ Surrender to love and find the way ♪
♪ Even if fate tries to forget her ♪
♪ Never despair,
for the heart burns with endless light ♪
♪ Waiting for dawn ♪
[Copyright of this short drama
belongs to]
[Shanghai Chuqi Weishi
Culture Media Co., Ltd.]
[and Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[Co., Ltd.]
[Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[holds exclusive global online
and broadcast rights]