JUNGRIMCHEON BEWARE OF RAPIDS
Your necklace.
It's really pretty.
Let's go.
The flag is just down here.
Flag one.
What?
- What's that? - What?
I think someone already got it.
Goodness.
You're incredible.
I wondered who'd dare go in there.
It was you?
You're incredible.
I want to be solid land.
- Hui-yeon. - Yeah?
What does it mean when someone wants to be land?
Like when asked what you want to become or do in the future.
Maybe they meant lamb?
Oh, man. Now I'm hungry.
Maybe it was something else.
Who said it? You should just ask them.
Well...
It's hard to ask them.
Is it Mr. Park?
You shouldn't be like that.
My husband said things I never understood, and I couldn't ask him too.
Especially between lovers,
you should share future goals or bucket lists!
You won the camper today.
Sneak him into your car and ask him.
What are you saying? So dirty!
Married women are so...
I can't do that.
Min-hwan can't be with me tonight.
In the past, I got number four which was the single tent,
and Su-min got number one, the camper.
And that night...
Hey, I can't sleep in a sleeping bag.
Let's go sleep somewhere else.
We left and came back at dawn.
I'll die if I sleep here.
We drank so we were overheated. It was horrifying.
Hey.
- Hey! - If I'm in the camper,
Su-min will be in the single tent.
If so...
Today could be D-Day.
What?
Nothing.
I should go out.
You're going out again?
You found the number one. Just rest.
We still have time. I have to follow the rules.
Goodness.
She's so inflexible.
That was dangerous and reckless.
I know I won't die from drowning.
What scares me the most
is living the same life as before with this second chance.
In order to not do that, I can do anything.
So since you have the number one flag,
has fate changed?
Or is there a chance that Su-min will take it before you sleep in the camper?
I don't know.
Then...
But there's one thing that's certain.
Park Min-hwan borrowed money from me,
and he bought a necklace before coming here.
He's simple-minded.
It's his killer move to get into a woman's pants.
I got it too.
It's so pretty, babe.
It's nothing much.
Are you saying he bought the same necklace?
No, it's a bit different. This one...
It looked quite expensive.
I must've been easier to him.
It's okay.
I'm doing all this to escape someone like him.
I'll only take what's good.
You should.
That's how you'll make today D-Day?
Yes. First, I'll make sure Su-min gets number four.
Then I'll get Min-hwan wasted.
Okay, I'll be rooting for you.
As much as I can.
Okay, I'll root for...
By the way, what did you say you wanted to be earlier?
Lamb? Lamp?
What was it? Or maybe champ?
Was that it?
Not me! Get someone else!
Can't you get someone else?
Someone else!
You're out.
Who the heck has number one?
No one here would go in the water.
Except for Ji-won.
I've never had nice things before, so protecting this is so hard.
Sorry, Ji-won!
Let go!
You scared me!
My bracelet's stuck!
Be still. Don't move.
That hurts!
Are you mad?
This is just a game.
And this wouldn't have happened if you hadn't tried to get me.
What's wrong with me?
Why am I worried?
Ji-won, you're out!
I knew you'd come back.
Did you really go into the water?
So this is why you impress everyone.
Find someone who's glamping.
Thanks for this.
Hello, everyone.
I hope you're having fun.
Anyway, I didn't know you'd all participate so enthusiastically.
You're all so great.
Now,
which female employee will get to sleep in the camper?
Number one, come out!
BASED ON THE NAVER SERIES WEBNOVEL MARRY MY HUSBAND BY SUNGSOJAK
Who is it?
What? Really?
It's me!
Please come forward.
I'll give you the key to your camper!
Congratulations!
Find someone who's glamping.
Thanks for this!
Isn't sleeping in a camper better than glamping?
The camper is right in front of me,
so why would I consider glamping?
Congratulations, Ms. Kang Ji-won from Marketing Team 1!
Let's give her a round of applause!
Congratulations!
Next, let's see which male employee won the camper.
Who found the number one flag?
Please come to the front!
Come on up!
Happy you beat me?
You know I can't just sleep anywhere.
Same goes for me.
Really?
Then why did I think you could sleep just about anywhere?
Because I did so for you.
What?
Nothing, I'm going.
Why are you like this to me?
What do you mean?
You won't let me win.
How much longer will you keep this up?
I feel like I've become a bad person now.
You're too harsh to me lately.
I don't...
like you anymore.
I tried not to show it, but I failed. I'll just tell you.
I just started to hate you.
You whine and try to act cute.
You think my things are yours. It's annoying.
You yielded them to me!
Is it bad I took that for granted?
You made me this way. What am I supposed to do now?
You're right. I always yielded
and let you whine.
So I'm going to stop now.
I'm marrying Min-hwan.
I'll start a new family.
I can't be tied to you forever.
Thanks for bringing it up first. Bye.
I feel like a bad person.
She's the one that was wrong.
She's the bad one. I only said what I should say, but...
You're just too good.
You're not bad enough to hurt others.
But I know better than anyone.
You did what you had to.
Good job.
Su-min must want to punish me.
If she thinks I'm being like this because of Min-hwan,
it's obvious how she'll try to punish me.
- I can't drink anymore. - What? You have to finish your shot.
- Gosh, I... - Drink it.
What are you doing here?
Shall we talk?
How did you know that I wanted...
to talk to you?
I can tell by your face.
Did you drink a lot?
Do you have a lot on your mind?
Just a little.
I feel uneasy.
Do you want...
to sleep with me?
Will it change anything?
You're Ji-won's boyfriend, and I'm her other half.
Is it the alcohol?
I only care about who's in front of me.
Me too.
I drank a lot.
I only need you too.
Maybe I'll push her off somewhere.
You can't check your wounds
or your opponent's on the mat.
Focus only on two things.
"I decided to fight."
"And I will win."
I decided to fight.
And I will win...
The entire company is excited
about our marketing team lately!
Of course, since the project's going so well.
We could go down in U&K history at this rate!
I'm sorry, Hui-yeon.
Why would you be sorry?
The original sin is with Mr. Kim.
And the boomer is Mr. Yu.
No wonder this is so fun!
Mr. Kim isn't here!
I hear aroused elks always appear during workshops.
I finally get to see it!
Are you insane?
- What? I want to... - Let's go.
Seriously! Just once!
No, let's go.
I think I found Su-min so pretty.
When I first met her at 15,
I couldn't believe someone so pretty and nice was my friend.
I was so proud. It was nice.
So I wanted to protect her.
And Min-hwan...
He was such a jerk.
But I needed someone to trust and lean on.
And after we got married,
I put up with him even more.
Aren't I such a fool?
It's all over now.
Stop thinking about them.
Think about one thing today.
Kang Ji-won won.
I haven't...
had someone touch my hand this affectionately
in a long time.
Since I came back to 2013,
I've felt so lonely since I was alone.
So I'm glad I have you.
Thank you.
To be honest,
my life is like a well-written novel.
A life without any worries or obstacles.
Just well-written.
So I'm glad I came back,
and I'm happy I get to talk to you like this.
I should thank you.
You never keep it simple.
Is that so?
What did you say earlier? What do you want to be?
I'll help you for helping me too.
I told you, I don't want anything from you in return.
I'm being honest, but you're not.
Then I won't let you help me.
Let's say I said champ.
No, you didn't.
Are you lying?
It's true.
Ji-won.
Did you sleep well when your boyfriend was sleeping in a sleeping bag?
You're so cold-hearted.
Did you really sleep there?
Where else, then?
My selfish girlfriend slept in the camper.
Weren't you even worried your boyfriend might be too cold overnight?
I was, so I went to you with hand warmers, but you weren't there.
I guess I was in the bathroom then.
Yes.
You could've just left them there.
Where's your common sense?
Where's Su-min?
How should I know where your friend is?
Where did she sleep?
I don't know.
Something happened between us yesterday, and it's uncomfortable.
Uncomfortable?
Did you fight?
Women are always fighting and making up. Goodness.
What?
Let's go eat breakfast.
Su-min.
This isn't your tent.
Where were you last night?
I was drunk, so I slept over there. I just left my stuff here.
Did you drink a lot too?
I was able to sober up a bit after a walk with Hui-yeon last night.
I see.
Let's not tell Ji-won.
What?
It's not like she'll break up with me. She'll only get hurt.
You're close friends. It's unnecessary.
Let's just be realistic.
As you said, things are too complicated between us.
Instead of rolling around in a messy reality,
let's keep it as a beautiful memory.
Is it too greedy of me?
Let's go eat.
I'm so hungover.
Okay.
Why can I never get the best?
What?
The workshop sucked.
I wanted to sleep in a camper or a glamping tent.
You'll have other chances.
Failure is the mother of success.
You're right. Nothing's impossible.
This is so nice!
Babe!
Here.
I'm so hungry.
Let's see the food over here first.
Babe, here. You like this.
Wow! It's been so long since I had an orange!
Here's a melon!
Avocado! Wow!
Let's see.
Can this help digestion?
I don't think it went as expected.
I've been with Su-min for 26 years, and 17 years with Min-hwan.
I'm sure something happened.
Then...
When I felt something was off, all my ex-boyfriends broke up with me right away.
Min-hwan was the first to do it behind my back.
I thought it was because of marriage.
But if Min-hwan is more of a scumbag than I thought...
It means
it's not over yet.
Why are you so full of energy?
I hit a homerun!
What? With your girlfriend's friend?
Shut up!
Wow! Seriously?
But she's her best friend.
I'll tell you in one sentence.
Autumn was coming,
and the night air was sexy!
What the... Okay, let's try again.
Can you handle the consequences? You work in the same office.
OUT ON BUSINESS LOG
PARK MIN-HWAN, JEONG SU-MIN
ACTIVITIES: JOMART TASTING EVENT
What's this?
You're going to Jomart.
It'll be tiring.
Why me?
Shouldn't you go instead?
Right, you guys fought.
Don't talk nonsense. I have a presentation today.
A presentation? The slides must be all ready, right?
I'll do it.
Is there a problem?
No, not at all, sir.
Mr. Park, shall we go?
Yes.
I'll get going, Ms. Kang.
Su-min's so smart.
She's working so hard. I hope she becomes a full-time employee.
To my other half, Ji-won.
I'm sorry I didn't know how you felt.
You're everything to me,
and I think it made me blind to your feelings.
I just blindly believed you loved me.
I didn't think about whether I deserved your love.
So everything you said and everything you feel towards me...
It's all my fault.
Still, can't you forgive me?
You're too precious to me. I can't live without you.
I'm going to wait until you feel better.
If I knock and you ever want to reopen your closed heart to me,
will you smile as if nothing happened?
You're my other half.
We can't just end things like this.
If I hadn't seen the end,
would I have been able
to not be swayed after reading this?
She's a good writer.
Maybe she really means it.
- You're doing well. Hurry up. - Yes, Chef.
I don't want to see you face.
I'm jealous.
My life is like a well-written novel.
But if Kang Ji-won is the one wrong sentence in it...
How would you feel?
Don't talk nonsense. Get up.
It's short and crooked.
The content and writing is a mess too.
So it keeps catching my eye and bothering me.
It opens to her page when thrown.
There's nothing special to find or remember in my life.
But only that part is so clear.
Nevertheless...
You're more qualified.
Because you'll be alive after ten years.
ALLERGEN LABELING
What is she thinking right now?
U&K FOOD UDAM'S CREAM TTEOKBOKKI
The rosé goes there. Make sure it's seen well.
TASTING EVENT
I'll try it.
What the hell?
It's so good. I think it'll be a hit.
This is our new product,
so try and make people taste all three products.
- Okay? - Okay!
Also...
I'll get the allergy sign.
Let's do two groups. Those who shop after work
and housewives.
We have to check preference too. So...
I need to go pee.
Mr. Park!
Why haven't you started?
What are you doing?
Can you check this?
Yeah, sure.
What the...
What is this?
What do you think?
What?
We'll start the brief on Chef's Table,
the meal kit project set to launch next year.
CHEF AND MENU INTRODUCTION
The winner of One Dinner,
Lee Gwang-min's chicken dish will be the pilot product.
Production will begin in the 1st quarter, and it'll launch in the 2nd quarter.
Then we have Daniel Kim, a traditional chef.
Along with Park Ji-ho who's popular with those in their 20s and 30s...
Sir!
Well...
Thank you for trusting and letting me take over this project.
Sure, you didn't trust me.
You just had no other choice given the circumstances.
I'm sure that's why you suggested it. Still, I was very thankful...
I just wanted to thank you...
That's not why.
I thought you would be capable of doing it.
Pardon?
And finish your sentences.
Don't trail off whenever you speak.
Just say, "Thank you."
Yes, sir.
And when you get both good and bad feedback, remember the good one too.
Pardon?
I said you would be capable of doing it.
Right.
Thank you.
Well, then.
RESTRICTED AREA AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
I WANT TO DO IT
Wait.
What? Why?
What will you do?
What? You wanted to do it! Let's do it!
What about us?
Are you toying with me?
I'll live with you both!
What?
Aren't you two like sisters?
In the old days, competent men lived with sisters. It's nothing.
Damn it!
- Let go of me! - Come on...
Just a second.
Excuse me.
I'm the one in charge.
What's wrong?
My husband's allergic to pine nuts!
But there wasn't any allergy sign!
- What? - What do we do?
Honey.
I'll get the allergy sign.
ALLERGEN LABELING: PINE NUTS
He should go to the hospital.
You must've been so scared, and it's impossible to make up for it,
but we apologize!
How could a big company like U&K make such a mistake?
I just don't understand.
We're very sorry.
Let it go. Nothing happened.
Things like this can happen while you work.
Yes, sir.
Since it's just us, we'll let it go.
If my daughter were here...
We apologize one more time.
Toss the receipt.
The ambulance fees and hospital bills.
But compensation too?
If he had such a dangerous allergy, shouldn't he have been more careful?
Everyone likes money.
If the company finds out about this,
it'll be bad for us.
Paying them off is the easiest.
Still, you spent so much of your own money.
It's okay. It's me!
I've gotten a good return on stocks.
- The CEO of TKU, - So... What?
Oh Chang-gyu, fled overseas, and it's been revealed only now.
A political emergency is happening.
Oh was once investigated for his relationship with politician Choi.
He claimed he was innocent, expressing his...
According to TMB's coverage,
it's been 27 days since he fled the country.
It has been revealed that TKU employees
haven't been paid wages for two months.
What do I do? Seriously? Damn it!
How about selling everything now?
Who will buy it?
I already put it up for sale.
But everyone's trying to sell now.
Then what do you have to do?
The transaction will be...
Why are you asking? So annoying!
Then you can't get a cent?
Ji-won.
The situation is much more serious than you think.
I used credit.
Credit? What do you mean?
Then what do you have to do?
What's the point of talking to you?
Yes, Ms. Yang.
Yes, I'm in the bathroom.
You dummy. The credit isn't important.
I even took out a private loan.
He didn't mention the private loan.
He didn't before too.
He never says things to hurt his pride. He's not the type.
Just in case, keep an eye on him.
I loved you.
What are you doing?
Was it our fate
to be a threesome, not just two of us?
Are you possessed? I don't understand you.
I'm going to marry Ji-won.
If we had more time,
I would've fallen for you completely.
But this fate puts the brake down.
Then...
Goodbye.
So keep my mouth shut?
What?
I won't...
say anything, Min-hwan. Don't worry.
I just want you to be happy.
What?
Happy?
Why does life suck so bad?
Drink slowly.
Hey.
Do you like me?
Of course, I do.
Thank you for liking someone like me.
You said to drink slowly, so I should.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to marry you next year,
but what's left...
is the Han River for me.
He's asking for money in such a literary way.
Damn it!
You're young. You can earn it again. I'm in no rush.
You can't say that.
Think of your age. What about kids?
You don't want any kids.
You're more important to me.
That's true.
I'm a third-generation only son.
How can I only think of myself?
That's true.
Then what should we do?
Ji-won?
Shall we get married?
I can't give you a glamorous life as I planned.
But we'll be a better family tomorrow than we are now.
I promise.
Family?
Family.
I know you get weak when I mention family.
What a crappy way to say you'll sponge off me for life. You call that family?
It took courage for me to say that. What's with you?
Is it because I'm broke now?
You're not that type of snob.
How funny, right?
He wants to marry without a penny.
No, he must want to marry me now that he's broke.
This is the same as before.
He proposed to me, saying he'd invest with his parents' money.
My debt started to get bigger when that went south.
But he was the person I chose, so I thought we'd work it out together.
He was selfish.
Anyway, all my choices were backwards.
You'll get fat if you eat like that.
I used to give a stray cat food in college.
I wanted to bring him home,
but I was scared I couldn't raise him properly.
Then...
the cat disappeared one day.
It was a cold winter.
I regretted it so much then.
He was so tiny. Like this big.
He had such a temper.
He got chased away after trying to fight other cats.
He hated people, so I don't think anyone took him.
To tell the truth,
I was discharged early.
It was similar to a car accident.
Similar to a car accident?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I ruptured my knee ligaments.
I jumped in front of a car to save a cat.
I didn't get hit, though.
Then...
the cat you're raising now...
It was the winter of 2005.
A cheese tabby with a bad temper.
Doesn't like people.
Are you going to work out?
Hello?
Where'd they go?
Was it you? It was you all along!
I thought you looked similar. It was really you!
It's 20130419.
My passcode.
Come anytime.
Really? Can I?
Let's see each other more often!
You're so cute!
Either way, Mr. Park must get married now.
Yes. Since he needs to get money from his family.
His debts are probably about half a billion won in total.
Maybe more.
It was worthwhile lending him
my money to make him go all in with TKU.
But at this rate, I don't think he'll give up marrying you.
So I came up with this plan.
Although,
I'll have to get his crappy proposal.
It must be so annoying for me, right?
But if I want to live a long life, I must work hard.
He proposed on my birthday.
Everything he did was tolerable back then.
But I hated it.
One, two, three.
I have to see that again?
Terrible, right?
It's my first birthday after being reborn.
Ji-hyuk did?
Yes, sir.
Oh, right. Also...
NECESSITY OF R&D
TEST FLIGHT RESULTS
Wait, so this technology is possible?
Apparently, the development team says we can finally try it.
As you can see, those are the test flight results.
U&K Aerobotics.
Shall I secure more stocks?
If this is possible, of course.
That's that. About Ji-hyuk again.
What on earth is he thinking right now?
Ji-won?
Min-hwan, what is all--
Don't say anything.
Tonight's for you.
My princess.
Kang Ji-won.
I love you.
Let me.
I'll do everything I can for you, Ji-won.
She won't know this is cubic, right?
But it's not like she'll toss it.
I won't let them marry.
You'd hate to see me happy.
Yes.
Please use whatever means necessary
to marry my husband.
Ji-won jumped in the water for me.
Ji-won.
It's your turn to make me happy.
It was the best first birthday.
I'm engaged!
I'm going to milk him for the first and last time.
She bought all this?
My mother-in-law has high standards.
Why are you here?
Isn't the family meeting today?
I'm happy with now.
It's obvious what kind of family she'll marry into.