♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my playful charm♪
♪Just to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for you♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 19=
=Wedding with No Bride=
Niannian.
What are you doing?
Does it hurt?
Ready to tell me now
what Xiaodi's death
had to do with your mother?
In this world, I trust only two people.
One is you.
The other is my mother.
If someone has to take responsibility
for Xiaodi's death,
it should be me.
As long as you're happy,
whatever you do,
I'm okay with it.
I'm giving you one last chance.
I saw
you enter Ye Mei's gallery.
What exactly do you
and your mother
have to do with Xiaodi's death?
Niannian.
Seems like there were
petals on your lashes.
Very beautiful.
Just like the night we first met.
In your hair,
there were petals too.
And I thought
if only you'd hold me like that forever.
Shut up!
We'll be happy.
Niannian.
Trust me.
I'll make sure
you're happy every single day.
Why?
I'm even treating you like this.
Because...
I love you.
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
From beginning to end,
I only have you.
Does your hand
still hurt?
You can hate me.
How could I ever?
Don't touch me.
I'm dirty.
(Organ Trafficking)
(Heart, Fresh Donor, O RH-Negative)
What's the owner's name?
A very famous artist, Ye Mei.
What am I supposed to do?
Ye Lang.
Is this your love
or your scheme?
(Typing Test Report)
(Ye Lang, Jiang Xiaodi)
No way.
Ye Lang.
Xiaodi.
No way.
The blood bank got units here in time.
Luckily you arrived in time.
Being a match for him is incredibly rare.
The surgery went well.
(Ye Lang)
Sorry,
the subscriber you dialed is power off.
Alright.
Go check the area around.
What's wrong, Ms. Jiang?
You agreed to a full exam now?
Dr. Zheng,
is Ye Lang with you?
He's not answering his phone.
He and I
would only meet in the morgue.
What?
Wanna join us?
Then this morgue
is quite unique.
Zheng Lu.
Love-brain,
your Ms. Jiang is coming.
You think I'd buy that?
It's just rehearsal these days.
Let her cool off first.
I'll surprise her later.
I can't stand a fool.
Bye.
Niannian.
Let's go, guys. Good work today.
What are you doing here?
I came to see
what you've been hiding from me.
This is the gallery you found
under my mother's name.
It's also the old house
where my mother and I lived.
I grew up here.
This is where you grew up?
That's right.
Later, my mom made it an art gallery.
I've been preparing everything day and night,
just to give you a perfect proposal.
(This is his home,)
(and also the source of that dark web IP.)
(What's going on?)
I won't give you a chance to throw it away.
I want to be your forever home,
your safe place
when you're tired.
Niannian.
I didn't expect
you'd say yes.
Only by staying with you
can I finally see clearly
what you're really after.
Ye Lang proposed to me.
We're getting married in three days.
From now on,
we'll be one family.
Congratulations.
I hope
you'll be my bridesmaid.
Of course.
My honor.
By the way,
how's Li Hong doing lately?
He's still in the sanatorium,
refusing to see anyone.
He hasn't been doing well.
Actually, I have a favor to ask.
I hope Li Hong can attend our wedding.
Don't worry.
I'll let him know.
Li Hong told me
he didn't blame Ye Lang.
Ye Lang
is always his brother.
That's great.
I'll get going then.
There's so much to do for the wedding.
Go ahead.
The most beautiful bride in the world.
Why did you agree?
Li Hong.
Stop ruining Ye Lang and Niannian's joy.
Why do you care so much about Ye Lang?
What about me?
Why did I end up with nothing?
Ye Lang has won over the board.
Everything is settled.
Hong.
Stop this.
Ye Lang
took everything that should've been mine.
Hong.
That's how the world works.
The winner
takes all.
You're no match for him.
Stop now.
Living an ordinary life isn't so bad.
Xue.
I'll make everyone see
who deserves to stand at the top.
Ye Lang and Jiang Niannian,
I'll make sure they rot unburied.
Why are you here?
Didn't you invite me?
What do you want?
I
want to take you somewhere.
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪