[Fated Hearts]
[Episode 23]
Feng Suige.
Since you know everything now,
you should understand
that what I've done
has nothing to do with my father.
My father is innocent!
Tell Fu Yixiao to let him go.
This is between you and me.
Don't drag my father into it.
Elder Marquis Murong is in my hands!
Whether or not he gets released
is entirely up to me.
You should be negotiating with me!
Back then, you ordered Xia Jingshi
to kill me.
You owe me a life.
The grudge between us
is far from settled.
Fu Yixiao!
Name your conditions for his release!
Then why don't you find a cliff
and jump off it too?
You don't dare?
Looks like you still can't bear to
part with that worthless life of yours.
Stop pretending to be a filial son.
All that talk of yours
is nothing but an attempt to use
your bond with Feng Suige
to save your father.
Murong Yao.
You're even more hypocritical
than Xia Jingshi.
Feng Suige!
My father once saved your life.
Tell Fu Yixiao to let him go.
What does this have to do with Feng Suige?
This is between us.
If you want to save your father,
you'd better first figure out
how to give me a proper explanation.
Stop him!
If I don't see my father
return safely today,
neither of you can leave!
Elder Marquis Murong's life
is in your hands.
Even for his sake,
you can't afford to act recklessly.
Fu Yixiao!
It seems you don't understand
what I'm capable of.
Stop challenging my limits any further,
or I'll make your lives
worse than death!
It seems you don't understand
what I'm capable of, either.
If I didn't have a backup plan,
would I be here today?
If Feng Suige and I
cannot leave safely,
your father's life
will also be worse than death.
Think carefully about the consequences.
Don't test my patience any further!
Fu Yixiao!
[Rongyang Palace]
Your Highness.
The weather's hot and dry.
Her Majesty the Empress Dowager
had a pot of sour plum drink
prepared for each palace.
I thank Mother for her kindness.
Your Highness need not be so formal.
I figured no one would deliver
to Rongyang Palace,
so I came personally.
If there's nothing else,
I'll take my leave now.
Please take care on your way.
The guards have withdrawn.
Seize the opportunity.
What is this about?
I remember telling you before
that even if you gave up everything
for me,
you could never take her place.
You said you'd grant me
one wish.
I did say that.
But a life of deep affection
and perfect harmony as husband and wife—
that I cannot grant you.
What if it's just for one night?
We're already in Jinxiu.
Now, I'm no longer a princess,
and you're no longer a live-in son-in-law.
We're just an ordinary couple.
Princess, please choose another wish.
This is my only wish!
From the first time I saw you,
you've been my only dream,
and becoming your wife
has been my one true wish.
I never imagined
anyone would win your heart
before I did.
You and I are bound by fate,
yet not meant to be...
But I'm trapped.
Princess.
Listen to me.
I'm the Princess of Susha.
I've lived in luxury
and never experienced hunger or hardship.
But I'm trapped in this obsession
and cannot break free.
My Prince.
Even if we cannot grow old together,
could you just help me
fulfill this one dream,
so that I can accept my fate and let go?
♪ Flying alone ♪
♪ With no need for direction ♪
What will it take for you to let go?
Let me be your true wife—
♪ Flying up to the clouds ♪
even just for one night.
♪ Yet the sun is hiding ♪
Then I'll have no regrets.
♪ Roaming freely ♪
♪ Unafraid of wind or frost ♪
♪ The wet wings ♪
♪ Will carry me far away ♪
Princess, there's nothing I can do
about your obsession.
♪ Don't cry, don't cry ♪
♪ I'll remember the way home ♪
♪ I'll find the way home ♪
Elder Marquis is in the village
north of Chongfu Temple,
just outside the city.
I tied him up
and found a farmer's family
to look after him.
Don't worry.
I didn't hurt him.
[Wutong Mansion]
Yun Fang.
Pass on my military order—
summon all soldiers of the Qiongqi Unit
of Feng Battalion to come and see me.
Come on.
I'll take you to see
my divine steed.
I personally captured it
from an enemy general.
Aren't all horses in this world the same?
They just differ in color.
What's there to see?
You'll know once you see it.
Let's go.
What steed in the world
could ever compare to you,
Susha's First Prince?
Hiya!
After you returned,
why didn't you send anyone to rescue us?
Why didn't you plead with His Majesty?
Aren't we best friends?
Where were you when I needed you?
Yao.
Yao!
Your Highness.
You're finally awake.
Fortunately,
the border patrol soldiers found you.
Where is Yao?
Where is Uncle Murong?
Well...
Your Highness, don't worry.
They've both been saved.
They're safe and sound.
His Majesty even said
he would reward them.
Elder Marquis Murong
is going to guard the northern border
and has already left with His Lordship.
Why should I hate you?
Feng Suige,
it's never you that I hated—
it's my own fate,
and this unjust world!
For once, I want to live for myself.
I want the Murong family
to get what it rightfully deserves.
Is there anything wrong with that?
[Zhuang Residence]
[1 tael of stalactite,
1 tael of red gypsum]
[Half tael of amethyst, half tael of
cinnamon twig with coarse bark removed]
Physician Xu found this prescription
in ancient medical texts.
He's absolutely confident
that it can awaken His Majesty.
Are you truly confident?
This is a serious matter.
You must not speak carelessly.
The pills produced from
this prescription I found
are actually highly toxic.
The medicine actually uses its power
to forcibly stimulate life energy.
Once His Majesty takes it,
he'll surely awaken.
However...
However, it will be like
a fleeting revival.
His life will soon end.
You mean
taking this medicine
means certain death?
Yes.
After waking from this medicine,
he'll live no more than 5 days at most.
By tomorrow morning at the earliest,
I can have
this pill prepared.
Physician Xu.
This matter must never be disclosed.
I don't need to remind you further, do I?
I wouldn't dare.
The lives of my entire family
are in Prime Minister Zhuang's hands.
I would never dare to betray him.
I'll definitely do
as Prime Minister Zhuang commands.
After it's done,
this person cannot be left alive.
Only the dead can keep secrets.
I understand, Uncle.
Miss Yixiao, come here.
What's wrong with His Highness?
I was talking to him just now,
but he ignored me. It feels like
he's radiating murderous intent.
Look, you're not talking either.
What's going on with you both?
He's obviously upset.
When he wants to talk,
he will.
Some things
are better left for him
to tell you himself
when the time comes.
Is it that serious?
Alright then.
I-I won't pursue further then.
At times like this,
I'd better keep my distance.
You'd better not
bring that bad luck upon yourself either.
Be careful.
I'm leaving now.
What are you thinking about?
I'll leave the wine here for you.
I won't disturb you any further.
Why is your name Fu Yixiao?
Didn't you say
you never met your parents?
Then who gave you your name?
Why do you have the surname Fu?
So all that brooding of yours—
turns out this is
what you've been thinking about?
Fu Yixiao.
Commander Fu.
That name of yours sounds like
you're someone's deputy.
Why don't you join
my Feng Battalion?
I'll make you a chief commander.
You can be whatever you want
and take whatever surname you want.
It's already come to this,
why do you still have
so many trivial questions?
Then why do you bother
answering these trivial questions?
Because you're the one asking.
It's only when I'm with you
that I can speak without restraint
and ask whatever I want.
I chose my own name.
It means that
no matter how sad things get,
I can just smile
and forget it all.
Isn't that wonderful?
It is.
You really have forgotten it all.
And here I was,
worrying that you were upset
and thinking of how to comfort you,
yet you're making fun of me instead.
I wish I could forget it all too,
but I can't.
Awake, I'm troubled.
Asleep, I'm still troubled.
You were betrayed by your friends,
yet I've been there by your side,
trying to say something profound
to comfort you.
Now that I think about it,
I must have been quite annoying.
Not at all.
Actually, I wish
I could comfort you
the way you did for me.
♪ Take down the setting sun as my heart ♪
♪ Fold the heaven and earth
to make my wings ♪
♪ If fate shows no mercy ♪
How about I teach you archery?
♪ Then don't blame my recklessness ♪
When I'm shooting arrows,
I become completely focused,
clearing my mind of all distractions,
and naturally letting go of my worries.
♪ I thought in this life
I'd drift like a solitary sail ♪
Would you like to try?
I'm the Commander-in-Chief
of all three armies,
♪ Yet I chanced upon you
in the smoke-filled alleyway ♪
second only to one and above all others,
♪ Like a fleeting flower falling into ♪
with countless master archers
under my command.
Do you really think
♪ My eyes ♪
I need you to teach me archery?
The greatest archer in all of Jinxiu
offering to teach you personally.
It's an opportunity not to be missed.
If you don't want to learn,
forget I mentioned it.
♪ Never thought who'd lay me to rest ♪
♪ Once unstoppable and sharp ♪
Don't go.
♪ Now my heart's tied to you ♪
♪ Thinking of you day and night ♪
I want to learn.
♪ I suddenly realize
ripples are spreading ♪
♪ Melting the frost,
lingering in my heart ♪
♪ The light between your brows ♪
♪ Is the kind of bloom ♪
♪ That I love the most ♪
♪ I truly feel I can forgive it all ♪
♪ The sky's vast and the road's long,
but with you by my side ♪
♪ The twists and turns don't count ♪
♪ I can tell with tears
that I have not lived in vain ♪
♪ Not in vain ♪
Where the arrow points,
the heart follows.
That's right.
Don't think about anything else.
Just focus on your goal.
There's only one goal
in my heart.
♪ If fate shows no mercy ♪
♪ Then don't blame my recklessness ♪
♪ I thought in this life
I'd drift like a solitary sail ♪
♪ Yet I chanced upon you
in the smoke-filled alleyway ♪
And what is it?
♪ Like a fleeting flower falling into ♪
♪ My eyes ♪
♪ I suddenly realize
ripples are spreading ♪
♪ Melting the frost,
lingering in my heart ♪
♪ The light between your brows ♪
♪ Is the kind of bloom ♪
♪ That I love the most ♪
♪ I truly feel I can forgive it all ♪
♪ The sky's vast and the road's long,
but with you by my side ♪
♪ The twists and turns don't count ♪
♪ I can tell with tears
that I have not lived in vain ♪
♪ Not in vain ♪
You were careless yourself.
It's not like I betrayed you.
Anyway, Feng Suige
would find out sooner or later.
You command the Imperial Guards.
What's there to be afraid of?
But my father is in their hands!
I don't care what plans
you have,
stop them immediately!
If anything happens to Feng Pingcheng,
my father's life will be in danger.
The arrow has left the bow.
How can I stop now?
Besides, your father
neither took part in our plan
nor knew anything about it,
and he even saved Feng Suige's life.
I don't think
Feng Suige would take it out on him.
Are you asking me to gamble
with my father's life?
To achieve great things,
one must take decisive action.
You lost your son and want revenge,
but does that mean
my father's life doesn't count?
What do you want then?
You want us to just stop now
and wait for execution?
I don't care!
Once I get my father back,
you can do whatever you want,
and I absolutely won't stand in your way!
Do you think this is
just kids playing house?
This is not a negotiation.
Your heart
seems to have something to say to me.
What does it say?
Shh.
Let me listen carefully.
It says
it aches,
betrayed by your closest friend.
But it's okay.
It's trying hard
to heal little by little.
Right.
Because I have you by my side.
It also says
it doesn't want to be hurt again.
If anything happens in the future,
just tell me directly.
Don't keep it to yourself.
It doesn't want to be a messenger anymore.
Okay.
I promise you.
But something's not right.
It says
it feels somewhat uneasy,
because you're not telling me the truth.
Nothing gets past you, does it?
I'm worried about His Majesty.
The Imperial Guards are under
Murong Yao's command.
Now that I discovered his true nature,
I'm concerned that the Jinwu Guards
won't be able to
protect His Majesty properly.
So you want to lead your men
into the palace to protect His Majesty?
But if you do that,
you could be framed
for attempting to rebel.
My conscience is clear.
Why should I fear such petty accusations?
Officail Website : kissasian.be
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Alright.
Since you've made up your mind,
don't worry,
I'll be with you.
Your Highness!
Your Highness.
What's the matter?
Wu Ying...
She bled to death.
She died?
It's a pity that you didn't get to
avenge her with your own hands.
Do you want to go see?
No need.
I don't want to soil my eyes.
Burn her.
Sure.
[Zhuang Residence]
Please.
Here.
-Congratulations, Minister.
Thank you.
Father.
I wish you longevity
like the pine and crane,
and fortune greater than the North Star.
Fortune greater than the North Star?
Have you lost your mind?
The North Star represents
the Emperor's position.
Fortunately, there're no outsiders here.
Otherwise,
you'd be guilty of treason.
Father.
Let's not talk about this now.
Didn't I tell you
I prepared a surprise for you?
Let me show you.
Father.
This is the birthday gift
I've carefully prepared for you.
I remember you said
that after turning 55,
you would petition His Majesty
to retire and return to our hometown.
So this past year,
I've been searching diligently
and finally found in Puzhou
the largest fortress.
This fortress has walls 50 feet high
and watchtowers 200 feet tall.
Inside, there're 10 halls, 9 pavilions,
and 300 rooms.
It can accommodate 1,000 horses.
Inside, there's also
a massive granary
that can store enough food
for 1,000 people for 3 years.
Why would I need such a thing?
Father, hold on.
I haven't finished yet.
I've also purchased
the 10,000 acres of farmland
surrounding it,
enough to station 3,000 troops.
You want to maintain a private army?
Are you planning a rebellion?
Why would I rebel?
I just want to give our family
a chance to live freely,
without having to please others.
Father,
you've worked hard your whole life.
It's time to enjoy some peace and comfort.
Don't tell me
you've already started
preparing armor and weapons?
You know me so well, Father.
The designs are ready,
but making them
takes time.
You cannot do this!
But, Father,
you've worked hard your whole life,
toiling for others.
I just wanted to give you
a chance to spend your later years
in peace.
With this fortress in Puzhou,
you can rest easy.
With our doors shut,
even if the King of Heaven himself came,
we wouldn't need to be afraid.
You rose to power together with
His Majesty,
so why
should you worship him
and work day and night for him?
You've really lost your mind!
If anyone finds out,
this is open rebellion!
If I had known you had such
treasonous thoughts,
I should never have
let you go out to gain experience!
Go to Puzhou immediately
and get rid of all these fortresses
and farmhouses at once!
Zhuang Jingheng.
Someone has reported
that you're harboring private troops
with intent to rebel.
Come with us.
Father...
Uncle.
Physician Xu has prepared the pill.
Prepare the carriage.
I'm going into the palace.
[List of Dowry]
That old emperor of Susha
is quite interesting.
His daughter eloped,
yet he arranged for her dowry
to be delivered.
Besides the dowry,
they've also sent
a maid of Princess of Susha.
By rights,
both the maid and the dowry
should be sent to Her Highness.
It's just the Prince of Zhennan
and his wife
are both residing in the palace now,
so I must ask for
Your Majesty's instructions.
Alright.
Just send them to my place
and hand them over to Bai Shouzhuo.
Find accommodation for that maid.
This matter
must absolutely not
be known to anyone else.
Your Highness.
The guards at the gate
have indeed been withdrawn.
Good.
I'll take this opportunity
to go out for a walk.
By the way,
take Princess Xiyang
out for a walk too.
She needs some fresh air
after all these days.
Yes.
You may leave now.
The water's cold.
It's still cold.
Feng.
Never thought
you'd see this day, did you?
Lying before me,
completely helpless,
with your life in my hands.
Do you regret
what you said that day
when I knelt before you,
begging you
to spare my son's life?
Prime Minister Zhuang.
You've always been impartial
and strictly fair.
You've never once asked me
for mercy out of personal feelings,
nor bent the law for private gain.
I beg Your Majesty.
He's my only son.
I boldly beg Your Majesty
to spare his life.
Look for yourself.
All these
are memorials denouncing him.
Hiding weapons and private troops
with intent to rebel—
that's the grave crime of treason,
punishable by the extermination
of his entire nine-lineage family.
I've already spared your entire family
out of consideration
for your loyal service.
Zhuang Shen.
You're the Prime Minister of Susha.
If I were to grant your request,
how would I command the respect of all
and face the entire court of officials?
If you were in my position,
what would you do?
I also watched Jingheng
grow up.
Though he committed a grave crime
and cannot be honored
in the ancestral temple,
I'll allow you
to give him a proper burial.
You traded your son
for the peace of my kingdom—
I'll remember
this debt of gratitude.
You said
I traded my son
for the peace of your kingdom,
and you claimed to remember
that debt of gratitude.
I've always
kept that debt in my heart.
13 years.
It's been 13 years!
Not for one day
or even one hour
have I forgotten about it!
Jingheng didn't have to die.
What crime had he committed?
All he did was spend money
to buy a house.
He only slightly overstepped his bounds,
but he didn't actually do anything!
It was all because of you.
It was me you resented!
You blamed me
for the late Empress's death.
But why make Jingheng
suffer for it all?
8 days.
During the 8 days
you've been lying here,
I could've killed you at any moment
to avenge Jingheng!
Even if the Jinwu Guards
killed me afterward,
it would only be a life for a life!
What's the worth
of this old life of mine anyway?
But I won't let you
die so easily.
I want you to watch
your son die with your own eyes.
I want you to feel
the agony of losing a child yourself!
I've prepared the pill for you.
As soon as I catch Feng Suige,
I'll make you take this pill.
This is a miraculous pill.
Once you take it,
you'll immediately regain consciousness,
so you can see your son die
right before your eyes
in a sober state!
Unfortunately, though.
Unfortunately, this pill is poisonous.
After you take it,
you'll die within 5 days.
How I wish you wouldn't die.
I wish you could suffer as I have,
enduring the pain of losing your child
for 13 years!
Only that would be fair!
Today is
the last time I came to see you.
These words have been hidden in my heart
for too long,
and I had to say them out loud.
It's just a shame
that you can't hear me.
You old bastard,
still luckier than I am.
Yesterday, when they
returned to Zhengnian Villa,
Fang asked
when Master would come.
I wonder
if they've settled in well.
Don't worry, My Lady.
They're all very sensible.
They understand that Miss Yixiao
has important matters to attend to.
I asked Mr. Qin
to hire a tutor for them,
and they've agreed
to settle down here properly.
That's good.
This is Physician Hou's prescription.
Instruct someone
to give him medicine on time every day.
He's out of danger now.
He'll wake up in a few days.
Got it.
By the way,
go help me pack a few things.
I'm going on a long journey.
My Lady, you...
You're not going to that
so-called mysterious place, are you?
Yes, I am.
I promised Sister.
Still no news of Ning Fei?
Don't worry.
I pestered my father for information.
The place where Ning Fei was sent
is called the Storm Alliance.
My father said
those of the Storm Alliance
are very skilled.
They'll definitely be able to
revive Ning Fei.
Rest assured.
Once I return to Zhengnian Villa
and get Fang and the others settled,
I'll go visit the Storm Alliance in person
and check on Ning Fei for you.
So do you know
where the Storm Alliance is?
Of course.
My father knows all too well
how I can never stop digging
once I start asking questions.
I kept pestering him,
so he finally told me.
But wait.
Master sent a letter
instructing Mr. Qin
to watch over you, My Lady,
and not let you wander off.
Eleven.
You just be good and stay here, all right?
I...
[Linfang Hall]
A life of deep affection
and perfect harmony as husband and wife—
that I cannot grant you.
Princess, there's nothing I can do
about your obsession.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Princess, did you personally
pick these flowers
for the Prince of Zhennan?
Such touching devotion.
Unfortunately, my brother
is too stubborn.
Once he's made up his mind,
it's nearly impossible to change it.
No one else knows this,
but I
am the one who knows him best.
What do you mean by that, Your Majesty?
After all, I've been
his brother for so many years.
Back then, I beat him, scolded him,
imprisoned him in the imperial jail,
yet he still refused to
admit his mistakes.
That's just the kind of person he is.
I'm feeling unwell
and must take my leave.
Are you leaving the flowers?
Giving such beautiful flowers
to my
romantically clueless brother
would be such a waste.
Fresh blooms are meant to
be paired with beautiful women.
If His Highness enjoys them,
then they won't be wasted.
Too bad he doesn't know
how to cherish beauty.
If I were him,
I wouldn't let a beauty
stand here brooding all alone.
Please show some self-respect,
Your Majesty!
This is the first time
anyone dares to treat me like that.
Interesting.
His Highness is waiting for you inside.
His Highness's instruction:
everyone, eat first!
Yes!
What has His Highness summoned
the Qiongqi Unit here for?
These are a bunch of lunatics.
Every single one of them
has dozens of lives on their hands.
Yun Qing.
Give them a heads-up
that when they meet Miss Yixiao,
they must not act rashly.
Your Highness.
You want the Qiongqi Unit
to enter the palace
to protect His Majesty?
That's right.
They'll enter as my household guards,
with no waist tokens
and no armor.
This is the only plan
we can think of right now
that won't give anyone leverage
against us.
If soldiers of the Feng Battalion
were to appear
to protect His Majesty,
people would suspect
the First Prince of plotting rebellion.
Then
Prime Minister Zhuang
would mobilize troops
to surround the Feng Battalion.
So our only option is
to achieve great effect with little force—
enter the palace as household guards
to protect His Majesty
until he wakes up.
Your Highness.
This is Fu Yixiao,
Jinxiu's finest archer.
She's one of our own now.
Your Highness, you summoned us.
Who do you want us to deal with?
Come with me to enter the palace
to protect His Majesty.
If anyone threatens His Majesty,
no matter who they are,
kill them without hesitation.
As you command, Your Highness.
Whoever Your Highness wants dealt with,
we'll take care of them.
You just need to take your men
and guard outside His Majesty's chambers.
I'll assist you.
When we work,
we don't need anyone's help.
After I finish the job,
I'll challenge you to a match.
Anytime.
Very well.
Keep your mouth shut
if you don't want trouble.
From now on, what Fu Yixiao says
represents my will.
To work alongside the famous Fu Yixiao
and fight enemies together
is my greatest honor.
Don't worry.
You won't need to lift a finger.
Those Imperial Guards
live on meager rations.
They're all weaklings.
All the better.
After finishing your meal, get changed
and get ready to go.
Yes!