[A Splendid Match]
[Episode 26]
[The Penal Court]
My Lord.
Miss Gu has been looking
for you these past few days.
She asked if you would be free tomorrow
and would like to meet you.
What is so urgent?
Well,
I do not know.
Then remind me tomorrow
to bring the new set of hair ornaments.
That color
looks good on her.
My Lord.
Miss Xue is here.
She is waiting in your duty room.
Did you let her in?
Yes.
She said she had an appointment with you.
Go get ten strokes.
Since you like
the Penal Court so much,
why not just stay here?
I have plenty of
empty rooms here.
The conditions are quite good.
For your father's sake,
I can arrange a private room for you.
You only talk to me like that
because you know
that I like you.
If I ever stop liking you,
try talking to me like that again.
Xue Qinglan.
Don't panic.
Although I am pursuing you,
I still know my limits.
This is the Penal Court,
not your residence.
I won't do anything to you.
Why are you here?
I came to tell you something.
What is it?
Say it quickly
and then get lost.
Chen Yanyun
has proposed to the Gu family.
What did you say?
To whom?
Who else?
Gu Jinzhao, of course.
You're talking nonsense.
Why would I make this up?
All the ladies and misses
of every household
already know about this.
And Chen Yanyun,
to help the Gu family keep up appearances,
even specially invited
Grand Secretary He's wife
to be the matchmaker.
You're lying to me.
I don't believe it.
You are lying to me.
This is impossible.
Ye Xian!
Get lost!
[Yuheng Gate]
[Ancestral Secret Recipe Meat Soup]
Hya!
[Gu Mansion]
Greetings, Your Lordship.
Your Lordship.
What...
what happened?
G-Go report this quickly.
Yes.
♪ Who, deep beneath the water ♪
♪ Once shared the warmth of a palm ♪
♪ Setting the gears of fate ♪
♪ In motion ♪
♪ One curtain divides two worlds ♪
I am not even afraid of Lord Chen,
♪ Winter and spring
entrust their unspoken feelings ♪
why would I be afraid of you?
Greetings, Uncle.
I pay my respects to you.
♪ Sparks dance in the air,
lighting up the night ♪
You are my elder, Uncle.
Did you bring a gift
for our first meeting?
Wait.
What happened to your hand?
♪ Alone, drunk in a fleeting dream ♪
What happened?
♪ In dreams, I miss you, beyond words ♪
You are awake.
Are you still
feeling unwell anywhere now?
♪ My hand gently brushes past,
and dust settles on the scroll ♪
♪ Amid endless twists and turns ♪
Hey.
♪ Love quietly sinks into silence ♪
♪ Time can never be looked back upon ♪
Thank you.
♪ I only regret missing
even a moment of togetherness ♪
♪ If longing bears no fruit ♪
♪ I'd rather we both sink away ♪
Young Lord Ye is here?
Yes.
They say he looked furious,
and went straight to
the Eldest Miss's courtyard.
At this hour,
what is he doing coming to see Zhao?
Old Madam,
I heard the servants gossiping that
His Lordship is much closer
to the Eldest Miss
than to the other sisters.
It would be fine in the past.
But now,
Eldest Miss is already engaged to
Lord Chen.
You are right.
We can't let him go to Zhao.
Go stop him.
Yes.
Come back.
We can't let outsiders stop him.
Cuilyu,
go tell the Second Master,
and get someone to guard the inner gate.
-Yes, Old Madam.
-Hurry! Hurry!
Remember,
don't let a single stranger in,
and don't let a single word out.
Yes, Old Madam.
I will go there myself.
I speak my mind,
so please don't take offense.
Have you told Xian
about your engagement to Lord Chen?
Then how are you going to tell him?
I...
I've always wanted to tell him.
And
I've arranged to meet him tomorrow.
What are we going to do?
He likes you so much.
You don't know this,
but the military nobility
is in decline now.
People outside say
the Senior Grand Secretary
is preparing to
make an example of our marquis household.
I really don't know
what kind of trouble he might cause.
I'm sorry, Zhao.
I didn't mean to pressure you.
It's just that Ye Xian's temperament…
and it's Chen Yanyun you're engaged to.
I've actually
never known how to bring it up.
What?
Has he never
made his feelings clear to you?
That fool.
Since we've come this far,
I'll just say it outright
and ask something I probably shouldn't.
Do you
have feelings for Xian or not?
I have always
regarded him as a confidant.
What did you just say?
Say it.
Say it again.
Ye Xian,
don't be like this.
So what they said is true.
You are going to marry Chen Yanyun,
right?
Yes.
I wanted to
tell you earlier.
Xian.
Don't come closer!
Why?
Because I like him.
I had planned to tell you tomorrow,
but I didn't expect
you to come today.
Ye Xian.
You like him?
I don't believe it.
You're lying to me.
My Lady.
I don't believe it.
Your Lordship.
Why did you suddenly come here?
-Shall we go to the front yard?
-Shut up!
Fifth Daughter-in-Law,
are you going to let your brother
make a scene here?
Ye Xian, put down the knife.
Xian.
Calm down.
Put the knife down and let's talk.
You like him?
Good.
Very good.
You like him.
Your Lordship, I'm sorry!
Xian!
Help Zhao leave through the back door.
Yes.
Go home with me, okay?
My Lady, let's go.
-My Lady.
-Let's go.
Be good.
Let's go.
-Let's go, My Lady.
Gu Jinzhao!
♪With every step, I look back ♪
Xian!
♪ My heart grows cold like rust ♪
♪ The stars see you off
on a thousand-mile journey ♪
Get a physician! Get a physician!
♪ Yet one thought still remains ♪
Ye Xian!
♪ You share bright days with another ♪
♪ I walk with my lonely shadow ♪
My Lady.
♪ Filling every broken fold
with memories of us ♪
No one is allowed to follow me.
No one.
Your Lordship.
Xian!
-Your Lordship.
-Xian!
♪With every step, I look back ♪
Zhao.
♪ My heart grows cold like rust ♪
Zhao!
Support her. Quickly.
♪ The stars send you far away ♪
It's alright.
Zhao!
♪ Yet one thought still remains ♪
♪ You share bright days with another ♪
♪ I walk with my lonely shadow ♪
♪ Filling every broken fold
with memories of us ♪
♪With every step, I look back ♪
♪ My heart grows cold like rust ♪
♪ The stars send you far away ♪
♪ Yet one thought still remains ♪
♪ You share bright days with another ♪
[Gu Mansion]
♪ I walk with my lonely shadow ♪
♪ Filling every broken fold
with memories of us ♪
[Gu Mansion]
♪ Filling every broken fold
with memories of us ♪
[Gu Mansion]
[Honor and Illumination]
Jiuheng?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Chen Yanyun, please rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Mentor.
Chen Yanyun.
Yesterday, Mr. Fu told me
that you are getting married.
And the bride is actually that
Miss Gu who once
beat the Drum of Grievance.
The more I think about it,
the more curious I become.
So I couldn't help
but summon you to the palace
to ask you in person.
Your Majesty.
Lord Chen is currently
serving his punishment.
Summoning him to the palace like this
is against the law.
I realize my mistake.
It won't happen again.
Chen Yanyun.
When do you
intend to marry
that Miss Gu?
Your Majesty, this...
Your Majesty,
how can you pry into
an official's private affairs like this?
Then let me ask it another way.
Chen Yanyun.
I heard
that Miss Gu's maternal family
are your surbordinates.
Have you two been
in contact for a long time?
Your Majesty.
I still have many memorials to review.
You and Jiuheng
can take your time talking.
I shall take my leave now.
Zhang Fang,
see Mr. Fu out for me.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Take care, Mentor.
Your Majesty.
Miss Gu and I...
I am hungry.
Go get me some snacks.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Today,
an imperial censor impeached
the Marquis Changxing
for great disrespect.
Mr. Fu wants to deal with it severely.
But I want to protect
Marquis Changxing's household.
However,
I cannot openly go against Mr. Fu.
So I can only
entrust this to you.
But what I
never expected was that
His Majesty would so directly ask you
to protect
the Marquis Changxing's household.
Isn't this clearly
forcing you to oppose
the Senior Grand Secretary?
Could he be testing you on purpose?
It is a test,
but also an order.
The disaster relief grain case
fell entirely on the Ministry of Revenue,
and I shouldered it alone.
Although this idea
was proposed by Wang Xuanfan,
Mentor remained completely silent
from beginning to end.
This is enough for His Majesty to infer
that it was tacitly approved by Mentor.
At the same time,
His Majesty may also suspect that
Mentor and I
could develop a rift
over this matter.
His Majesty
has grown faster
than we expected.
But even with an imperial edict,
if the Senior Grand Secretary
is determined
bring down
the Marquis Changxing's household,
what can you do?
Let's go see Ye Xian first.
Third Master.
-Third Master!
-Don't move.
Chen Yanyun.
Ye Xian,
are you crazy?
I've always been a madman.
Go to hell!
My Lord!
[Prosperity of Parents]
Stay back!
The imperial censor impeached
your father for grave disrespect.
His Majesty has ordered severe punishment.
Yet you still have the leisure
for matters of romance here.
[Prosperity of Parents]
My Lord.
Miss Gu and I are in love.
How could you possibly separate us?
It's simply wishful thinking.
Chen Yanyun.
I am sworn to
be your irreconcilable enemy.
[Prosperity of Parents]
Third Master.
Spread word of what happened today—
Xian Ye's public assassination attempt,
the carriage stop, and his jealousy
over me.
Make it as widely known as possible.
Okay.
The Marquis Changxing, Ye Guangsheng,
disobeyed the late Emperor
and showed disrespect to His Majesty,
acted obstinately and arrogantly,
and failed in his duties.
The Penal Court is hereby ordered
to immediately arrest the
Marquis Changxing,
and investigate the matter thoroughly
to appease His Majesty's wrath.
I, Ye Xian,
receive the decree.
My Lord.
Let's go.
Come with me to the Marquis' residence
to arrest the Marquis Changxing.
This...
[Marquis Changxing's Mansion]
Come in after an hour.
Yes, my lord!
[Marquis Changxing's Mansion]
My Lord, Madam.
Young Lord Ye is back.
Father. Mother.
So you do know how to come back.
Xian.
You've lost weight.
And you're darker too.
You haven't eaten yet, right?
Why don't you sit down and eat with us?
If you don't want to eat, that's fine too.
Let's eat then.
Okay.
Come.
Hurry.
Tell the kitchen
to add a plate
of stir-fried pork with yellow chives,
radish meatball soup,
and those
meat-filled flatbreads.
Xian
loves those the most.
Yes, Madam.
Xian,
is your work at the Penal Court
very busy?
It's fine.
What do you mean "fine"?
I heard you went to Shanxi earlier
and almost lost your life.
Is that true?
How could it be so dangerous?
Isn't Father also in constant danger
of losing his life on the battlefield?
What I do is different.
I was fighting enemies.
But what about you?
You've become a tool
in their factional struggles,
a blade
in His Majesty's hand.
It's rare for him to come back.
Why are you saying all this?
Am I wrong?
Go out and ask around what kind of work
the Penal Court
does every day.
In this vast court,
who is not the His Majesty's blade?
And who would dare not be his blade?
You...
You are an educated person.
Have you learned all that scholarship
just to feed it to the dogs?
I don't care what you think.
Tomorrow I will submit a memorial
to the Empress Dowager
and have you removed from the Penal Court.
I've already
talked to your Uncle Song.
You will be transferred
to the Ministry of War.
I won't go.
Uncle Song
won't listen to you either.
You brat, how dare you defy me!
Marquis Changxing, receive the decree.
[Great Merit and High Esteem]
My Lord.
I do not accept this.
Since His Majesty ascended the throne,
I have not stepped
out of the residence due to illness.
What crime have I committed?
If you have any objections,
you can state them in the imperial prison.
The imperial command cannot be delayed.
I will wait outside.
Please come out
within 15 minutes.
Xian!
Mother,
I am also...
You unfilial son!
Are you trying to kill your own father?
[Great Merit and High Esteem]
My Lord.
If I were you,
I would request to be imprisoned as well.
That way,
at least in the Penal Court,
no one would be able
to move against the Marquis.
And he would secure
a slim chance of survival.
Why should I trust you?
My Lord.
Vice Commander Hu.
[A Legacy of Virtue and Grace]
My Lord.
Since the imperial censor impeached
Marquis Changxing for disrespect,
as the heir of the Marquis's household,
I should also be imprisoned
to await trial.
Vice Commander Hu, please bind me as well.
You unfilial son!
What are you doing?
My Lord.
Is this really necessary?
What?
Does no one
obey my orders anymore?
Okay.
Xian, you can't go.
Don't go!
Xian!
No, Xian.
No!
Xian!
Madam.
Xian, you can't go!
Your Lordship!
Xian!
Chen Yanyun.
I have acted according to the plan.
If you dare to deceive me,
I will tear you to pieces.
My Lord.
Third Master.
Last night, Young Lord Ye
personally went to the Marquis' residence
to arrest Marquis Changxing
and then requested
to be imprisoned as well.
Now they've been taken away together.
I was worried
that because of Miss Gu,
he wouldn't trust you anymore.
I didn't expect him
to actually do it.
He's quite a character.
So what should
we do next?
Build momentum.
Build momentum?
Marquis Changxing enjoys immense prestige.
Mentor
not only wants Marquis Changxing's life,
but also wants to destroy
his reputation.
But His Majesty wants to protect
Marquis Changxing's household.
He will find no support
within the court.
We can only make efforts
outside the court.
Ye Xian arresting his own father
defies social conventions.
And his voluntary imprisonment
only further proves his innocence.
These two points alone
will cause a sensation in the capital.
If we build enough momentum,
His Majesty will
have grounds to intervene.
Then we can find a way
to get them a lighter sentence.
Brilliant.
Among all crimes since ancient times,
the crime of great disrespect
is the most elusive.
It is based on hearsay
and lacks any evidence.
It is truly the most convenient charge
for framing someone.
Precisely because there is no evidence,
it can be dealt with
either severely
or lightly.
But all I can do
is preserve the Marquis's reputation.
As for saving his life—
it will be difficult.
Ruixiang,
get me another pot.
Stop drinking.
You've already had two pots.
You always
look down on people
who drown their sorrows in drink,
and say they are pathetic.
If they truly get angry,
just kill someone.
So why are you acting like this now?
Kill someone?
Kill who?
Your brother?
I can't beat him.
And I can't bear to hurt Ye Xian.
Maybe,
I should just kill
Gu Jinzhao.
Stop talking nonsense.
You two don't have that much bad blood.
Don't tell me
you like my brother?
Who told you I like your brother?
He's full of schemes.
I like Ye Xian.
There you go.
Jinzhao doesn't like Ye Xian.
No one's trying to take him from you.
That's exactly the problem.
I'd rather she fight me for him,
so we could
settle it head-on.
But look at things now.
She doesn't care at all,
while Ye Xian has lost his mind—
storming into the Gu residence
and even trying
to assassinate your brother
in broad daylight.
Though, he does have my style.
Yeah.
I didn't expect Ye Xian
to like Jinzhao so much.
And I really didn't expect
Yanyun
to like her that much either.
Let me tell you.
Yanyun even stood up
to my mother for her,
and specially
asked Madam He to act as matchmaker.
I've never seen him
like someone so much.
But it makes sense.
Jinzhao
is really quite lovable.
Who said she's lovable?
She's not honest at all.
She clearly knows I like Ye Xian.
So why didn't she tell me
that he likes her?
She just wanted to make a fool of me.
Don't be mad.
I don't think Jinzhao
kept it from you on purpose.
Think about it.
She is an unmarried girl,
and she is not that close to you.
If you suddenly told her
you liked Ye Xian,
what was she supposed to say?
Was she supposed to say,
"Don't like him. He likes me,
but I don't like him"?
You...
Are you trying to confuse me?
Anyway, whether it was intentional
or not,
she is my rival in love now.
I won't be friends with her.
You are not allowed to either.
I won't be on good terms with her.
Anyway, she is my third sister-in-law.
You bad girl.
Come here.
My Lady. My Lady.
Something's wrong.
Young Lord Ye
has been imprisoned in the Penal Court.
What?
What happened?
They said
an imperial censor has impeached
the Marquis Changxing
for great disrespect,
and His Majesty ordered
to punish him severely.
Young Lord Ye
personally went to arrest the Marquis,
and then requested
to be imprisoned as well.
Can you go
and beg Chen Yanyun for me?
Ask him to save Ye Xian.
I...
Yanyun never allows the family
to interfere in court affairs.
I'm afraid my words
won't carry any weight.
Fine.
Your words hold no weight, right?
Then I'll go find
someone whose words do.
What?
Ye Xian has been imprisoned
in the Penal Court?
It happened just last night.
Rumor has it that
the Marquis Changxing
has committed a grave offense.
And the court will deal with it severely.
They even locked up Young Lord Ye
and the Marquis.
Zhao.
Fifth Aunt.
Ye Xian and my father
have been imprisoned in the Penal Court.
Right now,
I have no other way out.
I have to come beg you.
Can you please help me
and plead with Lord Chen
to save Xian and my father?
Please don't do this.
Get up.
I heard about it too,
so I was about to go find Third Master
to think of a way.
You are not allowed to go.
Lady Ye.
Didn't I warn you
not to come to Zhao?
Why didn't you listen?
The other day, Ye Xian
made such a huge scene.
How do you still
have the nerve to ask Zhao
to plead with Lord Chen?
Don't you know
what crime Marquis Changxing
has committed?
It's a charge of great disrespect—
enough to wipe out the entire clan!
Do you think
our Gu family hasn't suffered
enough already?
You're dragging our Gu family into this
just for your own household.
Don't forget
you are a daughter-in-law of our family.
I am a daughter-in-law of the Gu family,
but I am even more
a daughter of the Ye family.
If you're afraid of
being implicated by me,
then have Dexiu write a letter of divorce.
Do you think we wouldn't dare
to write it?
I'm warning you.
The current Marquis household
cannot protect you.
Well.
When the Marquis household was in power,
you came crawling to me
time and time again.
Now that we're in trouble,
you immediately turn your backs on us
and avoid us like the plague.
What a snobbish attitude.
If you want to write
a letter of divorce, go ahead.
I'm the one who finds
your Gu family disgusting.
Zhao.
I'm not talking about you.
I know I may
be asking too much,
but I have no other way right now—
I can only beg for your help.
Fifth Aunt, don't panic.
Since I promised to help you,
I definitely will.
Zhao.
Grandmother.
Right now, even if you ask Fifth Uncle
to write a divorce letter for Fifth Aunt,
it's too late to cut ties.
If the Marquis household falls,
do you think there will be
any benefit to our Gu family?
We are family.
If we don't help now,
when will we?
Zhao.
I heard rumors that
Ye Xian tried to assassinate
Lord Chen in broad daylight.
I heard that too.
That is why
I must go take a look.
Qinglan.
You are also here
for Ye Xian?
You're smart.
If you still consider Ye Xian
a friend,
then go and ask Chen Yanyun
to help save him.
Have a seat.
How is it?
Is there still any hope for
the Marquis Changxing's household?
There wasn't any at first.
But
Ye Xian went to prison
along with the Marquis Changxing—
so that's created
a slim chance of turning things around.
Right.
On the day of the palace coup,
Marquis Changxing was accused of treason.
Ye Xian risked his life
to protect His Majesty,
which made the charge of treason
fall apart on its own.
Now that Ye Xian has been imprisoned
together with the Marquis,
it may achieve a similar effect.
It's not just that.
Ye Xian going into prison
can also protect the Marquis a bit.
What do you mean?
Is someone planning to
move against the Marquis in prison?
It's just a precaution.
Do you have any way to save Ye Xian?
I do,
but
it will require you
to suffer some grievance.
For the Ye family case,
you should be the chief judge.
But I
haven't been reinstated yet.
After you finish
judging Marquis Changxing,
you can return to
the Hall of Literary Profundity.
Thank you, mentor.
However,
I think
it's still not quite appropriate.
I've heard about it.
Ye Xian
actually attempted to assassinate
a Grand Secretary in broad daylight.
Truly appalling.
It is just that you are magnanimous.
Otherwise, this alone
would be enough to condemn
Marquis Changxing's household.
My apologies for this, mentor.
I originally thought
it was just a private matter,
and blowing it up wouldn't do any good.
But now
it's known to
the whole court and the public.
Everyone says
the feud between Ye Xian and me
is irreconcilable.
If I were now
to try the Ye family case,
I fear people would accuse me
of using my public office
to settle personal scores.
Let them talk.
Whoever protests the loudest
is part of Marquis Changxing's faction.
I was just worrying about
not having enough people
to make an example of.
Go ahead and handle it.
Don't worry about anything else.
Yes.
Mentor.
In that case,
there's no time to lose.
I
will go back now
to prepare for the trial.
Okay.
Mentor.
You always manage to come up with a plan
whenever it comes to Jiuheng.
Isn't it all
for you, Mentor?
When I was in prison,
I wondered every day
who sent Ye Xian to go to Shanxi,
and how he managed
to get there so quickly.
Later I also recalled that
not long ago,
when Prince Ruichang rebelled,
Ye Xian entered the palace
at precisely the right moment.
Putting these two things together,
I dare say
someone among our people
has long been secretly
colluding with Ye Xian.
You think this person is...
This person can never be me,
let alone you.
As for He Wenxin,
he just wants to be a Grand Secretary
who avoids politics.
And has never had any ties
with the Marquis Changxing's household.
Then who else is left among us?
There is only Jiuheng.
Unless Jiuheng takes
heavy-handed measures this time
to severely punish Marquis Changxing,
otherwise...
Third Master.
[Thrice Reflections Against Greed;
Ninefold Virtues in the Sound of the Qin]
News came from Mr. Jiang.
As you expected,
Wang Xuanfan went to
the Senior Grand Secretary's residence
early this morning
and hasn't come out since.
He's been trying to sow doubt
about me in Mentor's mind.
Go tell the Penal Court.
Early tomorrow morning,
I'll interrogate Ye Xian and the Marquis.
I don't need you
to stay in prison with me!
Father.
Your wounds haven't healed yet.
Stop talking.
It seems this time Fu Hailian
is determined to see me dead.
And you still came in here with me.
Do you think that makes you filial?
How foolish!
Find a way to get out of here quickly
and protect your mother
and your sister.
If the marquisate is gone, then so be it.
You never wanted
to inherit the title anyway.
Stop talking.
Please.
Why are you here?
Greetings,
My Lord.
Did Fu Hailian
send you to interrogate me?
Why didn't he come
to interrogate me himself?
He hides behind others all day
and plays tricks.
And he still has the nerve to claim
it's for the country and the people.
The Senior Grand Secretary
is occupied with many affairs
and may not be able to come in person.
But
I will certainly
relay your words
to him.
My son
is naturally a bit foolish.
He was afraid I'd suffer here,
so he came to keep me company in prison.
This matter has nothing to do with him.
Let him go first.
Father.
Shut up!
Your deep love for your son
really touches me, My Lord.
But
I'm afraid you still don't know
that Young Lord Ye
almost stabbed me
to death on the street.
It's pure luck that I can still be here
questioning you today.
As for the food in this prison,
I doubt you and Young Lord Ye
would be able to eat it
or get used to it.
Then don't eat it.
Take it all away.
Chen Yanyun, how dare you!
What are you doing?
I
am the chief interrogator of this case.
Young Lord Ye,
you'd better think carefully
before you speak.
My Lord,
the prisoners are still awaiting trial.
We can't afford to have them die, My Lord.
Bring the Marquis out.
Yes.
Guards.
Ask whatever you want.
I have a clear conscience.
I have
nothing to ask.
[Confession of Marquis Changxing]
These are my charges?
It's a confession.
You have admitted to your crimes
without dispute.
All that is left
is for you to sign it.
Third Master.
When a nation is on the brink of collapse,
treacherous officials like you
are bound to emerge.
Even if it costs me my life,
I will rid the country
of evil men like you.
What a Marquis Changxing.
Truly majestic.
But don't forget,
your son is still in my hands.
[A Splendid Match]