[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 17]
Watch the heat.
[Xue Rui]
[The Yan Du Xian is well-received, right?]
Very good.
Hurry up.
Okay.
-No problem at all.
-Qiaoqi! Qiaoqi!
A customer is causing trouble
in the Chinese restaurant.
Go find the restaurant manager.
Why look for me?
Because...
You secretly changed the chef
without informing us customers!
If I hadn't asked just now,
were you going to keep hiding it?
It's not like that, sir.
Our official website has already...
Close it!
Official website?
I'm here to have a meal.
Why would I check the website?
What's so great about your place?
The Imperial Kitchen, huh?
Well, sir,
I am
the manager of the Chinese restaurant.
If you are not satisfied
with our Yan Du Xian,
we can replace it
with another dish for free.
The other dishes are also very good
and delicious.
Look, everyone!
Look!
They have a guilty conscience!
They know their food is terrible,
so they do this,
trying to buy their way out.
Is the Chinese restaurant at Purong Hotel
only at this level?
And you claim to be a time-honored brand
in Shanghai, huh?
-Our Chinese restaurant's...
-Excuse me, do you have any complaints
about the Chinese restaurant?
Sir.
I'm the acting chef of Purong Hotel,
Li Qiaoqi.
What do you think about our dishes?
Please tell me.
Your chef is a little girl?
That explains it.
Sir,
my cooking might not have satisfied you.
Please give me your suggestions.
I will definitely improve.
Come on! Come on!
Take a look, everyone.
The former head chef of Purong Hotel,
Jia Shikun,
has job-hopped.
I was wondering
why such a famous master
of Huaiyang cuisine
couldn't continue working at Purong Hotel.
So, there's a young and beautiful
female chef
waiting to get promoted, huh?
What a pity.
She only has good looks.
But her skills are
far inferior to Master Jia's.
Sir,
if you have complaints about my food,
just say it.
Isn't a personal attack
a bit inappropriate?
What? I'm unsatisfied with the food.
Can't I complain about it?
Is there a problem?
Your food is bad,
but you blame your customers?
With this service attitude,
I'll record it and post it all online!
Come on.
Sir,
please calm down.
I came all the way here
just to have some authentic Yan Du Xian.
But what do I get?
Your service is terrible.
And you even want to hit people, huh?
Sir, I'm sorry.
We've let you down.
I apologize on behalf of our hotel.
I will comp your Yan Du Xian.
You can try some other dishes.
I'm not trying anything.
I didn't get to eat the food,
but I am seething with anger.
I'm leaving.
Sir, you...
Qiaoqi.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry
I'm sorry,
ladies and gentlemen.
I'm sorry for interrupting your meal.
We are truly sorry.
Today's Yan Du Xian
is cooked
by our new chef.
Compared to the previous Yan Du Xian,
the taste is slightly different,
but they both have their merits.
So,
today, we would like to invite you to
try it for free.
We hope you can give us
your valuable feedback.
Thank you.
Please continue with your meal.
Why did you comp his meal?
Is the food I cook worthless?
Qiaoqi,
there is no problem with your food.
But in that situation just now,
it wasn't the place to reason with him.
You saw it.
That diner was here to cause trouble.
You knew he was looking for trouble,
so why did you do that?
By comping his meal like this,
it only makes it look like I was wrong.
That's not what I meant.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
This is the food returned by the customer.
I'll eat it for you.
What a waste.
Don't follow me.
Hello, this is
Purong Chinese Restaurant.
Okay, I've canceled it for you.
Good job.
Hold them off for a few more days
until they are completely dead.
By the way,
tell Chef Jia
to deadlock the salted meat channel
over this period
at all costs.
[Sales Analysis]
[Purong Chinese Restaurant]
Mr. Ji,
our rating on the platform
has dropped below 4.
It can't make it to the front page.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Qiaoqi,
they're all rotten.
Hurry up and throw them away.
What a pity.
The food quality is so disappointing.
The dining environment is just so-so.
The service attitude is not good either.
How can it be a five-star hotel?
It's even worse than the three-star ones.
The store bullies customers.
I'll never come here.
Mr. Ji.
What should we do now?
Notify the Marketing Department.
Tell them to give me
a closing plan within a week.
Chinese restaurant
is suspended.
Notice:
the Chinese restaurant will be
temporarily closed this week.
Foremen and forewomen of all floors
in the HSKP Department,
should communicate well with the guests.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I called you here for a short meeting.
Regarding
the notice of the temporary closure of
the Chinese restaurant,
the HSKP Department's work
needs to make corresponding adjustments.
The Chinese restaurant is closed down.
Is Purong Hotel going to close down too?
No way.
I've only been here for half a year.
Regarding the rumors about
the Chinese restaurant,
please do not spread them.
As a member of Purong Hotel,
I hope
we can have more confidence
and less panic.
No matter how the leaders arrange it,
as long as we
do our own jobs well
and provide good service,
we will definitely be fine.
Got it?
-Got it.
Welcome back next time.
[Purong Hotel Chinese Restaurant
Temporarily Closed]
The kitchen is so quiet today.
I heard the chef quit.
Yes, yes, yes.
I heard the chef is a woman.
How did she become the chef?
She's not the official one.
She's the acting chef.
I think this woman
is either related to the higher-ups,
or the higher-ups use her as a tool,
praising her first and then,
destroying her.
Anyway, the Chinese restaurant is
in big trouble now.
It's directly closed for good.
Hurry up, brothers.
Come on, come on.
It's all my fault.
[Staff Only]
[Management Analysis and Conclusion]
Mr. Ji.
I came to get your clothes
that need dry-cleaning.
Wait a minute.
Come on.
Here you go.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Are you crying?
I just went to the Chinese restaurant.
Today is the last day of business.
I feel a little sad.
The Chinese restaurant is
temporarily closed.
Temporary, okay?
Why are you sad?
Aren't you sad?
Your comrades-in-arms are still
going through fire and water for you,
but you have abandoned the city
and fled with your troops.
If you act like this,
how can anyone work together with you?
Go on.
Li Qiaoqi was promoted by you.
You know
her character and her cooking skills.
The closure of the Chinese restaurant
has nothing to do with her.
Why did you put her in the spotlight
and let others trample on her
and smear her?
Do you mean
I should have emphasized in
the notice that
closing the Chinese restaurant
has nothing to do
with Li Qiaoqi
and
called on everyone not to cyberbully her?
If I did that,
Li Qiaoqi would leave with glory,
and you would be satisfied then?
Huh?
Qiaoqi is
the biggest victim
in this incident,
who was promoted by you,
and then
cut down.
If it weren't for your whim,
she wouldn't have been on
this roller coaster.
She was a hero of the business banquet.
But the next day, she became
a despised chef who caused
the closure of the restaurant.
Is it fair to her?
Go on.
I'm sorry.
You asked me to speak.
Chickened out?
I'm not chickening out.
I know I have no right to say this.
I apologize for my attitude,
but not for this matter.
Do you know
what the purpose of
suspending the Chinese restaurant is?
Do you know
how many departments' interests
will be affected
by this event
and how many vested interests
will be intrigued?
Do you know that?
Do you know
how much resistance there is
from top to bottom,
and how much risk I have to take?
Then why did you...
Because
this concerns the overall reform
of Purong Hotel,
and even its life and death.
That's all I can tell you.
You don't need to know the rest.
Then what is Li Qiaoqi?
Is she a first-aid kit
to fill the chef vacancy,
or a pawn in your business empire?
You shouldn't ask me this.
You should go ask your friend.
Ask her
whether she wants to be a deserter
at this time,
or
stay with us
until the Chinese restaurant reopens.
She is the one that
should make the decision.
Not me.
So,
you're not going to fire her?
You should have more confidence
in your peers.
Good night.
Qiaoqi.
Are you okay?
[Resignation Letter]
You're resigning?
Give it back.
Qiaoqi,
don't make a decision so hastily.
No need, I've thought it through.
The Chinese restaurant failed in my hands.
I really don't have the courage
to face my colleagues anymore.
Most of them have already left.
As for those who barely stayed,
I believe they
definitely wouldn't want to
work with an incompetent chef.
Me leaving is best for everyone.
As for you,
you don't need to shed crocodile tears.
As for the decision to
close the Chinese restaurant,
you must have voted yes.
A slap in the face
and a pat on the back.
What's the point?
Qiaoqi,
I know the rumors in the hotel
are against you,
but you really misunderstood.
Look.
What's this?
It's the Marketing Department's
data analysis
on the Chinese restaurant's
last month of operation.
Look.
Numbers don't lie.
Qiaoqi,
during your time as executive chef,
the occupancy rate in the dining room
has increased significantly
compared to before.
[Purong Chinese Restaurant
Sales Data Analysis Statistical Chart]
Look at the main hall's occupancy rate.
Then, what dropped?
It's the occupancy rate of
private rooms and the banquet hall.
Look.
[Purong Chinese Restaurant
Sales Data Analysis Statistical Chart]
It's getting lower and lower.
But the cancellation of orders for
the banquet hall and private rooms
was basically related to
the personnel changes
of our hotel.
It has nothing to do with
the quality of our dishes.
Besides,
the internal questionnaire of
the F&B Department shows
that the customer satisfaction rate
is far higher than
[Purong Chinese Restaurant
Sales Data Analysis Statistical Chart]
the hotel's standard.
So,
when you said
the Chinese restaurant
failed in your hands,
or even that
you ruined the whole Chinese restaurant
alone,
I think such words
are nonsense.
Qiaoqi,
Mr. Ji and I
won't let these rumors
dictate your future.
Is this all true?
Numbers never lie.
That's great.
Thank you, Xue Rui.
If I really have to point out
your shortcoming, Chef Li,
it might be that you
do not have
the management perspective
that an executive chef should have.
But in the future,
you just need to
strengthen your leadership.
I believe
you can lead the team well
and let everyone fight together.
I will, Mr. Ji.
Thank you for your trust.
Now that the Chinese restaurant is closed,
you can
concentrate on
developing your signature dishes.
As long as the signature is established,
I think the appeal of
our Chinese restaurant
will be great.
I'm going to look for
new suppliers tomorrow.
I plan to look around
the nearby suburban counties
to see if there are
any suitable cured pork suppliers.
Hurry up.
We are waiting for your good news.
Okay.
Mr. Ji,
the board is ready.
Are you going now?
Yes.
[Purong Chinese Restaurant
Total Profit Statement]
The decision to close
and renovate the Chinese restaurant
was made based on our market research.
These are the successful cases
we have collected in recent years.
The closure of the Chinese restaurant
seemed to be
caused by the departure of
the star chef.
But in fact,
it was caused by the deep-rooted
management problems
within our Chinese restaurant.
So this renovation
[Wei Siyuan]
is by no means
a superficial cleaning project,
but a deep self-reflection.
Sounds good.
Let's go.
[Thank You For Listening]
[Quality Chinese Food Wins Reputation.
Excellent Service Creates The Future]
Thank you, everyone.
[Purong Hotel]
[Thank You For Listening]
When I heard that
[Purong Hotel]
the Chinese restaurant
was closed for reconstruction,
I was worried.
But
after reading this business plan,
I felt much relieved.
In my humble opinion,
we should
give young people
more opportunities.
Opportunities are
always accompanied by risks.
Your company
only holds 4% of
the shares in Purong Hotel.
It's hard for you to understand
our concerns.
Rushing to renovate the Chinese restaurant
is very likely
to let investors' money
go down the drain.
After all, they are not paying
to sponsor our renovation.
As the old saying goes,
preparation is the key to success.
After the Chinese restaurant is renovated,
if it can stimulate consumption
and boost business,
in the long run,
it will be good for Purong Hotel.
Mr. Gu,
stop sitting on the fence.
If you really had to pay for it,
you definitely wouldn't do it.
You...
Siyuan.
You are on the frontlines of
hotel management.
Tell us your opinion.
I can't be considered
on the frontlines anymore.
The one really leading the charge is
Mr. Ji.
But to be honest,
I just took a look.
This renovation will cost 5 million.
Mr. Ji,
please don't take offense.
I certainly believe you didn't overquote.
But for the hotel, this expense is not
a small amount.
Ultimately,
for a Chinese restaurant,
the taste of the dishes is
the most important.
I suggest we endure it if we can.
Taking a step back
will make things easier.
It's too late.
Guys.
I'm late.
[Duan Aoxiang]
Mr. Duan Jr. is here.
Madam.
This is Mr. Duan Jr.
He is an observer for the board.
He doesn't participate in decision-making.
Mr. Duan, you came here at this time.
Do you have any advice?
I wouldn't dare give advice.
I'm here to learn from you seniors.
By the way,
I am
a warm-hearted person.
I heard about Mr. Ji's
Chinese restaurant renovation plan,
and I just couldn't sit still.
There are some things
I need to get off my chest.
Mr. Ji,
may I speak?
Please.
Today,
I have two pieces of news to
share with everyone.
First,
Kuanli Group
has launched a high-end fusion restaurant.
As for the address,
coincidentally,
it's right opposite your hotel.
As for the head chef,
it's Jian Shikun,
whom you recently kicked out,
Chef Jia.
Chef Jia has
officially joined our group.
He was promoted to
head chef of the Chinese restaurant.
It's truly a case of
everyone in their right place,
and getting what they need.
Congratulations.
Mr. Duan, as far as I know,
the restaurant in your hotel
targets high-spending customers.
The service style
is more like a club
rather than a hotel.
It also uses a membership system.
These are two different tracks.
As for Chef Jia,
Purong Hotel doesn't plan to rehire him.
So, congratulations.
I hope you enjoy working together.
That's a matter of opinion.
There is a second issue.
Kuanli Group
signed a contract
with the famous Chenying Design Studio.
By the way,
Mr. Ji,
aren't you going to invite them
as the design consultant
of Purong Chinese Restaurant?
I'm sorry.
In the end,
they chose Kuanli.
But I believe
they will give you a reply soon.
Thank you, Mr. Duan,
for sharing information so selflessly.
Yes.
We did plan to cooperate with
Chenying Design Studio.
However,
this is just one of
our overall renovation plans.
I understand that everyone
lacks confidence in
our reopening.
But what I want to tell you is that
this is not a risk
but an opportunity.
I promise you all here
that we will break even
within a month of reopening.
For three consecutive months,
we will remain profitable.
If I fail to accomplish this task,
I will
resign voluntarily.
This is a military pledge.
It seems Mr. Ji is going to
fight to the death this time.
I don't think there is
any need to be so aggressive.
Anyway,
Mr. Ji is also
a management talent.
Why do you
risk your own career like this?
Alright.
I have heard
both sides' opinions.
I think we should end the discussion.
Next,
let's vote by show of hands.
Those who agree with
the Chinese restaurant's
renovation plan,
please raise your hands.
Three voted in favor.
Two voted against.
The resolution on
the Chinese restaurant renovation plan
passed.
Let's call it a day.
Aunt,
isn't it too hasty?
You are
always so conservative.
Overthinking everything
won't let you succeed.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
As for what you did
this time...
Mr. Wei,
don't be discouraged.
If we can kick Ji Feng out this time,
we're halfway there.
You want to eat yourself to death?
Why did you get so much food?
Didn't you see that?
The cooks of the Chinese restaurant are
cooking in our staff canteen.
We are enjoying Michelin-level cuisine.
When the Chinese restaurant reopens,
your good days will be over.
We don't even know when
the Chinese restaurant will be renovated.
Reopening?
You can wait until the cows come home.
Didn't they say the board
had approved Mr. Ji's plan?
Miyu,
since when do you care about gossip?
I...
Nonsense.
Isn't everyone in the hotel
caring about it?
Don't keep us in suspense.
Hurry up and catch us up.
The board
did approve it.
But I heard
the renovation team
Mr. Ji wanted to cooperate with
was snatched
by Mr. Duan.
No one knows what Mr. Ji is going to do.
Everyone is very pessimistic about
the Chinese restaurant project.
Let's talk about something happy.
Dianjiangchun is livestreaming tonight.
Goods are available at up to 70% off!
What does she sell?
She doesn't just
sell cultural tourism products now.
She sells everything.
[AIA&LEED]
[LIN & PARTNERS DESIGN ASSOCIATES]
[DANIEL TAN]
Hello.
Where is your forewoman?
She is off work.
Do you need me to contact her?
It's fine.
Thanks.
Mr. Tan.
Sorry to
bother you so late.
Then, why did you still come here?
You won again.
I bet with Mr. Tan.
I said after you read his business card,
you would definitely come.
He said nobody would
work after 10 p.m.
See?
What did I tell you?
You have to keep your word.
I promise.
Please come in.
Okay.
I'll leave you to it.
I'm leaving.
Good night.
Thank you.
This kind of color matching of
bright red and purple
with high saturation
is not popular anymore.
What is
popular now?
Warm,
simple,
wooden,
gray,
and so on.
I remember
the second floor of your hotel
only has a few private rooms,
right?
Yes, there are 12 rooms in total.
That's not enough.
Young people nowadays like
talking about work while eating.
I suggest
to build
a new Chinese-style
hollow-carved
private room in the lobby.
It won't block the view,
while still offering
privacy.
Since you are renovating the restaurant,
we can be
bolder.
This way,
the hotel will be more...
Let me pour you another cup.
No. No. No.
Get me some alcohol
to refresh my mind.
No way.
I caught you.
You are trying to drink secretly again.
This is my son.
Mr. Tan, nice to meet you.
He's a curator.
I asked him to come and give some advice.
We meet again.
Sit.
You seem to know each other.
Yes.
We met once abroad.
It's destiny.
That's great.
We can have a discussion together.
Then, I'll be straightforward.
Can we change all the wall lamps
to chandeliers?
Go on.
I know that the current wall lighting
provides very even illumination.
But in a setting like a restaurant,
it's more appropriate to use chandeliers.
Because they can
focus a softer light source
on the dining table area.
Then isn't it easier to
draw the guests' attention
to the dishes?
Also, from a spatial perspective,
the current layout after adjustment
looks a bit top-heavy.
Right?
If we use this vertical lighting,
arranged in a scattered way like this,
it can make the lighting and fixtures
more decorative.
It will also make the whole place
look more coordinated.
What do you think?
He's a curator.
He just brought his theories here.
They're all connected.
You are so serious.
- What he said makes sense.
- Daniel.
No, I don't want it.
Try this cup. It's different.
Try it.
I added lemon and honey.
Doesn't it taste much better?
Not bad.
Mr. Ji, you should have a cup too.
Stop drinking coffee all the time.
Honey cures headaches.
Thank you.
Mr. Tan.
Long time no see.
Thank you.
I'll leave you to it.
That makes sense.
Yes.
Mr. Ji.
About Qiaoqi.
I misunderstood you.
I'm sorry.
This brand of soothing tea
can help relieve headaches.
I hope it helps.
Xu Miyu.
Ms. Xu.
Tomorrow at 8 a.m.,
the crew will come to the VIP entrance
to shoot Qiao Feifei.
There will be many reporters present.
I need you to coordinate the service well.
Can you handle it?
Yes.
Are there any special requests?
Stars are also guests.
Just serve them
like you serve any other guest.
For this kind of thing,
I don't need to teach you
step by step, right?
I understand.
[Only You, Feifei]
[You Are My Ideal]
Room service.
Ou.
I'm looking for Dai Wei
to coordinate with him
on tomorrow morning's schedule.
He's already back at the studio.
He won't be coming over today.
Then, could you
give me his contact info?
I'm afraid not.
Wei usually hands out
his own business cards.
We can't just give out
his contact info.
How about this?
The crew arrives at 8 a.m. tomorrow.
I'll call you guys at 7:30, okay?
Okay.
Bye.
[You Are My Ideal]
Room service.
Butler Xu.
What is it?
Your VIP pass is ready.
So fast.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
By the way, tomorrow at 8 a.m.,
a crew will be filming downstairs.
At the VIP entrance,
there will be some media.
It might cause some inconvenience
to your travel.
Sorry for that.
Qiao Feifei's shoot?
Got it.
I'll leave now.
When the crew's cars arrive later,
let them park over there.
See those two parking spots?
Don't just focus on stargazing.
Be careful with everything.
Got it?
Don't worry, Miyu.
I promise to complete the task.
I won't let you down.
I swear.
I'll go attend to other things.
Room service.
Wait a minute.
Miyu, the car is here.
[Only You, Feifei]
Copy that.
Room service.
Wait a minute.
It's already 7:40.
I need to see Dai Wei.
Feifei,
I told you not to wear
this vintage Mugler.
For an occasion like today,
you must wear the outfit
specified by the brand.
Be a good girl.
We can't breach the contract.
Dai Wei.
Excuse me.
It's already 7:40.
The crew has arrived.
And for some reason,
a lot of fans and media are here too.
I...
Why are you rushing me?
Please
help me
get a dress of this brand.
The black one
in that pile of suitcases.
Shasha called and asked for you.
Why are you rushing?
Can't you see I'm trying to
figure something out?
My brain will explode
if you keep pushing me.
Miyu.
Is Qiao Feifei downstairs yet?
The media and followers
are blocking the entrance downstairs.
It's a complete mess.
I know.
I'll push her again.
Did you find it?
Dai Wei,
it's almost 8:00 now.
Can we...
Found it!
Hurry up.
Take Feifei to change.
When is Miyu coming down?
Does the only thing you could do
is to push people?
Instead of rushing us,
why don't you help us find the clothes?
Someone
should have coordinated with us
on this yesterday, right?
Does your hotel
lack this basic professionalism?
Yesterday, I...
What's to explain?
Instead of explaining to me,
why don't you arrange some security guards
to maintain order downstairs?
Dressed!
Hurry up.
Let's go downstairs.
We're coming down.
Why aren't they here yet?
Coming.
Let's go.
Turn it on.
Turn it on. Let's go.
Wait.
It's not Feifei.
Li Bingyan, go!
Wait.
Qiao Feifei isn't here.
Li Bingyan.
Ms. Li Bingyan,
is the man next to you your boyfriend?
Is he also in the industry?
How long have you been together?
Please answer our questions.
Please answer us.
Just answer us.
Why are there so many of you here?
Wait, it's not Qiao Feifei.
It's cold.
You should wear more clothes.
Ms. Li Bingyan,
is the man next to you your boyfriend?
How long have you been together?
Please answer us.
We are not ready to tell everyone yet.
Darn it.
Tell us about your relationship.
Please answer us.
When were you together?
It's really not convenient to disclose.