ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL
HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
Hello?
Yes, that's me.
All right.
Okay, I see.
-What is it?
-What's up?
I passed my interview.
-Really?
-Is that true?
-Awesome! You have an internship already.
-What is it?
-Here's the thing.
It means
that I can't go to the party.
No way! You promised me!
Hurry up and get ready.
How was the interview with him?
Well, it was like usual.
How is that?
There was nothing special.
I guess I should give you some advice.
First--
Stop. Please don't.
Your ways with Chen Qiang
aren't suitable for Wangwang.
Wangwang should
depend on herself.
Thank you.
All right then. All the best!
Good luck to me.
Compared to the intended results,
can we improve on the details?
Jiaxu, what do you think?
In my opinion,
this is good to go
since it reconstructs the design
of the previous scene
and the functions are optimized.
Regarding the lighting,
can we refine it
a little bit more?
It looks rather stiff to me.
Our game's weather system
should update in real-time.
At present, the daytime looks fine.
However, I think
we can still adjust the night view.
Look at that…
Siyun.
-Are you okay, Siyun?
-What's wrong?
What's wrong, Siyun?
Have a seat.
Are you okay?
I'll get her a cup of water, Jiaxu.
Okay, go.
Do you need to go to the hospital?
It's okay.
It's a chronic gastric problem.
Siyun, I think you should go
to the hospital
-or it will get worse.
-It's okay. I'm used to it now.
-Honey.
-Li Xun.
-Are you okay?
Is it gastric pain again?
Let's go to the hospital.
I'm not going.
Listen to me. Come.
This is a critical period. I must be here.
-We're all here.
-Your health is more important.
-Yes.
-They're all telling you to go.
Is work more important than your health?
-Yes, just go.
-You can come back to work later.
-Go on.
-Help her up.
-Let's go.
-Go, Siyun. I mean it.
I'll leave this to you, Jiaxu.
Stay here. I'll take her.
-Li Xun, I'll get the car.
-Okay.
-Be careful, Li Xun.
-Be careful.
Goodness, Ning Wei.
You're packing so many things.
Are you going to a beauty pageant?
It's my first trip with Chen Qiang.
More cosmetics and clothes are necessary.
Look at you.
It's so nice to be single.
You don't have to bring anything.
I'm going for an internship,
not a beauty pageant.
That's true.
Sangsang, you look like
a working professional today.
Nonsense.
Yes, you do.
Good job.
I wanted to dress more formally,
so my boss won't think that I'm weird.
By the way,
you'll be staying in the dorm alone.
Will you be scared?
I'll be okay.
Don't worry. Don't be scared.
I'm interning only two hours away
from the dorm.
If you feel scared, call me.
I'll come right away.
Who needs you to accompany her?
She has a boyfriend.
Let me interview you.
Are you getting an internship so early
so you can stay
to spend more time with him?
It's honestly to intern--
Okay, say no more.
We understand.
Your perfume smells so strong.
Does it smell nice?
It's a bit too much.
Is that so?
I think it's all right.
What is it?
Hello, little demon.
I've been busy dating.
By the way,
have you booked your flight?
I'll pick you up.
Didn't I tell you that I'll be interning
and not coming back?
Didn't Dad and Mom tell you?
Say that again.
I finally got
an internship offer.
It's hard to get an internship offer here.
I finally landed one.
Of course I need to go.
Besides, Dad and Mom have agreed to this.
You get one more chance.
Think before you speak.
I already…
I did think…
I did think before I spoke.
I'm not doing anything bad.
Why are you acting like this?
Fine.
Do whatever you want.
Listen, if you get scammed again,
don't you come to me sobbing.
I don't have time for your nonsense again.
Why would I be scammed?
Your rebellious phase is so long.
You've been rebelling since 11th grade.
Listen, you were dumb to begin with.
Once you date, you're even more dumb.
I'm dumb?
I'm…
I'm better than you.
You have to announce to the world
that you're dating.
Do you want to pick a fight?
You started it first.
If you were sensible enough,
I wouldn't need to meddle.
Think about it.
Fine. You can do whatever you like.
You can date all you want.
Don't come to me again.
Was that your brother?
My immature brother.
Your brother is really strict.
You're an adult now.
I mean,
he is this mad
just because you're not going home.
If he finds out
that you're dating an older guy,
won't he blow up at you?
I don't think he will.
They're close friends.
Are you sure?
Good luck.
He knows Duan Jiaxu well.
Never mind.
I'll be honest with him.
I'm sure he will trust Duan Jiaxu.
SANG ZHI
Sang Yan.
You don't have to worry about me.
I just want to intern over the summer
to gain experience
in the animation industry.
I'll be home for Golden Week.
I lied to you earlier.
My boyfriend isn't
a postgraduate student here.
You know him too.
He's Jiaxu.
Not some bad person.
MESSAGE REJECTED BY RECIPIENT
CHAPTER 19, LEAN IN CLOSE
THE RHYTHM OF HAPPINESS
You're our first intern
who is a college freshman.
Why are you interning so early?
I just want to gain some experience.
That's great. You're so proactive already.
Is this your first internship?
Our company mainly focuses
on animation design and management.
Some of our clients are advertising firms
or relevant media.
Other clients are agencies and firms.
This is the Planning Department.
That is your seat, Sang Zhi.
That is your seat, Wan Zhe.
Where is Wang Yun?
The client called me again last night
to complain.
If you can't understand his requirements,
call and ask until you do, okay?
Xiaoyu, I've made an appointment
with Mr. Chen.
We'll get his approval today. Don't worry.
That is Shi Xiaoyu,
the head of the Planning Department.
Nice to meet you, Xiaoyu.
Who are you?
What's wrong with you?
And what's wrong with you?
It's none of your business!
Do you know why I did that?
I don't care why.
Xiaoyu, I'm Wan Zhe, a new intern.
I'm…
-I'm an intern.
-Our department
is the design hub of the company.
All projects start
at the Planning Department.
After we get a project,
we're the liaison between
the Design Department and our clients.
Your job scope is to assist us
in project development.
Sang Zhi, this is your staff badge.
Thank you.
Here you go, Wan Zhe.
-Thank you.
-You'll assist me, Xiaowan.
Sang Zhi, you're with Xiaoyu.
Come on.
Where have you interned?
I've interned at a few companies.
All right, let's get started.
This one…
Put some colors and see.
Make some adjustments.
Hello, Xiaoyu.
I'm the new intern, Sang Zhi.
If you need anything--
Make ten copies of these three files.
Double-sided, side mount. Any questions?
No.
I want the copies by 10:00 a.m.
in the meeting room.
And prepare tea for the clients.
All right.
Why are you still here?
We still need to amend this.
His head is too big.
The proportions look off.
I'll amend it.
Are you having trouble?
If you don't know something, just ask.
We prioritize efficiency here.
-Help her with it.
-Okay.
Thank you. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
ZHIZHI'S FIRST DAY OF INTERNSHIP
RED PACKET FROM DAD, EMPTY
SILLY DOG
What's the matter?
SANG ZHI
TO SANG YAN
RED PACKET FROM DAD
TOO LATE, IT'S EMPTY
DAD
Brat, all you do is bully your sister.
What else can you do?
Exactly!
ANGRY
How was your first day of work, Zhizhi?
HOLD TO TALK
Today was the first day of my internship.
I'm quite happy
because my coworkers treat me well.
Also,
the work isn't as dull as I expected.
It's quite interesting.
I knew you would arrive early.
I'm not late, am I?
No.
What did you bring?
Let me see.
What?
This is for you.
You must be tired
after your first day of work.
Sunflowers?
-Do you like them?
-Why sunflowers?
Sunflowers.
I hope that your days at work
will be bright like them.
I like it.
Good.
Let's go. You must be hungry.
No.
Are you going to eat this?
Is it yummy?
It's good.
Did you enjoy your first day at work?
Was it tiring?
Did they give you
a manageable workload?
How are your coworkers?
Why are you laughing?
You're acting like…
-Like what?
-A dad.
Don't you think you're naggy?
You're really long-winded.
You have a lot of questions.
Do you find me naggy now?
Never mind.
Here.
You don't have to worry about me.
I'm working now.
I'm a mature adult.
I'm no longer a child.
A mature adult.
Very well.
Well,
I have a gift for our little adult.
It's so cute!
Doesn't it look like you?
Is this
a pig?
It's a rabbit! How is it a pig?
Its ears are so big.
It looks like a pig though.
It looks like Sang Yan.
I got this for you
because I remembered
when I first started my internship,
I was lost and clueless.
I was stressed out every day.
I tended to doubt myself.
So I hope that you won't experience this.
I hope you can be happy
and everything will go well.
And I know
that you stayed for the internship
so you can spend more time with me.
If you're upset,
you can vent to it.
It's great for relieving stress.
Screw you, Sang Yan.
Did you have a fight with him?
How did you know?
I'm not blind yet.
He blocked my number.
Why?
He doesn't want me to stay here.
He wants me to go home.
Moreover,
have you told him about us?
I haven't told him yet.
I planned to go back with you this summer
to tell him about it.
It's better to tell him in person.
But now,
I'll have to wait until Golden Week
to go back with you.
We need to be sincere.
Don't worry about it.
Just leave it to me.
He's so childish.
He's really childish.
I guess I'll need to buy a new one soon.
JULY 2ND, MONDAY
DON'T DOUBT YOURSELF
HAPPILY FACE THE CHALLENGES
On the cosmetic ad's creative direction,
I want to hear everyone's ideas.
But I have two requirements.
It needs to be more immersive.
Any other ideas?
Perhaps we can use cold colors
like blue or green.
Okay.
Handle this. Leave this for next time.
Take care of these.
Xiaowan, are you done with the report?
-Yes.
-Let me have a look.
Okay. Good job.
-I'll treat you to a meal.
-Okay.
Sang Zhi, why don't you eat first?
You can work on it later.
I'll pass.
Okay. Good luck.
Hello?
Are you going out to eat yet?
Not yet. I'll go after I'm done working.
Have you eaten?
I have a meeting later.
I'm afraid I won't have time to call you.
You can let me know after you're done.
Okay.
Are you not done yet?
If so, why are you on the phone?
I'll call you later.
I'm sorry.
Don't do personal stuff during work hours.
Okay.
Jiaxu.
Li Xun asks you over.
Siyun is on a video call.
-Come on.
-Okay. You can go first.
Come on, let's go.
Yawen, I'm clocking out now.
My boyfriend is here to pick me up. Bye.
Can you get off work early today?
I think so.
I plan to pick my boyfriend up from work
to give him a surprise.
Okay, I'll leave first.
-Bye. See you tomorrow.
-Bye.
Xiaoyu.
I've organized the invoices.
Where do I place them?
Just put them on my desk.
There's another box here.
Finish it before you leave.
Are you leaving?
-Let's go.
-We're leaving.
-Bye.
Don't stay too late, Sang Zhi.
-Bye, Pengxing.
You're so hardworking, Sang Zhi.
-Bye.
Why is it giving an error again?
Am I a Powerpuff Girl?
I keep battling errors.
I don't think
I'll survive until launch day.
Jiaxu.
Don't look at me.
I still have a lot on my plate.
You two must be why
Siyun is out of commission.
That won't happen.
Do you want a drink?
You'll be recharged.
Here, have a sip.
Spill it. What's the problem?
It's an error message.
Error message?
-Let me see.
-Dinner is here.
You've all worked hard.
-Thank you.
-But I have no idea.
-Try it.
-There's a food delivery for you, Jiaxu.
I didn't order anything.
It's yours.
What?
Is it from your girlfriend?
-What did she order?
-You're so lucky!
Here, let me have a look.
-Hurry up.
-Give me some.
Do you still want my help?
Eat your own food.
-Come on.
-Let's eat.
Let's eat our own food.
Come on.
Hello?
Hello.
Is the food delivery from you?
Of course. Who else could it be?
Have you eaten it yet?
Not yet.
If you ordered it for me,
I'll eat it.
Eat up then.
You ordered so much.
Is it good?
It's delicious.
After you finish it,
remember to take a photo
so I can see how much you ate.
Okay.
Are you still here, Sang Zhi?
Why are you back?
I'm getting something.
Remember to turn off the lights later.
Sure.
What are you doing?
I'm working.
I haven't finished some assigned tasks.
Have you eaten?
I've had my dinner.
I'm so full today.
I think I probably need
about
two more hours until I'm done.
I'll go to you now.
Wait for me.
Aren't you busy? Why are you coming?
No, I'm done already.
I'll go to you now.
Eat your dinner first.
-Besides, I still have work to do.
-I'll see you in a bit.
Bye.
You can lean on my shoulder.
How is it?
You've worked all day.
Are you tired?
I have a question.
Have you really
never had a girlfriend?
Have you?
No.
Wait.
Why do you ask?
Well,
it suddenly came to mind.
Hold on.
Did someone speak ill of me?
I have eyes around you.
I know whatever you do.
Eyes?
I get it.
Who doesn't have that?
The guy that sits on your left
is a short-haired fatty with glasses.
Did I guess it right?
Of course not.
Silly.
Dummy.
I was just tricking you.
Be careful.
I'm watching
your male coworkers.
You should feel
rather different now.
In school,
though there are a lot of schoolmates,
the social circle is smaller and simpler.
Now that you're in a company,
every department has its own agenda.
You also have superiors and bosses.
No matter what they say,
let it roll off your back.
Your job is to observe and learn.
Don't take anything to heart.
You're still an intern anyway.
Okay?
You're so strange.
I was so tired from work today.
But after seeing you,
I feel recharged.
Are you fully charged now?
Well,
I also want to recharge.
Are you fully charged now?
Not yet.
How about now?
Let me charge a little longer.
Your phone has been ringing.
You should answer it, intern.
Is it your boss?
Hello, Xiaoyu.
Okay, I'll do it tonight.
Okay.
I'll bring it tomorrow.
Jiaxu, Li Xun is at the office.
JIA YANG
Let's go.
I'll give you a ride.
Okay.
Intern.
Do interns get this much work?
Didn't you have work
when you were an intern?
So internships…
There's always a learning curve.
SANG ZHI
Are you going to sleep now?
DUAN JIAXU
Yes. What about you?
Are you done with your work?
Rest early.
SANG ZHI
I still have some work to do.
You can sleep first.
I'll sleep after I'm done.
Good night.
You're up, Jiaxu.
Jiaxu.
Where have you guys been?
We went out to buy supper.
We didn't want to wake you.
Jiaxu, here is supper.
-Come.
-Come on. Eat with us.
-Join us.
-Come on.
We can work after supper.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
ALARM
Why are you here?
I'll drive you to work.
Why didn't you tell me?
Hop in.
Breakfast.
Let's go.
Did you sleep well yesterday?
What's wrong?
Your outfit is the same.
You look tired.
What did you do last night?
Didn't we bid each other a good night?
Look.
If you have another girlfriend,
you should let me know
otherwise, you'll be tired.
You would have to be with me
during the day
and spend the night
with another girlfriend.
No. Sang Zhi, I…
I have many sets of this outfit.
Besides, for a girlfriend,
you are more than enough for me.
Don't try to change the topic.
Be honest with me.
Did you work through the night?
No.
I did work overtime,
but not through the night.
I did sleep.
I didn't want you to worry about me,
so I didn't tell you about it.
I know.
I'll inform you in advance from now on.
-Is that okay?
-That's not it.
You could've told me.
You didn't have to come.
You could've slept in.
No way.
I must still drive you to work.
Listen.
You must nap before going to work, okay?
Got it.
Keep at it, intern.
You remind me every day
not to skip my meals.
You should heed your word too.
Otherwise, I'll get mad.
Okay.
Bye.
See you.
-Hold on.
-Okay.
Hi, Xiaoyu. What is it?
Nothing much.
I have a question.
Are you still in contact
with Duan Jiaxu?
Why do you ask about him?
I just saw him outside my office building.
He's outside your office building?
Do you still remember that dinner?
He was with a girl.
That girl threw water on you.
She is now interning at my company.
I saw
that they're quite close.
Excuse me for a minute.
Are they in a relationship?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Should I come and meet you now?
I'm really fine. Go to work, Xiaoyu.
All right. I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
Has Xiaoyu given you her feedback
on the slides?
I submitted it to her last night,
but she hasn't replied yet.
She's taking a long time to reply.
Well, who knows?
Maybe she has no issues with it
and approves it.
Sang Zhi.
Please come over.
Is this your first proposal?
The client will be seeing this.
The most basic requirement
is a simple yet persuasive layout
with clear and concise data
for quick understanding.
Look at the title's font.
It's huge while the content is tiny.
Noted.
You said that the font size must follow--
I told you not to act on your own.
Did I say to be an inflexible fool?
Xiaoyu.
Help me take a look at Jiajia's draft.
It's really urgent.
Amend it at once.
Revise it following the original template.
Remember, keep it simple and organized.
Do you understand?
What's wrong with you?
She's just an intern.
Why are you so harsh to her?
Xiaoyu.
You don't seem to like Sang Zhi.
Look, we finally have two interns.
Sang Zhi seems quite smart and obedient.
Don't scare her away in less than a month.
Obedient?
You don't know
what she is like in private.
Judging by your words,
you seem to have a big problem with her.
She doesn't know anything,
but acts like she does.
I just can't stand her.
Hello, Xiaoying.
Hello, Xiaoyu.
Let's have dinner together later.
Tonight? I can't make it tonight.
My company has a team-building event.
Where?
It's at the KTV that we frequent.
I'll talk to you later.
I need to go. Let's have dinner next time.
Okay. Go on.
-Fifteen!
-Ten!
-Five!
-Fifteen!
-Twenty!
Come on! Drink!
How much did you drink?
DUAN JIAXU
Not much. Just a little.
SANG ZHI
I'm so bored.
I want to leave.
Find an excuse.
I'll pick you up.
Okay.
-I wait for you
-To pass me by unaware
-Only then can I have a good dream
-To compromise
It's almost my dorm's curfew.
Okay.
-I'll get going first.
-Next song.
-Goodbye.
-Pick a song.
-Pass me the mic.
Pass the mic, Mingming. This is mine.
-Nothing good is nearby.
-Let's eat.
-Everything is closed now.
-What did you get?
Supper from one of the restaurants.
Come and see.
-Eat up.
-Dig in.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
Just hang in there a little longer.
It's always hard in the beginning.
Back in the day, Li Xun and I
always coded until sunrise.
Eat up.
I really miss my bed.
I wonder
if my fish are still alive.
After this,
I'll go to the beach,
stay in the largest ocean-view suite,
and enjoy the sunset.
Sure.
Send me the receipt for reimbursement.
Really? Thank you, Jiaxu.
Jiaxu.
What are your plans after this?
I'll move to a new place.
After that,
I'll spend time with my girlfriend.
I want to have a girlfriend too.
Well,
you should wait until your program works.
You're right.
Let's eat quickly and get back to coding.
When I get no more errors, love will come.
Eat up.
You don't have to be that serious.
Hurry up. Eat up.