(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
-Why's someone lying there?
-What's going on?
SEVENTH DAY OF THE TENTH MONTH
What's going on?
Someone's dead!
Somebody died!
THE WELL-WOVEN HOUSE
Did you hear?
Last night, they found another body.
So scary!
FOURTEENTH DAY OF THE TENTH MONTH
Again, his heart was ripped out.
I heard a high-ranking demon's here.
So we can't stay in Luo'an anymore.
Now the whole town's in panic.
That demon will keep killing
and taking hearts.
Who knows who'll be next?
How terrifying!
To keep their wedding going,
the Wei family hired a demon hunter
from the Shilin Sect.
-This isn't just any demon hunter.
-Good.
-That's it!
-He has a flower on his forehead!
Good.
Miss, you are…?
I'm the Wei family's bride-to-be's…
cousin.
My name's Yu Wei.
Please, follow me.
WEI QING, HEAD OF THE WEI FAMILY
Here, Shengwei.
YU SHENGWEI, DAUGHTER OF THE YU FAMILY
Master Wei.
LUO WEI, STEWARD OF THE WEI MANSION
The wedding dress
will be done in two days.
I'll deliver it to the Yu mansion myself.
Guess we should go pray
at the Dragon Deity Temple.
May we stay deeply in love
and grow old together.
What do you think?
Come on, Wei Qing.
The Dragon Deity
doesn't handle that stuff.
LIU WEIXUE, WEI QING'S COUSIN
Master Wei.
Miss Yu's cousin has arrived.
You are…?
Shengwei.
I know it's been a while,
but you really don't recognize me?
I'm your cousin,
Yu Wei.
I remember now.
You're Yu Wei.
TWENTY-FOURTH DAY OF THE TENTH MONTH
I've got a hostage now!
Dare you chase me anymore?
Ow, that hurts!
What's your problem?
What kind of weirdo are you?
Why'd you hang me up? Untie me, now!
What's the problem with you demon hunters?
You are not going after that fox demon
who's been killing and stealing hearts.
Why come after me,
an innocent little weasel?
Save it. Get in!
No, please!
Thank you, kind sir,
for saving my life a second time.
No problem, Miss Yu.
Second time?
Master Wei's arranged a dinner banquet
to thank you, Master.
Please rest here for now.
Thanks.
WU SHIGUANG
YOU CHI, LOW-RANK WEASEL DEMON
So?
Did I nail my act?
All thanks to my majestic black smoke.
Absolutely brilliant!
Half a month ago,
a broken-tail fox attacked Miss Yu.
It must be linked
to the heart-ripping one.
Otherwise,
those arrogant demon hunters
from the Shilin Sect
wouldn't have been guards
for an ordinary family.
You Chi!
Come in!
Yu told me
how you were kind enough
to save her half a month ago.
She could've died.
Thank you, Master.
It was nothing.
But that time,
it was really dangerous.
HALF A MONTH AGO
Help!
SEVENTH DAY OF THE TENTH MONTH
Eight tails…
A broken-tail fox!
Run!
That fox demon moves without a trace.
Really terrifying.
Shengwei,
have your favorite chestnut cake.
It may comfort you.
Master Wu, you're truly amazing.
If you hadn't chased that fox demon off,
my cousin's heart
would've been ripped out too.
I didn't exactly chase it off.
And that day marked the first murder
in this heart-ripping case.
That broken-tail fox must be the culprit.
It might've been hiding in this mansion,
so it will try again
to harm Miss Yu.
Master Wu, are you serious?
The air above this estate
is thick with demonic energy.
I fear a high-ranking demon
has taken root here.
Master Wei, if you're willing
to hire me as a house guard,
I can definitely protect Miss Yu.
That's great!
Although Master Wu
is just a wandering hunter
with no real background,
although he couldn't actually defeat
the fox demon last time,
although he probably still doesn't know
where the fox demon is
or how to guard against it,
although no one knows
if he could win if it does show up,
one thing's sure…
He's so handsome,
with such a great build.
Having him stay by my cousin's side,
Shengwei will surely be "safe."
Yeah, sure thing!
Master Wu,
see you later!
I thought it was a sure thing,
but Wei Qing has such a small mind!
So petty.
The one who really wants us gone
isn't Wei Qing,
but Miss Yu's cousin.
Who's there?
Rucui.
Is it time yet?
Rucui?
Quiet.
Follow my lead.
Hey,
are we sure this isn't dangerous?
The heart thefts started on October 7th.
Every seven days, someone dies.
Today, the fox demon should strike again.
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
If you want to catch
the heart-ripping demon
and claim the bounty from the Shilin Sect,
then shut up, okay?
So the fox demon wanted
to kill Miss Yu that day, but failed,
so it killed someone else instead.
Then every seven days after,
it kills one person on schedule.
Yeah, that's it!
I'm just too smart.
Are you even listening to me?
Yeah.
TWENTY-EIGHTH DAY OF THE TENTH MONTH
AUSPICIOUS FOR WEDDINGS
Congratulations!
-Congrats!
-Please, come in!
Come on in!
THE WELL-WOVEN HOUSE
Put it over there.
Right this way!
Come, this way, please!
What a perfect day!
Congrats!
Come on, right inside!
THE WELL-WOVEN HOUSE
The nine-tailed fox's magic
is right in my hand.
JI LING
LI JIE
Impressive.
Let's go!
Alright!
-Please, come in!
-Come on in!
This way, please!
-No need for formalities.
-Congratulations!
-Please come insode.
-Congrats!
-Right this way!
Gentlemen,
it's crowded and busy inside.
Please leave your names
and your wedding gifts,
so I can record them properly.
Well, the gifts…
The gifts…
Li Jie.
What are you looking at me for?
Congratulations.
All these human customs
are such a hassle.
This door's flimsy.
I could smash it with one swing.
Rude.
THE WELL-WOVEN HOUSE
Oh, Master Qi!
Your presence honors our humble home!
-Madame Zhao, you've arrived!
-You are here.
-Come in, please!
-Madame Zhao!
You're not Miss Yu.
Miss Yu
doesn't have a vixen face like that.
And you're not Master Wei.
Master Wei
wouldn't hold a knife to me.
You're so eager?
They say
the first night together is priceless.
How could I not be eager?
Since we're now wed,
then
we should be open with each other!
I never thought
my husband would have two faces.
Too bad.
One woman shouldn't serve two husbands.
That makes sense.
So, how about
you let me down first?
Well then, sir,
you'll have to take that dagger
away from me first.
Trying to leave?
Such a beautiful vase,
and you have no taste for elegance.
Someone as beautiful as me,
and you have no taste either.
Tonight, I'm divorcing you!
So?
Pretty clever.
Isn't that Steward Luo of this family?
Why is she sneaking around
in her own house?
Something's off.
Let's check it out!
Who are you?
Her accomplices?
What's going on?
Why are you stopping me?
You reek of demonic energy.
You're a fox demon!
She's that heart-eating demon.
Heaven really is fair.
It gives you such a handsome face,
but no brains to go with it.
Groom,
why the sudden change in your face?
Your opponent is me.
You have no sacred power?
Does that stop me from fighting you?
Who exactly are you guys?
I'll ask you the same question.
I'm the demon hunter Wu Shiguang.
Since when do demon hunters
have to worry about so much,
even playing the groom?
I'm pretending to be the groom
for one reason only.
To catch a demon.
What a coincidence.
We're demon hunters too.
We're also here to catch demons.
But unlike you back-alley,
rogue demon hunters,
we're official demon hunters
from the Shilin Sect,
sent here to investigate
the heart-ripping case.
This is the Shilin Sect's
demon hunter commander,
Li Jie.
Stunned now?
An ice-wielding demon.
Sure enough,
you're the one we're after!
What grudge do we have?
I don't even know you.
Trying to run?
It's you!
Sir,
save me.
Let… Let her go!
Sir, what's going on?
Who's there?
Still trying to flee?
Thank you, sir, for saving me.
Well…
You're thanking the wrong person.
The groom saved you. Thank him instead!
Thank you, kind sir.
You're welcome!
What are those red threads made of?
I guess it's blood.
Submit now
or die trying?
It's your choice.
Do I look like I'm struggling?
I'm a demon hunter too,
here to catch demons.
What crime have I committed?
Fine.
Now the whole room's
full of demon hunters, isn't it?
Don't count me in.
I'm no demon hunter.
I'm a respectable woman.
Don't bother denying it!
We traced the demonic energy right here.
You're the nine-tailed fox
who ripped out hearts!
How terrifying!
Just now,
was she trying to rip out my heart?
Me?
A heart-eating demon?
Are you joking,
or serious?
-I…
-Who has time
to joke with a fox demon like you?
You're the sect's demon hunter commander.
And you?
What's your identity?
Me?
Sir!
What should I call you?
My name is Ji Ling.
Ji means "life's a journey,"
and Ling means "hearts that beat as one."
Stay here, and don't run off, okay?
Sir!
Please don't leave me alone!
This female demon is really terrifying!
I'm so scared!
So scary!
So scary…
You demon!
LI MAO, WEDDING GUEST OF THE WEI FAMILY
TAO XI, LI MAO'S WIFE
Weimiao Pavilion.
Blood.
It's frost.
It's not even winter yet.
Why is there all this frost?
It's demon magic.
Those prayer beads are amazing.
What's their story?
Don't touch them.
Keep them there.
You're so thoughtful.
Whatever you say.
And you're so clever.
Thanks to you tipping me off,
I was able to prepare.
Wangyan,
the groom's a fake.
He's here to catch fox demons.
Be careful.
Don't let him
make it real or turn the tables on you.
I thought we'd guarded against one,
and now two more show up.
That Ji Ling guy
and his long-blade friend
won't be easy either.
But the one really hard to shake
is that guy who won't let me go,
Wu Shiguang.
Oh yeah?
I don't believe it.
Wangyan,
want to make a bet?
Broken-tail fox,
it really is you.
Miss Yu?
I asked you to gather some intel.
Did you get it all?
Of course!
There are 952 weasels in Luo'an City.
From street gossip to corner rumors,
they know everything.
Let's start with the bride, Miss Yu.
She's Luo'an's famous embroiderer,
especially skilled
at stitching birds and beasts.
Now, Luo Wei.
This woman's something else.
A month ago,
the Wei family's business faced a crisis,
almost went bankrupt.
Then Luo Wei appeared out of nowhere
and turned things around.
After that, she joined the Wei mansion
and became the steward.
Everyone in the house
fears and respects her.
And gossip says
she's got a thing for Wei Qing.
So, she really dislikes Miss Yu.
As for Liu Weixue,
he's Wei Qing's distant cousin.
The Liu family's been generals
for generations.
But despite all his skill,
Liu Weixue refuses to go to war.
-Half a month ago,
-Go…
he fled an arranged marriage
and came here.
-Bring the wine!
-Word on the street
is he might be interested in Luo Wei.
Quick, bring the medicine wine!
What's all this?
So lively late at night?
And Yu Wei grew up in the countryside,
not from around here.
Their families rarely interact.
So her showing up for the feast
is pretty strange.
Oh, quite a crowd here.
Miss Yu Wei!
Weren't you supposed to stay in your room?
Why'd you come out?
It's so dangerous!
Since you called her a demon,
how could I stay
in the same room with her?
Plus,
she totally wrecked my clothes.
So I came here
to change into new ones.
So, sir,
do I look good?
Yeah… Good.
What's wrong?
Where's the bride I tied up?
Darling,
are you looking for me?
I followed the broken-tail fox here.
But the moment I entered this room,
it vanished.
What do you mean?
I mean,
among all of you here,
one of you
is the heart-ripping killer I'm after,
the broken-tail fox.
THE RUNAWAY FOX'S
HIDING IN THE WEI MANSION
Wu Wangyan,
proceed to Luo'an at once
and bring Xiaowei back.
Understood.
What about me?
My mission is still to assist her?
Your mission
is to get close
to a young man named Ji Ling.
He is your fated one.
Fated one?
Wangyan, what does this mean?
You hear that?
All five of you
are suspects!
And you two
are no simple cases either.
Bai Ze has brought news
of the nine-tailed fox, Xiaowei.
SHILIN SECT, SCALE CAVE
Right now, she's hiding
in the Wei mansion in Luo'an.
Li Jie,
it's time to bring her back.
Understood.