I'm going to try to understand
irrational numbers.
Did he mean me?
But why?
What for?
Why on earth?
What?
CHAPTER 29:
SOMETIMES, THE TRUTH CAN BE DANGEROUS
Um, why…
Why would Pythagoras
have killed his student?
Isn't it obvious?
He couldn't bear to see
his world collapse.
5TH CENTURY BC
What is the matter?
Master.
PYTHAGOREAN MATH ACADEMY
CROTON, GREECE
By any chance…
PYTHAGORAS, DIRECTOR
…have you discovered something new?
HIPPASUS, STUDENT
I tried to express the length
of the diagonal of a unit square
as a fraction.
Sure. All numbers can be expressed
as a ratio of integers.
That is the truth
we have always been spreading.
The thing is…
that doesn't seem to hold true.
What did you say?
This number
just cannot be expressed as a fraction.
Wait.
Just a moment.
Fine.
Prove it.
This is a square.
Please look closely.
It just does not work.
If your theory is valid,
then everything
we hold to be true is false.
Have you…
shared this with anyone?
I have not told anyone yet.
I wanted to tell you first, Master.
Good.
That is fortunate.
Hippasus.
Yes?
Let us pretend
your proof never existed.
Master.
Sometimes, the truth can be dangerous.
Master!
The existence of irrational numbers
would have threatened the world order.
Gosh. What a math nerd.
Why does he get a gleam in his eye
whenever he goes over math stuff?
It's freaky.
But still…
it is kind of attractive.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
That's what happens
when you keep daydreaming.
Yes.
So embarrassing.
Please, I've seen far worse.
They say suffering embarrassment
boosts your creativity.
I see.
So you're doing it deliberately?
What more have you got in store?
Why would I share it and lessen the blow?
Fine, work on your creativity.
I'll be rooting for you.
EPISODE 9
I'm home.
Hit the bathroom
before you do anything else.
No, I'm good.
I know you can't go when you're out.
From now on, go take a dump
as soon as you get home.
I mean, when nature calls,
don't hold it in. Answer it straightaway.
Okay already.
I can take care of myself.
Why are you fussing about me pooping?
Obviously because
you're not taking good care of yourself!
Fine.
I'm going.
Should I go and see your homeroom teacher?
Why?
He carried you all the way to the ER.
I'm both sorry and grateful.
Oh, no. There's no need for that.
I already thanked him.
He's swamped as is. Don't disturb him.
Promise me you won't, okay?
I guess he's got you good.
But then again,
he's given you all those demerits.
No wonder you're scared stiff of him.
Gosh, he must be quite the hard-ass.
You're in for a tough time.
Well, he's not that bad.
He's just a bit blunt.
He's a bit on the prickly side,
but he's not a bad guy…
Sometimes he can be childish and immature,
but he's not a bad guy at heart.
…at heart.
I get it now.
They say smart people
are masters of manipulation.
There we have it.
I'm being manipulated.
Just like Mr. Yoon.
When you're scolded
and yelled at ten times,
one kind comment will make you go,
"Wait, maybe he's not so bad after all."
Yes, that's exactly it.
Seriously though,
he's been so mean to me all this time.
The jerk says he'd try to understand me,
then my heart skips a beat?
How ridiculous!
Pull yourself together, Eui-ju.
Starting tomorrow, don't even look at him.
CHAPTER 30:
SOMEONE I SHOULDN'T AND CAN'T LIKE
Hey, did you see?
That thing I sent in our group chat.
About Professor Na Deul-i at Princeton
becoming the first Korean
to be awarded the Fields Medal.
What about it? Do you know her?
No, I don't.
But Woo-su does.
She was on his Olympiad team
back in middle school.
Really?
Aren't you jealous?
Don't you think that should have been you?
If only you hadn't dropped out
of the Olympiad.
If you had only studied abroad--
What's wrong?
I thought he was going places.
I had no idea he'd end up here,
bickering with math idiots like you
over toast with me.
I'm talking about my friend Woo-su.
Woo-su, my freaking genius buddy.
Whatever. Forget it.
-He could've won the Fields Medal and--
-Hey.
Give it a rest.
What's so special about some dumb medal?
Hey.
Do you even know what the Fields Medal is?
Of course, I do.
Then tell me who the first recipient was.
David Copperfield.
Forget it.
Why should I bother
talking to someone so ignorant?
Anyhow, Woo-su, you're…
I won't bother with you either.
Enjoy your toast.
When is he going to come out?
It's normally about now.
Do I have everything I need?
Did I bring all my textbooks?
I'd better wear my puffer jacket.
Why isn't he here already?
We're going to be late.
Da-ju, get a move on.
Woo-su left an hour ago.
Jeez, he's a real pain in the neck.
-What on earth?
-What time is it?
We're late for sure.
Jeez, he's always like this.
Isn't that Eui-ju?
Eui-ju?
She'll be late too.
-Good morning.
Good morning.
Why is he doing that with his hair?
Let's get started.
Why has he pushed his sleeves up?
Why are his fingers so long?
Why is he drinking water like that?
The way he's twiddling his pen…
It's so…
So obnoxious.
What is it you want to tell me?
Let's take a seat here.
Go-ya.
Fangirling used to be my only joy in life.
I know.
Of course, many were fictional characters,
but my love for them
was always genuine.
Thinking about those characters
gave me the strength to carry on.
But now…
The fact he keeps cropping up in my mind…
It makes me mad.
The thing is…
I don't want to think about him.
I shouldn't think about him,
but I can't help myself.
You're in denial.
In denial?
You're always like this.
You watch countless videos of some idol
while claiming not to be a fan
or save a gazillion photos
of the lead actor in some series
but say you only watch the show
for his acting.
Do I really?
Yes, you do.
Even when you're into someone,
you don't want to admit it.
No matter how much you deny it,
you're already into him.
No way.
That can't be it.
No. I shouldn't even like him,
and I just can't.
Why not?
Huh?
Why can't you like Mr. Jung?
What?
Why are you in denial about liking him?
Oh…
It's not like that.
No.
-Shall we get going?
-What?
You solved my problem. Let's go.
-Huh?
-Let's go. I'm good now.
Oh. Hey, Jenny.
Where are you going?
Oh, the teachers' office.
I'm gonna apply for a field trip.
I'm so jealous. Where are you going to go?
I'll dress up in hanbok
and visit the Gyeongbokgung Palace.
And then… The market.
I'm going to try gimbap
and tteokbokki there.
Then on to Hongdae before heading
to the Han River to eat ramyeon.
Finally, I'll check out
Namsan Seoul Tower.
Are you sure you have the energy
to do all that in one day?
-Sure.
-But Jenny,
you do know you have to write a report
when you get back, right?
Of course.
"I learned a lot about Korean culture."
That should cover it, no?
Bye!
I guess no one has shown her
the report form yet.
Leave her be. She looks so happy.
I guess. Goodness.
THE DANCING CARNATION
NOTABLE WORK "MY MOTHER" BY YOON DONG-JU
Wow.
Are you reading that again?
You must have it memorized by now.
Of course.
"On the face of the woman
who no longer smiles,
a single flower in full bloom emerged."
Maybe Dong-ju's mother is not smiling
because she passed away.
"And another small flower
that doesn't answer."
The small flower
is probably Dong-ju himself.
Why didn't he answer
when his mother called him?
Why didn't he look at her?
Probably out of resentment, right?
He must regret that so much now.
You know what?
If you'd put this much effort
into your studies,
you'd be crushing Korean Literature.
How are you getting on with your poem?
Well…
Hey.
It's Mr. Yoon.
Hello.
Hey.
Why didn't you come over and say hi?
You two have gotten really close.
Not at all.
He just gave me feedback on my poem.
I shouldn't even like him,
and I just can't.
That's what happens
when you keep daydreaming.
His voice
was definitely full of concern.
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 6
You're the future head
of the family company,
and you're carrying on
with some guy?
Are you out of your mind?
Who told you that? Who would dare…
It was me, Si-on.
I did it for you.
You?
So you joined the company
to get close to my mom and rat me out
about my relationship with Yoon?
I was only looking out for your future.
You're destined for great things.
You can't afford to set tongues wagging.
Don't make me laugh.
You think if you break us up,
he'll run into your arms?
He was the first person
to laugh at my jokes.
You've got to be kidding me.
He laughed at my jokes.
To spare your feelings, no doubt.
He's kind that way.
No, that's not it.
You have no idea
about the way he looks at me.
He doesn't look at anyone else that way.
-It's the same.
-No.
-Exactly the same.
-No…
You're welcome
to take your anger out on me.
But if you touch him, I won't let it go.
-No, I won't let you pass.
-Get out of my way.
No. Never…
-Mr. Kim!
-Yes, ma'am.
Lock him up until that Choi Yoon
or whatever his name is dealt with.
Let go. Let go of me!
Get him!
Are you okay?
What did I tell you
about wandering off alone, Yoon?
Are you hurt?
Let's go.
Shoot, what was that about?
Why did Yoon turn into a self-insert?
Why did I replace Mr. Yoon?
Why was I on fire there?
Everything was so vivid.
No way. Surely not…
TOPOLOGY OF ALGEBRAIC CURVES AND SURFACES
HEY, IT'S BEEN A WHILE
I'M BACK IN KOREA
CAN WE MEET UP?
MURIM GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
I'll try that.
Go-ya.
We need to talk.
What was that?
Oh, well,
I told Mr. Yoon I was having difficulty
coming up with a title.
He suggested using the first image
that came to mind when I read my poem,
or the word repeated the most in it.
So I tried it,
and I wanted his take on my ideas.
Why did you go by yourself?
You could've taken me along.
I did consider that.
But it was no big deal,
so I went to see him by myself.
"No big deal"?
I'm so nervous around Dong-ju
that I can't even say hi to him.
But for you, laughing and chatting
with him is no big deal?
Well, the thing is…
Tell me the truth.
The guy you like isn't Mr. Jung, is it?
You like Dong-ju, don't you?
What are you talking about?
I'm right, aren't I?
Otherwise, why would you go see him alone?
Why are you in denial?
Wait.
It's not Mr. Yoon.
If it's not him,
why can't you tell me who it is?
You're acting so weird right now.
Don't you trust me?
What?
I told you it's not what you think.
Do you have to keep going on about it?
Have I ever lied to you?
Fine.
I guess you're right.
Maybe I'm so blinded by love
that I can't trust an innocent friend.
Shall I give it a go?
-You think I can do it?
-Shall I do it, then?
Did you get cookies?
Leave me alone.
Hey.
What's up with her?
-You think they argued?
-No doubt.
They argued for sure.
She'll get over it soon, right?
CHAPTER 31:
EVERYONE HAS A SPECIAL SOMEONE
Wait.
What the heck?
Mr. Jung just left.
So why am I waiting for Mr. Ga?
No way.
Just looking at his face makes me sad.
Are you okay?
No way.
Love is…
like the first snow.
Love at first sight.
When you see them,
you know that person is meant for you.
That's how it is, kiddo.
MINI MOCK EXAMINATION 7
My first snow
isn't Mr. Jung but Mr. Ga?
What am I going to do?
Your cafe mocha is ready.
Thanks. Enjoy your drink.
Thank you.
What the heck?
What's he doing here?
Why didn't I see him earlier?
When I ordered this earlier…
At the counter…
I can't believe this.
Wait, did he see me
and come in on purpose?
My goodness.
Or maybe not.
Is this what they call fate?
Huh?
Cafe mocha?
It doesn't suit him at all.
He's got so much whipped cream on it.
What the heck? He has it just like I do.
What is he playing at?
Who is he waving at?
Long time no see.
I've missed you so much.
Until then,
I didn't understand my own feelings.
But in that moment,
everything became crystal clear.
My heart had been running wild,
without direction or plan,
and I finally understood it.
Everyone…
has a special someone
who makes their heart sink at least once.
Subtitle: Paul Carver