NO TAIL TO TELL
SEOUL SANGSEO POLICE STATION
Damn it.
Mr. Kang, you can step out now.
You just keep outdoing yourself.
You're really a piece of work, aren't you?
Hey, Si-yeol.
What?
Are you acting out
because I told you to quit soccer?
No, it's not like that.
Jeez, you're a total nutjob.
Is apologizing to me that difficult?
You've got a seriously nasty temper.
Seriously.
Fine.
You win.
Come back to training tomorrow.
But on one condition.
You'd better get your head in the game.
Listen.
Let's win the championship this season
and get promoted to the third division.
Are you crazy?
You expect me to play
in the fourth division?
Are you out of your mind?
I can't live like that.
No.
I won't, damn it!
Seriously…
Seriously, what the hell
is wrong with him?
- Hey, Woo-seok.
- Si-yeol.
Where are you right now?
Are you in London too?
Actually, Woo-seok…
- The thing is--
- No, wait.
Let's just meet up.
Let's talk in person.
I think
I've become a Premier League player.
That's the thing, Woo-seok--
It's all thanks to you, Si-yeol.
Hey, Woo-seok.
The thing is,
our fates have been switched.
What do you mean, switched?
You became
a Premier League player instead of me.
And I'm playing
in the fourth division instead of you.
Woo-seok?
So what do we do now?
What happens now?
Well, I asked.
She says you have to wish
to have our fates switched back.
A wish?
I have to make a wish?
Yes, because I don't have
anything left to pay for a wish.
I see.
Can you check your pockets or your bag?
Her business card
should be in there somewhere.
Woo-seok, come out here for a minute.
Just a second.
Si-yeol, hang on. I'll call you back.
Woo-seok? Hello?
Woo-seok, wait--
Woo-seok, do you have any idea
how crazy things are right now?
The clubs are fighting over
who's going to sign you,
and the reporters keep calling.
God, having such a perfect son
is exhausting!
Okay, today's the day.
Let's lock in your team!
And when your transfer fee comes through,
can I get…
a new car?
- Dad--
- I know.
I know we have plenty of cars, but…
Dad.
You're happy, right?
What?
Of course I am.
Thanks to you, I've got it pretty good.
Of course I'm happy.
I really was hoping for that one car.
Hello? Hey, Woo-seok.
Did you find the business card?
Well, the thing is…
What, it's not there?
No, that's not it.
Then what is it?
Do we really
have to switch back right now?
What… do you mean?
Just one month.
Let's switch back in a month.
I promise I'll switch us back then.
- Hey!
- If we're switching back anyway,
does it matter when we do it?
Of course it does.
Just give me a little more time.
Hey, Woo-seok.
You can't do this. Please.
I'm sorry.
Woo-seok!
Hyeon Woo-seok! Oh, come on!
I'm screwed!
I'm seriously screwed!
Damn it!
Damn.
REPUBLIC OF KOREA PASSPORT
KANG SI-YEOL
- Have a nice day.
- Thank you.
One ticket to London, please.
The earliest available.
- Would you like a round-trip ticket?
- No, one-way.
Excuse me.
It looks like your passport has expired.
What?
Then what do I do?
I have to get to London right now.
And here I thought
your friendship was special.
Not so special after all.
You!
Have you learned your lesson?
I'm not really fond of stupid humans.
Learned what lesson, exactly?
You think I'm the one who needs a lesson?
Apparently not.
Wait!
I seriously can't live like this.
Put me back!
Please.
You shouldn't have been
so cocky in the first place.
Well, that should do it.
I guess I've tamed you enough.
Shall we end this here?
When you wake up tomorrow,
everything will be back to normal.
- Really?
- Yes.
If you ever make a wish,
always remember what happened today.
So you don't make the same mistake
with me ever again.
And from now on,
don't be so quick to trust people.
Consider it a free lesson from me.
Man…
Seriously.
I'll never make a wish again.
Not even if my life depends on it.
Never, damn it.
Sorry.
What?
What was that?
Where to?
I'm sorry. I thought this was a taxi.
You're right. It is a taxi.
But…
VACANT
Sir.
I'll take you exactly
where you need to be.
EPISODE 4
THE PRICE OF GOOD DEEDS
Who are you people?
What's with the weather all of a sudden?
Something feels wrong.
Stay still.
Who the hell are you people?
What are you doing?
It's not here.
That's impossible. Look again.
Look for yourself then. It's not here.
You've got the wrong person.
I have jack squat right now.
I won't call the police,
so just let me go.
Shut up.
There's no business card
or anything remotely like it.
Are you sure this is the right guy?
I'll get straight to the point.
We're looking for something.
Hand it over,
and I promise nothing will happen to you.
You have the wish-granting
business card, don't you?
A business card?
That's right.
I have some business with that fox.
Unbelievable.
You did all this just for that?
Kidnapping an innocent guy
and tying him up?
Fine, I get it.
Just untie me first.
I'll just summon her for you.
You think this is a joke?
Hold it!
What did you just say?
You don't even have the card.
How are you going to summon her?
Dad, should we go look at some watches?
No, I'm good.
Let's find something for you instead.
You've already bought me plenty today.
Who knows when we'll have
a day like this again?
I really want to buy you one.
It's not like this is our only chance.
But I wonder if they still have
that limited edition.
- Let's go look.
- Shall we?
Hold on.
SI-YEOL
Who is it? Why didn't you pick up?
It's okay. I don't need to take that call.
Let's hurry.
We should go check out some cars later.
Really?
But that can wait
until the transfer talks are--
You said you wanted one.
Why wait? Let's buy it now.
Okay, then. Let's go.
Why isn't he picking up?
Just wait.
I'll get her here for sure, okay?
By the way, I don't know
what wish you're trying to make,
but you may want
to think it through one more time.
Thanks to that crazy fox…
Anyhow, wishes don't work
the way you think they do.
I know.
I'm not going to make a wish.
Then why are you
looking for the nine-tailed fox?
We're going to kill her.
You're going to kill her?
It's not for a wish?
Hey!
Hello?
Hey, Woo-seok.
Look, I'm a bit busy right now,
so I missed your call.
Okay…
Si-yeol.
I'm begging you, please.
I just need a month.
That's all I'm asking.
We're going to kill her.
Si-yeol?
Look, Woo-seok.
Let me call you back.
What are you doing?
I don't think this'll work.
Look, I don't like
that nine-tailed fox either.
But still, you don't have to kill her.
Fine.
If that's how you feel, then so be it.
We'll just have to find another way.
What is this?
I'm about to lose a huge chunk
of my spiritual power again.
I was wondering what was going on with me.
I should've known it was you.
Wait.
What is all this?
Look at you, crawling in here
not knowing this is where you'll die.
I recognize that face.
And you're that male shaman!
Your name…
was it Jang Do-cheol?
You're quite the wicked creature.
How did you know my name?
Oh my gosh!
Did you
trap me in here?
I spent years researching this.
You won't be able to do a thing in there.
Not even a centuries-old nine-tailed fox.
A human after a fox bead…
There used to be a few like you.
Ever wonder what happened to them?
Rumor has it
this dagger can cut through anything.
Humans, ghosts,
and even fate decreed by Heaven.
How disappointing.
I thought a centuries-old nine-tailed fox
would be different.
Are you about to leave?
The time has come, so I must.
Is your long watch finally over?
What?
Well?
Not so disappointing now, am I?
That really hurts.
It hurts!
Now do you wonder?
About what happened
to the humans who dared chase my fox bead.
How on earth…
It seemed like you were
digging into my past,
so I did some digging on you too.
Jang Do-cheol, 54 years old.
And?
And he's a former high-flying
fund manager.
He chose his profession wisely.
With his powers, he must've predicted
every stock price perfectly.
And he probably mistook it
for his own talent.
Anything else?
Ten years ago,
he quit a perfectly stable job
and has been wandering since,
with nowhere to call home.
His last known address is right here.
ID CERTIFICATE: JANG DO-CHEOL
YANGHEUNG-GUN, GANGWON-DO
I came to see if I could find anything,
but it looks like this will take a while.
If you have something to say, go ahead.
I'm listening.
What are you going to do with me?
I'm not sure.
Nothing at all, actually.
- What?
- You don't have long to live anyway.
You know that already.
You're destined
for a particularly miserable death.
So why should I bother
getting my hands dirty?
And as for you.
I'll be coming for you soon
since you clearly
haven't learned your lesson.
No!
This wasn't even my idea.
That guy made me do all of this.
I once heard someone say…
Damn it!
What is it now?
You…
…"Heaven's net is vast and wide,
yet nothing slips through."
What a joke.
Deities have no interest in humans.
There's no world
where the guilty are justly punished.
So I just need to deceive them
enough to get by as well.
Get up, Kang Si-yeol.
It'll be quite inconvenient for me
if you die like this.
If you're going to die, do it tomorrow.
Don't make it my problem.
If you die with your fate switched,
the ones above
will find out what I'm up to.
And that would be
extremely annoying for me.
Hey,
are you okay?
What happened to those people?
Why?
Planning on getting revenge?
Did you…
kill them?
What?
You must've forgotten already.
I don't kill humans.
Right.
Though I will pay them a visit soon
and make their lives a living hell.
Anyway.
I'm sorry.
What?
I feel like you got dragged
into this because of me.
Are you just going to sit there?
Get up. I'll take you home.
Yeah, okay.
I told you
this would happen,
Geum-ho.
You never once came to look for me.
Not when your child was sick,
or even after they died.
Not when your family was ruined,
when your husband died,
or when you were left to starve.
While you were living that miserable life,
why did you never once ask me
to grant you a wish?
You never gave me the chance to help you.
I smell the earth on you, miss.
It smells like the place
where I once lived, long ago.
I told you that you'd be miserable.
You knew you'd forget
everything in the end
and die as a lonely, withered old woman.
Why did you choose to endure it all?
Oh my.
You're such a beauty.
My, how beautiful you are.
I came to say goodbye.
Because you're going to die today.
There was something I needed to say.
I will never become human.
I won't love a human as you did.
I won't live in misery,
and I won't die in despair.
I'll never
live like you.
Gosh. Ma'am!
Ma'am!
- Oh gosh. Ma'am!
- My goodness.
- Goodness!
- Gosh.
Ma'am!
There she is.
Good grief. This senile old woman
is always wandering back here.
She can't even find her own home anymore.
How does she find
this place so well every time?
The sun's setting. Let's go.
Ma'am.
No…
Oh no. Ma'am!
Goodness me.
Ma'am…
Oh no.
Oh no. Ma'am! Poor thing!
Wait.
Are you crying?
Where am I?
I brought you here.
Are you feeling better?
The light's so bright.
What's wrong now?
What's wrong with me?
What just happened?
How is this possible?
- What did I do to deserve--
- What is it? What's wrong?
Yes, you.
It's because of you.
This is all your fault!
Why is it my fault again?
Do you know what I went through
because of you?
That's not the point!
Then what is?
I…
I've become human.
What?
I've become human because of you!
INN
Where are you going?
We should go our separate ways now.
What about me then?
What am I supposed to do?
Move to a new place every day.
What?
Don't stay in one place for too long.
That way, she'll have a harder time
finding your energy.
Hey, wait!
That's it?
What if that fox finds me here?
Maybe you're fine with dying,
but what about me?
That's not really my problem.
Calm down.
Explain it so I can understand.
I've become human.
What more is there to explain?
But is that really such a big deal?
What?
I mean, nine-tailed foxes eat
human livers to become human.
At least, that's what the stories say.
Are you out of your mind?
If you were me, would you really choose
to lose your powers, grow old and sick,
and die before even reaching a hundred?
- You think I'd eat a liver just for that?
- All right.
I get it.
Then how did this happen?
You wouldn't have suddenly
become human for no reason.
That's…
because I saved your life.
As you were dying,
I was losing my spiritual power.
So I saved you
just to stop that from happening.
But how can they count that
as a good deed?
How does that even add up?
Do they have any idea
how many terrible things I've done?
All because I saved one meager life?
Well, I agree.
You're not fit to be human yet.
There must've been some mistake.
You think so too, right?
Anyway, since you became
human against your will,
I really do feel for you.
But there is something
I've been wanting to ask.
What's that?
When exactly will I go back
to how things were?
What?
You said so last night.
That everything would be back
to normal by morning.
And it's morning.
Actually, it's already past morning.
It's lunchtime.
When will it switch back?
Have you even been listening to me?
I'm human now.
So?
I'm human now, so how am I supposed
to turn things back the way they were?
Wait, what are you talking about?
No way.
You're joking, aren't you?
Does it look like I'm joking?
This isn't a joke. This is hell.
No, no. This can't be happening.
Please don't do this to me!
Are you saying
I have to keep living like this?
Yes, for the time being.
"For the time being"?
For how long?
A few weeks?
Well…
A few months?
Say something!
What are you going to do?
There's no way I can live like this!
Do you think I want to live like this?
Then do something! Anything!
There has to be a way, right?
Do you even have to ask?
If there isn't a way, I'll make one.
Could you have gone any slower?
I said I was in a hurry.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
That temper of yours, seriously.
What are we doing here anyway?
I have some things to say
and questions to ask.
Something definitely went wrong.
You there, could you leave for a moment?
I have some business here.
- Hey.
- What?
He is
no longer here.
What?
He left last night.
That crazy old geezer!
Since you've come all this way,
why don't you stay for some tea?
Where did he go?
I wouldn't know.
How could a mere monk
fathom the divine will?
There's something I need answers to.
So I'd appreciate it if you could
just tell me where he went.
He didn't say.
But he told me to give you this.
Since you'll be living
in the human world now,
he said it's something
you'll definitely need.
What is this?
Your name is Ok-sun.
"Ok" for jade, and "Sun" for pure.
Lord Pagun hoped
that choosing a name like this for you
would help you rein in your temper.
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD
How did it go?
Is there a way?
Hey, say something.
How did it go?
STORAGE ROOM
What are you doing?
Hey.
Carry this and follow me.
What are these for?
What are you doing?
What is…
Gosh, that smell! Are you crazy?
Hey!
I'm going to burn
this place to the ground!
Jeez!
Let me go!
Excuse me, what's going on?
I'm going to burn this place down!
- What are you doing?
- Let me go!
- Why are you doing this?
- Put me down!
TRUSTED POLICE
WORKING WITH THE PEOPLE
The head monk spoke up for you.
He said you'd be able to
get out tomorrow morning.
Tomorrow morning?
Are you kidding me?
Tell them to let me out now.
You're here for attempted arson.
You should be grateful
they're letting you out tomorrow.
Can't we just pay them off or something?
Where would I get the money?
I'm broke because of you.
Whatever. This is pathetic.
Good grief.
Grab those two blankets over there.
There won't be any left
when the drunks get here.
By the way,
where's my wooden-handled dagger?
What?
The dagger I had.
It was gone when I woke up.
Don't tell me.
Did you not bring it yesterday?
Was there a dagger?
Oh, that.
I was all over the place yesterday.
You left it behind?
Yes. Was it important?
Go and get it right now!
Right now?
You want me to go back there?
Why? You want to wait until next year?
That's not what I meant.
After everything that happened yesterday,
how can I go back there alone this late?
Let's just wait until morning
and go together, okay?
It's the only Sajin Ritual Blade
left in the world.
Sajin… what?
It's a sacred dagger
that can sever and defy fate.
If we want to get things back
to how they were…
we might need it.
Jeez.
Is this the place?
Yes.
The NASDAQ is about to open.
Where are we going at this hour?
Jeez!
What is this place?
Where are we?
What are we looking for here?
There's a lot of weird stuff in there,
so don't be too shocked.
Weird stuff like what?
Hey, wait.
Si-yeol!
Damn it.
Oh, jeez.
Wait, why is it…
What's wrong? What's supposed to be here?
What is it?
- There's nothing here, Beom.
- What?
Seriously.
It's just a construction site.
You say there's something here?
Looks like there's nothing at all.
Are you okay, Si-yeol?
Yeah.
Top teams
from all over the world made offers.
Stop it, Dad.
Ms. Kim Ok-sun, you can come out now.
Ms. Kim Ok-sun.
I said, you can come out now.
I told you yesterday.
My name's not Kim Ok-sun.
Then are you going to stay in here?
I am coming out.
But I'm not Kim Ok-sun.
Hey.
How can I help you?
Call Kang Si-yeol for me.
- I'm sorry, who?
- I just got released from here,
but Si-yeol isn't here yet.
Tell him to get here fast.
This isn't the place for jokes.
Please leave.
Hey!
Kang Si-yeol?
I thought you'd abandoned me.
What are you talking about?
Why would I do that?
I need you more than ever right now.
Really?
Get in. We're going to Seoraksan Mountain.
We have to hurry before it closes. Get in.
Buckle up.
- Hurry up. Come on.
- Okay.
Okay, here we go.
Let's go.
Why Seoraksan Mountain all of a sudden?
Do you think we have time for that?
I found something.
Right. Did you find
the wooden-handled dagger?
No. When I got there,
there was nothing left.
The dagger was gone,
and so was all the shaman stuff.
What?
Then what on earth did you find?
Another
nine-tailed fox.
What?
How long are we staying here?
There's nothing there.
COUPLE SAVED BY NINE-TAILED FOX
STARTS NEW LIFE THROUGH VOLUNTEERING
That's absolute nonsense.
There is no other nine-tailed fox
in this land besides me.
How can you be so sure?
I just am.
If there were another being like me,
we would sense each other's energy.
Even from a distance.
Then what about those people?
They're just talking nonsense.
Humans are always like that.
They either hallucinated
or just wanted attention.
They didn't seem like that.
How would you know?
Because I met them myself.
Gosh, I really thought
I was going to die that day.
I think it was around 2 or 3 p.m.
when we entered Dinosaur Ridge.
Sometime around then.
But since it was winter,
the sun went down so fast.
It was freezing cold,
and we'd been hiking all day,
so we were exhausted.
We couldn't see a thing in front of us.
But she suddenly said
she was getting sleepy.
It was because of hypothermia.
If that happens on a mountain,
you're in big trouble.
I forced her to stay awake
and was dragging her along
when she suddenly appeared.
She was a very pretty young lady.
She suddenly appeared and asked,
"Would you like some help?"
We thought we were seeing things.
So we asked who she was
and if she was a ghost.
She said she was a fox trying
to become human by doing good deeds.
Anyway, she lit a fire for us
and helped us find our way.
So, thankfully, we made it back alive.
She said she was a fox, right?
The young woman said that herself?
I understand if you don't believe us.
But it's true.
Actually, there are
a few others besides us.
A few others?
After the article came out,
a lot of people got in touch,
not just you.
They all said they were saved
by that young lady on Seoraksan Mountain.
By the way,
you said there was nothing there, right?
What?
You said there were no shamanic items
and no Sajin Ritual Blade either.
Oh, that.
It was spotless,
as if someone had swept it clean.
Who could have cleaned the place up
overnight like that?
Maybe those guys came and went last night.
Not likely.
They wouldn't know that I've become human.
Why would they risk going back there?
And how could they have known
that you were stupid enough
to leave the dagger?
Hey!
Come on, that's not the point.
What do you think
about what I said earlier?
If we find that fox on the mountain,
couldn't she turn things back to normal?
Don't you think it's strange?
What is?
A deserted construction site wiped clean,
and a newspaper scrap
about a nine-tailed fox
lying around
as if it were deliberately left there.
I guess…
Take it out.
Sure.
COUPLE SAVED BY NINE-TAILED FOX…
SUNDAY, NOVEMBER 16, 1997
See? I knew it.
What?
Look at the date.
NOVEMBER 16, 1997
This newspaper is over 20 years old.
Isn't this a bit too convenient
to be a coincidence?
Someone is pulling the strings here.
Who?
Probably those guys up there.
That's just how deities treat humans.
Under the pretext of things like
fate or coincidence,
they manipulate humans however they want.
So there's no nine-tailed fox
on Seoraksan Mountain?
I wouldn't know.
Whether there's an actual nine-tailed fox
and they're sending us there,
or if there's another reason for this.
Let's go.
I need to see for myself
what they're up to.
Is that Park Bi-ryong?
How nice.
Do you know this bear?
The sun will be setting soon.
Wouldn't it be better to sleep nearby
and hike up tomorrow?
We're trying to get stranded anyway.
But aren't we a little unprepared?
You do have a plan, right?
It's just one night on a mountain.
Why are you making such a fuss?
Have you forgotten who I am?
I lived on a mountain for centuries.
Just follow me.
Wait for me.
Are you all right?
Go. Just keep going.
Eat this and hang in there.
You're still so young.
Just how much steeper does this get?
This useless human body.
Hey, young man!
- Take these with you.
- Pardon?
- No, I'm okay.
- Just take them with you.
And also…
Here, take this.
If you give all of this to me…
It's fine.
But…
What's wrong with humans today?
They keep giving us things,
looking at us with teary eyes,
and holding our hands.
Do we look that pathetic?
Excuse me!
Hold on a second.
Yes? How can I help you?
We received a report.
I'm telling you, it's not like that.
Who said anyone was going to die?
- Jeez.
- Are you sure?
If you weren't thinking such things,
why would you climb the mountain
at this hour dressed like that?
We've received several reports.
I don't know what you're going through,
but you're a young couple
with a future ahead of you.
Please think it over.
- No--
- We're not a couple.
And we're not here to die,
so just let us go.
We were dragged down for nothing.
How are we supposed to get back up?
You're going back up?
Of course I am.
Why else would I have come this far?
Goodness, you have no idea
how dangerous mountains are.
Anyway, you can't go up now.
You can't see anything, and it's cold.
Even expert hikers would be
in serious trouble without proper gear.
MULLEBOGO RESTAURANT
Oh man.
Jeez.
My goodness.
I thought you lived
on a mountain for centuries.
I've realized one thing for sure.
I'd rather die
than live as a human.
It's all cooked,
so you can eat it right away.
Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you for the meal.
- Sure.
Gosh, you're spilling everywhere.
You hiked with your legs,
so why are your arms shaking?
How should I know?
There's not one part of my body
that doesn't hurt.
Okay.
Here.
Say "ah."
Is it good?
Give me some more.
And some broth too. It's a bit dry.
Here.
Careful, it's hot.
You've got quite an appetite.
You want this?
Yes, the chives too.
- Please come again.
- Thank you.
Are you asleep already?
Jeez.
She must've been really tired.
Man, what on earth am I thinking?
Hey, wake up.
Come on, wake up.
What's this?
Why am I suddenly…
SPECIAL APPEARANCE BY SON SUK
NO TAIL TO TELL
Did you have a weird dream or something?
It wasn't a dream.
It was more like a prophecy…
You seem to keep forgetting,
but you're just a human woman now.
I get it. This is like hitting
on a female. It's called flirting.
Are you nuts?
Look into the records of the car accident
from nine years ago.
Find out everything
about where he lives and what he's doing.
You can't just do this all of a sudden.
How can you do this?
Have you ever seen
any other nine-tailed foxes?
- I have.
- Are you okay?
Do you need help?
Geum-ho?
Subtitle translation by Susanna Kim