ظآزThat dayظآز
ظآزNothing stays together foreverظآز
ظآزI've quit romanceظآز
ظآزWho hasn't failed againظآز
ظآزCrying in deathظآز
ظآزAnd in lifeظآز
ظآزEven nowظآز
ظآزWe keep learningظآز
ظآزIt's no surpriseظآز
ظآزBeing happy is so hardظآز
ظآزWeirdly, I became a role modelظآز
ظآزOn the day we met again, we said hiظآز
ظآزIt was a reminder,
a test, and a complaintظآز
ظآزWho can do anything without regretظآز
ظآزI am all rightظآز
ظآزMay you live in peaceظآز
ظآزLet the world roarظآز
ظآزSounds like a carnivalظآز
ظآزBeing alive is never dullظآز
ظآزHow wonderful to be freeظآز
ظآزI became even better without youظآز
ظآزNothing can be perfectظآز
ظآزWe bless each other in painظآز
ظآزWe nod and smileظآز
ظآزMay we both be wellظآز
= Love's Ambition=
=Episode 23=
Come in.
Ms. Xu, here's our latest
sample video feedback report.
Take a look.
We'll ship the goods next week.
Focus on customer reviews
and after-sales issues.
Got it.
Go ahead.
Alright.
Hello, Ms. Song.
Did anything go wrong
with Haochen at school?
No.
Haochen's doing well.
Do you have a minute?
Yeah.
It's Parents' Day next Saturday.
Got it.
(Relationship Guide, Real-World Clarity)
Brother-in-law.
Interesting paragraph.
Even for a married couple,
what keeps the marriage alive
isn't the certificate
or how much they sacrifice
for the relationship.
What really binds them
is their ability
to maintain the relationship
and resolve conflicts.
This is profound.
It requires deep thought.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
I know the theory,
but what should I do?
Listen to this.
World Literary Masters on Love.
Maugham said,
"In matters of love,
if you consider self-esteem,
the only explanation
is that you've only
ever loved yourself."
Therefore,
if you really love her
and want her back,
you should completely discard your pride
and take initiative.
Be fearless.
Be shameless.
Don't be afraid
to embarrass yourself.
Are you free tomorrow?
Meet me at the caf├ر.
It's about Haochen.
We can meet tomorrow. I...
Don't.
Don't send it.
Wait.
Not tomorrow.
Today.
Go to her place.
You came here fast.
Why are you here?
Didn't we agree to
meet at the caf├ر tomorrow?
I happened to have a meeting nearby.
So I thought I'd drop by
and ask about Haochen.
May I come in?
Shoes off?
No need.
It's Parents' Day
next week at Haochen's school.
The parent organizing this time
wants me to share our last event's plan.
But I've been swamped with work.
And I can't reach her.
I'll send you the documents.
Contact her, okay?
You're having guests?
I sent you the link.
Did you get it?
Just download it.
Okay.
Received it?
Poor connection.
Do you have Wi-Fi here?
My router's broken.
Download it when you get home.
Let me fix it for you.
I've scheduled a repair.
I got this. It'll be quick.
I'll fix it.
T-Thank you.
It just needs a reboot.
Okay.
Yan.
What's your Wi-Fi password?
My phone number.
Okay.
- 100.
- 100...
51807561.
Let's see.
Still not working.
Do you have a modem?
Where is it?
Just download it at home.
It'll be quick.
Where's the modem?
The modem is in the shoe cabinet.
Got it.
Go ahead.
Found it.
Let's see the living room signal.
It's good now.
Mind if I check your bedroom
for the signal?
Go ahead.
Yan.
Do you mind if I close the door?
It's more accurate.
It'll be quick.
Alright.
Looking for something?
Good signal under and above the bed.
Full coverage.
The bathroom.
Perfect.
Finally,
by the window.
You have full coverage now.
That's great.
Thank you so much.
Go back and check the documents.
I'll get going then.
Bye.
These curtains...
No.
I-I can change them myself.
It's fine. I'll help you.
It's dangerous and tiring for girls.
You don't have to do this.
It's okay. I got this.
Shen Haoming.
Smells amazing.
What soup are you making?
Coconut chicken soup.
Careful there.
This is your signature soup.
Must be an important guest.
Yan, look.
Smooth, right?
Thanks. You've worked hard today.
My pleasure.
You cooked quite a feast today.
It's already dark.
Head back home.
Pay more attention to Haochen.
Ask me if you need help.
Alright then.
I'll go back now.
Call me if your Wi-Fi ever fails again.
Okay. Thanks.
Finally here.
What did you say?
Your guest has arrived.
Go ahead.
I'll get the door.
Shen Haoming?
Sister.
Long time no see.
Come on in.
Yao.
Guan.
Hello.
I'm Shen Haoming.
Don't stand there.
Come in.
Keep the shoes on.
Yan.
I brought fruits.
A cake for you.
Thank you.
Sit.
I'll get you some drinks.
What are you doing?
Your sister and besties are here.
We should treat them well.
Shen Haoming.
Is this okay?
Okay, thanks.
What happened?
Why is he here?
No idea.
He fixed the router
and changed the curtains.
I don't know why he won't leave.
He won't leave?
Okay, let him stay.
Let me handle this.
Thank you for taking care of Yan
this whole time.
You've worked hard
and achieved such great results
in such a short time.
As her husband,
I'm really proud.
It's such a nice opportunity
to meet you and hang out here.
Annoying ex.
Why is he texting me again?
So annoying.
Unbelievable.
You haven't blocked him?
She shouldn't just delete his contact.
She should curse him every now and then,
block him,
unblock him after some time,
curse him again,
and block him.
That's what he deserves.
Some men are just like that.
When someone is in love with them,
they take it for granted.
But when that love fades,
they suddenly can't let go.
Aren't they mentally ill?
Yes, they are.
Those people are abnormal.
Don't be afraid...
To embarrass yourself.
Let's play a game.
Use two-word phrases
to describe our exes.
Okay?
I'll go first.
Stubborn fool.
Blind idiot.
Calculating brat.
One more.
Ungrateful wretch.
Nice.
So how should we treat them?
Obviously,
leave them to die alone.
Destitute in old age.
And what kind of attitude
should we adopt?
Ignore them.
Act like they're dead.
Oh right,
Jinda Group's new mall
is opening soon.
Feel free to visit.
Buy whatever you like.
My treat.
Your treat?
How much discount?
All for free.
My secretary will go with you.
Mr. Shen is absolutely
approachable.
Confident and kind.
Peerlessly handsome.
A true gentleman.
Showing off your vocabulary?
You know so many phrases, huh?
Ms. Xu is cooking alone.
Won't you help her?
Yeah.
- I forgot.
- Hurry.
Let's help her.
Let's go.
Ms. Xu.
Let us do this.
Take a break.
Rest for a bit.
We've got this.
Why don't you go home?
It's your first time
attending Parents' Day.
There is a lot to do.
It's fine.
Let me talk with Lin a bit more.
I have nothing to say to you.
Alright.
Then I'm off.
Call me if you need help
with your Wi-Fi.
Ladies,
Jinda Mall welcomes you anytime.
Thanks, Mr. Shen.
Bye, Mr. Shen.
He acted like the host here.
So shameless.
I don't get it.
Forget it.
Come on, let's eat.
Let's eat.
Set the table.
You have the appetite?
What happened just now?
You betrayed your friend
for some petty money?
Brother-in-law.
Why does the drink
taste so bitter today?
Brother-in-law.
Your sadness and sorrow
have been transmitted
to the brain,
which then signals the glands.
These glands received neural stimulation
and secreted melatonin,
causing low mood.
It's normal.
Just take some Vitamin B.
Yeah.
My previous advice was wrong.
As you know,
we doctors have
multiple treatment plans.
There's a Plan B?
Of course.
(Excerpt)
Your longing,
your regrets,
and your anguish
should all be shown to them.
As they say, "When a man cries,
a woman's heart softens."
The second tactic is to be love-sick.
(Yan Studio)
What brings you here?
Thanks.
Yan.
I thought about it a lot
and decided that
you should know about this.
Look.
What is this?
These are candid shots I took.
When you were away,
he often visited your building.
Many times, he almost went up,
but always gave up.
And he's been staring
out of the windows at work.
There's more.
When he was sent
to a regional subsidiary,
I secretly took some photos.
The local manager
picked on him to block his audit.
Mr. Shen fought alone
in unfamiliar territory.
What got him through the nights?
Your photos.
Yan.
I can tell
that you're everything
to Mr. Shen.
I haven't seen him smile
for a long time since you left.
You're really important to him.
I see.
The photos are well taken
and clear.
Good work.
I just want to know
what kind of candid shots
could get this close?
Shen Haoming seemed quite cooperative.
And this one.
He was in bed, right?
Yeah.
So you were in bed too?
Both of you were in bed?
Why are you having water?
Why are you nervous?
I get nervous when you're nervous.
And you're blushing?
Well...
You may leave.
(Chen)
I'm sorry, sir.
I failed.
(Yan's WeChat Moment)
(Jiang Liang)
Love preserved in old film reels
is charming because
it focuses on one person.
Radios and film projectors museum.
(Vespa125 motorcycle)
Careful there.
Watch your feet.
Alright.
Put it down here.
Be careful.
Be gentle.
- What's going on?
- Be careful.
Stop.
Put those down.
Mr. Jiang.
We're changing the exhibits.
We'll finish soon.
Who authorized this?
You.
Put it down.
A collector bought all the exhibits
at a hefty price.
He paid and asked for delivery.
They're sold?
Don't you know I'm your boss's friend?
I pay a fortune for maintenance
every year
just to see these items.
Now they're sold?
What were you thinking?
I-I had no choice.
He paid way too much.
Even our boss agreed...
Who is it?
Who's the buyer?
The heir of Jinda Group,
Shen Haoming.
What are you waiting for?
Start loading.
Hurry up.
Be careful.
You're causing trouble
in this scorching heat?
Faster.
Be gentle.
Hello?
Let's meet.
Alright.
You did this?
Want a drink?
Shen Haoming,
I've never seen you so agitated before.
But your actions are understandable.
You've finally realized
that the money and connections
you took pride in
mean nothing to her now.
Her career is thriving now.
She doesn't need to rely on you anymore.
Meanwhile,
as her partner,
I've supported her
every step of the way.
Not to mention
that your marital bond is crumbling.
Even if our marital bond is crumbling,
as you assume
without any basis,
we are still married, aren't we?
I'm still
her legal spouse.
This is indisputable, right?
If you're just an ordinary investor,
I'd appreciate your support for her.
But you'd better not approach her
with ulterior motives.
I won't tolerate anyone who wrecks
people's families.
Shen Haoming,
how can you be so confident?
You've long been excluded from her life.
Do you know who she is today?
Do you know her business scale?
What's Yan Studio's production capacity
for major products in the coming year?
What's the product matrix
she aims to build
within three years?
How much profit increase
does she target?
Do you know any of this?
Do you know how much effort
she's poured into
establishing Yan Studio?
Thank you for reminding me.
I'll make sure to
learn all these details.
However,
I think you might have
overestimated your importance.
You just happened to be the investor.
Her success isn't because of you.
Without you,
she could have still
accomplished her goals.
And I will always
stand firmly by her side.
Whenever she needs me,
I'll be there.
Your position is not
so irreplaceable.
Go ahead and try.
Mr. Shen.
Mr. Baraikin has made a request.
Jinda Group must undergo three months
of evaluation
before we sign the contract.
No risks or scandals will be allowed.
Then Mr. Baraikin
will confirm the terms.
Can you find a way
to delay the divorce?
Also,
what should I do about
the film equipment?
Store them in a warehouse.
What a waste of money.
Oh.
Buy some cosmetics.
Cosmetics?
For whom?
Someone.
Okay.
Still no leads on Shen Haoming
and Xu Yan's divorce?
They might still be married.
But my instincts at Yanbo Resort
can't be wrong.
Something is fishy between them.
They feigned harmony
just to secure the deal with Baraikin.
Xu Yan moved out
and started her own business.
Divorced couples naturally drift apart.
But strangely,
Shen Haoming keeps
mentioning her at work.
They're still intimate.
He's even visited her rented apartment.
Back at Yanbo Resort,
they put on quite a show.
They're kind of romantic.
Even if they're in a fight,
Baraikin's three-month inspection
will make Shen Haoming
try every means to keep Xu Yan
from leaving.
I don't care what you do.
Use Fang Lei
or your legal connections,
obtain evidence of their divorce
or marital breakdown in three months.
Remember.
Don't let your godfather down.
If neither approach works,
Yan Studio can also be the target.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
- Sister...
- No. I'm not your sister.
You'll remain my sister-in-law
until I'm divorced.
I stand by my sister.
I won't persuade her
to reconcile with you.
I tried every possible way
to make things right with Yan.
Last month,
we were supposed
to finalize the divorce.
I used every excuse to delay it
and missed the deadline.
That was the first time
I avoided facing reality.
It was also the first time
I was so terrified to solve an issue.
Sister.
I don't want to divorce Yan.
I want to win her back.
Why were you so cold when Yan said
she wanted to make things right?
It was my fault.
I was convinced that
she couldn't live without me.
But after we parted, I realized
that I can't live without her.
I might be her sister,
but I can't tell her what to do.
Figure this out yourself.
Just don't push me away.
By the way,
I met with Dr. Yu some days ago.
Why did you meet him?
Misery loves company.
His current state...
What...
What's wrong?
Stop beating around the bush.
How is he?
He's in terrible shape,
barely eating or drinking,
hiding his weakness,
while obsessing over
how to win back your favor.
I-I never imagined
you would hang out with Yu Yiming.
It's like the bottom two students
helping each other out.
You must be truly desperate.
Given your dedication,
I'll give you one more chance.
Yan's been through so much.
I hope you can support her.
Tell me.
Tomorrow's Saturday.
Yan will be working overtime.
Okay.
Thanks.
Jiang Liang will be there.
Huh?
These are the points I'll address next.
Shen Haoming? Why are you here?
I knew you'd be working late,
so I brought desserts.
Here.
How did you know my schedule?
Look.
There are cookies,
pastries,
and...
I'm in a meeting.
Can I observe?
Of course.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Go on.
My advice is pretty straightforward.
Seek investment.
China has seen
over 44 million new startups
in the past three years.
A new company emerges
every seven seconds.
The one-year survival rate
stands at 20%.
Two years, 4%.
Three years, only 0.8%.
Ms. Xu.
Do you know why
the survival rates are this low?
In my opinion,
they failed to develop
a truly market-approved product
or service.
Of course,
capital shortages,
talent deficits,
market expansion limitations,
and poor management
are also key factors.
Officail Website : dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Exactly.
For every 100 startups,
there are 99 ways to fail.
But the most crucial issue
is undoubtedly funding.
A new brand's cold-start phase
requires 3 million yuan
in one marketing cycle.
The annual marketing expenses
approach 10 million.
To put it bluntly,
if you want fame,
keep the cash flowing.
However,
besides funding,
another critical factor
is product quality.
A strong product
must evolve with market needs
through continuous updates.
For startups like ours,
the process involves
constant refinement
and trial-and-error.
This entire journey requires
massive financial resources.
Without solid funding,
there is no room for error.
As entrepreneurs,
we must prioritize financing
from day one.
Cash flow management
determines survival.
You're right.
Yan Studio has repeatedly
faced such crises.
But now you have me and Yuanhang.
We can do much more than inject funds
to support your expansion.
In the long run,
with our lead investment,
funding will never
hinder your growth ever again.
Money solves talent acquisition,
brand building,
and development challenges.
Mr. Shen, any objections?
You've listed so many benefits,
but ignored all the drawbacks.
What do you mean?
The internet ventures
have seen so many
capital-driven successes.
It's nothing new.
But even if you
depict investors as angels,
they are not charities
nor wishing wells.
They're investing in you,
expecting a return
that's dozens or even hundreds of times
their initial investment.
Mr. Liang.
Just tell me whether you will sign
a valuation adjustment agreement
with Yan Studio.
Even if Yuanhang requires a return,
it'll be based on Yan Studio's
actual operational performance.
I can guarantee
that I'll prioritize Xu Yan
and her co-founders' vision above all
and ensure their autonomy.
You guarantee?
Yeah.
What about the executives?
What about your sister?
Even if your sister agrees,
the company's Articles of Association
won't change.
We know that you remember
every data point
with photographic accuracy.
Recall for yourself.
How many cases follow this pattern?
(Equity valuation bets)
The investors want you to maintain
annual growth rates of 50 percent,
100 percent, or even 200 percent,
which is abnormally high.
Why?
To gain a higher valuation
in capital markets.
Such performance clauses
will force you
to conduct rapid expansion
or make prompt
and short-sighted decisions
that damage your fundamentals.
But what happens
if targets aren't met?
Your company would be acquired.
Years of hard work
could vanish overnight.
Do you think you'd still
have the right to refuse then?
Or do you want to create
a quick-profit brand?
Something marketable to sell
at peak value for fast returns?
That's not our goal.
Yan Studio never intended to become
a rapidly expanding
copycat business model.
Our true purpose is bridging
traditional culture with modern life,
making Neo-Chinese Style
with cultural resonance
accessible to and appreciated
by broader audiences.
We're creating
a distinct cultural style.
I understand
this process may take time,
but it is worth waiting for.
So,
with your clear positioning,
you must maintain control
firmly in your hands.
Be the decision-maker,
not the professional manager
who works for investors.
You're advising Ms. Xu
to avoid deep capital ties.
But where will funding come from?
Presales.
IP Ecology Matrix.
First, presales.
The brand isn't established yet.
So I suggest you focus on online sales.
Generate cash flow via presales
and maintain liquidity.
Remember.
Only financial independence
guarantees that you retain control
over your company.
IP Ecology.
The essence of the internet today
is standardization first,
and then personalization.
If you develop one or two hit products,
you can expand with other SKUs.
You could even create
your own derivative products.
Then the complete
IP ecosystem
keeps growing stronger.
What you'll own is creativity
and design copyrights.
With these assets,
you'll have better leverage
when negotiating with investors
to protect your interests
and maintain control.
Building your own unique IP brand
is the essence and core advantage
of cultural products.
Am I right, Mr. Liang?
I think
there's some validity to your points.
Thank you.
One final suggestion.
Whether it's me,
Ms. Jiang,
or higher-level executives
offering advice,
listen to them
but don't blindly accept them.
Final decisions
must come from your own judgment.
I see.
Good.
Thank you, Mr. Liang and Mr. Shen.
I'll consider your advice.
Thank you.
Let's conclude the meeting here.
Well,
I'll take my leave now.
- Want a ride?
I prefer walking these days.
Mr. Liang.
Please lock up for me.
Okay.
Shen Haoming.
My fingerprint locks the door.
Please leave so I can lock up.
Okay.
Remember this business model.
What nonsense.
Why are you here?
We agreed on a week.
It's already Monday.
Oh.
May I come in?
Have a seat.
Me?
These are for you.
You practice on yourself
for new makeup looks.
But some cosmetics
may damage your skin.
I've done my research.
These are made with safe ingredients.
Your dry skin is prone
to allergies in summer.
This contains hyaluronic acid,
aloe vera,
and ceramides.
It's great for hydration and soothing.
Here.
Your cool undertones
suit pink
and nude lipsticks.
This is 928, Milky Sakura.
This is 302, Nude Bean Paste.
They give a fresh daily look.
This is 396, Strawberry Red.
That's your favorite fruit.
And 564, Clear Peach Glow.
Low saturation, natural flush.
Here.
- And this...
- Okay.
Enough.
Thank you.
But
why did you suddenly decide
to learn about these?
Because you like them.
We'll have more topics
in common like this.
You'll like me more.
Lin.
Have you decided?
I gave you this whole week
to make up your mind.
I've thought it through.
I think all your concerns
are unnecessary.
I've never felt that our degrees
or jobs put us on different levels.
On the contrary,
you came alone from your hometown,
worked diligently from scratch,
never belittled yourself,
and strived to learn more.
I've always
thought that you're shining.
So I'm sure
that I like you.
I want to be with you.
You're not proposing, are you?
What kind of proposal is this?
Can't you do it...
Sorry, did I hurt you?
Let me see.
Anatomically speaking,
it's around the left third, second,
and first rib,
and deeper in.
What?
Where?
The heart.
You scared me.
I thought I actually hurt you.
Annoying.
But it doesn't hurt now.
Because you're in there.
Is this an orthopedic romance?
Did I not express myself?
Lin,
though I'm just a doctor,
I can support you in Jingzhou.
Feel free to do whatever you want.
Decide on
the trial period.
Then,
when do you think...
when do you think
we should start counting from?
ظآزLike fireworks that lovedظآز
ظآزRushing toward the starsظآز
ظآزUndaunted by painظآز
ظآزWe regained freedomظآز
ظآزIf you remember meظآز
ظآزThen I'm pleasedظآز
ظآزLike fireworks that lovedظآز
ظآزRushing toward the starsظآز
ظآزUndaunted by painظآز
ظآزFearless of flamesظآز
ظآزEven if just a fleeting sparkleظآز
ظآزWe shed tearsظآز
ظآزDeep blue seas turn to foamظآز
ظآزWe regained freedomظآز
ظآزIf you remember meظآز
ظآزThen I'm pleasedظآز
ظآزI just wanna take my time tonightظآز
ظآزTo do all the things I said I'd tryظآز
ظآزI go surfing, go diving, go driving,
and go flying to a different placeظآز
ظآزI go drink, go party, and go danceظآز
ظآزEven if I'm lonelyظآز
ظآزCause I just have been hurt
too many timesظآز
ظآزI'm giving it all to get nothing backظآز
ظآزI was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even seeظآز
ظآزSee the world and how it flows.
We never let goظآز
ظآزSo I'll take my timeظآز
ظآزTo reigniteظآز
ظآزThe love I should deserveظآز
ظآزWhen the time is rightظآز
ظآزYou realizeظآز
ظآزIt will all be alrightظآز
ظآزCause I just have been hurt
too many timesظآز
ظآزI'm giving it all to get nothing backظآز
ظآزI was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even seeظآز
ظآزSee the world and how it flows.
We never let goظآز
ظآزSo I'll take my timeظآز
ظآزTo reigniteظآز
ظآزThe love I should deserveظآز
ظآزWhen the time is rightظآز
ظآزYou realizeظآز
ظآزIt will all be alrightظآز