( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
[This drama is fictional and any similarity
with reality is purely coincidental.]
[Production guidelines were followed
when filming children and animals.]
So,
[Episode 3]
let's meet at least three times a week.
What?
Love. Let's give it a try properly.
Are you always this clingy?
What did you say?
I have absolutely no intention
of marrying or dating you.
Not at all.
So,
it seems you've misunderstood me.
I said I'd help you...
So I'm telling you I don't need your help.
- Not even a little?
- Not even a little.
Then what about that night?
Let's just say we both had fun.
Let's be cool about it.
Keep your voice down. People are staring.
Unbelievable.
This is ridiculous.
She doesn't need any help?
'Be cool about it'?
I'll handle it, so just rest.
Is she giving up everything
and just going to Germany like this?
Seriously...
I even turned a blind eye to her
being with another man.
You know what? Fine.
This is for the best anyway.
Let's just go our separate ways.
What? Where'd he go?
Secretary Go.
Sec... huh?
Where'd he go?
He actually said that? The father?
I told you.
He's from a completely different world.
I have to face him at work every day.
He's the president. And I'm just an employee.
Would someone like him suddenly
claim the baby is his? Does that make sense?
Ugh, your stubbornness is unreal.
Would a guy propose marriage
to a woman he doesn't even care about?
Do you think he said that
because he likes me?
Oh my, then why?
Responsibility.
It's obviously out of responsibility.
I never planned on marrying anyway,
leaving that option only raises expectations.
Ms. Hui Won.
Hold on, I'll call you back later.
What brings you here?
I was just passing by.
Have you eaten?
Here are the resume and documents
of Jang Hui Won that you requested.
[Manager Jang Hui Won]
This baby wasn't planned.
At the most crucial moment,
a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
has arrived alongside this new life.
Are you after the money?
Or are you trying to trap a man
to climb the social ladder?
I'll pay today.
Order anything you want.
I asked you out, so I'll pay.
No, you treated me to meat last time.
Actually, I got paid today.
Have you made your choice?
I guess my own life is
still more important to me.
Life has taught me
that a child who could be a blessing to some
can become a burden to others.
You can have a child again
when you are ready.
Again?
What does the father say?
He's not against it?
He doesn't know yet.
It's my decision alone.
Dragging it out only harms the woman's body.
What can men even do?
They can't carry the baby for us.
The food's getting cold.
[Mom]
She came alone and seemed a bit drunk.
I'm sorry.
Get up, I'll take you home.
I can go alone.
Stop being so stubborn.
How bad must it be if you called me?
I've managed just fine on my own.
What are you saying?
Goodbye.
I'll pay for this...
Thank you for your hard work.
Mom!
Why do you keep saying
you'll do everything alone?
What's wrong with you?
You acting like this makes me uncomfortable.
Am I a stranger to you?
If you don't rely on me,
who will you rely on?
That's your problem, Mom.
You never let anyone close,
and it just drives everyone around you crazy.
So,
that's why your dad cheated?
Is that it?
Why are you twisting my words?
You mean that, right?
You're blaming me now, aren't you?
Basically, you're saying
it's all my own fault!
Yeah.
I never even asked for your devotion.
All I wanted was a little praise or a smile.
How can you only think
about yourself until the very end?
If I were you,
I would never live like you, understand?
You should've been on my side.
Even if everyone else turns their backs,
you should have been with me!
You bad girl.
Hui Won, drink this.
She's so selfish.
She can't possibly be that indifferent.
She was like that earlier too.
She doesn't care at all
that her daughter is pregnant.
But what annoys me more is
that I might become like Mom.
I might end up regretting
things just like she said.
You...
Hey, you blockhead!
Why are you worrying about that?
Just because you made the same decision
doesn't mean it'll be the same.
You're not your mom.
Even if you have a baby,
you can live well. So why not?
Just do what you want.
If someone throws stones,
I'll take the blow for you.
If you're having the baby,
I'll help raise it.
So go on the path you truly want. Okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
What will you do now?
You're not actually going
to keep it, are you?
Are you even thinking
about marrying that guy?
No, it's not like that.
Hey, aren't you going home?
Staying here?
Anyway, I'm your secretary.
My boss is pulling that stony face now.
How could I even go home?
What is it?
What's the problem? Tell me.
Have you ever fought with your mom?
If anyone in Korea hasn't fought
with their mom, tell them to step forward.
If there's anyone, I'll applaud them all day.
I got scolded a lot by Mom.
Got punished for talking back,
even beaten with a stick.
Kicked out in freezing winter
wearing just long johns.
No, not that.
I mean fights where you hurt each other.
Don't tell me you fought with your mother?
No, it's not that. I'm just curious.
Fought and hurt each other?
- I have.
- How was it?
It hurt, both me and Mom.
We dug at each other
with sharp words, of course it hurt.
But you know those wounds can heal, right?
Clean the wound,
put a bandage, wait a few days,
and new skin grows back.
So,
that's why what comes after
the wound is important.
What if new skin doesn't grow in days?
Then you wait patiently until it heals.
If you fought with your mom, make up fast.
How old are you now,
still fighting with your mom?
That's not what I...
Anyway, thanks.
Thanks... what? I didn't catch that.
Thanks... what?
Secretary Go, go home now.
You're driving me crazy.
Turn off all the lights when you leave.
I'm really hurt.
I'm hurt!
Oh, please.
[Hui Won]
Hey, how did you...
A thirsty person digs a well.
Though I confess and get rejected,
we can't be friends?
No.
It's not that I didn't try to contact you...
Oh, whatever.
We've kissed. What kind of friends is that?
I want to stay
as someone who can
cross the line with you anytime.
This is making me uncomfortable.
Do you have a girlfriend?
- Or someone you like?
- Huh?
Tell me if you find someone.
So I can try harder.
Hey, Hwang Mi Ran.
This is frustrating.
Why hold back your feelings?
If you overthink, you'll miss good people.
Gonna miss me?
Tell the president to come out!
You gave alcohol to a breastfeeding woman?
Are you insane?
What are you doing?
Call the president here. Get him now!
- Let go!
- You can't do this here.
- Let me go!
- Come out!
I won't just stay still.
- I'll sue!
- Seems like there was chaos this morning
demanding the president come out.
I heard he ramped up beer shipments
and gave them away for free
at postpartum care centers.
Doesn't that smell fishy?
See?
Then and now, he does whatever he wants.
Kang Du Jun, always stirring up trouble,
becomes the president of Taehan Liquor?
It's the Chairman's order.
We'll just have to wait and see.
Whether he arbitrarily increased shipments
or gave things away for free,
none of that matters.
What matters is giving the woman alcohol.
We just need to frame it.
[Han Jeong Eum]
A woman hidden at the care center.
Kang Du Jun's illegitimate child.
Plenty of bait, right?
Readers will judge
based on the articles anyway.
Ahem.
I was already looking for the right timing.
There's no such thing as the 'right timing.'
You make your own timing.
You're good at that, Uncle.
Just like 15 years ago.
But if I get caught by your brother...
I'll help you out.
It seems like it's time to take over
Taehan Group.
Why are you in such a hurry?
If I stay put, the position
will go to Se Hyeon next.
Well,
my life feels too precious
to be satisfied with just that.
I never even asked for your devotion.
All I wanted was a little praise or a smile.
How can you only think
about yourself until the very end?
If I were you,
I would never live like you, understand?
I told you to cut back on the foundation work
and unprofitable ventures.
And what's with the postpartum care center?
And the shelter for single mothers?
It sounds like you think I'm so powerless
to handle even charitable and volunteer work.
Charity itself isn't the issue,
but depending on the organization,
it could easily become scandal fodder.
I've heard Moo Young's been
doing rounds with journalists lately.
Don't worry.
I won't just take it
lying down like last time.
Good.
No issues with your sister-in-law lately?
Why do you ask?
After what happened to your brother,
I wondered if she still holds a grudge.
Ah, enough about that.
Your mother seems to be
stirring up something again?
Mother?
Madam.
Here are the materials
from Grace in Cheongdam.
As requested, they've selected
well-regarded candidates
from prominent families.
Oh, really?
Let me see.
Politician's child,
hospital director's daughter...
Their faces...
I only need one thing, character!
What? Mr. Lee? Has that punk lost his mind?
Tell him to get out.
Show him what happens
when he stabs me in the back.
Jeez.
If my second daughter-in-law is like her,
I won't live out my days peacefully.
Where is the gentle, polite woman
who can comfort our Du Jun?
What, you have something to say?
Vice Chairman Kang Moo Young
is famously two-faced.
I was wondering if working with him is okay.
Have you ever grown plants?
Pardon?
You know about pruning
when growing plants, right?
Ah, yes.
You don't just cut off the dead branches.
You also cut healthy ones.
Why do you think that is?
Because they steal too many nutrients?
At first, they're needed
to grow together vigorously,
but no matter how strong,
if they steal too many nutrients,
they just become obstacles.
That's when you prune them.
I've already calculated
the timing for the cuts.
Since it's our first ale beer in a long time,
let's lower the IBU level more to balance
the bitterness as much as possible.
Yes, understood.
And for the marketing plan,
let's also target new channels
like trendy bars or emotional pubs.
Yes, I'll review it according to
your direction and get back to you.
President.
We've got a serious problem.
[100% Aroma Hops]
[Premium Ale Beer]
Less bitter, more substantial.
Premium Ale Beer made with 100% Aroma Hops!
[Draft Beer Wave]
Wave Beer!
100% Aroma Hops and Premium Ale Beer.
This is way too similar, isn't it?
Did you properly conduct the market research?
Yes, of course.
We've been closely tracking competitors
and ensuring strict confidentiality
from before planning
the new product up to its launch.
So is there any chance the idea was leaked?
That's absurd, sir.
Actually, it's not entirely impossible.
They released it way earlier than we did.
There's no way they plagiarized us.
This isn't about assigning blame.
We need to verify the facts.
Who's in charge of this?
Come to think of it, the manager for this
is the one chosen for Germany, right?
Is it Manager Jang Hui Won?
Before the Germany results were announced,
if launching this new product
was counted as bonus points,
wouldn't that make the plagiarism claim
highly plausible?
Now...
That's ridiculous.
How could both the concept
and recipe overlap by coincidence?
We've been working overtime
for months on this launch.
Even if I copied it, I'd surely
get caught, so why would I do it?
- Why would I?
- Bonus points.
- Bonus points?
- Really?
- No...
- No way.
You wanted to study in Germany, right?
Didn't you plagiarize for bonus points?
Team Leader.
Rumors are spreading that
the scores from this new product
are included in your
Germany study application.
Did you think you could just
wrap it up and dash off to Germany?
Well, Team Leader.
You're being too harsh.
True, no matter how much she wanted Germany,
I doubt the manager would go that far.
Why not?
Hearing it now, I think it's possible.
Why are you siding against her too,
Assistant Manager?
Think carefully, all of you.
Because of her, our whole team
is about to take the fall.
Because of you, our whole team
is going to be investigated, okay?
Ah, I shouldn't have asked.
She's not getting punished
on my account, right?
- Jeez.
- Oh, my.
- You scared me!
- You startled me.
What is it?
Where are you heading?
No, nowhere.
Then what brings you here, Ms. Jang Hui Won?
I came to see you, President.
Then come on in.
Sit.
Do you need any help from me?
No.
I didn't copy it.
Are you here to explain yourself now?
Explanations won't help now.
We need to manage the situation.
Then,
I'll take responsibility.
Responsibility? How?
I'll resolve this quickly.
But please just punish me alone.
Our team did nothing wrong.
Ms. Jang Hui Won.
Who do you think you are?
Since you handle everything alone,
you can clean up this mess alone too?
- That's not what I...
- Since we're short on time,
report to me in real-time as soon as
the new concept comes out.
Bring it over as soon as it's ready.
In person?
Why? Don't trust yourself?
Yes, I'll do it.
What on earth is happening?
Exactly. Everyone knows
Manager Jang is competent.
Only Manager Jang knows the truth.
Still, plagiarism is out of the question.
You've all seen her working alongside us.
Anyway, let's wait here
awhile before going in.
Sit down, sit down.
Isn't it just that you want to take a break?
I feel like the team leader
will scold us if she sees us.
It's okay. The atmosphere is
tense enough already.
Huh? Team Leader?
Where?
Sorry, my mistake.
I didn't stand up
because you said 'team leader'.
- Me neither.
- A colleague
is in trouble.
I can't just sit here comfortably!
- Let's get back to work quickly!
- Go!
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Are you done already?
This is a recipe our team
succeeded with in another project,
and it should work well with this ale beer.
- Not impressive.
- Pardon?
Try again.
I have something urgent to attend to.
President, wait a moment.
What is it?
Well...
I'm sorry for trying to grab you
- all of a sudden...
- Focus on doing it right, not fast.
But why the serious face over this?
Wow, the food at the cafeteria was excellent.
The balance of carbs, protein,
and fat was absolutely perfect.
Can you even eat in this situation?
I haven't even eaten yet.
Actually, the more critical the situation,
the more you need to eat properly.
By the way, Manager Jang must be
busy fixing this. I wonder if she's eaten.
Should I get her something to eat?
Why are you worrying about Manager Jang?
Am I not allowed to worry?
She's struggling
to handle it alone right now...
You should worry about me like that.
- Aren't you my secretary?
- Wow.
What? You really think that?
You are not even a child.
Little Kang Du Jun, so what
should I prepare for lunch?
Like sausages with ketchup in a heart shape?
I'm not in a good mood,
so go and get back to work.
Oh, right.
Find something light to eat, like a sandwich.
Yes, yes, little Kang Du Jun.
Ah, and.
Pay attention to the wrap too.
Make it special.
Don't do it half-heartedly.
I'll put a heart on the wrapping paper
for you, little Kang Du Jun.
- Don't overdo it.
- Yes.
What proof do they have that you copied it?
Why are you taking all the blame?
It's too identical to be a coincidence.
And it's not a small amount of money.
So I just said I'd handle it.
You said that recipe didn't exist
when you first developed it.
That's right.
I feel wronged too,
but what's the point of arguing?
I have to start reporting
in real time from today.
So, speaking of which,
what are you doing today?
Busy?
That's a very familiar look.
Anyway, she never asks
for help until the end.
Is she skipping meals while working?
Just once, okay? Just this once.
You only come to me
when you need help, don't you?
Who else would I ask
for a favor like this besides you?
You'll help, right? Huh?
I don't know.
Ugh, seriously. I have so much
to do today, Jang Hui Won.
Fine, how could I ever win against you?
Yes!
Your Highness.
What would you like to eat?
Ah, let's go with meat today.
I shall prepare the meat, Your Highness.
Oh, that's refreshing.
Again.
Let's have a cup of coffee.
Ah, yes.
Manager, coffee...
Maybe we should just go ourselves.
[Project Overview, Development Background]
Again.
Kang Du Jun.
You're so annoying!
President, wait a moment.
Heave ho!
Here.
You selfish brat.
Why are you picking a fight all of a sudden?
Either be nice or be mean. Just pick one.
- What did I do?
- Don't tell me
you're not getting back at Hui Won
for rejecting you before.
She said she'd handle it herself.
She said she doesn't need my help at all.
Do you think she really meant that?
I heard Hui Won has been
working weekends all this time.
Now that a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity is right in front of her.
And on top of that, she's pregnant.
Plus, she's been unfairly accused.
How do you think she feels now?
[Drinks Menu]
Jeez.
Jang Hui Won isn't answering her phone.
Is she that busy?
President?
She can't drink coffee anyway.
Is tea okay?
[Tea]
What kind of tea is good for pregnant women?
Ah, I'm not really sure.
Ah, yes.
[Good Tea for Pregnant Women]
[Tea]
Rooibos.
A warm cup of rooibos tea, please.
Yes.
Ah, since it's hot, please add two ice cubes.
[Si Hyeong]
Yes, Si Hyeong.
Hello.
One lemon tea, please.
With lots of ice.
Yes.
Thank you.
[Jang Hui Won]
Enjoy your meal.
Is Assistant Manager Choi treating?
I heard you had a blind date yesterday,
and it seems like it went well.
Yeah, I messed up the blind date badly,
so I bought this to fill the void, okay?
Ugh, looks like you lost your temper again.
No, I mean I'd enjoy it.
Eat it before it gets cold.
Alright! Let's dig in!
Wait, isn't Manager Jang coming?
She's crazy about tteokbokki.
Ah, she said she has
a lot on her plate today.
Is it because of that recipe incident?
- Assistant Manager Choi...
- Even lunch earlier,
she just had a sandwich.
Ah, why live so rigidly?
We're all just trying to get by.
Back in my day,
if the senior skipped a meal,
the juniors did so too.
A camaraderie forged
through hunger, you could say.
I offered to bring her some,
but she said it might upset her stomach.
If you do that nowadays,
you get reported for workplace harassment.
It's not like we're living in the Stone Age.
No, I'm saying I did that back in the day.
I'm not telling Ms. Se Hyeon to starve.
See what happens when you
don't manage your stuff properly?
Managing things is also a skill
and a measure of competence.
Honestly, at our company, who works
as hard and is as successful as Manager Jang?
You couldn't find one
even if you looked hard, right?
Even within our team,
I think she works the most.
- Right?
- It's delicious.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Stop and eat. It's good.
- Right?
Suddenly lost my appetite completely.
Then I'll go
and work much harder.
I need to do a ton more work.
Team Leader, you should eat a bit too.
Hey...
You said back in your day if the senior
starved, you all starved together.
The past is the past. Don't you know?
We need to move forward towards the future.
The future leading Taehan Liquor.
Phew.
Ms. Se Hyeon, eat a lot. My share too.
Just stop it!
Oh, seriously.
Uh, well then, I'll be off.
What if we try changing the final hop?
[Project Document]
Until now,
we've relied solely on
imported aroma hops for brewing our beer.
If you look here,
in Hongcheon,
there's a domestic hop producer...
Let's call it a day.
It feels like you're just skimming
the surface in the same way.
Why? What on earth is the reason?
Explain to me, even briefly,
what's wrong and how.
The reason...
Then shall we start
with the first concept you proposed?
Do you know why Taehan Liquor
abandoned ale production ten years ago?
Because sales didn't meet expectations.
Yes, exactly. We failed to achieve
the expected results.
So we boldly cut our losses
and decided to invest in what we do better.
But now, after ten years,
when we're barely meeting expectations
with a fresh concept for this ale challenge,
do you really think recycling a recipe
used elsewhere will work?
- That's...
- The second concept.
Despite ale's strengths,
emphasizing lager's refreshment
doesn't seem to suit
the top-fermentation method.
- Third...
- I get it.
So you're saying there were
reasons behind everything.
From the start, Manager Jang,
your approach was wrong.
Just because you're the manager in charge,
you think you alone can solve
this huge project's problems?
Don't you think that approach is reckless
and irresponsible from the get-go?
Since it's come up,
why sacrifice your health
and stake your life on results?
You've already received ample incentives,
and your study program
in Germany is confirmed.
- Why are you bringing that up...
- The company clearly has
a hierarchy and system.
But why didn't you ask me for help?
Pardon?
Why didn't you ask me for help!
Don't laugh.
So all of this was just to get her attention.
- It's not!
- It is!
I said no! You weird-looking guy.
Why do I look weird?
Don't laugh.
Yes.
Did you find something?
Focus on doing it right, not fast.
Can the Audit Team access
employees' internal messenger logs?
No, just one person.
I only need to check one person's.
About the materials you requested
over the phone last time.
It's still just suspicion, so I wasn't sure
whether to tell you.
Here...
Uh, wait a minute, here.
Let me talk to Team Leader Baek.
Will he actually keep his promises?
It's a bit hard to do it immediately,
but he said he'd call after some time.
Let's discuss the details over the phone.
Is there any Team Leader Baek in our company?
Hello.
Oh, welcome.
What would you like to have?
- What should we eat?
- What?
Has he been sulking
about that this whole time?
I don't know. Honestly, I just don't get it.
I mean, even so, making a pregnant woman
go through that is harsh.
But his reasons were all valid though.
Can't the manager solve
some things on their own?
I just don't want to inconvenience
the team since it's my responsibility.
That's why I did it.
I know. I know very well.
Don't stress yourself out
over that for no reason.
It's not good for the baby.
Breathe. Breathe.
Yeah, breathe.
What is it?
So you're off work now?
What, did you come to apologize?
Or did you come to hear an apology?
After thinking about it,
it wasn't completely unreasonable.
Switching the aroma hops
to domestically grown hops.
It might actually be the best solution
for our current situation...
Did you come all the way
here just to say that?
No, actually, the audit team...
It's fine. You don't need to sugarcoat it.
It's true that my proposal wasn't great.
No, that's not really it...
I admit it.
I was desperate and only
thinking about fixing things.
I ignored responsibility and hierarchy,
and took it all upon myself.
But,
the choices I made
might seem irresponsible to you, President,
but they were choices
made for specific reasons.
They weren't decisions I made lightly at all.
So...
I mean...
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
It's...
- My belly...
- Belly?
- What's wrong with it? Huh?
- Ow!
The baby...
Nothing's wrong with the baby, right?
That shouldn't be the case,
so relax and get examined.
I'll handle things here, so don't worry.
Excuse me.
Guardian for Jang Hui Won?
Yes.
Please fill out this form.
It seems the mother has been
under a lot of stress.
The risk of miscarriage is high
in early pregnancy, so be extra careful.
Are you here to explain yourself now?
Explanations won't help now.
We need to manage the situation.
Just because you're the manager in charge,
you think you alone can solve
this huge project's problems?
Don't you think that approach is reckless
and irresponsible from the get-go?
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
[Min Uk]
Yeah, what happened? Did everything go well?
Hello?
Isn't this Jang Hui Won's phone?
- Who are you?
- And who are you?
- Are you that male friend?
- Do you know me?
I'm the person responsible for Jang Hui Won.
Ah, yes.
Since Hui Won's next to you,
can I talk to her?
- It's work.
- Hui Won is sleeping right now.
It's barely 8 PM.
Isn't it rude to call a friend
with a boyfriend at 8 o'clock at night?
No matter how tired she is,
she doesn't sleep at 8 PM.
Why are you interfering
with her sleeping schedule?
What?
No, what I meant was...
From now on, please refrain
from calling Ms. Jang Hui Won
for personal matters after 7 PM.
And if you have business,
text instead of calling.
If there's nothing else, I'll hang up.
- That's not it, hello?
- What are you doing there?
You're awake.
How are you feeling?
How's the baby?
Ah, well...
As you can see, it's now
about the size of a gummy bear.
This is the yolk sac.
And over here is the head.
- See it?
- Yes.
Shall we listen to the heartbeat?
The ultrasound shows it's healthy,
but because of the stomach cramps
and spotting this time,
I'll give you a shot to prevent miscarriage.
Please get absolute rest
for the next few days.
Okay.
I'm sure I've heard that voice somewhere.
Cha Min Uk? What brings you here?
Coming all this way to find me?
I have something to ask you.
Tsk, what is it?
The baby's father, how did he look
at the OB-GYN?
Do you happen to know what he does?
- One tteokbokki here, please.
- Rolled omelet.
One rolled omelet too, please.
Got it. I'll make it delicious.
- Yes.
Hold on.
You absolutely cannot tell Min Uk
that the father is the president
of our company, got it?
I know, but...
Won't he feel worse if he finds out later?
Don't you remember?
Back in college,
Min Ji and Jae Hyun got caught
dating in the club room.
They begged the three of us
to keep it secret.
But Cha Min Uk couldn't control
his expression and was fidgeting.
Then the whole school found out in a week.
Not a week, three days.
Right, right!
That legendary incident.
He's completely transparent.
You can read everything on his face.
Okay, got it. I'll keep it secret.
Promise.
- Promise.
- Wow, unbelievable!
Why? What is it?
Jae Hyun and Min Ji are getting married.
Did you guys know? They got back together?
- Yeah.
And they're getting married just
three months after getting back together?
Yeah.
How come I didn't know?
Why didn't anyone tell me?
- I'm good at keeping secrets.
- Yeah.
I know.
Well, I called Hui Won,
and that guy just answered,
said his piece, and hung up.
Was it the same that day?
Rude and inconsiderate?
Well, I only saw him briefly,
so I don't clearly remember...
Ugh, seriously, where did she
even meet a guy like that?
By the way, you came all the way here
just to ask that?
Do you like Hui Won or something?
- Me?
- I mean,
it's unlike you to suddenly
come over and interrogate me,
and that you care whether he's a good guy.
Hey, you!
I've known her for ages.
You know how she is. Is there anything
she does properly besides work?
Well, that's true.
But you came all the way here to ask that?
I could have gone for the check-up alone.
Hold on.
Yes?
What?
Sorry, but is that...
Huh?
No, I thought you were pregnant.
Ah.
This is non-alcoholic.
Oh.
I actually get scolded by the elders here
a lot because of this.
No matter how much I explain
it's just a drink, non-alcoholic, no less,
the elders only believe
what they see and know.
Right, it's understandable
they'd misunderstand.
I try not to drink it much at the hospital.
But lately, without even this,
I'd have no joy at all.
My husband shows up dead drunk every night,
whether I'm in the hospital or not.
There are so many days I just
want to get completely drunk myself.
A friend who got into the postpartum
care center before me snuck this in.
Was it Taehan Liquor?
I heard their president has been giving
ten boxes of this non-alcoholic beer
to every postpartum care center lately.
The president?
Yes, he said it's a gift for mothers
who've endured so much
while carrying a child for ten months.
Reporter Park,
while you've been hushing up
the secret supplies to company sports events,
soccer clubs, even a certain
politician's alumni association...
Ugh, you idiot.
Aren't mothers the ones
who really need a change of mood?
Honey, I think the baby's coming.
Honey, will it take long?
Can I quickly grab a bite right here?
- What?
- I'll be super quick.
I'm just so hungry.
Jeez.
It's not about doing it for women.
It's about helping mothers.
When the mother is at ease,
the baby will be comfortable too.
Mothers are humans too.
Thank you for today.
I've already spoken to Team Leader Bang.
Don't come to work
for a few days and rest well.
Recovering your condition is
the most important thing right now.
What? But it's the busiest time right now...
I'm not just saying it.
About your idea of domestic hops,
we're planning to develop
a new product based on that concept.
Really?
I've already marked a few viable items
from the ideas you submitted.
We can start developing them
once you're back.
And since we're on the topic,
Ms. Jang Hui Won, about your dream,
that study program in Germany
isn't your ultimate goal, is it?
That's when I made up my mind.
I've decided that I must
study in Germany next.
I've decided to create my own beer
that will captivate foreigners' taste buds.
That's my dream.
Launching your own original brand.
Isn't that your ultimate goal?
That's right, but...
Then do you really need to go far away?
Why not take on the challenge right here?
That dream. I'll help make it possible.
President.
I'll respect whatever choice you make,
but you shouldn't have regrets
about whichever path you take.
I'm sorry.
Thinking back,
I was only pushing my own position.
Mom!
Ugh, what now?
Mom, if you keep that up,
I'll play conservative around you,
then go all out the second I step outside.
I can't stand Gen Z.
Tsk.
They say the internal performance evaluation
will include individual presentations
and project participation rates.
Just step up saying you'd do everything,
without skipping anything.
That's exactly your problem, Mom.
It's like teaching bike riding
to a kid who just learned to walk.
You said you hate parachuting no matter what.
Then you have to stand out
through your own efforts.
Mom, I'm still an intern.
And for management issues,
there's Uncle, so... whatever.
Taehan Liquor is yours.
You need to think of yourself as the owner.
It's not that I don't have ambition.
I just want to rise based on my own skills.
- And what if your chance never comes?
- Huh?
Your uncle has a woman, and a kid too.
Do you even talk to Uncle
about things like that?
What if they end up getting married?
Forget it.
Do you know how they met?
I don't know that much.
I wouldn't have known either if I hadn't seen
them at the OB-GYN.
OB-GYN?
But they seemed like strangers back then...
What are you talking about?
Huh?
Nothing, it's nothing.
Aren't you hungry, Mom?
Why do I suddenly feel peckish?
What do you want to have?
I'm feeling a bit peckish.
You caught the culprit?
Ah, Manager Jang, you weren't
here that day, so you missed it.
It was utter chaos since the morning.
You know Team Leader Shin
from Marketing Team?
We are the Audit Team.
Yes, what's the matter?
What are you waiting for? Pack his things.
Was he not happy with this year's
salary negotiation?
Looks like he was even lining up another job.
You know Director Park from Sales
who jumped ship
to a competitor about a month ago?
He teamed up
with that Team Leader Baek on their side,
and set up the meeting in exchange
for selling off our new product information.
The competitor thought the idea
was solid and rushed it forward.
But President Kang caught onto it.
- How?
- During the team leader meeting,
he overheard Team Leader Shin
making a call as soon as he stepped out.
He heard something like, 'Make sure
you clean it up if the leak gets exposed.'
That sparked his suspicion,
and he got Audit Team to gather evidence.
Did you think you wouldn't get caught?
Or did you think even if caught,
you'd make a hefty profit anyway?
President Kang, that's...
I don't need excuses.
Just take responsibility.
You were expecting criminal punishment
when you did this, right?
Um, President...
I've committed an unforgivable sin.
Team Leader Shin, you seem to be quite lucky.
Because I happen to have a lot of time today.
Let's go over exactly
how much damage the company took
because of the new product leak.
President.
Anyway, it's still not over,
but it seems to have worked out.
I see.
That's a relief.
Also, President Kang said once Manager Jang
comes back, we'd have a team dinner.
Not this, though.
He gave this monetary gift.
President Kang did?
Isn't it his way of acknowledging
how you struggled alone to save the team?
He acts cold, but he's
actually soft underneath.
- Totally.
- Just like me.
[Beer Recipe]
Okay.
[Study in Germany. This time,
I'm going. No matter what!]
[Beer Recipe]
Team Leader!
Huh?
I won't be going to Germany.
I'm giving up on the study program.
What?
As mentioned earlier, Team Leader Shin
will be dismissed as soon as possible.
And we'll handle the legal work properly,
with our in-house lawyer involved.
President Kang Du Jun.
I said we'd follow the procedures.
Yes, keep me updated
as the lawsuit progresses.
Is that all for today's schedule?
Yeah, heading straight home?
I guess so.
Wait, no.
Come to think of it,
I set up the dinner gathering.
Wouldn't they feel disappointed if I skip it?
Don't tell me you're going to
the New Product Development Team's dinner?
I was thinking about it.
They might be eagerly waiting for me.
Do you know who the coolest person
at a company dinner is?
The president who just pays
and doesn't attend.
No.
Making an appearance
is basic presidential etiquette.
Let's go.
I said it's not etiquette!
Nobody's waiting for you.
- Try!
But why would she give up?
That's the mystery.
Maybe she's sick?
Is it because people think she got
bonus points to study abroad?
So why did you take
Team Leader Bang's side back then?
Oh, Manager Jang.
Assistant Manager Choi wants to treat you
to a drink to clear up the misunderstanding.
Oh, Manager Jang.
My apol...
You'll accept my apology, right?
No, I'd love to drink too,
but I'm on herbal medicine these days.
My peace offering drink.
See? She's not accepting it.
No, that's not what I meant.
Oh, Assistant Manager Choi, good work today.
But we're really curious,
why did you suddenly
decide not to go to Germany?
Isn't this what all the fuss is about?
I realized there's something
I need to stay and handle.
I can achieve my dreams here too.
Why dig into someone who's not going?
Since we're gathered because of you,
down a drink to kick things off.
- Me?
- Why?
You're refusing a drink
from your team leader?
I'll drink it for her. Give it to me.
Hey, since when does an intern get so bold?
Manager Jang, my arm's getting tired.
Drink! Drink! Drink! Drink!
Down it! Chug, chug, chug, chug.
How long will you keep us waiting?
Pretend to take the glass
and accidentally spill it?
Or pretending to drink
and then throwing up right away?
Ah, this is driving me crazy.
Does this forced-drinking culture
still exist nowadays?
Oh my!
Wow, our president is amazing.
Is the star of the night leaving already?
Are you drunk?
No.
Just pleasantly buzzed?
Drink with me.
I have to drive,
so it's just water.
Oh.
That's okay, I'll stop now.
Why?
I don't want to get drunk.
And I don't want to look stupid
in front of juniors.
Then,
only get drunk in front of me.
I can't do that.
I hate
how I act when I'm drunk.
Why?
People say I start acting cute
when I'm drunk.
You are cute.
It's not acting, because you just are.
You seemed to drink pretty well today.
Why? Do I seem different to you?
Ugh, I can't even say anything.
I drank a bit because of the two of you.
The two of us?
The baby and I are already a package deal.
Why? Does that bother you?
Forget it, seriously.
Thank you.
I heard you caught the real culprit for me.
Even when I went to the hospital before,
I didn't say it, but I felt supported.
When you said you'd help me achieve my dream,
and that you'd respect any choice I make...
So here's the thing.
I'm going to keep this baby.
This doesn't mean
I'm marrying you or anything,
so don't misunderstand.
Then what about taking it slow?
Is that not possible either?
- Pardon?
- Since you've decided to keep it,
I don't want to stop here.
There she is!
- Get her!
- Get her.
We have to catch her!
- Where do you think you're running to?
- Don't you leave right now.
We have to go to the second round!
Let's all go together!
Boss, come with us!
Second round! Karaoke!
Our second round is karaoke.
Karaoke!
- Ah, I'll should go.
- Karaoke.
Karaoke!
Karao...
Why don't you tell the company
and take some rest?
Whether I finish it or hand it over,
I want to decide my own ending.
A field trip? Just the two of them?
Wouldn't it hurt more if someone
you trusted betrayed you?
Could there be some story she can't tell us?
That makes sense. She's been
acting suspicious lately.
Do you want to go to the hospital?
I'll go with you.
If anyone sees, they'll misunderstand.
While you're thinking about this,
where is he, and what is he doing?
Maybe it's better not to start at all.
I've never thought of it that way.
Do you think I'm playing games with you?