♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 30=
Your Majesty is merciful
and forgives their deception.
Yet General Fengyun,
as military commander,
deceived us all
for personal reasons.
It may
disappoint the troops.
Your Majesty.
That makes sense.
Moreover,
Attendant Wu'an is a woman.
Her presence in military camps
is inappropriate.
If soldiers start
following this example
and hide women in camp,
military order will be ruined.
Your Majesty.
Though I have personal motives,
I'm not keeping a lover.
I know He Yan's capabilities.
After deliberation,
I enlisted her in the army.
She stayed in Yezhou Garrison
after rigorous evaluations.
Her current achievements
are evident to all.
As Commander of Yezhou Garrison,
whether she passed tests
or earned military merits
was all under your authority.
Miss Xu.
Before His Majesty,
mind your manners.
Attendant Wu'an
fought against Rida Muzi of Liehe tribe
and killed Wutuo's general Huyate.
She also helped lift the siege of Rundu.
These accomplishments
were witnessed by all.
It can't be fabricated.
Your Majesty.
Miss Xu was wrong.
I passed my evaluations
and earned
my military merits publicly
in real combat.
My comrades in Yezhou Garrison
and buddies in Rundu
can all vouch for me.
Regarding the military order mentioned
by Chancellor Xu...
Your Majesty,
though I'm a woman,
I have aspirations to protect our nation
and serve Your Majesty.
Fortunately, I possess some skills
and opportunities to fulfill my wish.
Your Majesty.
I firmly believe
that one's virtue and capability
shouldn't be judged
by gender.
Women
with genuine talent
deserve opportunities
to serve Wei.
Your Majesty.
Soldiers follow rules.
So do women.
Attendant Wu'an eloped with a man.
It's inappropriate
and damages social morals.
She is virtueless.
No matter how capable she is,
she doesn't deserve
to serve in the army.
Mr. Wei is mistaken.
Your Majesty.
I
never eloped with He Yan.
I respect her,
value her,
and won't let anyone
slander her.
She graces my view,
occupies my mind,
and claims my heart.
Well said. "My view, my mind,
and my heart."
I can't believe a straight man
like you
can be so affectionate.
Empress.
You are
a paragon of virtue for all women.
What's your judgment
of Attendant Wu'an's virtue?
Common soldiers are plentiful,
but good generals are rare.
Attendant Wu'an serves Wei
and defends our territory.
She's loyal to the nation.
If we constrain her
with conventional rules
for women,
our nation will
lose a brilliant soldier.
Thus, I believe
Attendant Wu'an
has committed no offense.
On the contrary, she is meritorious.
That makes sense.
The Empress is from a military family.
When I led the expedition years ago,
she not only accompanied me,
but also fought alongside me
on the battlefield.
Attendant Wu'an
follows the Empress's example
by serving in the army.
That's a good thing for Wei.
Attendant Wu'an.
I think
you deserve to
be promoted.
Therefore,
I'll bestow upon you a marquis title.
Starting today,
you are
Marquis Wu'an.
Thank you so much, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty is wise.
- Your Majesty is wise.
Who would have thought
Attendant Wu'an was a woman?
She's now Marquis Wu'an.
I never expected
that General Feihong
would lose to a woman.
It was humiliating.
General.
I lost because of my existing injuries
that gave her the advantage.
Of course.
Let's go.
Commander.
Did I embarrass you today?
Absolutely not.
You are...
I am
your view,
your mind,
and your heart.
Why are you here?
Why aren't you
chasing after He Yan?
Pingting.
Don't be mad.
Don't try to fool me.
I saw it clearly.
Chu Zhao,
since you're with me,
you can't
like other women.
I'm very possessive towards you.
I'll never permit my husband
to keep concubines.
You misunderstand me.
I've long suspected
He Yan's gender.
I planned to figure it out
and then impeach Xiao Jue.
Really?
Of course.
Then why
didn't you speak for me?
Instead, you defended her!
Pingting.
As an official,
openly speaking for you
would make it worse.
His Majesty would grow suspicious,
suspecting my motives
and even Chancellor Xu.
He might think the Chancellor sent you
to deliberately target Xiao Jue
and He Yan
to eliminate rivals.
I see.
I made a mistake
and ruined your plan.
You haven't ruined anything.
I should thank you.
Thank heavens
you exposed it publicly.
Had I blindly reported it
to His Majesty,
I'd be facing punishment now.
By the way,
how did you
discover Attendant Wu'an
is a woman?
Come on.
Because I
saw the painting in your study.
You won't blame me, right?
How could I blame you?
But based on a painting,
you accused He Yan
before His Majesty.
That was risky.
If Attendant Wu'an were a man,
wouldn't you
face punishment?
Don't worry.
I did that with complete certainty.
Fine. I'll tell you.
He Rufei told me
that He Yan is a woman.
So your plan
was to challenge He Rufei
publicly?
Exactly.
The valiant General Feihong
couldn't even defeat
a novice like Attendant Wu'an.
The competition
not only humiliated He Rufei,
but also made His Majesty and officials
grow suspicious.
But today,
it was truly perilous.
Huaijin,
thank you
for telling His Majesty earlier
that I am a woman.
Otherwise,
I'd be in trouble.
Xu Pingting
only met you once,
yet she was certain in court
that you're a woman.
Someone must be behind this.
Who else could it be
besides He Rufei?
But I heard Xu Jingfu
dotes on Xu Pingting, his only daughter.
He actually
used Xu Pingting.
He's in big trouble.
Chancellor.
This was all premeditated.
She wanted to humiliate me
in public.
This is revenge!
Chancellor.
We can't just...
Can't what?
He Rufei,
my daughter Pingting
never pays attention to state affairs.
How did she know
He Yan is female?
You used her.
How dare you!
Forgive me, Chancellor.
I made a mistake.
I only wanted His Majesty
to punish them for deception,
ruining His Majesty's trust.
Then,
we'll be safe.
Why didn't you
expose He Yan yourself?
I've told you.
We should make our decisions together.
Seems I'm too old
and I've lost my authority.
Since you have your own plans,
why should I work with you?
Chancellor.
I made a mistake.
Forgive me, Chancellor.
Don't abandon me.
Should I help you?
I told you to wait,
yet you stirred up things.
Now the entire court knows
she's a woman.
How could they not suspect?
With endless rumors,
if His Majesty
orders an investigation,
could your family
be tough enough
to endure an interrogation?
He Rufei.
It's not that I'm abandoning you.
The point is you're hopelessly foolish!
Yes.
None of my family
has any backbone.
We won't withstand the interrogation.
Chancellor Xu.
In desperate circumstances,
I'll choose to die together.
If I suffer,
you, the mastermind behind treason,
will suffer too.
Do you think
anyone would believe a disloyal man
like you?
Verbal claims mean nothing.
But what if I reveal
your correspondence with Wutuo?
You actually deceived me
and didn't burn those letters!
Chancellor,
I know my abilities are limited,
and I am not
as ruthless as you.
Therefore,
I have to keep something
to protect myself.
Fine.
Young people always make mistakes.
He Rufei.
Pingting
is my only daughter.
If you use her
again,
I'll show no mercy.
I'll never
let it happen again.
With current tensions high,
you must stay composed.
I need time
to think about the remaining matters.
Once I devise a plan,
I'll let you know.
Yes.
As you command.
Anyway,
thank you.
He Yan.
From now on,
I will
deal with all your worries with you
and trust you
completely.
Okay.
It's a deal.
A high five?
Anyone watching might think
we'd become sworn siblings.
I didn't mean that.
Xiao Jue.
I've liked you for a long time.
Now,
I like you even more.
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
Yan.
When we heard news from the palace,
we were terrified.
We knew you were amazing,
but never imagined
that even General Feihong
wasn't your match.
Of course.
I'm the top one of Yezhou Garrison.
By the way, Miss Song,
Mrs. Xiao mentioned
that you just returned today
and came here without going home.
It's the Mid-Autumn Festival.
You should celebrate with family.
Are you facing difficulties?
Yan.
As you know,
we ran away to avoid marriage.
If we return home,
how will we explain to our parents?
Back then, you and Mr. Cheng decided
to cancel your engagement.
Now, it seems
you're getting married.
Who knows what he's thinking?
He's usually so eloquent,
but he avoids talking about marriage.
He might as well
marry his medical books
for all I care!
Enough of that.
He's ruining our mood.
Yan,
when will you
and Commander Xiao get married?
Preparations should start.
Six wedding rituals
must be observed.
Don't let Miss He be slighted.
Mrs. Xiao.
We
haven't decided to get married yet.
It's too early to prepare.
It's not too early.
There's so much to prepare.
I think we're pressed for time.
I never expected
that the accomplished Marquis Wu'an
would be a woman.
This Huaijin.
I know it's serious business,
but he should've at least
told us
about the girl he likes.
This is all I could prepare in time.
Later, we'll go to shops
to buy more stuff you prefer.
These are
all women's garments.
Taotao told me everything about you.
You've suffered a lot
to become what you are.
But after suffering
comes happiness.
Now,
as the marquis appointed by His Majesty,
you needn't wear men's clothes.
Time to wear women's clothes.
Exactly!
We'll show everyone
how brilliant you are
as Marquis Wu'an.
This will
make all women proud.
Brother.
Why are you
joining them?
You kept such a huge secret,
yet I'm the one being scolded?
You brought that girl to your courtyard
upon entering the city.
You could be careless before,
but continuing like this
would show disrespect to Miss He.
Commander Xiao,
if you treat Yan poorly,
though I can't fight you,
I can poison you.
The court banquet is formal.
Let's relax and have
a Mid-Autumn dinner.
Under the full moon,
let's celebrate with liquor.
He Yan.
Even carefree souls
become restrained
before their beloved.
Really?
Why do I feel
you were quite bold back then?
You never knew
how nervous I was.
Are you nervous now?
You'll know later.
(Chu Mansion)
You don't have to watch lanterns
with Miss Xu.
Just make an excuse to decline.
Given Pingting's temperament,
if I don't say yes,
she'll make a scene.
The time isn't right yet
to break with Chancellor Xu.
He Rufei actually dared
to use Xu Pingting.
He will definitely
rile Chancellor Xu.
He won't have a good end.
Finally, she no longer needs
to hide her gender.
Next, she will
reclaim her status as General Feihong.
Have the Chengs sent
the betrothal certificate?
Not yet.
But don't worry.
After your pride
was hurt that day,
the Master and Madam were heartbroken.
They won't allow the Chengs
to waste your prime years.
They confront the Chengs
to cancel the betrothal.
They should have arrived by now.
My parents
went to the Chengs'?
Miss.
Where are you going?
(Cheng Mansion)
To be honest,
I truly
like Taotao.
It's just a pity
that Lisu isn't fortunate enough
to marry her.
Children have their own happiness.
(Betrothal Certificate)
Lisu's betrothal certificate.
Today, we return it to your family.
Mother.
Mr. Cheng, Mrs. Cheng.
Father, Mother.
Well...
Taotao.
You want...
Father.
I'm having a headache.
Could you feel my pulse?
Let...
Let me check for you.
Your pulse shows good health.
Just some liver heat imbalance.
Taotao is a physician herself.
- She knows she has a headache.
- No...
Yet physicians can't treat themselves.
That's why she came to you.
Taotao.
Your father misdiagnosed.
Since you're unwell,
you should return home to rest.
See you.
Let's go.
Wait...
I...
With my years of experience,
how could I misdiagnose?
Song.
Wrong diagnosis, period.
Why so chatty?
Exactly.
Hurry back and rest.
I won't keep you any longer.
How is that possible?
(Cheng Mansion)
Careful.
See?
I told you she's not ill.
Now I understand why Lisu and Taotao
haven't been together yet.
Why?
Because of you.
What do I have to do with that?
Taotao is your own daughter,
inheriting your stubbornness.
Lisu is your disciple,
learning your stubbornness.
When stubbornness clashes,
they both get hurt.
I...
Well...
Wait...
What kind of reasoning is that?
Xu Jingfu
didn't punish He Rufei.
This shows
He Rufei has something
incriminating against Xu Jingfu.
That's why Xu Jingfu feels threatened.
But after this,
mistrust will grow
between them.
We'll have them sawing off
the branch they're sitting on.
You seem to have a plan.
How can I help?
I'm meeting someone.
Miss He.
Commander Xiao.
Mr. Chu.
Please sit.
Miss He.
On the Mid-Autumn Festival,
Miss Xu was certain
that you were a woman
because...
Because I painted a portrait
of you in women's clothing,
and she saw it.
Anyway,
it's my fault.
I apologize.
Please forgive me.
No need to apologize.
Actually,
He Rufei
is the true mastermind.
So, you knew too.
To prevent further issues,
I hope Mr. Chu
will properly keep that painting.
If inconvenient,
I'll handle it.
No need to trouble you.
Since it's my portrait,
I should
keep it.
By the way,
congratulations, Miss He.
You can finally stop pretending
to be a man
and become a female marquise.
One day,
you will
become a female general.
I appreciate your kind words.
In fact,
I invited you here today
because I have a request
to ask of you.
I won't help bad people.
But regarding your request,
I'm afraid I cannot help.
After all,
he's my mentor.
I cannot
betray my mentor.
Mr. Chu,
don't reject me at once.
Let me share a story first.
He Rufei and I
are step-siblings, no blood relation.
Back then,
he was frail and sickly,
living at Yuhua Temple.
I took over his identity.
That's my history
with He Rufei.
Now that I've returned,
I will reclaim
what belongs to me.
Miss He...
Mr. Chu,
I'm not telling you this
to seek your pity.
I want you to understand
how the mentor you revere
resorts to ruthless means.
To eliminate dissidents,
he colluded with enemies
and planned the Mingshui massacre.
Not only that,
to cover his crimes,
he repeatedly conspired with Wutuo,
plunging Huayuan,
Rundu,
and Jiyang
into war.
Now,
he can sacrifice lives
for personal gain.
One day,
he'll continue doing evil
to satisfy his desires.
Mr. Chu,
you claim officials
are helpless sometimes.
But since you serve the court,
shouldn't the nation come first?
You said you go
with the flow.
But have you considered
what kind of flow you go with?
Therefore,
I hope
you will help.
What's your next plan?
Just let me know
if there's anything I can do.
He Rufei must possess
evidence of Xu Jingfu's crimes.
And the evidence
is hidden in his house.
I've been away for too long.
It's time to return home.
But that's only part of the plan.
I need both your help
with the rest.
Congratulations.
You'll achieve your goal.
Chancellor Xu's power wanes.
Exposing his misdeeds
is already inevitable.
(General Feihong's Mansion)
(I'm back.)
(Times have changed.)
(Things have changed.)
(I once believed this was home.)
(Yet it nearly)
(became my burial ground.)
(He Yan's true gender)
(must never be revealed.)
(Otherwise,)
(you two)
(will die without a proper grave.)
Madam,
since you're here,
go and see Miss He.
Watch your words.
There is only the Young Master.
The Young Lady...
is recuperating at Yuhua Temple.
(In this house,)
(the only person)
(I care about is my mother.)
(I wanted to see her, but didn't dare.)
(I wonder)
(how she's doing now.)
He Yan?
She...
She actually came here herself.
Perfect timing.
Let me see
what she
is up to.
(General Feihong's Mansion)
Seems like
I really scared you badly.
Brother.
What brings you here,
Marquis Wu'an?
Is General Feihong too frightened
to remember basic hospitality?
Aren't you going
to invite me in for tea?
Look.
I come bearing no sword.
Please, Marquis Wu'an.
You're our honored guest.
(General Feihong's Mansion)
Please come in.
Come in.
Okay.
(General Feihong's Mansion)
(Not tempted by praise)
Chancellor.
General Fengyun Xiao Jue is here.
(Not tempted by praise,
nor cowed by slander)
Let him in.
Yes.
General Fengyun,
this is a real honor, having you visit.
Forgive me for not welcoming you
at the gate.
I apologize.
That's alright.
Please sit.
Tea for our guest.
What brings you here
today?
I want to talk about He Rufei
with you.
He Rufei?
General Xiao,
you've come to the wrong person.
I'm barely acquainted
with General Feihong.
Nothing to talk about him.
I heard
you and he studied together
in your youth.
I think your connection
runs deeper than mine with him.
I'm familiar with General Feihong,
but He Rufei
is the real General Feihong?
Your words puzzle me,
General Xiao.
Chancellor Xu,
stop pretending not to know.
He Rufei persuaded Chai Anxi
to steal the Xiao Army's march map.
Colluding with Wutuo forces.
Suppressing my father's urgent missives.
Leading to Xiao Army's defeat
at Mingshui.
30,000 Xiao Army soldiers died.
He Rufei harmed He Yan
and pretended to be General Feihong.
To cover the truth,
he repeatedly tried to kill He Yan
and got the Seven Tiger Generals
killed in the Huayuan Battle
as part
of his deals with the Wutuo.
He deliberately abandoned Rundu,
leaving it besieged
and nearly conquered.
What a shock!
That is
outrageous!
He Rufei's guilt is undeniable.
However,
he's merely a pawn
in someone else's game.
The real villain
is the mastermind pulling the strings.
This is
the tea you've liked since childhood.
Does it not suit your taste?
No.
I just fear poison.
You tease me.
Everyone, leave.
How guilty
you must be.
Dismissing them like this.
Shall we
speak frankly?
Let me guess.
Both of you
must have regretted.
You regret
not having killed me.
But I promise you.
Very soon,
you'll be more regretful.
Rufei.
Don't think
becoming Marquis Wu'an
makes you invincible.
I killed you once,
and I can kill you again.
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪