My parents said to tell you
they'd like you to come over for a meal.
Why are you only telling me now?
You promised me you'd socialize.
Don't follow me.
The student exchange program
in the USA you asked about
is now accepting applications.
One year?
I love you, Sun.
I want to spend every day with you.
I love you too, Ongsa.
I want to spend every day with you too.
What does that mean?
Sun, don't look. Don't look!
-Ongsa, you don't look.
-I'm not looking. I'm not seeing anything.
What's going on?
What is it? What?
Did someone break in? What happened?
Why are you holding a knife, Alpha?
Ongsa, try this clear soup my mom made.
It's so good.
Thank you.
Good?
It's good.
Ongsa.
Sun told me you moved here from Phuket.
How are you doing?
Have you finally adjusted?
I think I have, Auntie.
No. Mrs. Fueang.
Did you just say Mrs. Fueang, Miss Ongsa?
"Mrs. Fueang." I like that.
Honey, don't tease her.
You too, Sun.
Ongsa, you can call me Mom.
Sun's girlfriend is like a daughter to me.
Mom.
Mrs. Fueang…
I mean, Mom.
Did you just say I was Sun's girlfriend?
I did.
You are Sun's girlfriend, aren't you?
Come on, Mom.
You don't have to broadcast it.
Says the girl who is smiling
from ear to ear.
Dad! Don't tease me.
My daughter is just the coolest.
Of course I am.
So you are okay with Sun dating me,
who is also a girl?
Girls date girls these days.
There's nothing weird at all.
Love is not defined by gender.
That's right. We're totally fine.
Sun can be with anyone, boy or girl,
as long as she loves them
and they love her.
My daughter might be small
but she can be a big pain, Ongsa.
Mom, I'm not.
Don't believe her, Ongsa.
Mom and Dad,
I will take the best care of Sun.
Please do so, Ongsa.
I should be the one who takes care of you.
You've always taken care of me.
Well, I want to.
You're still a kid.
You're also a kid, just like me.
You can take care of each other.
And do you know the secret
to a long-lasting love?
What is it?
No keeping secrets.
It's the key to our love.
That's how we've stayed together this far.
True. Especially about money.
No financial secrets.
I'm full.
-Excuse me.
-Sit back down and eat.
Sit.
-Have some.
-Okay.
Ongsa.
What's up?
Do you think one year is a long time?
Why do you ask?
I just want to know if one year
would be a long time for you.
I think it is.
It's long enough
for many things to change.
Like when Alpha and I were kids.
We were both the same height.
But then Alpha moved to Bangkok
and we didn't see each other for a year.
I grew a lot taller.
And do you love Alpha just the same?
I do.
Why do you ask?
I've got something to ask you.
What is it?
Let's suppose
that one day,
we have to live far away from each other.
How would you cope with that?
Far away? How far?
Well,
very far away.
If it happened, I could always call you.
But if I miss you too much,
I might have to go there to visit you.
Really?
Why do you ask?
Where are you going?
Nowhere.
It was just a hypothetical question.
I'm not going anywhere.
That's good.
I'd be so lonely
if I didn't get to see you for that long.
Mini Sunny.
Hey.
What's going on, Luna?
Is Aylin home?
Isn't she with you?
She hasn't come home yet.
She's not picking up.
What happened? Did you have a fight?
No.
There was just a small incident at lunch.
I urged her to try socializing
and have lunch with other people.
She promised me she would.
But when the time came,
she just disappeared.
She's not picking up her phone.
Do you know anything about her?
Did something happen to her as a kid?
To be honest…
I know nothing about Aylin.
I really suck.
We live under the same roof,
yet I know nothing about those two.
It's okay.
I'll try calling her again.
Hey. Aylin just messaged me.
I'm seeking the cessation of suffering.
Be home soon.
What's going on with her?
-What the heck is wrong now?
-Are we really going?
Heck yeah!
The gate is closed, man.
Does it look closed to you?
Take a look.
You're breaking and entering.
Shit. Ton.
Let's leave.
Are you scared?
You said you didn't believe
ghosts were real.
Well, the surroundings are scary.
And I've never been to a temple
at night before.
Haven't you attended a funeral?
No.
Has no one in your life died at all?
No!
My dad, mom, grandpa, grandma,
uncles, aunts, close relatives,
and distant relatives are all fine.
You'll be the first person
in my life who dies.
What a mouth, asshole.
No wonder Charoen doesn't like you.
It's not the time to talk about Charoen.
We are hunting down a ghost
at Luangpu Sek's temple, my friend.
No way.
You came to see her.
Do you really think she will be here
at this hour?
Use your brain.
Why are we even here?
Shut up. We're already here.
Holy shit! What is that?
Don't spook me, man.
I don't know.
-What the…?
-What is that?
Don't push me. I might fall.
Get closer and take a look.
It must be a Preta ghost.
What?
Pretas can't hide in bushes.
A small one could. It must have committed
fewer sins than its folks.
-What?
-Let me film it.
-You're still in the mood to film it?
-Yes.
-I'm not a Preta.
-Holy shit!
A talking Preta?
Ton, you dumbass.
That was a human voice.
Hey.
What are you doing here, Aylin?
Are you looking for a Preta like we are?
Stop talking about Pretas, will you?
Has something happened, Aylin?
Is something bothering you?
Hey, you lot.
What are you guys doing here
so late at night?
We're sorry, Luangpu.
We're just…
I didn't know where to go.
I can't seem to find peace of mind.
So, I came seeking mental help.
Would you like to hear a sermon?
No, sir. I'm leaving.
Are you sure?
Goodnight, sir.
Hold on.
Let your seniors take you home.
Nighttime can be quite unsafe.
Would you mind taking her home?
You guys go to the same school, right?
Yes, Luangpu.
Remember.
If you feel troubled or have concerns,
talking about them with someone
can be helpful.
Do you understand?
May you all be blessed.
Let's go, Aylin. We will take you home.
-If we all go together, we should be safe.
-That's right. Come on.
TEMPLE
What's taking them so long?
Here they are.
Aylin.
What…?
We were worried sick.
Are you okay?
I am okay, human senior, human cousin.
We took good care of her. Don't worry.
So how come you guys
found her at a temple?
Mawin and I went to Luangpu Sek's temple
to hunt down a ghost.
We coincidentally found her there.
What were you doing at the temple, Aylin?
I'm going to bed. I'm tired.
Excuse me.
I think she's got something on her mind.
You were there with her.
Don't you know what happened?
We still can't figure out
why she was there.
I tried asking her
but she refused to answer.
It's like she's keeping a secret.
I think we need to find a way to help her,
at least as the Student Committee.
Thank you guys so much
for looking after Aylin today.
You're welcome.
We're leaving now.
See you tomorrow.
Get home safe.
Go inside.
Bye-bye.
See you tomorrow.
See you.
Come on.
Now take me home.
Yes, Miss Luna.
What? Aylin did that?
Yes.
She smeared a plate full of food
on Ton's face.
Has she been stressed about something?
Aylin isn't usually like that.
Right, Ongsa?
Right.
But I don't know much about Aylin.
I got to know her better
after I moved to Bangkok.
But as for what happened before that…
she's never told me.
I think
I get her.
There must be something
she doesn't know how to tell people.
So, she chooses to keep it inside.
But we're friends. She can tell us.
Some things aren't that easy.
I asked around about Aylin.
What do you know?
She doesn't have friends
in her class at all.
And it's been worse lately.
She doesn't talk to anyone.
But before this, she followed my advice.
It seemed like she was fine.
Why is she like this now?
Do you know about the graph of courage?
What are you talking about?
Hold on.
Hold it.
To do something, we need courage.
This line will go up, up, and up.
Especially with some support,
the line will shoot up like this.
But at some point,
you'll feel like you're up too high.
Then you get scared,
and when you're scared,
the courage you once had will disappear.
And then
you fall.
Bam! Even below your starting point.
See?
I think this is
what is happening with Aylin.
Wow, Ton. You're capable
of getting serious.
Come on.
Don't ruin my cool, man.
So that means that
if we know what she's scared of,
we might be able to help her.
But the problem is,
we don't know what she's scared of.
Hey.
Maybe we should take this
to Teacher Bambam.
She might know a way to help Aylin.
We should.
Yes, we can talk to her.
I think teacher Bambam and Aylin
share some similarities.
Why would you think that?
Because…
Because Teacher Bambam
is similar to Aylin.
You're talking about beauty, right?
Your weirdness.
Teacher Nida.
Please, Teacher Bambam. Please help Aylin.
I'm glad that you two
are worried about her
because I am worried about her myself.
But I'd like you guys
to think from a different point of view.
If someone doesn't want to express
what's inside just yet,
what do you think would be the reason?
They aren't ready?
Correct.
And what do they need
in order to be ready?
Time?
Correct.
Everything takes time.
Different people
take different amounts of time.
Some people are hesitant
to speak their minds
because they are still taking their time
to find a way to say it
or decide on what to do.
That's what I would do.
What if, in the end,
Aylin decides not to tell?
If she decides not to tell,
that's her choice.
All we can do is support and trust her.
At the end of the day,
we can never force someone to share
their true feelings, right?
Human Sun.
Why are you up here?
It's peaceful up here.
I came to clear my head.
Am I invading your personal space?
No.
Then may I sit?
Aylin,
how long do you think
a person can keep a secret?
As long as they can…
till they decide
it shouldn't be a secret anymore.
You've got something on your mind,
haven't you?
Me too.
If you're afraid to say it
because you think it'll make you feel bad
or look weak,
don't be.
It's not that simple.
I know.
But you must say it
in order to remember that
there's someone who is willing to listen.
What about what's on your mind?
It will happen too…
after I say it.
Say what?
Thank you for dropping me off.
Ongsa.
I've got something to talk to you about.
What is it, Sun?
Sun.
Is something bothering you?
I…
I'm thinking about taking a test
for the US exchange program scholarship.
What did you just say?
Exchange program?
Teacher Nida told me
there's this scholarship available
for our school.
I told her
I wanted to be an exchange student
and experience living abroad.
So…
how long would it be?
About…
a year.
A year?
But I'm thinking…
Thinking what?
I'm thinking you should
take the test with me.
There are two spots.
If we help each other study,
we can both make it.
I can't go with you, Sun.
Why not?
Don't you want to be with me?
Still here?
Do you still need to do something?
Why do you look troubled?
I've just got something on my mind.
Is it about love?
Why would you think that?
Well, I can tell by your expression.
But I can help.
Help?
Any problem can be solved
with a few flips of the tarot cards.
Though just to be clear,
they're a only guideline.
Can those be trusted?
It doesn't hurt to try.
The card clearly says you are in love
and thinking about someone at the moment.
What else does it say?
It says you love the person
but are afraid to express it
because you don't know what they think.
If you're afraid of saying it,
they can only be
an acquaintance or a friend.
Oops!
Are you being friend-zoned?
And what if I say it?
Will they be able to take it?
Can you pick three more cards?
These cards say that
the person is quite dense
and doesn't understand anything easily.
Wow. How accurate.
Precise.
Also, they're an unlucky person.
Hapless, to be exact.
I always have to help them.
Then you must confess directly.
If I want to confess,
how should I do it, Teacher Bambam?
Are you asking me or the cards?
I am asking you.
If you're afraid to say it straight up,
how about sending flowers?
Send them to the one you like.
What flower?
How about orchids?
Why orchids?
Because orchids are the symbol
of love and graciousness.
More importantly, in love language,
orchids say, "I can't stop myself
from missing you."
Good?
Will that person know it?
You can write a note with the flowers.
I hope the person isn't too dense to read.
The famous steamed crab meat curry.
A gift from Phuket.
Thank you.
Eat up.
You don't like it?
It's from your favorite place, Ongsa.
It's not that. It still tastes good.
Thank you for bringing them.
Did something happen
while we weren't here?
Nothing.
Kids, we are family.
We shouldn't keep secrets from each other.
Whatever it is, we can share.
Honey.
Let's put it this way.
Whatever problem you may have,
you don't have to keep it to yourself.
You always have us
standing right next to you as your family.
Ongsa,
have you talked to Aylin lately?
Not really. She seems like
she doesn't want to talk to anyone.
What about you?
What about me?
Are you doing okay?
You seem stressed.
It's about Sun.
What about Sun?
Sun asked me to join
the exchange program in the US.
Do you want to go?
I think Sun will understand.
The real problem is how you guys will be
when living apart.
Right.
It's a whole year.
Don't stress.
I think you guys
can maintain this relationship.
You really think so?
It's good to talk often.
True.
From now on, feel free to come to me
if there's any problem
or if you just want to vent.
Thank you, Alpha.
So, when will you tell Mom about Sun?
I get you,
but you can't hide it from Mom forever.
One day, she's going to find out.
Aylin, sweetheart.
Yes, ma'am?
Are you okay, Aylin?
I understand that
you don't trust your classmates
due to your painful past.
I used to be like you.
I know how it feels
to feel like you're different.
Sometimes, choosing to be alone
does not resolve your miserable past.
Opening up to empathetic friends
is the way to forget the pain
from your past.
I get it now.
Is there anything you want to vent?
We are all ears.
No.
Please excuse me.
What?
With all that talking,
I thought she would open up to us.
Right.
We came all the way up here.
I hope I don't fall down the stairs again
on my way back.
But there are elevators, Teacher Bambam.
Why didn't you say so
when we came up here?
Well…
-Elevators?
-Yes.
About the exchange program…
Why do you want to join
the exchange program?
How should I explain?
It's important to you, isn't it?
I…
I have a dream.
I dream of exploring the world.
I want to travel.
Live with people
who speak different languages than us.
I want to try living abroad
for once in my life
because after I graduate from college,
I'll have to take on the family business.
Though my parents have never said so,
I, as their only child, can't abandon
what my mom and dad have built.
Wow. Your answer is so cool.
How?
It's cool because
you have everything in your life
planned out.
While we're the same age,
you seem a lot more mature.
You are cool too, Ongsa.
I'm not.
I've never planned anything out like you.
I just thought I'd like to be a vet
because I like spending time with Latte.
I don't have a solid plan like you do.
The reason I said you're cool
is because you are kind,
lovely,
and funny.
So…
I have decided that…
I will not join the exchange program.
Why not?
Because you are my happiness.
I don't want to be away from my happiness.
But I don't want you to do that.
It is your dream.
I've thought about it for a while.
If you're not going,
I won't take the test for the scholarship.
You're very important to me, Ongsa.
But…
Human cousin, human Sun, follow me.
I've got something to say.
What is it, Aylin?
It's about me being "Alien."
Humans.
Alien knows that everyone here…
thinks of me as their family,
little sister,
and…
friend.
You don't see me as an alien
like other people do.
Then why are you acting like
you're an alien, Aylin?
Because humans aren't friendly.
How?
Who did something to you?
From when I was young,
before I moved to live with Aunt Aor,
people have always given me weird looks,
teased me, and…
They bullied you, right?
You've always been bullied…
to the point where you don't trust humans.
Is that right?
You must've been bullied
since you were a kid.
That's why you don't open up
to new friends.
How harsh was the bullying, Aylin?
That's not the point, Ton.
Bullying and harassment, harsh or not,
always leave scars on people.
Aylin.
Do you know that those
who bully and harass people
are not actually humans?
What are they, Sun?
Germs, I guess.
Or garbage that should be gotten rid of.
Exactly.
But the amount of this type
of garbage is excessive.
So, how should we fix that, Alpha?
I guess all we can do is not abandon
those who are bullied like Aylin.
Right. Do not abandon your friend.
What are you doing?
Doing what friends always do
when their friend is down.
There, there.
Don't cry.
We will protect you, Aylin.
From this moment on,
you don't have to be alone.
You can hang out and eat with me,
Tinh, and Charoen.
Though we are in different classes,
we can be friends.
Thank you, human friends.
Jeez, Ton.
Are you crying?
I think…
I feel inspired.
I will not run
the Mysterious Stories Club anymore.
What?
What will you do then?
I'll set up a club for those
who have been bullied.
-I'll be their spooksperson…
-Spokesperson!
Yeah, that.
I'll be the spokesman
for people who've been bullied.
Because I
love everyone.
Hey. She's smiling because of you, Ton.
That's new.
That's a good thing, right?
I can make her smile.
A round of applause for the man, please.
Good job.
You did great.
Whose is it?
"I hope you're not too dense
to figure out."
"From your secret admirer."
Who is it?
But this seems familiar.
Flower.
"Dense."
Wait. Is this…?
Do you get it now?
Teacher Nida, you like me?
That dense person you like is me?
That's right.
That dense person is you, Teacher Bambam.
Will you tell me now
if I'm out of the friend zone?
But I don't have the cards with me now.
I'm not asking the cards. I'm asking you.
Why are you putting the flower
behind your ear?
I am blushing.
You're blushing.
Does that mean
you like me too?
I'm not sure.
I'm gonna go ask the cards first.
Hold on. Your cards are over here.
Stop.
Good job.
Slowly.
All right. One, two, three.
You've mastered it, rider.
I have a good teacher.
-Where is it?
-Right here.
Okay.
Thank you for seeing me off, Miss Sun.
It's the duty of a good girlfriend,
Miss Ongsa.
Your hair is all messy, rider.
Do you still like me with this messy hair?
It's too late to back off now, isn't it?
I like you with all my heart already.
Sun.
I have something to say.
What is it?
I want you to join
the US exchange program.
Why?
But I don't want to go anymore.
It's a whole year.
I can't bear it.
Sun.
I don't want you to throw away your dream.
Don't tie our relationship to this.
Why would you say that?
Don't get me wrong.
I just want you to follow your dream.
Realizing your dreams
is one kind of happiness.
Will you be able to handle
us being apart for a year?
Is everything all right, girls?
Hello, Mrs. Aor.
Hi.
Is everything all right over here?
Did Ongsa do something to you?
No, I didn't.
We were just talking.
Sun, you should go home.
It's getting dark.
I'll get going then.
Hold on, Sun.
Would you like to have dinner with us?
Of course.
-Do you like the food, Sun?
-I do, sir.
Eat up.
Alpha and Aylin
won't be joining us for dinner.
Alpha has a study group
and Aylin is having dinner at Luna's.
Luna also asked us to join them
but Ongsa didn't want us to be
a third wheel, so we turned her down.
Aylin and Luna?
Seriously?
Yes, ma'am.
Since when?
I think
your food is so delicious today.
Right, Dad?
Aylin and Luna are dating?
Why didn't I know that?
You and Alpha never told me.
No wonder why Luna has spent
the night here a lot lately.
That's the reason.
What about my girl, Ongsa?
Are you dating someone?
-It's me…
-No! I'm not.
I'm not dating anyone.
What?
Why would you say that?
What is it?
What's going on here?
So, you're never going to tell
your parents about me?
About what?
I'm not following.
Ongsa, are you keeping a secret?
Well…
Ongsa and I aren't just friends.
We're girlfriends.
Why are you saying that?
No, why are you doing this to me?
Sun.
Sun, wait.
Sun!
All this time, I've been trying
to understand you, Ongsa.
I think we should call it off here.
The Earth without the Sun is not livable.
What's the matter?
Sun doesn't love me, Alpha.
What the heck are you doing
in the middle of the field?
There's only one sun left now.
At least I'm visible to this sun.
Ongsa, are you out of your mind?
Don't run.
Whatever you need, you can tell us.
I need Sun back.
Can you give me that?
Do you want Luangpu Sek's holy water?
No.
Sun.
If you don't want to see me, fine.
But I want to talk to you.
It's late. Let's go home.
You can come back tomorrow.
Ongsa.