(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 30=
Simu.
Simu,
based on what I saw
in your father's illusion,
I built this place.
It carries the memories of your family
in the Mortal World.
I want you to see a lively world
full of colors.
I believe
you love this world.
If only you could
love me a little more.
If I hadn't come today,
what would you do?
If you lost this bet,
what would you bet with next time?
I have no more chips.
It's a desperate bet
on your compassion
and on you falling for me.
I bet that you'd come to me.
I don't know
what you want from all this.
I want to be with you.
I once told you.
I'm a wish you can't fulfill.
Even so,
will you persist without turning back?
Simu,
I love being with you.
Your Grace,
I adore you.
I wonder if I have the honor
to be the 23rd grave
behind the Void Mountain.
All right.
I accept.
I accept you.
You're so cunning.
You want the Sovereign as a gift.
♪Light the lamps
to pierce the old night♪
♪Borrow mortal warmth to ease the cold♪
♪Warm winds bring fragrant blooms♪
Simu,
I have a blessed flower.
Fengyi is really generous.
Let me give you my sense of touch.
I want you to remember me.
♪With you by my side♪
All right.
Whatever you say.
♪Falling into your gentle smile♪
♪Light and color are there in your eyes♪
♪If you'd let me know how to tell♪
♪The difference between spring
and autumn, love and worry♪
♪Borrow mortal warmth to ease the cold♪
♪Warm winds bring fragrant blooms♪
♪Let me love with all my heart
in youthful grace♪
♪With light, carefree words,
still shining bright♪
♪A pot of wine in fleeting dreams♪
♪A brief life dares seek eternity♪
What...
What is this feeling?
I feel as if a gust of strong wind
is flying out
from my heart.
♪May I roam drunk in dreams♪
You're falling for me.
♪And never forget♪
I'm so delighted.
This is like a dream.
♪Through this life♪
I've never had such a sweet dream.
♪I see a ray♪
♪To what home shall I return♪
(Virtue of the Land)
Don't you know who those guests are?
You made a serious pledge there.
Did your trip to the border
make you so arrogant
that you thought you could
confront Chong troops?
They insulted me like that.
I was just so angry
that I made a big boast.
Now, Qin Huanda
has lost his power.
Duke Pei's influence within the army
is severely crippled.
Chancellor Du wants to build up
his military strength.
I don't actually want this.
But indeed,
you're the best choice.
You will probably
stay in the army.
The heroic boast you made yesterday
would go around town
within just one day.
Once His Majesty hears it,
he will definitely reward you.
I guess
that's the only benefit.
Whatever you decide, Father.
I thought you would be gone
when I came back.
You and Fengyi teamed up
to rid me of my power.
Where else could I go?
What's the color of an orange?
Orange.
The color of an orange is just orange?
What about that?
Grape?
Oh, that one. That's...
Purple.
What about this?
Who slapped you?
It's all right.
I have no sense of touch now.
I can't feel pain.
Was it your father?
He didn't save your life back then.
How did he have the face to slap you?
My father wouldn't think
he did anything wrong.
Do you remember
the Tianluo Ore
I once told
those generals?
Yes.
Wensheng Agency was
the spy outpost my father set up.
Its director,
serving under my father,
knew the purification of that ore.
Chong soldiers abducted me
and threatened my father
to tell them that method.
But my father
ultimately didn't yield.
What do you think?
When my father was young,
he was a great hero, wasn't he?
How could I blame him
for giving up on me
to defend this nation
and protect a national secret
from our enemies?
But he's old after all.
That director's daughter
is Luoxian at Yuzao Pleasure House.
Now,
she's in charge.
My father always thinks
Luoxian is loyal to him.
But actually,
she has long been my subordinate.
Whatever he learns from Luoxian
is what I want him to know.
Are you upset about it?
With no expectations,
nothing can upset me.
Maybe before,
you never relied on anyone.
But you can rely on me from now on.
Because you're mine.
I never make promises casually.
But once I make one,
I'll always keep it.
You can trust me.
I can?
From now on, I'm your family too.
High Priest,
I'm so sorry.
To make my life smooth,
my father was bewitched
and did wrong things.
He atoned for his sins.
But everything happened because of me.
I'll take my punishment.
Your father
actively made a pact with an evil spirit
in exchange for the wealth and glory
of your clan.
Please see the truth.
My father was really bewitched
to take the wrong path.
Guards!
Move!
Father.
Father. Father.
- High Priest.
- Luda.
I...
You're the disciple I care about most.
If people get to know
that your father had a pact
with an evil spirit,
how will they
trust us anymore?
Here.
Execute Yili'er.
Then you'll only be stripped
of your position.
Luda.
High Priest,
I'll give up my position
to atone for my father.
You...
Mentor!
Mentor.
Mentor. Mentor.
Father!
Father, Father.
Father.
Be the High Priest.
You must be the High Priest
to bring honor to our clan.
Father. Father!
Wake up.
Don't scare me, Father.
Father.
Father, wake up.
I beg you. Don't scare me.
For your family's honor,
your father even died
with your mentor.
Now, you're no longer the Young Priest.
Luda,
are you reconciled to this?
The world is vast.
Living beings are small.
This is karma.
Yet it might be reversed.
Have mercy upon us.
When you cover your ears,
you just can't hear the mortals.
I'm different.
Your heart is unsettled.
Even Cangshen can't protect you.
But I can.
What do you say?
How dare you come to me
after my father died because of you?
Because we're of the same kind.
Your obsession and desire
have drawn me here.
I can get you out
of today's predicament
and make you the High Priest.
I'd rather die
than go along with evil spirits.
He won't let you go
unless he's dead.
I'll wait for you to come find me.
The world is vast.
Living beings are small.
This is karma.
Yet it might be reversed.
Xiaoxiao.
Xiaoxiao, I missed you so much!
Xu said he would bring me to you.
Then here I am.
Jingyuan.
Look around.
I've been doing everything Xu tells me.
I take classes
and do martial arts.
Now I'm really good at martial arts.
I can help you
fight bad people.
Xiaoxiao,
how long will you stay this time?
Will you stay forever with us?
I'll stay for some days.
That's great.
You, Xu,
and I
can be together again.
You are the one
I met
at Yueran Fragrance.
Jingyuan.
This is the girl I love,
He Simu.
So,
Miss Wang wasn't abducted.
You planned all that.
She eloped with her sweetheart?
I helped them
and appeased Father.
I also stayed true
to my own love.
Triple win.
But Xu,
you just made that oath.
How will you marry Miss He?
She's from the martial world.
Single heir for generations.
To be with her,
I must join her family.
If Father finds out,
he'll break your legs.
So Xu,
you and Xiaoxiao
are secretly betrothed?
Chenying,
it's been a long time.
Shall I quiz you on your schoolwork?
Well,
let's change the subject.
Look, what a beautiful windmill.
I've always wanted to know
what I look like in your paintings.
The first time I saw you,
I thought you were
a dazzling young man.
And then?
When I saw the wounds on you,
I thought...
You were like porcelain
with ice crackles.
So I look really good
in your eyes.
Aren't you very afraid of pain?
I'm very sensitive to pain.
But I'm not afraid.
I yelled about pain
just to make you care about me.
To me,
this is what a family is.
Hey, don't smudge it.
Then paint another one tomorrow.
Know the meaning of ice crackles?
Winter is over.
Spring is back.
It's the same for you.
Nightmares are gone.
Wounds will heal.
I love it when you care about me.
I'm afraid I can't stop myself
from being weak around you.
I allow you to be weak.
Simu,
I've always wanted to know
what it was that moved you
and made you accept me.
What a fool.
Your Grace, you're bighearted.
So please tell me.
(Foolish devotion.)
(You're a clever man,)
(but you act like a fool)
(to keep me worried.)
Get out of the way.
That's him.
Get out of the way!
- Move aside!
All of you, move aside!
How detestable.
Isn't that Young Priest Luda?
I heard
he was deprived of his status
and exiled to Youzhou.
I heard he became the Young Priest
because his father bred an evil spirit
and sacrificed the lives
of his siblings.
A traitor deserves to die!
Get out of the way!
Move back!
Back, move back!
Step back.
Move back now.
Kill him!
Just die!
Hit him! Kill him!
Move back.
The world is vast.
Living beings are small.
This is karma.
Yet it might be reversed.
Have mercy upon us.
There's confusion.
They're all my people.
The world is vast.
Living beings are small.
This is karma.
Yet it might be reversed.
Have mercy upon us.
There's confusion.
(Yuzao Pleasure House)
There's a vacancy
for the Minister of War.
What's Duke Pei's plan?
Duke Pei
wants this position
to remain vacant.
When things cool down,
he'll decide.
Who is
Chancellor Du's choice,
you or Meng Qiaoyan?
Meng Qiaoyan, I think.
According to my father,
I'll be kept in the army
to replace Qin Huanda.
That's perfect.
It's what you want.
I won't be staying
much longer.
14 northern prefectures
are waiting for us.
His Majesty expanded
the horse ranch in Yunzhou.
He'll certainly appoint
a governor for Yunzhou and Luozhou
to command all the affairs.
I want
this job.
To recover the north,
Yunzhou's horse ranch
and Luozhou's mine are very important.
You risked your life for them.
I won't trust
anyone else with it.
Fang Ji,
do you like Jingyuan?
In the first few years I returned,
Jingyuan talked to me
all day long.
Her praises never repeated.
But she wasn't praising me,
but you.
If you like my sister,
I believe you may
make a good couple.
Don't be ridiculous.
Everyone knows
we're mortal enemies.
Besides, she'd never accept me
unless you told her the truth
of what happened in Daizhou.
And your father.
He's been hating me.
There's no way
he would approve of this.
Quite a lot of reasons.
None is that you don't like her.
Close the doors and windows!
Keep out thieves!
- Shunxi, you're leaving?
- Keep out thieves!
My lady
painted in the yard with her hair wet.
Then she caught a cold.
I should take care of her.
Your lady?
Yes, it's her,
the Sovereign.
A spirit can get sick?
She's special, you know.
Fang Ji.
I have one more
lifelong wish now.
To marry into her clan.
We had a deal.
I'll be a general,
fighting wars everywhere.
You'll be a chancellor,
governing the court.
I don't mind if I will
no longer be needed.
By then, I'll retire.
And you'll just govern the court.
Let me see.
Come on.
(He Simu,)
(you still chose that mortal.)
Come on. Wrap it tighter.
I'll go get the medicine.
(You're pushing me this hard)
(just like everybody else.)
Take it later.
It's hot.
Being human is really a bother.
Just some wind got me sick.
It's a rare experience.
Sickness is part of a full life.
Here.
I'd rather have
fewer experiences like this.
Open your mouth.
I can't taste the flavor.
Why did you give me this?
Simu,
you aren't afraid of bitterness.
But I am.
So?
I'm going to kiss you.
Restrain yourself.
Do you also want to get sick?
One more sip.
Simu,
when will you be fully recovered?
Why?
I should take you out for a stroll.
There's a ball game in a couple of days.
Do you want to watch me play?
I'll ask Jingyuan to go with you.
Miss He,
you're the most beautiful girl
in the whole place.
I told you, huh?
You look great in this.
Let's go.
The ball game in Nandu
is held in spring, summer, and autumn.
Since my brother started to play,
he has always scored first.
They had no other choice
but to change the rules.
One can't win
until he scores five points.
My brother just played for fun.
He scored once and exited.
But he said
he'd play the full match.
Miss He,
you just wait and see.
Look.
That man is so handsome.
Mr. Duan.
That's Duan Xu.
Look.
He's charming.
He scores first every time.
Xu!
Meng.
Duan Shunxi?
A few days ago, you had a big problem
and stayed indoors.
We all thought
you were so depressed
that you would quit.
Yeah.
That's right.
Then why are you still in the mood
for this game?
Staying depressed
won't solve anything.
Today I'll see the ball
as the Chong enemy.
I'll vent my displeasure on the court.
So, I'll play the full match.
Gentlemen, no hard feelings.
- Full match?
- Full?
Only Meng Wan and Qingsheng
will be on my team.
You make up your own teams.
Can't you corner and stop
only the three of us?
- Fine.
- All right.
That'd be perfect.
- Yeah.
- All right.
How come Xu's team
only has three people?
Are they bullying him?
Who could possibly bully him?
That's right.
I've been repressed so much.
Today, I'll have enough fun!
Miss He!
My brother scored first!
- Xu!
- Hurry.
Xu!
Stop him!
Quickly!
Honey, let's go closer and watch.
All right. Let's go.
Stop him.
Block him.
Miss He,
let's get down there too.
You can shout as loud as you want.
You'll enjoy it.
I don't want to shout.
How could you not want that?
You'll want to shout by then.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on.
Hurry.
Honey, look.
Stop him.
Mr. Duan
plays so well.
Bravo!
Xu,
beat them!
He's going to score.
Beat them!
Bravo!
Nice!
Impressive!
Xu!
First score! First score!
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪