The plates match a stolen vehicle.
I repeat, it's a stolen vehicle.
Stop!
Exit the vehicle with your hands up!
What are we doing?
I won't say it again!
Exit the vehicle!
Waiting till they get closer.
What?
What are you doing?
-They'll swerve.
-Why?
Stop the vehicle!
Because I won't.
Now they'll have to maneuver.
Those extra seconds will give us the edge.
Here I thought I was the crazy one!
You're really off your rocker.
Fancy a drive through the woods
in the moonlight?
I sure do.
Isn't it romantic?
Our first heist as a couple,
on a boat in Seville…
Yes, very romantic.
Even the moonlight is with us.
Look at it.
The Torre del Oro bathed in light for us.
Our first kiss was on a boat.
Maybe it's a sign we should live on one.
Maybe in… I don't know.
Venice or Amsterdam.
It rains a lot there, right?
Good. That way,
we'll never leave the boat.
Talk to your mother.
Let's hope she's not sick again.
Yeah, don't worry, Mom.
It's not that late.
How are you?
I've been hearing the chimes
in the attic in my head for 17 days.
You can imagine how I feel.
I keep my phone on me all day long
waiting for a message from you.
When I finally get one,
I have to put it down.
Because I'm scared
you'll say that message is the last.
But then I think about how beautiful
it'd be if you felt the same way I do.
And I open it.
I never felt anything like the night
I went up to that attic with you.
When I read that message,
I ran out of my house
and didn't stop till it got dark.
Crazy.
I'm the crazy one,
wishing I could've waited at the door
to see you sweaty and panting,
to crawl into your drenched T-shirt
and soak in there with you.
Looking at the Torre del Oro
and unable to appreciate its beauty
because I see only you.
I have to go.
You must be thinking,
"Wow, what an odd conversation
to have with your mother," huh?
Say whatever you want to your mother.
You won't ask,
but I want to tell you anyway.
It all started at that party Bruce threw
to mark the end of an era.
The going out, dancing, traveling,
experimenting, seeing a thousand girls.
Enjoying life like there was no tomorrow.
He decided to leave all that behind.
You know why?
He fell in love with me.
Now all he wants
is to curl up on a sofa, make popcorn,
and watch one movie after another.
But I haven't tried
all the things he's grown bored of.
So what if you haven't tried them?
As long as you're okay.
I was a virgin, Roi.
At 36, I had only had sex
in virtual reality.
Okay.
Bruce is the only man
I've ever slept with.
Well, not anymore.
Now there's a second man.
He came into my life like a wild wind.
One I couldn't stop.
Sorry, I was cleaning off the meringue
and dozed off.
I'm leaving.
No, I'll leave.
I'll go now.
Thanks.
Or maybe I didn't know how to.
Or rather, I didn't want to.
Are you coming out, or what?
There's a line!
How do we get out of here?
I felt this irrational attraction.
My brain stopped working.
Suddenly I felt like nothing mattered.
I heard the noise, the music, the people,
but over everything else,
I heard his heart.
Boom, boom, like the bass drum
of the Rolling Stones.
I don't know why I no longer felt
guilt or fear.
I just wanted to be there,
naked, wrapped around him,
moving through that crowd.
I would have gone anywhere in the world.
I remember the orange lights
in that attic,
like a lighthouse.
And the sound of the chimes
vibrating with us.
I experienced absolute climax.
He said to wait so we'd reach it together.
I had to dig my nails into the carpet…
Okay, stop, I got the idea.
I'd say these things happen once,
and it's better to just forget them.
But from what I heard you tell your mom,
that night was the start of something.
Yeah, I thought it was nothing too,
till he did something that changed it all.
I want to see you again.
Do you have a good memory?
Sometimes too good.
655-347-949.
I have his number tattooed in my brain.
I'd remember it,
even in a nursing home with Alzheimer's.
I didn't text him those first three days,
but I did on the fourth.
At first, it was one
or two messages a day.
But now we text like 30 times
and call each other.
Once even in front of Bruce.
I saved his number as "Mom"
so Bruce wouldn't suspect.
I told him she has kidney issues.
It was the first thing that came to me.
This is torture, Roi.
I love Bruce and feel guilty
but can't wait for the next text.
When he doesn't text me,
I think about his previous messages.
I replay them in my head.
I know them by heart.
Are you sure you love Bruce?
Yeah, of course I do.
That's why I haven't seen Claudio.
We just talk on the phone.
What?
-That's worse.
-Why?
There's more infidelity in a text
than in a bathroom quickie.
Basically everyone has had a hookup.
And it doesn't really change your life.
But constantly waiting
for the phone to ring, hoping it's him…
Rereading messages,
reliving moments, well…
Keila.
You know you're cheating on Bruce.
You saved Claudio's number
under your mom's name.
Bruce doesn't deserve this.
Get up!
Up and at 'em, troops!
Breakfast time!
Come on! Up, you laggards!
It's a new day!
I know what you're thinking.
Why this breakfast?
Why am I in yesterday's clothes,
only dirtier,
and with bullet holes in them?
Well, actually, fairground pellet holes.
But some things are happening to me
that have never happened before.
What things?
They stole my wallet.
With such artistry…
By prestidigitation.
And then, that woman gave me
such a delirious night…
She's the one who shot me.
And I don't care.
I'm fascinated by her, and that's
the strangest thing. Because Candela…
Her name is Candela.
She represents some of the things
I've repudiated most of my life.
What are those things you repudiate?
Those loud women
who walk into a restaurant yelling
as if they were at home,
or who grab you by the arm
and drag you here and there,
who laugh up a storm.
Those people who boss everyone around
and run the show,
who eat with their hands
like they've just ended a hunger strike,
who lick their fingers.
Who, like an Irish setter,
lick the orange yolk
left behind on their lips.
But today
I discovered the poetry behind all that
in Candela.
Nobody had fed me since I was five.
My mother playfully pretending the spoon
was a little plane made me anxious.
But from Candela,
everything tasted heavenly.
But there's more.
Afterwards, we went for a stroll
with her pet.
A rabbit.
A hairy one.
Charming thing called Pomelo.
Funny, right?
She takes it for a walk every morning
with a harness, like a German Shepherd
so it can draw fresh energy
from the ground at sunrise.
And I, who was never
an animal lover in general,
or a rodent lover in particular,
ended up lying on the grass
and communing with this rabbit.
Everything I always considered vulgar
felt magnetic today.
What I thought vulgar and coarse,
seems like an ode to life coming from her.
She doesn't live in hushed tones.
She touches everything,
her feet in the earth.
And walking a rabbit.
I had to tell you, in case you worried
about who could enamor me
in this new adventure.
But this time, she has nothing to do
with the heist, as in Paris,
or with the duchess's treasure.
I'm picking up my fork
so you don't get excited
if I get some yolk on my mustache.
Opposites attract, right?
-Why did she shoot you?
-Did you get caught by a boyfriend?
There's no longer a boyfriend.
And there was no bed, no kiss,
not even a look too many, like she says.
I got the bullet holes when she caught me
gaining entry to her home.
And, to celebrate this ode to life,
today we're going to give ourselves
a day in the countryside.
The property registry says
the estate covers 8,300 hectares,
but that's all we know.
Weird, there aren't even
Google Earth images.
It's like a ghost estate.
There are photos of the winery.
These are from the late '60s.
A building with a glass dome
where they held the tastings.
It had an underground cellar
dedicated to wine fermentation.
The building was demolished years ago.
Right after they built their train.
We need to find that cellar.
What do we do? Climb over the fence?
We have a new crew member for that.
The Iberian imperial eagle.
Today we'll just study the area.
And now…
fly away.
Keila, fly west.
Once we find the family country house,
we can get our bearings.
What's that?
Keila, zoom in.
Dead animals. A lot of them.
That's an electric fence.
It seems to use much more power
than usual to keep animals away.
Upwards of 30 milliamperes
can cause cardiac arrest.
There's something behind that olive grove.
There's the country house.
Cameron, mark it on the map.
They have a bullring
in their country home? For real?
Closer. I want to see
how the duke entertains himself.
Zoom in all you can.
Fly up.
That's where the train starts.
So the cellar must be
within an 830-meter radius, tops.
Along those 830 meters,
there must be an air vent.
They're required
for all underground structures.
If we find that vent, we can draw
a straight line from the country house
and find the winery.
Stop there.
Zoom in.
The air vent.
Write down the coordinates.
Draw a line from the country house,
and let's keep going in that direction.
It's the same dome
from the old winery building.
Only now there's no building.
Who would want to hide a treasure
under a glass dome?
Someone with enough artistic sensibility
to know
that some things
can only be appreciated in natural light.
Maybe some sapphires, a blue diamond…
Or maybe a wonderful work of art.
Aren't you extremely curious
to know what's hiding down there?
-What's going on?
-I don't know. It's not responding well.
We're losing altitude. 70 meters.
It's gone crazy.
The connection's unstable.
-What's happening?
-We're dropping and have no visual.
Sixty meters and dropping.
They probably have inhibitors.
Our radio frequency is high,
but it's not enough.
-Keila, bring it back now.
-Twenty-seven meters.
-I'm trying.
-Twenty meters.
The GPS is working.
It's within 200 meters of us.
-It's nosediving.
-Fourteen meters.
Keila, it's seven meters high.
Try to land it.
It crashed.
Do you hear that?
Turn up the volume.
That's a bull, dammit.
Sniffing the drone
and scratching the ground.
We must retrieve that drone immediately.
No.
Going in without a plan is suicide.
I don't mean the electric fence.
The duke isn't just
a capricious Andalusian lord.
-He's a criminal.
-Tell me.
Who will he suspect
if he finds a camera at his estate?
Oh, maybe that guy
who showed interest in his collection
and has a band of thieves
who stole the chalice.
If that happens,
the best outcome is he'll report us.
Do you see?
Because the other outcome
is he'll kill us.
I'll go.
I can find it quickly
with the tablet of coordinates.
No, Keila.
If you go, I'll go with you.
The drone's frequency was very high,
and the inhibitors jammed it,
so our earpieces likely won't work either.
You'll be on your own.
We'll be watching you.
If you notice anything amiss,
don't take any risks.
Come back immediately.
Look.
Careful! Slowly.
Do you know why I had to let
Keila go retrieve the drone
when she's obviously
the brains of our crew?
Because if I send you two,
you may end up
throwing stones at each other
on the other side of the fence.
Curt replies,
looks of disgust since you arrived…
What makes you think the rest of us
are interested in eating your shit?
You broke the rules of the game.
Well, to be fair, so did Bruce and Keila.
No, they know how to be happy.
So I'll ask you two questions,
and I want answers.
Do you want to stay in the crew?
Yes.
I'll ask you a second question.
If I had to send you undercover,
I don't know, on a train…
The Orient Express, for example.
…and you had to pass for a couple
who needs to share a bed for one night,
could you do it?
Yes.
No.
I don't know what could have happened
for you to be 25 years old,
have four million euros,
beauty, health, energy,
and squander it all.
Because you had it all.
-There it is.
-Oh, yeah.
Bruce.
Lean on me.
You just twisted your ankle, and it hurts.
Put it away.
This is private property.
Yeah, sorry, we wanted to see the bulls.
My girlfriend fell and twisted her ankle.
You have to be careful where you go.
And how.
There are signs everywhere
saying this is a dangerous area.
If we see something move,
we shoot, thinking it's a hare.
-You wanted to see the bulls?
-Yes, to photograph them in their habitat.
Let's go see the bulls.
I give them hay every day.
Get your camera and take some photos.
Don't feel like it anymore?
Come, sit on that tree trunk
and we'll take a look at your ankle.
I see sprains during the hunts.
Sit down.
Let's see.
Let's see that ankle.
-Does it hurt?
-Yes.
A little, yes.
How much is that?
When I put weight on it, mostly.
This…
looks bad.
You have a bad sprain.
Look.
I'll put this on you.
I do this to the dogs, my little girls.
When it happens to them,
to get rid of the swelling.
Lift that phone up, man.
Try to get coverage.
Call.
Call!
Call, dammit!
There's no signal.
There's no signal in the whole district.
Let's go to the first-aid post.
There's really no need. It's no big deal.
-It's much better now.
-Yeah. Get up.
Don't worry. I'll take care of her.
-Really.
-Thanks.
Even if I have to carry her.
I'll take her.
No, man.
How would you take her?
Will you hop the electric fence?
And the wall?
Easy.
Get in the truck.
Get in.
Go in the back, with the dogs.
I'm not getting in. Keila, get out.
Open the door.
Open the door!
-You need a key.
-Open the door!
Please.
-Bruce!
Please, stop!
Bruce!
It won't open!
I'm helping you, and you get mad at me?
Get moving, you son of a bitch. Move.
Go.
Turn around.
Bruce!
Turn around, dammit!
Tell me why you're here, kid.
I can just as easily take two to the post.
I'll stop here.
Keep walking.
I said keep walking.
Fine.
We sneaked in. Happy?
We'll leave. No harm, no foul.
-I'm getting her.
-Stop there, dammit.
One more step, and you're dead meat.
Aim well, then.
If you miss,
I'll bash your head in with a stone.
Oh, yeah?
The next one goes to the head.
Why are you here?
To find an air vent
to get into the duke's vault.
Don't move or I'll shoot!
Keila, we need to take this guy.
He just shot you! Let's go!
We need to take him.
First, if he dies, I'm a murderer.
Second, if he doesn't,
he knows what we were doing here.
-How can he know?
-I told him.
Let's go.
How do we get out of here?
We drag him out.
How do we get him
over a three-meter fence?
Is he humming?
Or does he want to tell us a secret?
Check if he has a phone.
They don't seem to miss him yet.
I see no new messages or calls.
We have only a few hours before sunrise.
We'll have to release this wretch
and disappear from Seville.
Do you know what that means?
We have one last chance.
To do what?
Rob the collection this very night.
Subtitle translation by:
Soledad Etchemendy