(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
What's wrong, Chu?
Past this forest
is Great Yong's territory.
Yan Xun,
I can't leave.
Ximeng needs me.
Chu,
you've finally figured it out.
I think you're right.
No matter why Zhuge Yue left,
he must have his own things to deal with.
And I have mine.
I need to protect Ximeng
and the people on this land.
Okay.
Come with me.
Chu,
ahead is Xincheng of Great Yong.
It is the border
between Ximeng and Great Yong.
It's Great Yong's northwesternmost city.
Further to the west
are Ximeng and Great Yan.
If we plant kindling
in Ximeng and Great Yan
and use the wind
to launch a fire attack on Xincheng—
the nearest force
is the 20,000 elite troops of Great Yong
stationed
outside Ximeng Pass.
By then,
they will definitely withdraw their army
to save Xincheng.
In this way,
the crisis in Ximeng will be solved auto—
No.
Chu!
This is the best way to make Great Yong
withdraw its troops.
The people of Great Yong
are also human lives.
I can't hurt them.
Yan Xun,
from the very beginning,
you didn't come with me
to chase Zhuge Yue.
You brought me here
to make me listen to your plan.
Chu, have you ever thought about it?
The reason you can maintain this stalemate
is that Great Yong
has not launched an attack.
If they find a new excuse
to occupy Ximeng by force,
the Ximeng Army,
even with the Great Yan Army,
will be no match for Great Yong.
Your Majesty.
The Lanchuan Tribe
actually dared to rebel?
You originally came to Ximeng
to obtain the black gold mine.
But under Helian Ling's name,
you borrowed a large number of troops
from the Hongchuan
and Lanchuan Tribes to support Ximeng.
You went back on your word.
Even if the Lanchuan Tribe
hadn't rebelled,
I'm afraid you wouldn't have a good ending
when you return.
Wait here for a moment.
Our general needs to say a few words
to His Majesty before coming over.
I have already taken away their troops.
Why did they still have
such military strength?
Elder Lanchuan
traded their Yunxian and Jixian
for 10,000 people from Great Yong.
In less than half a month,
they took the west of Lexian.
He dared to collude with the Yong army?
I will go back now,
reclaim these 2 cities,
and then kill that old man
as a sacrifice to our flag!
You think,
after everything that has happened,
Great Yan
can take back these two cities?
General Huan has ordered
that you may only rest here
and are not allowed to go over there.
Your General Huan's orders
don't work on me.
Chu!
Chu,
are you alright?
Chu!
Huan Huan,
what are you going to do?
I'm going to trade her
for Yunxian and Jixian.
Not only that.
Right now, the Emperor,
the Thirteenth Prince,
and Princess Protector of the State
of Great Yong all want her.
As long as we hand her over,
we can get Yunxian and Jixian back,
take back half of the black gold mines
in Ximeng,
and bring the war to an end.
Buying time for Great Yan to recover
is what we need most right now.
What makes you think I will agree to this?
Because it's not just about 2 cities.
It's also about your throne.
What did you say?
Over the past two years,
the 13 tribes of Great Yan
have been rebelling one after another.
Are you going to kill
all the tribe elders?
Yunxian and Jixian
are the military fortresses
on the border of Great Yan.
If you don't take back these 2 cities,
with the tribe elders of Great Yan
not submitting to you
and Biantang and Great Yong
eyeing us hungrily,
do you really think this throne
will still be yours?
What if I don't agree?
What will you do?
Kill me
and take the throne yourself?
You've already killed me once.
For Great Yan
and the old King,
what makes you think
I wouldn't dare kill you?
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 34]
[Lingfeng Hall]
[In Memory of My Grandfather,
Zhuge Muqing]
Young Master.
The convoy
for the Master's ancestral rites is ready.
The mourning robes have also been distributed
to each branch according to regulations.
Is Grandfather's study still in use?
No.
Now that the Master is gone,
it has long been locked.
No one goes there anymore.
As expected of the grandson
I personally trained—
you figured it out so quickly.
So...
this was all your plan?
Why?
If I hadn't faked my death,
would you have come back
to Qingshan Manor with me?
Since you are fine,
I don't need to stay.
Do you think you can walk out of here?
Yue Shiyi just died,
and you have forgotten?
Not just Yue Shiyi.
There were also the 3 Moon Guards
killed by Zhao Yang.
You should know better than I do
why they died.
Today,
if you take one step
out of Qingshan Manor,
His Majesty, Zhao Yang,
and Muhe Lie—
which of them would let you go?
And which of them
would let the Zhuge family go?
So this was your plan.
You faked your death
to make me
take over Qingshan Manor from you.
From the moment I stepped into
Jinsheng Palace
and saw His Majesty,
even if I discover the truth,
I can't change the fact
that I've already taken over
Qingshan Manor
and can never escape Great Yong.
Muhe Lie has reported
your betrayal of Great Yong
and the things you did in Ximeng
to His Majesty.
If I hadn't faked my death,
would His Majesty
have spared your life so easily?
Why did I go to Ximeng Pass?
It was to trade Chu Qiao's life
for His Majesty sparing you.
But you refused to take that path.
Yue,
you forced me to do this.
Didn't you...
lose your martial arts ability
and become crippled?
Qingshan Manor has studied
the world's strangest poisons for years.
There is no poison we cannot cure.
I know
you always wanted
to abolish Qingshan Manor.
But...
you couldn't even handle
this little trick of mine.
Yue!
I trained you myself.
You will never defeat me,
nor Qingshan Manor.
Yue,
with such little skill,
you think you can abolish Qingshan Manor?
You can't even protect
your own Moon Guards.
Why?
Once you are a member of Qingshan Manor,
you can never leave Qingshan Manor.
Qingshan Manor is my tomb,
and yours too.
This is destiny.
Thank you...
Yue.
Thank you for personally
killing me here.
I want your heart...
to stay...
in Qingshan Manor forever...
as atonement.
Zhuge Yue?
Why are you here?
What about you?
Aren't you supposed
to be stationed at the border?
Why did you bring troops
and sneak into Zhenhuangcheng?
You don't know
what I've been through.
That's what happened.
All my trusted subordinates—
1 lieutenant, 3 guards,
and the officers including commandants,
captains, and generals—
25 people in total—
were executed on the spot.
And I could only hide in the dark,
watching helplessly
and unable to do anything.
Zhao Yang framed you
for such a serious crime
as colluding with Great Yan.
Does the Emperor of Great Yong
know about it?
So what if he does?
My father is cold and ruthless,
stubborn and suspicious.
Over the years,
he has been extremely wary of me
and tested me in every possible way.
Compared to Zhao Yang, what he has done
is even worse.
He let Zhao Yang turn against me,
his own brother,
just as he is using the Muhe family
to suppress Qingshan Manor.
Over the years, the 4 major noble families
in Zhenhuangcheng
have never stopped fighting, locked in
a life-and-death struggle, each rising
and falling at the other's expense.
It's all part of his schemes for power.
I originally just wanted to serve him
wholeheartedly,
even if it meant assisting Zhao Yang
in the future.
But he wouldn't even give me
a way out.
But,
the imperial guard of Zhenhuangcheng
is 10 times larger than yours.
Have you ever thought
that once you take this path,
there's no turning back?
That's why I need your help.
I can't turn back anymore.
You want me
to join forces with you?
Zhuge Yue,
I have no way back.
Neither do you,
do you?
Your Majesty,
further ahead
is the territory of Great Yong.
I have selected a troop
to escort you back to Great Yan from here.
I am still the King of Great Yan.
Since we will negotiate with Great Yong,
you can't represent me, can you?
You've already fed Chu
the muscle-softening powder
and sent so many people to escort her.
What are you worrying about?
Alright.
You can go with us,
but please do not carry any weapons.
General Cheng.
My Lady,
why are you here?
I want to choose a suitable horse to ride.
Could you help me?
This is a pony from Great Yan.
Although it is not as tall
as the Huolei horses,
it rides smoothly,
with a gentle temperament
and great endurance,
capable of traveling 100 li a day
without rest.
Would you like to try it, My Lady?
Helian!
Take me to the place you mentioned.
Come.
Yesterday, General Huan recalled
the 5,000 elite cavalry
bestowed on her by His Majesty
from the Snowy Region Tribe
and stationed them
north of the Capital and Lexian,
together with
the Capital's Black Eagle Army.
The rebels of the Lanchuan Tribe
have all been taken down.
His Majesty has gone
to reinforce Ximeng Pass.
Great Yan can take this opportunity
to unite with Ximeng.
Once Great Yong fears
our combined power with Ximeng,
securing several years
for Great Yan to catch its breath
will not be a problem.
By then, there will be renewal,
and the people will live in peace.
Have you ever thought about
living in a different way?
I was born in Great Yan,
grew up in Great Yan,
and have been fighting for Great Yan
and His Majesty my whole life.
I have never thought about anything else.
I was never valued by the Helian family
since childhood,
and I was often bullied by my clansmen.
My brother
only saw me as a tool
for wealth and power.
I dreamed of making something of myself,
because only then could I earn
the family's recognition.
Now I have become
the Princess Consort of Great Yan as I wished,
bringing glory to the Helian Tribe.
My brother has also obtained
the wealth and power he wanted.
That time, my brother tricked me
into going to Tubu,
and Tubu tried to harass me.
I thought I was going to die
in the Capital of Great Yan,
but you appeared
and saved me.
The day the Lanchuan Tribe rebelled,
you saved me again.
You made me understand
the meaning of living.
Great Yan, Great Yong,
and the rise and fall of my tribe—
none of them has anything to do with me.
I just want to live the rest of my life
the way I choose.
What kind of life do you want to live,
My Lady?
I want to move forward.
I want to live a life
that truly belongs to me,
finding a place where no one knows me
and living peacefully and freely,
without benefits or disputes.
What about you?
What kind of life do you want to live?
Helian.
I...
♪ The dust in the world ♪
♪ Is blown away easily by the wind ♪
♪ Who can stay calm ♪
♪ And not be scared? ♪
Your sincerity toward His Majesty
is rare and valuable.
♪ A slight ripple ♪
♪ Floating life hangs by a thread ♪
I know
that no matter what,
♪ The more pulled, the softer it gets ♪
you would never betray him or Great Yan.
♪ Who dares to say forever? ♪
Your faith
and your life
♪ Let it be ♪
both belong to Great Yan.
♪ Grudges and grace
were never meant to be ♪
♪ Why must you take and demand so much? ♪
♪ Go weaving ♪
♪ Grand and glorious excuses ♪
♪ We face ♪
♪ The heavy thunderstorm together ♪
♪ Even with extreme pain ♪
♪ We don't even wince ♪
♪ Why in this world ♪
♪ The staunchest heart
and strongest soul ♪
Helian!
♪ It will eventually disappear ♪
Thank you for the horse, General Cheng!
General Huan,
I have been ordered
to welcome you into the city here.
But it's getting late today.
The Thirteenth Prince has ordered
that you go to the posthouse
to settle down first.
Thank you, My Lord.
Please lead the way.
Sorry, General.
The troop cannot enter the city.
His Highness has ordered
that you are only to take
the guilty slave, Chu Qiao,
and three guards with you.
The rest of the troops
must be stationed
20 li outside Zhenhuangcheng.
Is this how Zhao Yang made arrangements
for the King of Great Yan?
His Highness' intention was to
prevent the people of the city from seeing
the troops of Great Yan again.
You three, come with me.
The rest of you, stay here.
[Taihe Palace]
Your Highness.
Our agreement terms
were sent to Zhenhuangcheng
by a messenger three days ago.
I wonder if you have read them
and
have any opinions.
Your Highness.
Your Highness!
What did you say?
Our agreement document—
have you read it?
I haven't.
Go ahead. I'm listening.
According to our previous discussion,
we will offer Chu Qiao to Great Yong.
Great Yong must keep its promise
to return Yunxian and Jixian
and call a truce with Great Yan
on this basis.
Within five years,
Great Yong shall not interfere
in Great Yan's internal affairs
in any form.
Where is Princess Chun'er?
Where did Princess Chun'er go?
Your Highness.
Princess Chun'er just sent someone to say
she went to the hot spring today
and will come later.
Hot spring?
Hot spring is good.
It nourishes the skin.
A beauty in a hot spring...
Keep going.
In addition,
there is an additional clause.
After Great Yong takes down Ximeng,
half of the black gold mine in Ximeng
will belong to Great Yan.
Anything else?
No.
Then let it be.
Your Highness.
Sister, you're here?
How could you let them go
without even reading the document?
Sister, you can read it.
Everything else can be discussed further,
but we can't give you the black gold mine.
Princess Chun'er.
Every condition on this
has already been agreed upon.
Your Highness.
Great Yong and Great Yan
have been fighting for so many years.
The national treasury is tight.
If you can hand over this black gold mine
intact to His Majesty,
he will definitely reward you again.
Okay, I'll listen to you.
We won't give you the black gold mine.
Since you have gone back on your word,
we don't have to keep our promise either.
We won't
make this deal.
Wait.
Great Yan can give up the black gold mine,
but the five-year truce
must be extended by another 5 years.
General Huan,
are you making a decision for me?
Your Majesty,
I am making a decision
for the elders of Great Yan
and its people.
I hope you can also think for them
and approve my decision.
Alright.
Then it's a deal.
From now on, Great Yong and Great Yan
will not fight again for 10 years.
Chu.
Chu Qiao is not here anymore.
Where is Chu?
After today's negotiation,
I handed her over
to that princess of Great Yong.
Yan Xun!
Don't be stubborn anymore.
It's over.
There is no turning back.
Go back to Great Yan with me.
Princess Chun'er,
Chu Qiao is here.
You were a slave in Zhenhuangcheng
for so long,
but you've never been here, have you?
It's been a long time since we last met
in Biantang.
I thought you had figured it out.
How could you say such things?
Don't you know
why I'm like this?
Everything I had was destroyed by you.
But it's all good now.
You have nothing, just like me.
How is it?
Does it feel good
to be betrayed by everyone?
We both have nothing.
You're not afraid,
so why should I be?
You are just a lowly slave.
What makes you think we are the same?
How is it, General Chu?
The muscle-softening powder works well,
doesn't it?
Lock her up!
Your Highness,
someone requests an audience.
Huan Huan,
I will definitely
become the master of Zhenhuangcheng.
I hope you can help me
take back Great Yan.
Chun'er!
An ominous sign. It's an ominous sign!
Yan Xun,
did I make the wrong choice?
Qingshan Manor, hear my command!
Capture the King of Great Yan
and Chu Qiao at all costs!