I want you to film the footage of the five members
to make it worthy of being their last concert.
Their last concert?
After he got his solo single
and became more famous than the others,
a Korean company showed interest in signing him for a solo contract.
How could you do that?
When the opportunity suddenly came,
you chose to leave those who have been with you for many years
and get by alone.
How about the person who has to leave them?
Don’t you think that hurts, too?
If you want me to continue with this job, the person I want to get to know the most
is you.
Hello? What’s up?
Hey.
Imagine there are
Mr. A and Mr. B.
Mr. A said…
If you want me to continue with this job,
the person I want to get to know the most
is you.
If it’s just for work,
that’s not necessary.
What if it’s not for work?
Do you think Mr. B would take it
as more than a coworker thing?
Like, would he think Mr. A has a crush on him?
Because after that question,
he just walked away.
Do you think he felt awkward about the question Mr. A asked?
Are you Mr. A or Mr. B?
It’s just hypothetical.
Fine, if you say so.
But after hearing this,
one thing I can guess
is Mr. A definitely has a crush on Mr. B.
No way!
When he said he wanted to understand,
he meant just that, to understand.
There’s no crush involved.
It’s just like when coworkers understand each other.
Fine.
Mr. A doesn’t like Mr. B.
But I think, now,
I bet Mr. B thinks Mr. A has a crush on him.
What’s up?
I’m just getting some water.
About last night…
Oh.
I won’t tell anyone about our conversation last night.
But…
I want to clear something up
because you probably misunderstood.
The sentence was that clear.
How could I misunderstand?
Eh?
It wasn’t that clear, was it?
-I think it was so clear that you… -Thame!
I didn’t mean it in a romantic way.
Huh?
How did it have something to do with being romantic?
Well…
I mean,
I won’t tell anyone
that I misunderstood you were a sasaeng.
I see.
I thought you were talking about something else.
Something else?
What is it?
Well…
I see.
You mentioned about
something more than coworkers?
No. Nothing like that.
Was that romantic?
-Well, the thing is… -Thame. Let’s get your makeup done.
Yes.
Hey, Po.
How was the footage you filmed yesterday?
I’m sorry.
I was too tired to work yesterday.
I partied too hard.
Well,
yesterday, I still didn’t get any good footage.
A lot happened yesterday,
so I…
This isn’t right, Po.
I hired you to work,
so I want you to do it well.
Think about it.
If you can’t do it well,
how much damage will it cause to someone like me?
Po.
I’m a senior here,
whom everyone respects.
Yes.
I just think
I need a little more time.
We’ve got no time left, Po.
Thame is heading to Korea soon.
He has to learn the language there.
He’ll head back just one week before the concert.
If you want to interview him, do it now.
But…
I’ve only known Thame for a day.
Come on.
Someone like Thame
can give you the footage you want without you even knowing him well.
Bro, is it you or me filming for the first set?
It’s you, of course.
They must film your face shot first, anyway,
but I’ve secretly seen they’ve prepared a stand-in for your back shot.
I’m sorry
for jumping ahead in your breakdown queue yesterday.
I was confused, too.
You said you wouldn’t come but suddenly showed up.
At first, I didn’t think I would,
but things turned out that way.
Do you enjoy
when people gossip that you are a big-name celeb
who is self-centered and demanding?
It’s easier that way, isn’t it?
THAME
Who put it here?
I asked who did it!
I’m sorry.
Nobody did that. Everything is fine.
Please excuse me.
Hello.
-Hello. -Hello.
-Please take a seat. -Thank you.
How have you been, Thame, Ice?
-I’m good. -I’m good.
Have you tasted our new flavor snack?
Of course. It’s very delicious.
Please take care of it for me today.
-Sure. -Please don’t worry about it.
-Ming. -Yeah?
Did you bring the gifts members are giving to Thame?
Are they all here?
Of course.
Here. Gloves, socks,
a coat, and a scarf.
See? You’d better worry about yourself.
Did you miss out on anything?
If you did again, I’d call you Mick Number 2.
Oh, come on.
I won’t ruin your reputation, Miss Ming.
-Here. -That’s good to hear.
I brought some, too.
-Here. -Show me.
These are birthstones Thame is going to give his members.
See? Do you think it’s a good idea?
Almost.
You’re almost turning into Mick Number 2.
-Eh? -Hey.
Pepper’s stone should be amethyst, not crystal.
Hey, come on.
Figuring out what gifts they should give each other to create moments
was tiring enough.
How could I have time to check if the stones were correct?
Let’s put it this way. How about switching to lucky stones,
so months won’t matter?
-You silly! -Ow!
But it’s better than getting the wrong month.
Po, you’re here just in time.
Let me see your hand.
Your hand.
Perfect. Follow me.
Come with me. Come, come.
You’re here just at the right time.
We’re almost there.
Here.
All right.
Put your chin in his hand.
Smile a bit.
Smile.
By the way,
you read the script already, right?
Let me tweak it a bit.
You won’t give them birthstones anymore
because we bought the wrong one.
Let’s say they’re lucky stones.
-Deal? -Okay.
Okay.
Come.
Hurry up.
What a relief.
This looks more like his recent photo.
Luckily, we’ve got a great hand talent.
If I had to ask each member to pose one by one,
I bet it would take forever.
It wouldn’t be finished in 30 years.
Thanks a lot.
Are we missing something else?
How about adding more photos?
Here you are. These are the gifts you’re giving to each member.
Got it.
I’m putting them here.
Hey, did you forget to arrange the meeting time?
Me?
It’s Mick’s job.
Eh?
Ugh, he’s giving me trouble again.
As expected. No response yet.
I’ll call Jun and Pepper.
You call Dylan and Nano.
Give me their numbers.
What? All right.
-Call them, meanwhile. -Okay.
Nobody is picking up.
Same here.
Who else can we call? Let’s keep calling.
Come on.
I have this number.
Po, please help bring back the rest of the stuff.
Hey, I have a question.
What is it?
Whenever Jun sleeps in other provinces,
he has trouble falling asleep.
He feels worried and often has nightmares.
Dylan is an analog boy.
Whenever he works on something,
he prefers using a pen and paper.
We even have to print scripts for him.
As for my bias, he’s afraid of flying.
He starts panicking the moment the van leaves.
Ouch!
He can’t keep his hands still.
He even squeezed and hurt his friend’s hands.
Nano likes to collect his favorite shoes in his room at the group’s house,
but there’s still one edition he couldn’t find and buy.
So, how is it? Are you not confused anymore?
Actually, I’m still a bit confused.
Why are you this confused, huh?
Just forget about it.
By the way, while you were talking about Nano,
you mentioned the group’s house.
What is it?
How come you don’t know what the group’s house is?!
Well, it’s where the members have been living together since the debut.
I see.
How's your work on the documentary going, huh?
You don’t even know something as basic as their house?
Well,
anyway,
I’ll get more information myself.
-That’s it for now. Bye. -Hold on.
I have something to ask you, too.
What is it?
You’re Mr. A,
and who’s Mr. B?
I bet it’s Mick.
Is it him for real?
Actually, I think you should film some footage there.
I think nobody is living there anymore.
I’ll get a key for you.
If you get inside the group’s house,
try searching for an old planner.
Members wrote down their feelings for each other in it.
I don’t know what they wrote,
but if you find it,
I think you can include a lot of those things in your documentary.
Let’s continue the interview from yesterday.
Sure.
Say something to your members, please.
Let me start with our youngest member, Nano.
Stay cute and lively like this forever.
Eat a lot, so you’ll grow up fast.
Next is Pepper.
I hope you find success in the MC job you’ve always wanted.
-You’re the best. -Q: SAY SOMETHING ABOUT YOUR MEMBERS
Dylan, you’ll get to write a lot more songs.
Every song you wrote is amazing.
In the future, I’m sure you’ll become a really famous producer.
Finally,
Jun,
your acting career might be a bit challenging,
but someone determined like you
certainly has a very promising future ahead.
Was it a tough decision to make when you decided to go to Korea?
It was.
I had to consider lots of things.
My members and I talked it through,
but they all supported me to make the decision for myself
because they believe parting ways
to do what we love is the best option.
They’re happy we’ve come to this final decision.
MARS started with us supporting one another,
and even if we’re saying goodbye,
we’re doing that for each other as well.
OH THAME! HELLO JUN FRIED CHICKEN, THAME AND FRIENDS
Until the last day,
we’re giving one another meaningful symbolic gifts.
These are birthstones Thame is going to give his members.
See? Do you think it’s a good idea?
Stop it.
Did I mess up my script?
That’s because you followed the script exactly.
That’s why I don’t know how you actually feel.
So, you're going to keep nagging me about this, huh?
For a job like this,
it’s not necessary
to involve our own feelings.
Can you stop doing things that aren’t part of your job?
But what you're doing now
isn’t part of your job either, right?
All day today,
from watching you,
I noticed you followed everything
the company instructed you to do exactly as told.
Throw it away.
-How have you been, Thame, Ice? -I’m good.
Have you tasted our brand’s new flavor snack?
Of course.
I think your newly launched flavor is really delicious.
Wow.
That was totally on point.
He followed the script exactly.
Lucky enough, Thame noticed the product from another brand on set.
Otherwise, we’re definitely in big trouble.
THAME
Mr. Bunpoj is super hard to please.
Even a single strand of hair will bother him.
-Yeah, I think it’s… -Yeah.
But Thame knows it well
that no matter what,
he can’t hold any brand’s product where anyone can see it.
If he does, the company loses out on the benefits.
Shit.
What’s up?
But except for this…
The item each member really wants.
You want the farewell to be nice and real once before you leave?
But you know what?
Doing this
probably hurts them even more.
Why would it hurt them more?
These are not silly stones they just thoughtlessly bought.
Giving them something that seems thoughtlessly chosen…
would hurt less.
What do you mean?
It’s because this clearly shows
you’re leaving them because you really don’t care about them.
These things…
can’t make those left behind understand
why you have to leave them
while you still care about them.
And in front of the camera,
they have to force themselves on everything already.
What kind of face do you think they can put on?
I just want to do something nice for them.
Why don’t you say what’s really on your mind
through this footage
and let me show it to your members?
This is not about me wanting to understand you,
but it’s because you told me you feel hurt.
If you want to do something nice before leaving,
this might be the only way left.
Are you recording it already?
Not yet.
I don’t know what to say.
I don’t know if I should say it, either.
In the end,
if it doesn't turn out okay,
we can just delete it and record it again.
It’s as simple as this.
Mm-hmm.
Okay?
Camera, speed.
Please say something to your members.
I’m sorry
about everything.
It turned out…
I couldn’t say anything apart from saying sorry.
How about this?
You talk, and I’ll write it down as a script.
Then you can follow the script again.
You’re really serious about your work.
Well,
this job is important to me.
That much?
Yeah.
Well, someone once looked down on me,
saying I’m useless and good for nothing.
All I could do was work part-time at a suit shop
or getting hired by a fanbase account.
So, I want to prove
that I can succeed, too.
Just forget about my story.
Anyway, what do you want to say?
I’ll write it for you.
I don’t think…
I can put it into words,
but I can tell you what I’m sorry for.
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry, back then, I thought…
Thame,
I’m giving you a solo single
to boost MARS’ popularity.
Here.
Look at this.
Our first album didn’t sell that well.
Honestly, from a business perspective,
keeping MARS going has been a loss.
I even thought about shutting it down.
The last image I’ll remember is…
I thought releasing my solo single
would improve the group’s situation.
I thought everything would work out
the way the company promised.
All I need is
You… you… you
A solo contract?
Just sign it, Thame. Do it for your group.
I thought this income would strengthen MARS.
I want us to produce this single for MARS.
-It’s the song that… -We aren’t going to do it, Thame.
But I fixed the lyrics…
No matter how good it is,
we aren’t producing it under MARS anymore.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Aren’t we making enough profits for you to keep the group going?
I signed so many endorsement contracts.
We’re gaining this much popularity.
Isn’t it enough?
This is not what I mean.
But now, we’ve got a better offer.
A Korean agency wants you to sign with them.
I’m not going.
I’ve done all these things
because I want to do this with my members.
I understand you’ve done everything for MARS,
and you’ve kept pushing forward as the leader.
But I want you to look back
at what happened along the journey.
So, I have to drop my series lineup just to fit his schedule?
Yes.
Let me be frank with you.
Is MARS now still MARS as a group?
As the leader,
do you think you’re making the group better or worse?
I’m not saying all this to make you go to Korea,
but I want you to reconsider
if staying as MARS is really good to your friends.
Jun!
SECRET AGENT 005
Jun really wants to become an actor,
but he can’t sign the contract because he’s tied to MARS.
Nano wants to get back to studying.
Pepper is now so popular with his MC job
that he’s always spending time at the studio.
As for Dylan, you know full well he doesn't like pop music.
Thame,
I want you to look around yourself once again…
OH THAME! HELLO JUN FRIED CHICKEN, THAME AND FRIENDS
…to see if your friends are now happy or tortured.
I’m sorry for having been selfish for so long,
keeping my members under the name MARS,
while, in fact,
none of them wants to work under MARS anymore.
No one has even returned to the group’s house
we used to live in together.
I’m sorry,
I never looked back.
I’m sorry for being such a terrible leader.
You agree, don’t you?
You’re back.
This is Uncle Joei.
Uncle, this is Thame.
-Hello. -Hello.
Can you help tidy up the shop for me?
I have to go out and run an errand.
I'm sorry for reaching out to you so suddenly.
Don’t worry, Uncle. You can leave.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
I’m sorry for dragging you here and continuing the interview.
It’s all right.
Actually, the company told me to spend time with my family
before flying to Korea tomorrow,
but my parents aren’t free either.
Do you want some water or anything first?
Your previous job looks nice.
Really?
Who said
it wasn’t good?
My ex did.
I fixed this suit, you know.
You’re really dedicated to your work.
Am I?
I can tell what kind of person you are.
Otherwise,
you wouldn’t be working this hard on this documentary like you’re doing now.
Actually,
it’s also because of you.
You said I’m doing my job well.
I see.
Anyway,
thank you for cooperating.
Well,
you said you wanted to understand me, right?
Did I help you understand me somewhat better?
Well,
yeah.
We must wrap up the interview.
By the way, while you were talking,
there was one thing I wanted to tell you.
What is it?
On my last visit,
it seems someone is still going back to the group’s house.
The sour orange tree isn’t dead yet.
It even has some fruit.
The house is still clean.
I don’t think it’s Mick’s doing, though.
He doesn’t even do his own tasks.
That’s why I think someone is still living there.
Perhaps, it isn’t empty like you thought.
Also,
I don’t know if I have any right to say this,
but you aren’t a terrible leader at all.
At least you had a goal to benefit others,
and you realized your mistakes,
but it’s a regret
you chose to protect their feelings
by walking away,
not by fixing it.
Which country came up with the idea
of hanging wish messages on the orange tree?
It’s just from Thailand.
It’s cute, isn’t it?
-Each member’s promises. -I'LL CHOREOGRAPH A COOL DANCE,
-He wants to do it, so let him. -SO OUR SONG WILL ALL-KILL - NANO
See? Even Dylan is cooperating.
Cultural cultivation.
Do you get it?
I WILL MAKE MARS ALL-KILL THE CHART PEPPER
I WILL WRITE THAT SONG
AFTER THE ALL-KILL LET’S EAT HOT POT INSTANT NOODLES - JUN
Thame,
it’s your turn.
I WILL MAKE EVERYONE’S WISHES COME TRUE THAME
You’ve sent the van to pick Thame up, right?
Let him go with the team.
Yes.
He’s definitely coming, Miss Pemika.
Here you are.
Well, I ordered one.
Pardon?
Nothing.
Eh? Two sandwiches again?
When will the seller figure out you’re single now?
Come on, Uncle.
It's bad enough I have to spend money on two sandwiches.
Now, you're bringing up that I'm single again.
I’m wrong again, huh?
Why don’t you just talk to him directly?
Tell him your partner passed away.
I don’t need a reminder.
I know the alumni gathering is at 9 p.m.
I’m not talking about that.
I just want to know who Mr. B is.
I told you, it’s hypothetical.
I don’t believe you.
I bet you’ve got someone new sharing sandwiches with you.
Am I right?
No!
I don’t have anyone sharing sandwiches with me.
I’ll hang up!
Why are you here?
How about your Korea trip?
Oh, there he is.
Sir, where is Thame?
I’ve got an answer for you.
Are you crazy?
Why are you telling me now when to send clips to your members?
You’re supposed to be boarding your flight.
So, this is my answer.
Huh?
I want to tell them in person.
How about your Korea trip?
I’m not going anymore.
Huh?
Someone is still going back to the MARS house.
I WILL MAKE EVERYONE’S WISHES COME TRUE THAME
I might have been wrong,
thinking MARS was dead.
Maybe it’s just waiting for a rebirth.
I just have to fix it, like you said.
-But… -Can you help reunite us as a group?
Whether you can or can’t,
give me a sign.
When I walked in,
you were about to throw that sandwich away.
If you’re not okay with this,
just throw it away, like you were about to.
But if you’re okay to help,
can you give me that sandwich?
What the hell is damn wrong with you, Thame?!
Hey.
-Jun, what are you doing?! -What the hell?
Stop doing something insane and go back to Korea already.
You’re in trouble because of me, right?
It’s I who put you in trouble.
How about convincing other members to join us first?
It might be easier to pressure Jun that way.
No matter what, Jun must be the first one.
To make the plan successful,
Jun really must be the first one
because he’s the one I believe in and trust.
I think Thame isn’t someone who would plan and do something alone.
Do you want me to find out who’s helping?