ظآزThat dayظآز
ظآزNothing stays together foreverظآز
ظآزI've quit romanceظآز
ظآزWho hasn't failed againظآز
ظآزCrying in deathظآز
ظآزAnd in lifeظآز
ظآزEven nowظآز
ظآزWe keep learningظآز
ظآزIt's no surpriseظآز
ظآزBeing happy is so hardظآز
ظآزWeirdly, I became a role modelظآز
ظآزOn the day we met again, we said hiظآز
ظآزIt was a reminder,
a test, and a complaintظآز
ظآزWho can do anything without regretظآز
ظآزI am all rightظآز
ظآزMay you live in peaceظآز
ظآزLet the world roarظآز
ظآزSounds like a carnivalظآز
ظآزBeing alive is never dullظآز
ظآزHow wonderful to be freeظآز
ظآزI became even better without youظآز
ظآزNothing can be perfectظآز
ظآزWe bless each other in painظآز
ظآزWe nod and smileظآز
ظآزMay we both be wellظآز
= Love's Ambition=
=Episode 32=
(Outpatient, Yuekang Hospital)
Alright, Dad.
Qu Mingcheng's land deal
(Shouke &amp; Jinda Accused of Bid-Rigging)
has been frozen by the authorities.
There's no way to complete
the bet with the board.
He will be in tough times.
He's like someone sprinting
who suddenly trips
and falls hard enough to get dazed.
When he wakes up,
he finds himself
tied up tight.
All thanks to
your cooperation.
Regardless,
I've always
respected you.
Well,
we compete in business,
but
I genuinely
hate seeing you like this.
You don't need to say anymore.
My dad can't hear you anyway.
He's been unconscious
with no awareness at all.
Haoming.
Your dad had
a sudden cerebral hemorrhage.
This wasn't foreseeable.
I also feel sad
to see him like this.
That's why I came to visit him.
Are you done?
My mom will be here soon.
She won't want to see you.
Alright.
Well,
take good care of your dad.
If you need anything,
just let me know.
Bye.
Who do you think
acted better,
me or Qu?
Of course, your acting is superior.
Careful.
Before the bidding concludes,
I need you to stay
at the hospital a while longer.
Okay.
I'll do that.
Having me hospitalized
was to make Qu Mingcheng
drop his guard.
The board's bet with him
was also your doing,
right?
Most importantly,
most board members
support you.
I approached them privately
with the proposal,
and they agreed.
But
one thing
puzzles me.
Qu Mingcheng
and Huang Chuming's bid-rigging
is internal information.
It isn't something
just anyone could uncover.
Very good.
Mr. Huang.
Qu Mingcheng
has been officially arrested.
The Diamond Plot project
involves massive funds.
Qu Mingcheng
won't escape legal punishment.
This charade
is finally over.
Without your personal involvement,
Mr. Huang,
our plan to take down Qu Mingcheng
wouldn't have gone smoothly.
Mr. Huang,
why did you ultimately
choose to work with me?
Frankly,
you and Shen Haoming
offered similar terms.
But you have Jinda,
so Shen Haoming stands little chance.
I have one more condition.
Go on.
Beyond our agreed terms,
I want
the two companies you own
in Hong Kong, China.
You're really asking for the moon here!
This is my only additional condition.
As you know,
I spent years on those two companies.
When you officially become Chairman,
you won't have time
to manage them personally.
Those two companies
are crucial to
my development strategy there.
Fine.
If you say no,
I won't insist.
Are there other options?
This time,
I'll take risks with you.
The compensation should
naturally be higher.
You try putting.
I can't.
He's greedy.
I should be greedier than him.
That's how I gained his trust.
Judging by the situation back then,
he did hold the upper hand.
Just one thing has always puzzled me.
Why did you
choose to trust me?
Firstly,
he dragged me into bid-rigging.
He made a mistake
from the very start.
Secondly,
you were generous,
meeting my requirement
for mutual benefits.
Thirdly,
I've done business
for so many years
and have seen many people and things.
But I meet
very few trustworthy people.
In life,
genuine sincerity matters.
Haoming.
I admire both you
and your wife.
I believe
you'll go even further.
Thank you.
Yan.
I just met Mr. Huang.
It went smoothly.
What?
Fang Lei came to our home?
Okay.
I'll be back soon.
Fang Lei.
Why did you come?
Look at this.
I'm sorry.
Haochen
is not your child.
I'm sorry?
Speak!
What's going on here?
Explain this!
Back then,
my sister suddenly came to me.
She told me
she was pregnant.
You are pregnant?
Whose child is it?
I don't know
if it's Shen Haoming's baby.
Are you serious?
You and Haoming
have already broken up.
Yes, but we
broke up
just two months ago.
Does he know?
I can't confirm if it's his child.
On the day we broke up, I went to a bar.
Then,
I met an ethnic Chinese artist.
That night,
we both got drunk.
And then...
But
it really only happened once.
Who was that artist?
Where is he now?
I didn't even keep his contact.
What will you do now?
Later,
my sister came to you
and told...
Tell me!
Why did the old paternity test
prove that Haochen and I
were father and son?
Why?
It was all my fault.
I thought
as long as you kept believing
that Haochen was your biological son,
you and I
would never
be separated.
And being together would feel natural.
It was me.
After learning you
wanted a paternity test,
I replaced the real test result
with a forged one.
You're insane!
I know I've been absurd and childish.
Absurd? Childish?
You're so selfish!
I was scared.
I know...
I know I was wrong.
I truly feel sorry now.
I'm sorry.
I hurt Haochen.
Look,
I'll go to Jinda right now
and reveal
Haochen's true identity.
Then you and Mr. Shen
can reclaim your board positions.
Fang Lei,
you're not even human.
Heartless creature!
Have you ever
considered Haochen's future?
What will happen to him?
Haochen has finally
seen Haoming as his dad.
Do you know
how hard we've tried
and how much he's done?
Let me make this clear.
No one will
hurt Haochen.
He only stays with me.
Got it?
Haochen will always be my son.
Yan and I
are his parents.
This home
is Haochen's home.
I know, I know.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I'm terribly sorry.
Sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
I'm terribly sorry.
Forgive me.
My fault.
Hello.
I'm Han Weiping.
My business card.
Currently, I'm working
at a shell law firm as junior counsel.
Contact me anytime
for legal matters.
What else do you want?
Steve and Qu Mingcheng
have gone to prison.
You should be grateful
that they discarded you early
as their pawn.
Waiter!
Give her a glass.
Are you here
to mock me?
Fine.
Let's drink while you do.
I'm returning to the UK.
Go ahead.
Come with me.
I don't like enigmas.
However, I know
you're obviously a bad man.
To keep you from hurting others,
I'd better keep you in sight
under my control.
You have one day to decide.
(Conference Room)
Haoming,
though Qu Mingcheng is gone,
your family's scandal
severely damaged
Jinda's reputation.
Since you're proposing
to return to the board
and rejoin Jinda,
we have a question for you.
What tangible benefits
can you bring to Jinda?
Exactly.
You can't enter the board
(North Waichuan Project No. 1137)
without solid performance.
My plan remains unchanged.
Secure the Diamond Plot
at North Waichuan.
Jinda has already
lost the bidding rights.
The original funds
could be invested in my company,
Xinye.
Using Jinda's money
to handle your own affairs?
Well...
When Xinye wins the bid
and secures the plot,
we can co-develop it
with Jinda.
We need to review
the bidding proposal
and development strategy.
I've prepared everything.
Take a look.
(Project Catalog)
Before our meeting begins,
let's welcome newcomers
to Yan Studio.
Welcome.
The combination of Yan Studio
and botanical dyeing
has increased
tourist numbers
in Gubei Town by 32 percent.
Thank you all for your efforts.
I'd also like to announce
that Yan Studio's offline stores
will be opening soon.
I hope
we will not only
promote new Chinese-style clothing
but also
create more job opportunities
through offline expansion.
That's equally crucial.
Now let's have Ms. Qiao explain
our offline expansion strategy.
Alright.
Moving forward,
we'll focus on
our three-year plan.
We plan to open
50 physical stores
and estimate that it'll create
over 300 new jobs.
Our marketing department will
implement integrated promotions,
online and offline,
to elevate brand visibility.
The summer-fall collection
will start soon.
Let's wait and see.
Come on, folks!
I can't wait!
You know what?
I've been working so hard
to walk the runway at home.
Guess what?
Some of our new colleagues
are actually your fans.
You know?
They also want...
- Do it! Show us!
- Do it!
(Project Description)
(Goals &amp; Vision)
What happened?
What did the board say?
Rejected.
Their reason?
They had no issues
with the bidding plan,
but they were
rather dissatisfied with
the development proposal.
They considered it mediocre,
lacking the creative highlight.
If I fail this time,
I only have one last chance.
I know nothing about architecture,
but take, for example,
Yan Studio.
When I established Yan Studio,
we really struggled
to find our brand identity.
When I first showed
my proposal
to Jiang Liang,
he completely rejected it.
That's why we changed direction.
I pivoted
from pursuing perfect clothing designs
to creating accessible fashion,
the practical needs in daily life.
It's this very shift
that makes Yan Studio
find something new.
Yan.
Do you remember
you said that local governments
placed great emphasis
on cultural heritage and history?
Sure.
So,
could I formally invite you
to become the co-planner
for North Waichuan's development?
Show me your proposal.
Here it is.
Look at this.
But many renowned developers
have shown interest
in this plot.
Thank you all
(North Waichuan Plot 1137)
for coming
to our presentation on Plot 1137.
Mr. Shen.
Let's start with the project's features.
Our previous rejection focused
on this critical aspect.
This is the main structure.
The core design element
revolves around the river.
The kinetic water curtain technology
will amplify the light-shadow effects
very dramatically.
Impressive.
It's essentially
an exquisite art piece.
Mr. Shen.
While we appreciate
the main building's design,
how can you guarantee
Plot 1137 will
become a first-tier development?
Regarding cultural positioning,
let's welcome Xu Yan,
my special art director,
the founder
of the renowned Yan Studio,
a Chinese-style brand,
to present her vision.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Xu Yan.
About the interior
of Plot 1137,
our preliminary plan
is to increase its value
through cultural events
and art exhibitions.
Traditional commercial complexes
typically relied on
international brands
for core value demonstration.
However, consumers have shown
growing interest
in Chinese cultural stuff
and spent on it.
So this reflects
the resurgence of Chinese culture
and the boost of national pride
and cultural confidence.
Over the past three years,
(Art-Commercial Complexes)
the intangible cultural heritage market
has grown annually by over 40 percent,
reaching a scale
of 150 billion yuan
of market value.
Last year,
Chinese-style apparel sales
surged 43 percent,
while intangible heritage crafts sales
grew 60 percent.
Elaborate on your strategy.
Our core strategy involves
introducing Chinese
intangible heritage brands.
We've made three phases.
Phase one
focuses on
traditional textile crafts,
such as Su embroidery,
Yunjin brocade of Nanjing,
and Hunan embroidery.
Phase two
focuses on
traditional craft brands,
such as
Yixing Zisha clay,
Longquan celadon,
and Henan Ru porcelain.
Phase three
focuses on jewelry
and art brands,
such as filigree enamel,
(Jewelry and Art Brands)
filigree and inlay,
and cloisonne.
These kinds of brands
all serve our purpose
to create an intangible heritage zone.
The mission of our entire project
is to establish
an economically sustainable community.
We want these artisans
to have
a stable means
of sustainable support.
Moreover, we hope
this area
won't just be
for a temporary festival event
or a one-time exhibition.
Instead, we want people
to live here
and work here.
So, they can
feel a true sense of belonging.
Regarding Jinda's investment risks,
how to mitigate them?
My family's money
will serve as junior capital,
while Jinda's investment funds
will be senior capital.
You'll have priority
in receiving returns
but bear risks last.
My goal is to minimize
Jinda's risks
as much as possible.
After two and a half hours
(One month later)
and 186 rounds of bidding,
Xinye won the bid
at 3.806 billion yuan
for the North Waichuan plot.
The premium rate
reached 27.4 percent.
Mr. Shen.
What are your plans for
Xinye's future?
Well then,
today marks a milestone
for Xinye.
I hope you will
continue supporting us.
Thank you.
Today's meeting
is significant.
First,
we'll withdraw the compensation lawsuit
against Shen Jinsong and Shen Haoming
and reinstate their positions.
Next,
we need to revisit
the new personnel appointments.
Currently, Jinda and Xinye
have successfully
signed the acquisition agreement
to jointly develop
Plot 1137 in North Waichuan.
Haoming played a crucial role
in facilitating this collaboration.
He has demonstrated
exceptional management skills
in project operations.
We will aim to
assemble a strong leadership team
to oversee the entire project.
After careful consideration,
I propose
that Haoming formally join the board
and be promoted
to President of Jinda Group.
Please raise your hand if you agree.
Good.
Unanimously approved.
Congratulations, Haoming.
Thank you all
for your support and trust.
Thank you all.
Haoming.
I hope you'll lead everyone
and Jinda
to a better future.
Chairman,
I'll spare no effort
to live up to expectations
from you all
and Jinda.
Add more filling!
Grandma.
Obviously, I made this one.
And you made this one.
Why does mine look like this?
Yan.
No matter how you make them,
I'll always love those you make.
I think
Haoming will love them too.
Definitely.
For sure.
Grandma, look!
How's my dumpling wrapper?
Not bad.
You've improved so much.
Haoming.
Making dumplings
is making wishes.
Each dumpling
is a blessing.
You're rolling wrappers
bringing good luck.
You're wrapping dumplings
carrying wellness.
Officail Website : kissasian.biz
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
And I am
wrapping happiness.
There's some insight.
Did you read that online?
Stayed up late again?
No, I didn't.
Look at these plump dumplings.
They make me so happy.
Plus,
we are
making beef dumplings.
That means good luck!
A family
gathers like this
to make dumplings,
which means we will
always live a happy and lucky life.
Grandma.
Look,
if you live here,
Haoming and I can eat dumplings
every week.
But if you leave,
who will make dumplings for us?
Why don't you just
stay here?
I've been here
for a while now.
But I have
missed my garden plants
and my little chickens and ducks.
I had neighbors
taking care of them.
Your place is wonderful,
really lovely.
I'm happy to live here.
But I still
miss my own home.
Well,
I just want you both
to stay happy.
That's all I hope for.
Wipe off the flour.
What's he doing?
Photos.
Today's reunion dinner
deserves a photo.
With the dumplings?
Sure.
Let's take a selfie.
Like this?
Well...
Is it okay?
How should I pose?
Just look here.
Dumplings.
One, two, three!
Look!
ظآزRushing toward the starsظآز
ظآزUndaunted by painظآز
What's wrong?
See?
- You look beautiful.
- Grandma.
- Half your face is captured.
- No.
Let me
show you a magic trick.
Watch.
Ready?
Come closer.
I'm watching.
What happened?
What is this?
Well,
it came out from up here!
What's going on?
Magic trick!
Look.
Cover it like this.
You teach Grandma to use this.
Cover it.
Abracadabra.
It's magic.
Cover.
Cover it!
- Warm it.
- Rub our hands.
Okay.
Time for the magic show.
Alright.
Let's give it
some magic power.
Good.
Open!
I can open it?
- Yeah.
It better not disappear.
Colors are emerging.
Yes, colors!
Look.
Eyes in the photo
look big.
Manifest.
Manifest?
What's that?
Grandma,
this is an instant camera.
Grandma, your head
is perfectly framed here.
Great camera angle.
See how happy we are!
So happy.
ظآزWhen I look backظآز
ظآزWill you wait for meظآز
ظآزLike fireworks that lovedظآز
Grandma's asleep?
Sure.
What's that?
This is
my gift for you.
Isn't this my photo album?
Look.
How old were you?
I was 23.
(In 2008, I was 21.)
(In 2013, I was 26, and you were 31.)
ظآزIf you remember meظآز
ظآزThen I'm pleasedظآز
(Today, we got married.)
(Dad, Mom, and Kid)
ظآزI love you, that's rightظآز
ظآزHow I wish to say itظآز
(Dad, Mom, and Kid)
(Today's watermelon's so sweet.
Dad, Mom and Kid)
ظآزDeep blue seas turn to foamظآز
(Lucky wrapper, healthy filling,
happy folds)
ظآزIf you remember meظآز
From now on,
this will
be our family album.
Here,
here,
and here
will all be filled.
ظآزI think by now you know itظآز
ظآزAbout me and youظآز
I'm happy to have you.
Me too.
ظآزRight now just to be here with youظآز
ظآزI like youظآز
ظآزHere in my armsظآز
ظآزWhat already happenedظآز
ظآزFeeling so lost and feelingظآز
ظآزSo much distractionsظآز
ظآزNever imaginedظآز
ظآزYou'd stay by my sideظآز
ظآزComforting my sorrowsظآز
ظآزOn the midnight streetsظآز
ظآزIn shadowed cornersظآز
ظآزRemember that momentظآز
ظآزYou smiled and looked at meظآز
ظآزAt that moment, the worldظآز
ظآزJust you and meظآز
ظآزEnjoying the city lifeظآز
ظآزHolding your handظآز
Grandma.
Let me remind you again.
If anything happens,
call me immediately.
Got it.
I'll always remember.
Yan, don't worry.
You and Lin focus on work.
We'll take care of your grandma.
Your mom and I plan
to sell the barbershop
and move in with your grandma
to care for her.
That's good.
Let's walk you out.
Don't bother.
You'll be late for work.
Hurry and get ready.
Mom,
let's go.
I'm leaving.
Dad, Mom, you can come anytime.
Come with Grandma next time.
Stay for a while.
Yazhen.
After we return,
let's expand Mom's vegetable plot.
Here.
Plant more broad beans.
ظآزEntangling my bodyظآز
ظآزCut off malicious labelsظآز
ظآزI got rebornظآز
ظآزFlashing smilesظآز
ظآزI'll make you adore me, ready to shineظآز
ظآزLike a raw diamond,
my presence shapes the worldظآز
ظآزBlooming in my colors,
every frame's perfectionظآز
ظآزMy beauty's defined by none
but my own commandظآز
(Entrance)
ظآزEntangling my bodyظآز
ظآزCut off malicious labelsظآز
ظآزMy face radiates lightظآز
ظآزMetamorphosis declaresظآز
ظآزButterfly breaking free in the mirrorظآز
ظآزPerfect, for no oneظآز
ظآزI got rebornظآز
ظآزFlashing smilesظآز
ظآزI'll make you adore me, ready to shineظآز
Don't be scared. Hold tight.
Go.
ظآزBloom for myselfظآز
ظآزSharp tailoringظآز
ظآزThe present I wantظآز
ظآزDiscard what doesn't fitظآز
(Signing Day)
Wake up.
No rush today, right?
Who said Yan Studio
is a key attraction
for the North Waichuan project?
Who begged me to sign?
No rush now?
I'm sleeping.
Thank you for joining.
- See you later.
(Jinda Group and Yan Studio Signing
for the Joint Development of Plot 1137)
The agreement terms
have been verified by both parties.
If you
have no further issues,
we'll proceed to signing.
Mr. Shen. Nice working with you.
Likewise.
(Party B Representative: Xu Yan)
(Party A Representative: Shen Haoming)
ظآزLike fireworks that lovedظآز
ظآزRushing toward the starsظآز
ظآزUndaunted by painظآز
ظآزFearless of flamesظآز
ظآزEven if just a fleeting sparkleظآز
ظآزWe shed tearsظآز
ظآزDeep blue seas turn to foamظآز
ظآزWe regained freedomظآز
ظآزIf you remember meظآز
ظآزThen I'm pleasedظآز
ظآزI just wanna take my time tonightظآز
Looks absolutely stunning.
Beautiful?
Gorgeous.
Wait.
Let me film a video.
We'll post it online.
If you post it online,
I'll become more famous
as the designer.
Ms. Qiao looks fabulous in it.
Exactly.
Thanks, Ms. Qiao.
ظآزEven if I'm the only oneظآز
ظآزCause I just have been hurt
too many timesظآز
I want to wear this outfit
on my wedding night.
Go ahead.
You can't take it off from now on
until the wedding night.
I won't.
The next morning,
I'll still wear this.
Looks really nice.
You and Yu Yiming are
about the same height.
Come on. Stand next to her.
Let me see if it looks good.
Come, my handsome groom-to-be.
Is this appropriate?
Strike a pose.
What's wrong with this?
Stay still.
Beautiful.
Like this?
Stunning.
Let me change angles.
This side.
Don't move.
- Sweetie.
- Smile.
Newlyweds, stand closer together.
ظآزYou realizeظآز
ظآزIt will all be alrightظآز
ظآزCause I just have been hurt
too many timesظآز
ظآزI'm giving it all,
just getting nothing backظآز
ظآزI was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even seeظآز
ظآزSee the world and how it flows.
We never let goظآز
ظآزSo I'll take my timeظآز
ظآزTo reigniteظآز
ظآزThe love that I should deserveظآز
ظآزWhen the time is rightظآز
ظآزYou realizeظآز
ظآزIt will all be alrightظآز