[insects chirping softly]
[cat meowing in background]
Margot?
Margot, it's me.
[metal clangs]
What's she doing?
[door unlocking]
Are you kidding? It's four in the morning.
[sighs]
[Margot] Is that coming inside?
Just for a little.
[breathes deeply]
- How much?
- At least 30 kilos.
Let's go.
You can put two of them in there.
[plates clatter]
[sucks teeth] It's cool, we got it.
It's all right.
Go to bed.
Here.
Be careful.
Look after yourselves.
- We will.
- [Kingsley] We got this.
LEGAL NOTICE
[Margot sighs]
THE PAYMENT OF 350 EUROS OWED
CONCERNING A 125 CC SCOOTER
WE STILL HAVE NOT RECEIVED PAYMENT
IF PAYMENT IS NOT RECEIVED
WITHIN THREE DAYS
GARNISH YOUR WAGES
I've been thinking.
Now that we know each other,
you can carry shit for me.
- Are you for fucking real?
- [laughs]
Hey, how many times do we have
to sleep together for you to help me?
[chuckles] I may have some friends.
[Kingsley] Hmm…
Measurements?
- Out of your league.
- Pfft.
I'll introduce you to one,
but I'm taking 10%.
Mmm-mmm. That's damn greedy.
["Rosalie" by Ayewai & DJ Skyro playing]
[sensual song continues]
Give a little package deal?
Mmm-mmm.
[espresso machine whirring]
So who knew?
Just my guys.
And my guys never talk.
[sighs heavily]
Kingsley Lafleur, that son of a…
How did he know?
The Lafleurs are pissing me off.
And I expect you can fix it?
Tell me if I'm wrong.
Don't worry, I'll fix it.
I'm gonna… [sighs]
[plane engine roaring]
Where's my sister?
A sauna in Paris.
Pépé!
- Can we be serious now?
- [darkly intriguing music playing]
[Marco] Pick one.
For a ton,
it's 500,000 upfront and a deposit.
We'll take care of him,
unless you fuck us over.
In which case, you'll get your deposit
returned in small installments.
Why you pick the young ones?
We prefer fresh fruit. Nothing rotten.
Once we get the money and the deposit,
the shipment will head out.
- [Pépé whistles]
- [darkly intriguing music continues]
It's too bad.
You could have given King or Annabelle,
but he prefers fresh fruit.
Watch what you say to me.
The whole trip almost got fucked up,
all because of her.
Okay, it was a mistake sending her over,
I'll admit it, but she knew Xhésus.
Oh, they're pretty close, it seems.
In fact, she's getting to know him
damn well right now.
We do this one, we make bank,
and then we're over.
Everyone's got their shit.
Yours is your family.
But it's not mine. It's too dangerous.
["Luffy" by J Kevlar playing]
[dramatic rap song continues]
- [song fades]
- [chimes]
YOU'VE JUST RECEIVED 2.85 BTC
Bravo, Putin.
I've got one ton coming soon.
One ton. That's pretty good.
Can I still count on you?
Someone robbed a boat
yesterday at the Marin.
- You hear about it?
- No.
It belongs to Alex Croquet.
What was on the boat?
Who knows?
This smells like Kingsley Lafleur.
Why would he butt in? Why is he involved?
I'm not sure.
You with me? That's all I need to know.
Hell yeah.
But this ain't kid shit. They're tough.
And tough guys will cut off your arm
if there's dead weight attached to it.
Think you're tough enough?
I've always handled it.
So I'll handle this. Got it?
[Chloé] Can we make an appointment?
Could we…
Yes, I understand
what you're telling me, but…
Yes, I know it's been a week, but listen…
Yes.
We'll figure something out. Yes.
Chloé?
[Chloé] Yes, I know.
- We'll review the explanation page.
- Chloé?
Yeah, it's been picking up, though.
[man on phone] I looked
at your crowdfunding page.
It's still insufficient.
- Who's on the phone?
- We got refused by the bank.
- Hey, let me. Give him to me.
- Yes. Yes, I know, but--
Hello?
- [man] Mr. Lafleur?
- You're refusing the loan?
That's what I was telling your partner.
You don't have the down payment.
We're gettin' it.
I looked at your crowdfunding page,
and you've only raised 120 euros.
We need at least 15 grand.
It's going up, though.
That may be, but right now
my hands are tied.
When you hit 15K, let me know,
but until then, I'm sorry.
Look, we really need this.
I'm begging you.
I understand,
but there's nothing I can do.
I've already had my supervisor
look at your application.
Listen, my house burned down,
it needs repairs.
My siblings gotta have
a roof over their heads.
What about a personal bank loan?
I'm really sorry, Mr. Lafleur.
We only grant business loans
for specific projects.
Come on, please!
I'm sorry, Mr. Lafleur.
You've talked to my friend, Chloé, yeah?
Uh, yes, when you came into the office.
- Are you interested in her?
- Um…
- She'll suck you if you want.
- What? Marvin!
- [man] Wait--
- You prefer men? Then I can suck you.
- Marvin.
- [man] Sir…
[angrily] What the fuck
do you want from us, huh?
Motherfucking cunt!
- Whoa! You're messed up in the head.
- God damn it!
[door slams]
[somber music playing]
We're not gonna make it.
Come on.
[sucks teeth]
It was crazy to think we would manage
to keep everyone together like before.
It was Mama who did that.
We can't leave them with Aunt Régine.
What do you want us to do, Ambre?
There's my music, your app.
My app is stupid.
But we still gotta hold on to some faith.
King and Kylian were actually right.
Hang on, are you serious?
We don't have a choice, not really.
I'm making a choice.
But I need you to stay strong.
Marvin, look at you. You've got muscles.
You're tough.
Where is your strength?
You're like our father.
You flinch, it's over.
I never flinch.
Well, good.
I gotta go to work.
So what's your plan?
Soon, I'll earn enough
to provide for everyone for many years.
- When?
- A month.
Till then, I'll give you the money
to fix the house back up.
What money?
I have it.
I'll have to launder it, though.
How about that app of yours?
The app will hold the money?
You're gonna get plenty of clients.
More than you think you will.
The clients will pay you in cash.
It'll be entered into your account
and into the books.
Then you can help us.
[sighs] How have you fallen this low?
[sighs]
Didn't have a choice.
I need more than survival.
I don't want to be disrespected.
I'm done being kicked down.
I'm not ending up like Dad,
and especially not like Dark.
I'm not gonna work my ass off
but still get my kids
placed in goddamn foster care.
You remember how hard our Ma worked?
And look at us now.
This job will give us a windfall.
After, we'll stop.
Swear it.
I swear it.
- Chloé can never find out.
- [Pearl laughs]
What's so funny?
Mmm, nothing.
Tell me, I'm interested.
Let it go, Marv.
Your girl is gonna find out eventually.
If it's only once, she won't find out.
Just this once.
I'm really glad you came.
Yeah.
- Know where King was last night?
- I don't know, why?
Can you find out for me?
Yeah, I'll try.
[indistinct chatter]
Twenty grams per liter of water.
Drink it during the day.
Mmm. Thank God you're here.
This menopause is killing me.
- Thank you.
- Here.
And how's home?
- We're doin' okay.
- Chin up, my dear.
- All right? Take care.
- Thank you. Yeah. You too, see you.
[scooter approaching]
- [chatter continues]
- [menacing music playing]
- [woman] Need any help?
- [SherKhan] Where's the Lafleur stand?
- [woman] Uh, it's right over there.
- [SherKhan] Thanks.
- Oh shit.
- [menacing music continues]
Ah! You were at the hospital,
little idiot. Where's your brother?
- Tell me!
- Uh, which brother?
God, how many you got in your family?
Kingsley!
I don't know who that is.
Seriously? You want me to rough you up?
He's not at home.
He left when our mother died.
It's true, I'm not lying.
- [man] Hey! What are you doing?
- [woman] Miss, do you know that man?
- Do you need help?
- [man] Back off, man. Get away.
Listen here. You're gonna
give a message to that imbecile.
"Bring back what he stole
or I'll cut him up like a pig."
- Let me go! That hurts!
- [crowd exclaiming]
[crowd muttering]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [Kingsley] Shh! Shh!
- Ahh!
- Don't worry, ma'am. Don't move.
- [muffled grunting]
- [muffled grunting continues]
- Quiet! Shh!
Tell Jérôme
that Robin fucking Hood did this.
[muffled grunting continues]
[bell ringing]
- [woman] Goodbye.
- Bye.
Mr. Novilo?
Hello.
[door closes]
Is this the place to file for bankruptcy?
Yes, but there's a wait. Have a seat.
Okay.
I think it's safe to say you'll be fine.
- Your first time?
- Yeah, but one debt is enough, right?
So true. So true.
What should I expect from this?
Well, they'll poke through
your whole life.
How much goes towards your nails,
if you show up to work regularly or not,
If you have a great-aunt
who can lend you money.
Don't worry, hon,
they won't be too hard on you.
If I say how I live alone
with my two girls, maybe they'll be nicer?
Oh, I'm sure.
Got family?
- Yeah. My mother.
- [door opens]
Margot Quetier?
- You keep me posted, okay?
- Yeah. Here.
FOLLOW
REQUEST SENT
Good luck.
Thanks.
[phone vibrating]
[SherKhan on recording] You lucky your
mother's already dead, you son of a bitch!
You go after my mom?
I'm gonna string you up and bleed you dry!
- You better run and hide! You ain't ready!
- [phone chimes]
You're just a piece of shit
who goes after kids.
Trust me, your locks
won't be going in your mouth.
- It'll be in your asshole, you bitch!
- [door opens]
And I'm gonna be balling
thanks to that dope of yours.
I'mma make at least 700K minimum!
So thank you, you sad little fuck.
[phone chimes]
[phone vibrates]
[Margot] 10%.
[SherKhan clears throat]
Well?
Like fish in a barrel.
So she has no idea?
[scoffs] No, of course not.
- But how you'd know where to find her?
- Her boss is a friend of mine.
He told me she's got a ton of debt,
so I figured she would be there Monday.
Hell yeah. Well done.
Take this.
[SherKhan sighs]
That's it?
If Lafleur wants to see you,
I want you to tell me.
We got shit to resolve.
You'll get the rest after.
I never agreed to that.
Shit, what planet you live on?
Think I will pay you in advance?
You do as I say and get the hell out.
I got it.
- Is it dangerous?
- [sucks teeth] Nah.
- You swear?
- I swear.
He swears.
- Okay.
- ["Doliprane" by Kalash playing]
[song fades]
[phone vibrating]
Gotta step out a sec.
[vibrating continues]
Hello?
Thirty bottles of rum on the way.
You want in?
As good as your brother's?
Better, you'll see, and speaking of him…
Hey, let's not tell him about this.
BIG FLOWER IS BACK WITH 30.
Got some bad blood? Is that it?
We prefer sticking to our own lanes.
DOC
Take it but make him go up
Listen, shipping's gone up 5%.
Wait, what? Man, you're fucking my sister.
We're practically brothers. Do me a solid.
Where's this stuff from?
From my ass. It's damn good quality.
You know my conditions.
- [line disconnects]
- [sucks teeth]
Done
Who was it?
Kingsley. He's got goods on the way.
No more lies? That's good.
- Does Kylian know?
- No.
Should he?
- Might take it badly.
- [laughs softly]
I'll tell him.
Dating his sister has its perks.
[phone vibrates]
DOC - Could it ruin
little flower's one-ton deal?
Your brothers are okay?
Seems they're not getting along.
They're okay.
But there's 11 of us.
We all gotta fight for the best piece.
Mama would save it for Kylian.
I understand.
Right. Come on.
- Let's go relax.
- In a sec.
[breathes deeply]
No. But there's a chance to play
with the whole bouquet
- [music playing in background]
- [Léo] Whoa!
- Is King coming?
- No clue.
He doesn't come here?
He does, but I haven't seen him in a bit.
What's he doing?
He's your brother, man, not mine.
What's your grade in Spanish?
Low.
So you suck.
We've got one ton arriving soon.
Now, we use that money
to fix up the house, make it cooler.
There'll be enough
to go on vacation in Dubai.
I'd be down.
We might need you in Venezuela
to keep an eye on the goods
until the transaction is complete.
- You want to go?
- I'm ready.
You'll leave in a few days.
I'll figure out the school shit.
You'll be taken care of by my partner.
He'll show you the ropes,
teach you everything.
That's cool! Milord knows
how to take care of his soldiers.
- [bittersweet music building]
- [knock on door]
- Hey, man.
- What's up, dude?
All good? What's up?
- Doing well, you?
- Yeah, it's all great.
It's real good to see you, Marv.
Yo! Hope you're not planning
to lecture me again.
Chloé, is Marvin gonna
beat me black and blue today?
No, King. He's not beating up anybody.
[Kingsley] Mm-hmm.
Come have a drink.
[both chuckle]
We wanted to invite you over for dinner,
but for some reason, I couldn't reach you.
- Oh yeah? Did you try?
- Several times. Where were you?
Here, there.
I like to just move around, you know?
[Marvin] Thanks.
[Kingsley] Thanks.
All right.
Here's to family.
So then what's up, man?
I wanted to ask you
could you maybe help with the repairs?
You mean right now?
Mm-mm. I can't.
After I'm done with all my shit?
Totally, man.
[laughs softly]
'Kay, bring on the lecture.
Nah.
- All what shit?
- You really asking?
- You know I'm a fortress. I never spill.
- [laughs] Okay.
But give me ten days.
Ten days, that's all.
- Sounds great.
- You know perfectly well why I do this.
- Okay?
- [laughs]
All right. Gotta piss.
[phone vibrates]
SHERKHAN
You're going to join your bitch mother
in the family grave you fucking thief
Kylian…
[darkly intriguing music playing]
You bring it?
- You've never done this before.
- You want to do it?
No.
- Right.
- [darkly suspenseful music playing]
Man, if my brother did half of
what King did, I'd take care of him.
No.
A man wants to kill your brother,
that's who you take care of.
- [sighs]
- Even SherKhan?
Hell yeah, SherKhan.
Cover for me if shit hits the fan?
[suspenseful music continues]
- [bottles clinking]
- [suspenseful music continues]
Fuck.
[line ringing]
[suspenseful music continues]
- Mama can't take her?
- After her exam. Two more hours.
I gotta run. Bye.
- See you.
- Bye.
Hey, you! You good?
You've grown!
We'll take the quad out later.
[grunts] Before Grandma shows up.
Right? She's a real buzzkill.
Keep that a secret between us.
I've got soda. What kind you want?
[suspenseful music continues]
[SherKhan] Ice cream.
What flavor? Chocolate? Vanilla?
Here, sit here. Don't move.
Cover your ears, okay? Don't move!
- [gun cocks]
- [suspenseful music continues]
[tires screeching]
- You come into my home, you little bitch?
- [gun firing]
I'll show you! I'll fucking kill you!
[suspenseful music fading]
I got an offer for you.
You need money.
Me too.
I've got a plan for us both to get some.
What kind of plan?
Going abroad.
Over to France.
You and me?
Can't bring myself to fly.
But you'll meet my guy…
I take a small fee,
and you keep the rest.
And how much is "the rest"?
You'll work out the numbers with him.
I know you can.
[laptop chimes]
My God! Marvin…
Someone invested in our app.
You serious?
Look!
SOS GARDENING
2 CONTRIBUTORS - 60 DAYS REMAINING
LIST OF CONTRIBUTORS
"Amazing project, I'm in!"
Let me see his face.
- [laptop chimes]
- [Chloé gasps] What's going on?
Wait, this rings a bell.
Some mainlander wants to lower his taxes.
But this man is from the Emirates.
Uh, he works with a guy from Brittany.
I recognize his face.
- What? How?
- Mm-hm.
I met him, uh…
couple of weeks ago, I think.
You kept it secret?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I didn't want to jump the gun.
- We have an investor!
- [laughs]
- We can get the loan! Let's call the bank!
- [both laughing]
[Marvin] Oh baby.
[upbeat music playing in background]
[man] Ambre.
What's going on?
Your music is hella tight, Ambre.
[chuckles] You must be thrilled.
Yeah, I am. Sure.
You'll need someone
to help leverage the heat.
I'm fine on my own.
[man on radio] Young artist from St-Joseph
who is blowing up at the moment.
- Take a listen.
- ["La Chute" by Ambre playing on radio]
It's my brother.
He's down with any song I recommend.
He plays it, no questions.
I've heard of you, you know?
What you heard?
I've heard you leech off artists.
Nah, just jealous bitches tellin' lies.
So Shado is a jealous bitch?
Shado is just salty
because he played at Bacchanal
and still had
to go back to selling burgers.
[scoffs]
Make up your mind.
Bacchanal or burgers?
["La Chute" continues on radio]
I mean, okay.
I write all of my songs.
I don't touch anything.
Nobody touches me
and I'm not taking my top off.
And 500 in advance.
["La Chute" sung by Ambre playing]
[car approaching]
So the damage is in the kitchen
and the second floor. This way.
- Hey, what's happening?
- ["Chez moi" by Actrice playing]
What's going on?
We're fixing the house.
- "We"?
- ["Chez moi" continues playing]
[man] No, you should start
with the roof first.
[Kylian] He'll work his way up, trust me.
["Chez moi" continues playing]
[song fading]
On his way.
- [Marvin] Mmm.
- Is it true, this foreign exchange thing?
Come on, you think
everything's a conspiracy? Even school?
I want Willy to come home.
First things first.
We gotta see eye to eye, Auntie.
Willy is not coming home, not yet.
And Léo won't miss his chance to
learn proper Spanish in a native country.
Remember, Willy can't work where he is.
Find a new man.
This one was awful.
Hey, now, it's not easy.
- You think men are lining up?
- Nah, nah, nah.
Hey, give yourself a little credit.
- What are you doing?
- Double checking.
You mean you didn't double check already?
It's gonna make us look like morons.
I've double-checked already. It's a tic.
[bag zipping]
[car approaching]
[Kylian] It's fine. It's my guys.
Your guys?
[Fatso] Marvin?
What the hell is goin' on?
Dealing with my shit, can't you see?
Let's go.
- He's coming with us?
- He is one of us.
[car starting]
- [in Spanish] Good evening, friends.
- Good evening.
Léo, you come with me.
- [in English] I'm going.
- [Léo] Oh!
Who are you?
He's my brother.
[clicks tongue] I said "fresh."
Take me, it's the same thing.
But it's not.
You're all full of nerves.
Even boiled in a big pot,
you would still be too tough to chew.
Léo's good meat. Right, Léo?
[in Spanish] Yes, sir.
Come with me.
[in English] Wait.
Come here.
Come on.
Your hand.
- [bittersweet music playing]
- Whoa.
Means you're a real Lafleur.
[in Spanish] Amazing.
Oh! Ooh…
[in English] Wait, this is a nettle.
You gave me a nettle leaf?
- [chuckles] Come on. They're good for you.
- But they sting.
There you go!
Ah! Okay.
It stings.
Cool!
[bittersweet music continues]
[Marco] Sorry to interrupt.
[in Spanish] But let's go, fuck!
[bittersweet music continues]
[in English] Remember.
You want your deposit returned?
Everything's gotta be smooth.
In the meantime, just relax.
Keep a low profile.
Lots of money at stake.
[sweeping music building]
[Léo] Let's go!
Whoo-hoo!
We really better not fuck this up.
[sweeping music continues]
[muted dance music playing in background]
So, show me and leave right after.
I'll point her out,
but afterwards we dance.
I want to see your moves.
Ah, I'm like a snake. You'll see.
- I follow the sound of the bass.
- [both laughing]
["Toko Doak" by Natoxie playing]
[loud dance music continues]
That's her.
[inaudible]
Go! Have fun!
[loud dance music continues]
- On me.
- Thanks.
- King.
- Floriane.
3K for a little spin in Paris.
It's all paid.
And benefits versus risk,
explain it to me.
It's cool.
And what if I end up busted?
Same rules. You've never heard of us.
You've no idea. You were framed.
Problem?
It's my first time.
Hey, people here aren't snitches.
How will we do it?
- [inaudible]
- ["Walpa 2" by N'Ken playing]
[loud dance music continues]
[Margot] Let me through.
Hey, come on! Let me through! Come on!
Damn it, get the fuck out of the way!
[man] Yo, man, how's it going?
Where you been?
[inaudible]
- [gun firing]
- [patrons screaming]
- [music stops]
- [screaming continues]
[patrons screaming and clamoring]
- [patron] Run! Run!
- [gun firing]
- [patrons shrieking]
- [gunfire continues]
[woman shrieking and sobbing]
[Margot whistling] Psst!
[darkly intriguing music playing]
[darkly intriguing music continues]
[woman breathing raggedly]
My babies…
[darkly intriguing music continues]