Let's eat something first.
We can play in a bit.
Ranking until 3 AM this morning
wasn't enough for you?
Late at night is the best time to rank up.
Look, I'm in Tier 3 now.
[Episode 4: Was It Love
or Just the Moment?]
[Secret Lover]
[School of Design]
Do you really think
sending our game design to Stellar Studio
will get us an internship?
Of course, it will.
You gotta believe in yourself.
You promised to join Stellar with me.
Are you backing out?
No.
I'm just not sure.
There are still so many bugs
that we haven't fixed.
You guys ready?
If I win, we do this my way.
Don't get touchy-feely with me
until I say it's okay.
Not yet.
The more we test, the more bugs we find.
Bugs or not, we still gotta eat.
True.
Alright.
Let's talk over lunch.
Let's go.
[Exclusive:
Top 100 Influential Figures Series]
[Zhan Wensen]
Why isn't Tuo
sitting next to me?
Are you sure you can meet
Stellar's deadline?
Should be fine.
Right,
Junxi?
We should be able to make it, right?
Yes, we should.
Wensen, do you have anything
you'd like to say to the students?
I think school is a great place
to build a solid foundation.
Get that right,
and you'll adapt to society more smoothly.
May I ask how you manage
[Zhan Wensen]
to balance all aspects of work and life?
What are you watching?
Zhan Wensen.
Work and life are like love.
[How do you balance work and life?]
You need passion for both to make it work.
I decided to study architecture
at Xingwu because of him.
I heard you have a theory,
"Architecture of Love."
[What is
the "Architecture of Love" theory?]
You even know about that?
I think architecture and love are
the same—
both require consideration of needs,
stability, and resilience.
You have to understand
the kind of love you need,
lay a strong foundation, and only then
will it endure through challenges.
So what's the current state
of your "love architecture"?
Right now... I'm
madly in love with architecture.
What's your type then?
Wasn't I invited to give an alumni talk
and promote internship opportunities?
Why does this feel like
I'm on a dating show?
Okay.
[What's your type?]
I like smart, capable,
and responsible people,
but it's even better
if we share common expertise.
Feel free to apply.
Zhan Wensen is really amazing.
The American International Design Award
and the Rising Architect Award in Asia.
He won awards every year.
He's also designed malls
and art museums in Japan.
His work shows a unique ingenuity
in the fluid integration
of light and nature.
He's truly impressive.
If only I could intern at his firm.
What's wrong?
I'm heading home.
Let me walk you home.
No need.
Go back to organizing
your Zhan Wensen collection.
Okay.
Be careful on your way back.
I just feel like
we're moving too fast,
going from best friends
to something more.
Can you give me some time
to get used to this?
Haven't you read those enough already?
Are you trying to memorize them?
[Multimedia Design Department;
Industry Expert-Led Curriculum]
[Magic]
Sorry, sir.
Come on, class rep.
Take attendance.
Huang Xinyi.
Huang Guocheng.
Ye Xuan.
Why isn't Tuo here yet?
Beats me.
Zhou Chenglin.
Chen Zecun.
Chen Enjie.
That's all for today's class.
Class dismissed.
Tuo just texted me
that the school rep
assigned him a errand today,
so he won't be joining us for lunch.
[You're not having lunch with us?]
[Tuo]
[Junxi, can you come help me
with something in the club office?]
[Club Office]
Weird.
Weren't we supposed to meet
at the club office?
Where is she?
I like you.
I want to be yours,
or you can be mine. I'm good either way.
What do you mean?
[The Legend of Takara]
Here's the game disc.
[The legend of the brave]
Thank you.
[The Legend of Takara]
Well...
[The legend of the brave]
You're the dream teammate
I've been looking for forever.
The moment I meet you,
I get a buff to defeat
the ultimate monster.
Together, we can be
the perfect ranked duo.
What are you talking about?
You called me here
just to ask me to be your gaming partner?
No,
I'm confessing my love to you.
Ever since you came to my rescue
at that game store last summer,
I've had a crush on you.
What game store?
Are you seeing someone?
I...
If not, go out with me.
I'm into esports too.
We have many things to talk about.
We've barely talked.
We don't know each other well.
If we're not close enough emotionally,
we can make up for it physically.
I'm okay with that.
Calm down, He Youmei. Don't be like this.
Stay away from him!
Get lost!
You guys...
You and Han Tuo are dating?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I...
Yeah, so what?
Don't go near him again.
Stay away from him.
Why are you being so aggressive?
Can't we talk nicely?
What's your problem?
You're trying to pursue Junxi,
and you expect Han Tuo to be nice to you?
I didn't know they were dating.
Now that you know, stop causing trouble,
and don't tell anyone
about their relationship.
Otherwise...
It's true that...
all the good guys are already taken.
That hurts!
So you do have feelings!
How come you didn't notice
that Youmei likes you?
I honestly didn't see that coming.
Who knew she would like me?
If Tuo and I hadn't seen her
sneaking toward the club office
after class
and followed her out of curiosity,
you would've lost your virginity
without even knowing it.
Lost my what?
I'm a guy.
Tuo, slow down.
-I can't keep up.
-Tuo is seriously mad.
Hope you live to see the sunrise tomorrow!
Don't say scary stuff like that!
Tuo, I want to go home.
Tuo.
Tuo, Tuo, Tuo.
Don't ignore me.
Say something.
You don't act like we're dating at all.
He Youmei almost...
I'm sorry.
That's why I want to
make our relationship public,
so no one else will
set their sights on you.
This time was really an accident.
You know that.
I'm not as popular as you are.
You don't know anything.
Tuo.
Don't be mad anymore.
I'm just sticking to
our no-intimacy agreement.
I lost.
Even though we had this agreement,
you've been ignoring me for days.
I feel so lonely,
and I even wonder if you hate me.
I could never hate you.
Never.
According to our agreement,
you have to let me do what I want.
For a whole month,
I'll only kiss and hug you
when you say it's okay.
But you need to do something
I want with me.
"Something you want?"
Wait...
Hold on.
What?
We haven't decided
who's going to be on top
and who's on the bottom.
Let's settle this
with rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
Your hand.
Wait a sec.
Best two out of three.
Top or bottom,
I'm fine either way,
as long as I'm in you.
You jerk.
Be gentle.
This is my first time.
Mine too.
♪ I just wanna be your good boy ♪
♪ True love knows no hesitation, I love
how you look lost while waiting for me ♪
♪ Wanna be your good boy,
close your eyes and hold me tight ♪
♪ 'Cause I know this is
how you'll love me right ♪
♪ I love you, no one said
love has to make sense, right? ♪
♪ I've been waiting for you every day ♪
We're really doing this now.
What?
Let me help you.
No need. I can wash myself.
No, you can't.
Wait.
Stop it.
Let's shower.
I am helping you shower.
I can't take it anymore.
I'll be gentle
this time.
You said that earlier too.
Get up, and let's have breakfast.
Turnip cake, soft-boiled eggs,
and an iced latte.
All the stuff you like.
What time is it?
Half past ten.
Ten...
You still dare to laugh?
Forgive me,
I'm inexperienced too.
Keep laughing,
and there won't be a next...
Good morning.
It's true
that every relationship needs a push
to move to the next level.
Don't listen to Tuo's nonsense.
Nothing happened.
The sweater you're wearing
is Tuo's, right?
So... nothing happened,
or everything happened,
Tuo?
Thumbs up for sure.
What thumbs up?
Congratulations.
For what?
Try touching him again
and see what happens.
You really need to stop.
You'll be in trouble
if Tuo really gets angry.
Wait for me!
I know you want to hold hands,
but we're at school.
Gotta be cautious.
Wait for me!
Alright.
You guys walked too fast.
Keep up.
Some friends you are.
It wasn't my fault.
-It was Tuo.
-Not you?
-Ditched me for some lovey-dovey time.
-He loves to walk.
I'm here to apologize,
not to steal Junxi from you.
I mean it.
I'm here to return something.
Thank you for helping me that day.
I remember now.
It's
"The Legend of the Brave," right?
Yes! That was the day I fell for you.
Not anymore, I swear.
I've washed your jacket.
Thanks for coming to my rescue that day.
You're welcome.
I'll buy you a new one.
If you don't want it,
I'll keep it as a memento.
Thank you, guys!
Wishing you two everlasting happiness!
I told you to keep it a secret,
and yet you're shouting it out?
Do you want the entire campus to know?
Oh, right.
Han Tuo is so mean.
Who said he was
the campus heartthrob anyway?
Total lies.
You've crossed the line.
Who else was he supposed to snap at?
You're so nice to me.
You're saying all this for my sake, right?
I get it.
I don't get it.
Can I call you "Big Sis"?
I was born in February.
What about you, Big Sis?
Your big sis here was born in April.
You're literally older than me.
Then you're my little sis, Xiaoyang.
From today on,
we're best friends!
I don't want that!
Come on, let's hold hands
and go to the bathroom together!
Who wants to hold hands with you
to go to the bathroom?
Then how about ranking up together
in the game?
No!
[Junxi]
[Mr. Ex, it's time to pay me back!]
Mr. Ex,
it's time to pay me back.
[Mr. Ex, it's time to pay me back!]
[In the Next Episode]
Han Tuo has been leaving
without saying a word lately.
He must be hiding something.
Where are you going?
I'm getting a cheating vibe.
He must be hiding something.
[Ginkgo]
Junxi!