=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 11=
Did you have a dream?
A dream?
You mean the kind mortals have?
What are you doing here?
When I woke up,
I couldn't feel my body.
I thought I was dead.
I couldn't sleep, so I came by.
It seems you
had a pleasant dream.
You dreamed of your parents.
Were you missing home?
I dreamed
they taught me dining manners.
What dining manners?
Like Chenying's father.
I took his obsession,
so I'd look after Chenying
and then entrust him
to a decent family.
That is the deal.
Is it the rule of the Spirit World
to make a deal
before taking one's obsession?
No.
It's my rule.
Why?
As the Sovereign of Spirits,
why do you use an exchange
to grant mortals their wishes?
Why?
There aren't so many reasons
in this world?
I just want to, okay?
Your parents
must both be very gentle,
just like you.
Gentle?
You can't taste flavors.
Yet you can make sugar figurines.
You can't see colors,
yet you paint masterfully.
You can't hear the tune,
yet you can play instruments.
You can't even sense
such ordinary things
as breathing or dreaming.
Why learn these skills
that even mortals
find hard to master?
Surely, your parents
hoped that through these,
you could feel this world.
Perhaps.
They...
have passed away?
My mother
passed naturally with age.
As for my father...
I heard it was for love.
So, with five senses, I can dream.
I dream mortal dreams now.
Everything in the dream
felt so very real.
I'd already forgotten
that they were gone.
I could even
still feel
their warmth.
Wake up.
The dream is over.
If I still had spirit power,
your hand would be gone by now.
So, luck favors me after all.
I got to keep this hand.
(His hand)
(is soft and warm.)
I don't need mortal food.
You're in a mortal body now.
You use up strength every day.
Food does more
than fill the stomach.
At times, it brings new sensations.
Please give it a try.
This is tofu.
Tofu is soft and silky.
You have to hold it like this.
Have a taste.
The texture of tofu
is as smooth as a jade bangle
and as soft and slick as mud.
You can try this one too.
This one is crisp.
This is delicate and dense.
Try this.
And this as well.
What is your name?
Hey,
come and eat.
Xiaoxiao,
don't you like it?
Since you have no kin,
I'll look after you for a while
and then entrust you
to a good family.
Finished crying?
Go bury your father.
You've just been out for a day.
If you catch a chill,
I don't want to tend you.
Xiaoxiao,
you won't cast me aside, will you?
Nonsense.
I'm your only family now.
How could I cast you aside?
You scared me.
Xiaoxiao,
I won't throw a tantrum again.
Just let me stay by your side.
Xiaoxiao,
I...
Hi, Chenying.
Come and eat.
Come on.
Xiaoxiao has eaten plenty.
You should eat too.
Xiaoxiao, you...
You hardly eat much.
Why so much today?
Usually,
food is scarce,
so I leave it for you.
This time, the General is treating,
so of course, I'll eat more.
Is it too hard?
General.
- Xiaoxiao.
- That's not how to eat it.
Don't use your hands.
Here.
Open your mouth.
That's it.
(How can Xiaoxiao)
(eat so much?)
(How strange.)
Simu,
I prepared a gift for you.
I do not need gifts.
- I said…
- Take it
as my apology for the offenses.
Wait a moment.
♪Spring comes; ice and snow thaw♪
♪All things wake, with the east wind♪
♪In the season at its fullest♪
I've noticed
you like soft and furry things.
This is fur
from a white fox
I hunted two years ago.
I didn't know
what I should make of it.
Now, I'm giving it to you as a charm.
That should be its finest usage.
Well?
Do you like it?
♪Let me love with all my heart♪
It's okay.
♪In youthful grace♪
♪With light, carefree words♪
♪Still shining bright♪
Since you had time for such trinkets,
I think Marshal Qin
must be prepared
to strike Youzhou.
If your plan succeeds,
and North Chong is forced
to sign a peace,
your plan
to reclaim
the 17 Prefectures
may never come true.
I'm glad
you care about me.
(Shuozhou)
So lively.
Xiaoxiao.
Xiaoxiao, where are you going?
The General said
people are having the Rite of Spring.
I want to go see it.
Xiaoxiao,
weren't you once
too lazy to even move?
Why do you
go out strolling every day now?
I have money, so I love shopping.
Xiaoxiao.
Well,
why not take me with you?
Sure. Let's go.
(Xiaoxiao used to dislike)
(joining in on lively events.)
(Forget it.
I'll have fun with Xiaoxiao.)
The Spring Ox!
- My shoe.
- The Spring Ox!
Make way, make way.
- Thanks.
- Slow down.
Slow down.
Xiaoxiao!
What a beautiful Spring Ox.
Yes, the General
had people prepare it.
Prepared by the General?
The General had it made.
It's huge.
This ox is really huge.
So huge.
Xiaoxiao!
Chenying.
Chenying!
Who are you?
Chenying.
Who I am isn't important.
What is important is
who the He Xiaoxiao beside you is.
Xiaoxiao
is just Xiaoxiao.
Clever child.
You already saw through it.
Why deceive yourself?
I'm not.
She is fake.
No.
Fake.
- Fake.
- No.
- She's fake.
Fake.
Fake!
She's fake.
No.
First whip for favorable weather
and abundant rain.
Good.
Second whip for fertile land
and warm soil.
Good.
Third whip for prosperity.
Fourth whip for peace
through the four seasons.
Good.
Fifth whip for a bountiful harvest.
Sixth whip for spring blessings.
Good.
Next,
let us all join in whipping
the Spring Ox.
- Good.
The first
to whip the grain
from its belly
wins this little Spring Ox.
- Good.
Give me one.
Walk the ox around;
wealth and grain fill the home.
Crack the whip three times;
grain stacks reach the rafters.
Touch the Spring Ox…
Help!
Xiaoxiao!
Wait!
Stop.
Stop right there.
Stab!
Who is this? Who is he?
I was passing by.
I sensed an evil spirit here.
It's inside this clay ox.
Who exactly are you?
Stab!
Chenying, Chenying?
Chenying?
Everyone.
- Chenying?
- Save yourself.
- Run!
There's an evil spirit!
How could there be
an evil spirit today?
Chenying!
She is not your Xiaoxiao.
She's fake.
- She's fake.
- No.
- She's fake!
She's fake!
Chenying.
Chenying, save me!
She wants to harm me.
She wants to harm me!
Who wants to harm you?
Xiaoxiao, don't be afraid.
I will protect you.
Chenying.
Save me.
You are awake.
Remember what happened
before you fell?
From this day on,
don't go out.
Stay home and recover.
Do you hear me?
Greetings, Marshal Qin.
I've thought
about your plan
to attack Yunzhou and Luozhou.
Yunzhou is not as strategic
as Youzhou,
but it has many plains,
with open land and no cover.
Reconnaissance would be very hard.
We haven't set foot
in the Guanhe River for 30 years.
And we know little about Yunzhou.
Attacking Yunzhou and Luozhou
may not be the best move.
If you have doubts,
I'm willing to go
and scout out Yunzhou.
The scouts sent there before
never returned.
General Duan leads the army.
How can he risk himself?
I will not fail you.
General Duan,
think this through.
The battle is imminent.
The time you have left
is running out.
I'll finish the task
within ten days.
Good.
(Liang)
General,
this is dangerous.
Say no more.
I know my limits.
Go prepare with Han Lingqiu.
You'll go with me.
Yes.
(Without the sense of touch,)
(every movement I make)
(relies on my body's momentum.)
(Essence of Spring)
(If I encounter danger)
(in Yunzhou,)
(with only this momentum,)
(what are my chances of victory?)
(I can't feel the instant I land)
(nor the slightest shift)
(in the air.)
Dried fruits.
Candied fruit.
Mother.
Mother, wait for me.
(I wonder if hearing can replace touch.)
Mother.
(It seems not.)
(The battlefield)
(is far more complex.)
Watch where you're going.
(How am I supposed to judge)
(what's happening?)
Is this...
raining?
Sir, are you alright?
I'm always so clumsy.
I'm so sorry.
Luckily, you're fine.
(Without touch,)
(my awareness is much weaker.)
You like rainy days?
I only just started to.
Why?
Look.
At first, it's a fine, soft itch.
Then it turns cool and moist.
When it pours,
it becomes a faint ache.
I used to like rainy days too.
I often carried out missions
in the rain.
After that, whenever it rained,
I'd think of the dampness
and blood-tinged stench
hidden in the rain.
But just now, I changed my mind.
Rain
is only rain.
Rain didn't bring the evils
hidden in it.
You do recover easily
after being hurt.
So different from the dazed man
in the rain just now.
Simu,
we must part for a while.
I'm going to Yunzhou
to scout.
But without touch,
you're almost an invalid.
If danger finds you,
you may not leave unscathed.
You're worried about me?
I only fear
you'll harm your five senses,
or even lose your life,
wouldn't my promise
to you be for nothing?
My father taught me
how to sense touch
by drawing on the wind.
But mortals can't see the wind.
You mean the wind
like silken threads?
Dust is extremely sensitive
to subtle fluctuations.
You can use it
to sense the changes around you.
Foxy,
stay alive.
Chenying,
I haven't seen you
with Miss He lately.
You keep sighing.
If you keep sighing like this,
your Xiaoxiao
won't be able to stand it.
Lin,
tell me.
If another fake you
appears,
and I still can't tell,
what should I do?
Then look even more carefully.
A fake is still a fake.
He'll slip up.
I believe
that with your wit,
you'll know how to tell.
The new reform is
not yet complete,
and you're already leaving?
The administrative framework
is taking shape.
It can be carried out
by the Vice Commissioner.
I'm heading to Shunzhou
to handle a few minor matters.
Shunzhou's local powers run deep.
What you are planning
must be perilous.
It may not go as you wish.
No need for you to worry.
General Duan,
worry
about your position instead.
Yunzhou is dangerous.
Aren't you afraid of no return?
Rest easy.
I'm looking forward to the game
with you in Nandu.
I'll return safe and sound.
In that case,
let's meet again in Nandu.
Marshal Qin invites you
to the Yamen.
It's her.
She's the one troubling Shuozhou.
Marshal Qin summoned me here
for something like this?
How dare you?
You brazen evil spirit,
surrender at once!
What a fraud!
How dare you mislead the crowd
before me?
Captain Meng, that's not true.
We invited her here
(Clear-sighted and Astute)
based on proof.
Indeed.
If she aided
General Duan with heretical arts
and disrupted discipline,
that is a grave offense.
What proof do you have?
It was her.
She stole my identity.
Don't be afraid.
I'll back you up.
Come on.
Tell everyone here
what happened.
I'm the real He Xiaoxiao.
This evil spirit
took my post
and tried to trap me.
Luckily,
Daoist Mingfeng saved me.
Only then could I seek justice.
Are you finished?
You could find no fault
with General Duan,
so you smear him
and those around him?
That's right.
It's just her story.
You can't frame us so easily.
Since you claim it's a frame-up,
how do you explain
there are two He Xiaoxiaos?
I've spent decades vanquishing demons.
What I do best
is forcing evil spirits
to reveal their true form.
Everyone, look!
This...
The evil spirit...
It revealed its true form!
An evil spirit!
He Xiaoxiao,
do you plead guilty?
If you want to lock me up
and investigate me,
go ahead.
You have less than a day left.
Move fast.
Take her.
Yes.
General Duan ordered me
to protect Miss He.
Who dares lay a hand on her?
Meng,
it is alright.
Lead the way.
Marshal!
Lock it now.
Hurry.
Move, move.
Go on. Move.
I've come to the mortal world
many times,
but prison is new.
To hold this mortal body,
these are less useful
than wooden bars
and iron chains.
General,
I had to suffer for trading five senses
with you once.
Miss He,
what are you, truly?
Don't tell me
you never had your doubts.
So, you really are...
I'm the spirit you speak of.
I will distract the guards.
You must leave at once.
Don't you dislike me?
Go as I tell you.
You helped Xu and us
against North Chong.
I don't care what you are.
I'm not an ingrate.
Since I came out of prison,
you've followed us all the way here.
Why not make your move?
Did you think a few dirty tricks
would be enough to deal with me?
True.
We can't handle you.
But...
he can.
They said
you're not the real Xiaoxiao.
They lied to me, didn't they?
There was never any He Xiaoxiao.
There is only me, a spirit.
Chenying, look.
Did you hear?
She admitted it herself.
She is that spirit.
I am
your real Xiaoxiao.
Chenying,
help me get
that jade pendant.
That belongs to me.
All right?
So, your aim
was the Spirits Lantern after all.
Chenying,
go now.
Help me bring that thing over.
Otherwise,
I will cast you aside.
Go.
Hurry.
Boy,
this is your moment.
Child,
I'll give you a chance.
Pick up that knife.
Kill this malevolent spirit.
After he kills her,
you must give me
the wealth as you promised.
Yes. Pick it up.
Pick it up.
She killed your father.
She's the one who killed him.
Don't you want revenge for him?
But...
My father was killed
by the Chong people.
Not by her.
She consumed your father's obsession.
If your father still had
an obsession,
he would not have died so soon.
Quick.
Kill her.
- Quick.
Quick.
- Kill her.
- Quick.
Hurry and kill her.
Quick. Kill her.
Quick.
Kill her now.
Kill her.
Didn't you want to fight?
Kill her, and you can go fight.
Quick.
Kill her. Kill her.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪