"Wooju Bakery."
What the… when did you wake up?
Why are you sleeping in my room?
I had a nightmare last night.
Then why didn't you wake me up? Why were
you just staring at me?
You looked so peaceful when you were
asleep.
And…
And what?
You looked beautiful.
What are you talking about…
My face?
You know, don't call me 'Boss' anymore.
Just call me Wooju.
Why?
I don't know… you keep calling me 'Boss'.
It makes it feel like we're only connected
by money.
But isn't that exactly what we are?
Listen to me.
Don't call me 'Boss' ever again.
Got it?
Wow.
The bread looks really tasty.
My prince is a really good baker, so…
You know… I'm curious.
How did the prince become such a good
baker?
A prince doesn't usually bake bread in his
own palace, right?
Well, when he was a boy, he used to eat
this delicious bread.
And he wanted to learn how to make it.
So the King ordered the best royal pastry
chef in the kingdom.
To teach him how to bake.
Oh, so he had a teacher, huh?
He was his his best friend, but then…
he disappeared.
Disappeared? Where?
I don't know.
Hey! Don't touch the bread!
And keep your drool to yourselves. These
are for the customers.
I didn't touch the bread.
Then don't get so close.
Everyone.
Let's work hard and sell out today!
What's with you?
You're not the boss, what are you doing?
It's called taking initiative.
Taking initiative?
Hey.
You guys are just here to pay off your
debts.
What initiative?
"Don't call me 'Boss', call me Wooju."
Who said that?
That's only for when it's just the two of
us…
Thanks.
So you're saying aliens kidnapped you?
I'm telling you, it's true!
When did this happen? I'm not even sure.
I told you, I was kidnapped! My hands and
feet were tied.
And they wrapped me up in plastic wrap…
Oh! And I even called the police.
You called the police?
Yes, I did.
And then what happened?
Well…
I don't really remember.
You don't remember?
No, it's just…
The people who kidnapped me…
You might not believe me, but they were
aliens.
No, seriously, they were definitely
Oh, stop talking nonsense…
Cancel that police report right now.
Hold on, I know you think I'm spewing
nonsense, but…
- I told you!
- But I have my reasons.
I don't like loud noises.
Secretary Lee.
Yes, Chairman.
Good grief…
Keep that video up on YouTube.
I want him completely ruined.
Thank you, sir.
Hmm.
Ms. Mina.
Um… please, stop investigating that
person.
What do you mean by "stop investigating"?
About the alien thing… I misunderstood. I
was just overthinking it.
What are you talking about? We were just…
There's no such thing as aliens on Earth!
It's all just conspiracy theories.
I understand.
Something feels off… It's like my memory
was wiped.
Let me ask you a question.
Hmm? Let's assume aliens actually exist.
And let's assume they're planning
something on Earth.
What would be their motive for coming
here?
Are they here to commit crimes?
If they're here, they must have a motive,
right?
Think about it.
What kind of advanced aliens would have
the motive to commit crimes?
A motive…
Exactly, a motive! It doesn't make sense,
right?
Exactly!
A motive!
Thanks, senior.
Geez… this guy has really lost it.
Thank you for coming!
Take care.
Hey! You're that YouTuber, right?
Come on in!
Hmph.
What…
Are you here for?
She's the one who featured us last time,
and we went viral.
That video got 1.2 million views!
I'm so sorry about our employee biting
your finger last time.
I'll cover the medical expenses.
Medical expenses…!
Medical expenses?
Is that all you're going to do?
Hachi! Apologize!
I'm sorry.
You're a bad customer!
Seriously…
YouTuber… um… go ahead and start your
livestream.
Starting now.
Hey everyone, it's Mina from 'Publicity
TV'.
The response to the last video was
amazing.
So I'm back!
Ta-da! This is Wooju Bakery.
Honestly, this place is weird and not that
great.
But I didn't expect so many comments.
Should I try the bread again and tell you
how it tastes?
Here we go!
Try this one.
The bread looks really fancy, right?
But how does it taste?
Hmm… this taste… this…!
Ah!
What a liar!
What a bad customer!
Air, you try a bite too.
Oh! Please, stop messing around!
Hey! Stop!
Don't eat it!
Hey!
What if something happens to you?
Raon!
What on earth did you put in this bread!
I heard Earthlings love alcohol…
So I tried making alcohol bread.
Was it too strong?
Wake up.
Ah… my head hurts.
What's going on?
I'm sorry, the bread you just ate had
alcohol in it.
Alcohol… alcohol bread?
I can't drink a single drop of alcohol!
I'm sorry.
Then try this bread instead.
What is this?
Hangover cure bread.
You'll sober up immediately.
My stomach hurts so much. Can I even eat
that right now?
You can that bread as your suppository,
don't worry.
I've tried it once before.
Hey! Keep it down! Get out!
I can't stand either of you.
So our contract is over just like that?
Does that mean I don't have to pay you
back?
Who said you didn't have to pay me back?
Just get out of my sight for now.
Get out for an hour and then come back!
Hachi!
Break time.
Let's go out for a bit.
Wait a second…
Good grief…
Are you okay?
Hmm?
What is this? I'm actually sober.
Really?
I'm really sorry.
Is this supposed to be fun?
You don't think it's fun?
Why would it be fun to go back and forth
like this?
What's the concept of this equipment?
Are you trying to make me feel gravity?
Isn't it amazing?
Earthlings play like this when they're
kids.
Prince!
Studying the Earthlings isn't our mission.
- Mission?
- What did you just say when you seduced me?
You said you were going to Earth for a
special mission.
Not running away from that arranged
marriage.
That's what you said, right?
Well, actually…
Was it all a lie?
It's not exactly a lie…
Prince, tell me!
Did you just use me to run away from that
marriage?
I mean…
What are we even doing here?
Why did we come here?
Exactly, that's what I'd like to know.
Welcome to Earth!
Do we know each other?
Prince! He's the owner of the exchange
shop who cheated us!
He exchanged our money from the sale of
the two buildings only for 115,000 won!
That's called an exchange rate.
Thank you very much.
Someone has been looking for you.
Follow me, quietly.
My name is Lee Sung-ryong.
I run a small business here on Earth.
Nice to meet you.
You've come a long way. You must be
exhausted.
Yes, we've come such a long way.
But…
What do you do for a living?
I am a Prin…
I'm the Bread King.
Why would business people come all the way
to Earth?
The bread on Earth isn't even that good.
I… I'll give you back the money I took.
Huh?
I can't let that bakery go under.
Let's step outside and talk.
Wait, that hurts! Let go of me!
Don't move!
It's the police!
Ms. Mina.
The aliens tried to kidnap you again,
didn't they?
- No, that's not it.
- That's not what happened.
Look, it's really not like that…
Chairman Lee Sung-ryong.
We received a report that you are an
alien.
We're here to investigate.
Aliens? What are you talking about?
We came here because we have the facts.
Who filed such a ridiculous report?
Aliens only exist in sci-fi movies.
How could there be aliens on Earth?
Right?
Everyone, hands up! Against the wall!
Move it!
You look busy, so we'll be going now.
We have bread to bake.
Run!
What's wrong now?
The power unit and communication device
are not working.
Really?
The power unit and communication unit of
the spaceship are also broken.
Shut up.
How many more days are you going to waste
on that toy?
If it's broken, just throw it away.
Throwing it away? Do you know how
expensive this is?
How expensive could it be? I'll buy ten
when I get my paycheck.
Boss, are you actually going to pay me?
Yeah.
I wasn't going to pay you a dime
until you paid off your debt.
But you look a bit pathetic… No, wait.
I'm not a heartless boss.
I'll give you half your pay.
Really?
Yeah.
Thanks, Boss!
Go clean up.
Boss, are you gonna pay me, too?
You'll get paid. Now go buy yourself some
clothes.
That's a top notch pilot suit!
Not dull clothes.
Wooju, what is this bread?
Prince, it's a Kauncilion!
That's right! A Kauncilion.
Kauncilion? What's that?
It's the name of our home planet.
My dad always called it 'Star Bread'.
Wait, you mean… your dad made this bread?
Yeah.
People from my place would recognize this
bread by its shape.
Wait, your dad must be from my home town?
Yeah, your dad is from our home.
Why do you think my dad is from your home?
Because…
I know your father very well.
You're such a liar. Do you really think
I'll fall for that again?
Don't you dare start with that 'Prince
from another planet' nonsense again.
I don't believe you!
Wooju… be polite to the Prince.
Hachi.
I'd like one signature Moon Bread.
Card, please.
Sure. Enjoy.
Thanks for your hard work.
Welcome!
Can I have one Star Bread and one Moon
Bread?
Enjoy.
Raon.
Yeah?
Have you really seen that bread before?
Yeah, I ate it all the time back home.
Are you and my dad… really from the same
place?
Didn't I tell you?
We're from the same place, that's how I
know him.
I still don't believe you.
You'll believe me eventually.
Everyone, listen up!
We have Star Bread here.
It's the best bread in the universe.
Made by the greatest baker in the
universe.
Many lovely people live here.
Friends, family, and lovers.
And companions.
The taste of this Star Bread…
is the sweetness of love.
And what about the taste of the sun?
It's the warmth of comfort.
And the taste of the moon?
It's the soft, warm feeling of happiness.
Dad…
What are you looking at?
The stars…
Stars?
My parents… they must be somewhere
out there in that starry sky.
No.
Huh?
They're right here.
In this home.
In this room.
Even under the covers.
They're right by your side.
And in every loaf of bread.
They're always watching over you.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Are you…
Are you leaving?