Where's Zhang Xiaobei?
What did you do to Zhang Xiaobei?
Really.
We really switched.
What did you do to Zhang Xiaobei?
His mom's still waiting for him at the hospital.
My mom...
Where'd you hide Zhang Xiaobei?
Zhang Xiaobei!
He called me Zhang Xiaobei.
Does Sheng Yuanzhou still have his memories?
Who exactly is it?
Sheng Yuanzhou, you dare show up?
My mom had a heart attack because of you!
If any harm comes to her,
I won't let you get away with it!
Looks like...
his mind's been replaced with
my original memories.
Just now was probably
an unconscious reaction to the recent switch.
I'm here to
pay for your mom's medical bills.
Tell me.
How much do you need?
Sheng Yuanzhou, what are you doing here?
Bullying our Xiaobei...
How far are you going to take it?
You already got my daughter killed!
Now you won't even spare my only son?
Ma'am, I... I'm here to...
I'm here to pay your medical bills.
And... and the surgery fees.
We don't want your money!
I'm begging you...
Please leave my son alone.
Mom!
Weren't you two good friends in school?
How did it end up like this?
Why did you steal what's his?
Why would you hurt him, too?
Mom, Mom!
Do you even know
he just passed out at the intersection?
He looked so pitiful.
Mom!
If anything happens to him,
how am I supposed to live?
Mom!
Doctor!
Doctor, hurry! Doctor!
Mom!
Doctor, hurry, hurry!
Hurry!
Mom, hang in there! Mom!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Here!
That 100,000 is my mom's life-saving money!
Please give it back to me, okay?
I'm begging you!
Please give it back!
So this is the power of money.
It can save lives... and change fate.
Mr. Sheng.
I've paid the surgery and hospital fees in full.
I also left your card number on file.
Any further expenses will be deducted directly.
Thank you.
The Chairman is still waiting for you to return.
You even paid their medical bills?
Call it hush money.
After all, they got a video of me injuring someone.
Give them some money,
so they won't run their mouths.
It's late.
Go get some sleep.
Okay, Dad.
You should get some rest too.
Wait.
Since when did you start
speaking so casually?
Remember.
From now on, call me Father.
She should get better soon.
Yes, Father.
So there really is
a Key of Fate that can swap lives.
Even though you've chosen to switch,
you still have two more chances to choose.
One month. One year.
If you want to keep the swap,
on the day it expires,
in the home of the person you want to be,
use the Key of Fate
and have one more meal.
Thirty days.
I've got to make the most of these 30 days
to change my family's fate.
Good morning, Young Master.
Morning, morning, morning.
Young Master, today's flowers were airlifted from the UK.
They were delivered directly to our central garden.
If you don't like them,
we'll replace them right away.
Mom.
Has this gone bad?
Gone bad?
No, it hasn't.
It's delicious.
Have some water.
Father, you wanted to see me?
Your performance lately is still just average.
Release the news today.
Father, you mean...
Zhu Zipeng.
A young entrepreneur.
Returned from studying abroad.
With his parents' resources behind him,
he founded Tianpeng Entertainment.
A nepo baby.
He and Sheng Yuanzhou seem quite close.
Come in.
Mr. Sheng, you wanted to see me?
That file on Zhu Zipeng from before...
Where did I put it?
Hasn't it always been in Xiao Tianshi?
Xiao Tianshi, Xiao Tianshi...
Mr. Sheng! Mr. Sheng!
Xiao Tianshi!
Zhu Zipeng, I'll kill you!
Move!
Calm down!
Get out of the way!
Didn't you see that video?
Get off!
This was the Chairman's arrangement.
Have you forgotten?
Must be nice, living it up.
Right now, out there,
Zhang Xiaoyu's death
is being completely blamed on me.
It's all because your secretary was too sexy.
That tiny waist, that little ass...
So much fun.
How are you gonna make it up to me?
Compensation?
What kind of compensation do you want?
How about this.
Why don't you screw my secretary?
But he's a guy.
That's what you're into?
I'm Sheng Yuanzhou.
Let's see who dares make a move.
You should watch who you're talking to.
Watch your mouth.
I'm kidding.
Just kidding.
You'd better make it worth my while.
Did you hear me?
Answer me!
I was wrong.
I heard you.
I was wrong!
Let go, you murderer!