No.
Nothing yet.
Yes, sir, we are looking
everywhere for him.
I'm about to talk with
the lead now, though.
Mm.
God, please…
Please help me.
Please…
Oh!
Please, I'm begging you.
The line.
Come on, baby, come on,
run like the wind, move.
What's going on with the TV?
-What's going around here? Josey!
-Crap!
Hey, look, if we go
to Big George's,
maybe we get that big satellite--
Big George, what?
Big George is a
good 30 miles away.
And cut it with that.
Besides, does Big
George serve you
a very special
Montecassino Birra?
-No, uh--
-Does Big George serve
the best damn hot
wings in the county?
Well, I do love
those damn wings.
Yes, you do.
The internet will go back.
It always does. Relax.
Okay, so the vehicle moves
from rest at the speed
of 25 meters per second.
You gotta be kidding me.
Come on, man, stock the shelves
and get your head
outta that thing.
How many times I gotta tell you?
And Chase, this is your job.
This is my job.
What good does an education do
if you just work a deadbeat…
job?
It's great.
It makes sense.
Be good.
We're outta Red Bull again.
I'm sorry, my dad
forgot to order it.
It won't be here
until next week.
Alright.
You mixed your vectors up here.
What?
That it should go right there.
You're right.
Yeah.
Cheeky, is your
internet working?
Yeah. Why?
The game just went out. It's a mess.
They're gonna slit my throat.
Hey.
Um, I'll figure it out.
I don't know. Gotta go.
Kenny says we jump in the truck,
and we have to go all the way down.
What is it, 30 miles?
I feel like it's a "Poltergeist".
It's gonna run
out of the TV and
hit me in the head
I'm just sayin' bud.
Gotta watch this. I got
a football game here.
I gotta still settle
up and all that…
Hey, calm down, this
round's on the house.
-Alright.
-Well, that changes things.
Two yards shy…
We got the big one, we got it.
And Stuart will throw.
You fixed it?
Was that you?
I…
yeah.
Well, you saved my ass.
The least I can do
is buy you a drink.
-What's your poison?
-I gotta get back.
Come on, everyone loves
alcohol and football.
This round here.
Okay, I know we don't
follow their rules,
but as a fellow
alien in this town,
I deserve to know your mission.
I got my own secrets.
Let's negotiate.
Where are you from?
Ay, you come by
every other Sunday,
if not for the game,
then what, confession?
What, are you
keeping tabs on me?
Not much happening around here.
Look, I live out of town a ways.
I gotta come in once in a
while for these supplies.
Okay.
That's…
Maybe next time?
Drinks on me.
Toilet paper?
Really?
Jesus Christ.
And we have scanned
Europe, Asia…
Asia!
Jack didn't go to Asia.
You barely get him to
come into the office
when I used to work with him.
Look, we've talked about this.
The reason his passport's
being flagged is he wants you
to think he's left the country.
Probably gave it to somebody
to transit internationally.
Here he's tapped into the
Customs Department network.
So you think he's
here in the States?
It's not where I'd hide.
But Jack, he's not really
the exotic type, is he?
He's more of a Red Bull,
dirt bike, paranoid
prepper type.
Hey, put your satellites
on the Southeast, okay?
And I mean, deep in the bayou,
one of those shit dirt
towns where nobody visits
and everybody minds
their own business.
You'll find him.
Belcor is fixated
on his golden boy.
He wants him back and quick.
It doesn't matter.
I'm heading the
program up now, Marcus.
That's…
-that's not what I hear.
-Hmm.
Belcor made a deal with
our Italian friends,
promised them a working
design six months ago.
I'll find him.
You'll find him?
Not if he finds you first.
Good.
Yeah.
Rook…
to A5.
Goddammit.
Okay.
Anything?
Satellites came up empty.
So Ranish is full of it.
Maybe not.
Someone ordered an Nvidia
A100 graphics card.
Six months ago, one was
shipped to a PO Box,
Memphis, Tennessee.
Name on it. Get this…
Guy Smith.
Get me locations on any
towns in that region,
every asset, every eye
in the sky in this…
And get me on the next flight!
Alright. Alright.
Excuse me.
Need help?
Oh.
I'm not from around here.
Yeah.
Yeah, I figured.
You figured what exactly?
Well, nobody from around here
rocks clothes like that, so.
The sharp eye.
No, I'm just um…
passing through.
Looking for a place to stay.
You know any good places?
There's just one.
There's a bed and
breakfast down the street.
Josey and her family run it.
Josey runs the Rocking Horse.
Bed and breakfast.
-Yeah.
-Down the street.
Yeah.
I'll get you on the next one.
Okay, we're ready.
Welcome to the Land
of Hospitality.
I am Josefina, everybody
calls me Josey.
And this is your temporary home.
It's our little slice of
Latino flavor in town.
Your room is up the stairs.
Are you okay, are you
looking for anything?
Can I help you with
something or…?
All good?
-Okay.
Here's your room.
Be my guest.
How long are you staying?
I'll let you know.
What?
You need anything, let me know.
What's all this?
Oh…
they're drones.
What do you need that for?
Getting recordings of the
tree growth in the area.
I'm with the
Department of Interior.
I got my ID right here.
Your trees are full of disease.
Yeah, the feds are going
all high tech, huh?
You could say
something like that.
We've been begging
for a bigger budget.
Begging.
And look at all the little
toys you got over here.
Ah, I feel you, sheriff. I do.
We are understaffed and
overworked all the same.
I can't remember the last
time I had a day off.
Can you?
I remember.
How much help you got out here?
If you need anything,
you give us a call.
You have a nice day.
Let's go.
Okay, I need a second opin…
Here you go.
Hot and fresh
-for my little nerd.
-Thank you.
You have to feed the brain too.
Oye.
It's so good.
That weirdo with the egg, I
saw him come through here.
-He came here.
-Yeah.
-What's up?
He didn't even pay.
-He just left.
-Excuse me.
He's trouble.
Trouble? He's an asshole, is what he is.
I don't understand you.
-Okay.
-I don't understand.
Literally, he shut
the door on my face.
He shut the door on your face?
In my…
He went like this, you know
what I'm talking about.
-Oh yeah.
-He was just rude.
He was disrespectful.
Was he mean to you?
-How was he?
-No, he was just,
he was acting really weird.
Creepy is what he is.
-He is creepy.
-God! Yeah, I don't like him.
How are things back there?
What's going on?
If I get that scholarship, I'm gone.
Not looking back.
Thank you for the food.
-Hey, you guys.
-Are you serious?
Jesus Christ.
Gotta calculate, huh?
You scared the crap outta me.
Yeah, it's… This stuff is hard.
Yeah.
You need some help?
Now you gotta take that number.
Break it down. Split it up.
No, split. Yeah, split that.
-Like this.
-There you go.
Oh.
Look at the big brain on you.
Alright. It's just step by step.
So what's new?
Anything ever go
on in this town?
Actually, this asshole came in
looking for a place to stay.
Had beady eyes,
looked kind of creepy.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
It was probably just a tourist.
Tourists never
just show up here.
Well, maybe it was an illegal
in search of the American dream.
Either way, it's probably best to
trust your instincts.
You let me know if
you need any help.
I will.
Thank you for the help.
The man who was just in here,
do you know him?
-Who?
-Boy, what are you, a fucking owl?
That guy with, uh, a beard.
Beards are kind of in
fashion these days.
Don't…
I just saw him leave.
A lot of people come in here.
So a lot of people come in here.
Now…
you seem like a smart kid.
Stop fucking around.
I am pretty smart.
I got a 1580 on that SAT, so--
Talk.
Uh…
Okay, okay.
There's a guy that
comes in here sometimes.
He buys supplies.
He lives somewhere off the grid.
That's all I know. Okay?
Okay!
If I find out
you know more,
I'll be back.
And next time,
well…
you know what happens
if I come back.
You're a smart kid.
You got 1580 on your SAT.
Chase.
Delivery guy out back. Give me a hand.
Anything else I can
help you with, sir?
Bobby , you're finally back.
Oh my God, where
were you? Please.
Marcus, I picked up a highly
active wireless signal
coming from an area near you
that has been uninhabitable
for the last 20 years.
I attached the location.
Alright, fellas.
Target's supposed to be
brought back alive, okay?
Alive!
Rock salt only.
So we're going after
some Oppenheimer wannabe?
Just focus.
Hey Marcus.
He's eight miles
south of Marker 52.
How'd you find him?
These are the best guys you got?
These are the best
guys I could get
in short notice, Marcus.
I got two more guys
blocking the street.
Alright, guys, let's go.
Come on, let's go.
Load it up.
Excuse me, sir, but someone
has bypassed the firewall
and accessed the
employee tracker.
How do you know?
Because there's multiple logins
from a former employee account.
We're on it. I'll keep you updated.
Yeah, sure.
Have security
confiscate every phone,
every fucking computer.
We've been hacked.
I'll get on it right away, sir.
Also, Ranish is waiting
outside for you.
Have him waiting.
Shit!
Why is this happening to me?
Now.
Alright, look out, here we go.
Move forward. Forward now.
I see you.
Oh, shit.
What the hell? These lights.
Why are these here?
What the fuck?
Don't touch me!
Move it. Get through.
Go, go, go!
Marcus. Come on, let's go.
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit!
Landmine.
Come on, toss it.
Toss me the weapon.
Smoke grenade.
Smoke grenade. Smoke him out.
Do it!
Throw in the fucking smoke.
Holy shit!
Hold your breath!
Up, on your feet!
Let's go! Come on!
On your feet! Let's go!
We don't leave until we get him!
Fuck you! You go in
there and get him!
I told you, you're
not leaving here.
We're hired help.
You're on your own now.
Yeah, yeah. I get it.
I just want some good
news for a change.
He knew we were coming.
He wiped out the entire team.
That's not fucking good news.
Get Ranish in here.
Yes, sir.
Hey. Hey, that's him, right?
That's him!
Go, go, go! Let's go!
Sorry. I was
across the street.
What's so urgent?
Come in, close the door.
First of all, we've been hacked.
All the information's
leaked out.
And I don't fucking
care, we might be bugged.
People might hear
what we're saying.
And your friend Jack,
he's been located…
Let me guess, some
forgotten town
in the southeastern part
of the United States.
I always liked you because
you're fucking smart.
-Sit down.
-Thanks.
So, now…
you're smart, so you think,
would it be a possibility
to end this project by yourself?
I'll get you any help you need.
I mean, but do you
really need Jack?
He would be helpful,
but I taught him most
of what he knows.
Best student I ever had,
figure out and solve
solutions in time
that it'd take most
scientists a decade.
Yeah.
And you think it's
smart stealing research,
research that I
paid millions for.
We always knew he
was a wild card.
He was brought in here
because everyone believed
he could finish this.
Now, it's not my fault
that somebody disclosed your
intention was to weaponize it.
Marcus and his team,
they found him.
Marcus is in the Southeast?
Yep.
He'll come home in a body bag.
Let me go! Let me go!
-What are you doing?
-They found me.
Who found you? What?
The asshole tourist guy?
Yeah.
Look, he works for
my former employer.
What do they want?
It's a long story. Listen.
Have you seen any other
guys like him around here?
No. No, I don't think so.
Well, they're coming.
-Who's coming?
-I gotta go.
Who's coming?
Wait, hold on.
Wait, where are you gonna go?
I'll figure it out.
Wait, hold on, I got
a place you can hide.
It's this war bunker thing.
They used it to hide
weapons from the north
after the end of the war.
-I can show you where it is.
-Well…
does anybody else
know about this place?
No, I don't think so.
It's pretty impossible to find.
I can show you where it is.
-I can go with you.
-No, no. You stay put
and you stay right here.
Do you understand me?
Do not follow me.
These people are extremely dangerous.
Hey.
You're a good kid, Chase.
Stick to your books, alright?
Wait!
I got you.
Come on, come on, come on.
My beer, Amelia.
Quick, quick, quick.
Here you go.
Oh my God, let me take
this out of your way.
Marquito, clean this up.
So sorry for the delay,
your pizza's gonna be right here.
Hey.
-Hey.
I just wanted to tell
you that I'm leaving.
-Leaving. Why?
-Yeah, look, I need you…
It doesn't matter. Okay?
I just need you to keep
looking after Chase.
He's a good kid.
He's got huge potential.
And I just need you to
know that I really wanted
to have that beer with
you and watch the game
and just been able
to sit here with you.
-I keep--
-What is that?
Down there?
-Yeah.
-No.
-Listen to me, I'm not doing it.
Don't even debate me.
-No, I'm not--
-You're going.
I need somebody who
knows how he thinks
and how he maneuvers out there.
You know I hate the South.
I'm not going down to
those mosquito-infested…
-old country.
-Yes, you are!
And you're going to
get my best strike team
to do all the heavy lifting.
All you gotta do is to
lead them to the target.
I apologize, I don't chase people
around in backcountry woods.
-And I'm not gonna go down--
-Hey! I paid you a fucking fortune!
Now it's time for payback.
You get out there
and you get him
and you bring him back to me.
Okay?
Go run to my house,
and get my bag packed.
No need.
The bag is packed.
You're leaving right now.
Break a leg, pal.
I don't need you here.
Marcus.
I thought you'd be dead by now.
Just tell me all the
ways it went wrong.
It was an ambush.
Whole team was taken
out by booby traps.
How was it an ambush if
you were going after him?
This, this is your mess now.
I'm just working cleanup.
-What's your plan?
-Oh no. No, this is our mess.
And it's very simple.
We're gonna go to his place.
We're gonna salvage
all of his research.
We're gonna find it and
bring him back to Belcor.
Simple as that.
-Just the two of us?
-No.
Belcor has lost complete
confidence in you.
No, he sent in the private team.
They'll be here in two hours.
Look on the bright side,
they're gonna have another
shot at the golden boy.
Hey!
How's the scouting going?
You getting your shots, Spielberg?
It's great, Sheriff.
Who's your new sidekick, director?
I had to call in some extra hands.
-What'd you say?
-Some extra hands.
You're very lucky to have him, sir.
He's a uh…
He's a real auteur,
real Robert Bresson.
Huh, outstanding.
Y'all need anything,
I'll be right here.
Have a nice night.
You do the same, Sheriff.
Hey, hey.
How many more people
coming to my town?
Just be a few of us, Sheriff.
You have really
fucked this up, huh?
Don't worry about it.
The whole town has
that deaf bastard,
and a deputy looks like
he's 18 looking after it.
I'm not staying there.
Oh.
Stay in your car then.
No! Let go!
Chase, what the fuck
are you doing here?
-What the fuck are you doing here?
-I knew you'd found it.
I told you…
-not to follow me.
-I know what you said.
-Did anybody see you come up here?
-No!
-Nobody followed me. I made sure.
-Goddammit.
I brought you your supplies
from the store,
the stuff you usually get.
Oh my God, you gotta stop
sneaking up on me like that.
Jesus!
Thank you for the supplies.
Yeah, of course.
What?
This reminds me of home.
Your mom made you eat this shit?
Yeah.
How many are there?
Maybe a dozen.
Give or take.
Drones?
Yeah, I've seen a
few buzzing around.
Why are they looking for you?
Well…
cold fusion.
Yeah. Cold fusion.
I was building a
mini-reactor prototype.
Small enough to fit in
the palm of your hand.
Could hold a charge
for 20 years.
Okay.
What happened?
I didn't finish it.
Why not?
You could have unlimited energy.
-That would change everything.
-Yeah, well, that was the idea.
But they wanted to weaponize it.
A tweak here, a little
adjustment there and…
So I took my research and I…
I disappeared.
What's next?
I think it's time
to disappear again.
Maybe it's time to stop running
and stick it to these creeps.
I mean, you're way
smarter than them.
Chase, I think it's
time for you to go.
Get back before they
realize you're gone.
These guys are dangerous.
I don't think you know
what you're doing here.
Yeah. Okay.
I'd talk to the
sheriff if I were you.
-What?
-Talk to the Sheriff.
Sheriff. Yeah, okay.
Thank you for the stew.
Yeah, of course.
Okay.
Make sure every vehicle's
been tagged with a tag.
Copy that.
You should be able to pull it up.
Couldn't just disappear
to the south of France
or vanish to the Amalfi Coast. Right?
He had to come to this shithole.
If you're finished,
Mia's got a pin
on the motorcycle.
Really?
Pull it up.
That's…
He should be right here.
Okay. Let's pay him a visit.
Don't bother.
It's a damn kid.
Facial recognition.
Nice, Jack.
You don't belong here.
Ow. Fuck!
Oh, shit.
It's wired to blow.
Alright, let's go.
No!
Set the charge.
Oh, fuck.
This is the A team?
Blow it, please.
Grab everything.
Notebooks, drives,
anything that might contain
research is potential.
Holy shit, Jack.
What a shithole.
You gave up 50 billion for this.
Oh God, no, no, no!
Get him off!
Goddammit.
He wired this table.
Probably half this
room is armed.
Keep looking.
Don't touch anything
unless I say it's okay.
Let's go, let's go. Pack it up.
Rotate the men
guarding the highway.
Keep sending out
patrols, alright?
I want every vehicle in
this shithole tagged,
-every exit covered.
-Got it.
Marcus, see if Mia's
got anything for you.
I'll see you down here
in 30, 30 minutes.
Hey, is…
Hey, what's wrong, Cheeky?
They're after me.
I don't have time. Okay?
-What? Who?
-Wait!
Welcome in.
What can we get you?
How about a Maker?
Yeah.
What's your name?
Josefina. Josey.
Josey.
Thanks.
This is a sweet little
place you have here, Josey.
Thank you.
I couldn't do it.
The whole organization,
upkeep, cleaning, sweeping.
There's amazing
history about brooms.
Broomsticks's been around
since thousands of years.
First the Greeks,
then the Egyptians.
Medieval Europeans,
they standardized it.
But it was the Shakers,
in the 1800s, that
really changed the game.
Gave it that long, flat profile
that you're using there today.
Wow.
Not much on history.
No?
It is.
History tells us everything we
wanna know about the future.
Believe it or not,
that broomstick,
like all things,
it has a historical evolution.
Do you know, with time, true
story, people figured out a way
to use that cleaning
device there as a weapon?
That broom has been used
for horrible things,
unspeakable humiliations.
It'll make your skin crawl.
Documented cases of people
being physically assaulted
and penetrated over
and over again.
Now, where's the young
man I saw come in here?
-Look--
-Where is he!
Hey, Josey. What is on the TV?
We got a game going on.
-The game's on, right?
-Two draughts, right?
I'll fix it. We'll fix it.
Give me the remote, please, Maya.
Yes.
Alright.
Hey, thank you for the drink.
Ay.
-You alright, Josey?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah…
-Chase, stop, tell me what's going on!
-I don't have time. I'm sorry.
You got a rock-hard pillow
in that shitty B and B.
And bugs, ticks,
bloodsucking ticks.
I need to get home, Marcus,
and you're not helping me.
Oh, this is your show, Ranish.
Remember?
And what we have is a signal.
We know that he is
within two miles of us.
How do we know that?
Because we have a tag
and a mark on every
signal in the area.
-He moves, we'll know.
-Okay.
And this auxiliary team,
they got all these
exit points closed off?
Every exit out of this filthy,
fucking shithole
has been covered.
How do they say here?
The noose is tight.
We found something.
Clear the door.
Go ahead.
Tim.
Open it.
On you.
Go.
This fucking…
Jesus Christ.
Open it.
Don't waste your time.
He didn't leave behind
anything that matters.
How do you know that?
Because he's watching us.
Mia, you said you
had a signal earlier.
Can you jam it?
-Of course I can.
-No.
Jam the signal, he gets spooked.
We should be so
lucky, sweetheart.
Just give me a few minutes.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Come on.
Over here.
Up the fucking hill!
-Ha! up top!
-Yeah, okay.
Okay.
It's him.
He's here.
Fuck!
Over here!
Get him!
Wait! Pau, stop!
Smile, Marcus.
Pau, keep the guys up top.
Follow the stream down.
Got it.
Let's go.
I've got something
that'll flush him out.
Back to the van now!
Oh, fuck.
Oh!
No more running.
Now, I told you I'd be back.
What do you want?
Little shit!
Leave me alone!
Why are you chasing me?
You fuck! Let go!
-I got it.
-Move!
Look out.
Go around!
Yeah. On it, on it.
Shit.
I'm sorry, Sarah. I'm sorry.
Little shit!
Shit.
I'm okay.
-Nowhere to go, kid.
-Holy shit!
Shit!
Stop!
Pau, grab him!
Shit! Let me go!
-What did I do?
-Get him, get him! Okay, get him!
-Hey, what…
-I'm sorry.
-Hey, what's going?
-Please help! Please!
Grab him!
-What?
-Move!
Oh, God.
Freaking kid.
What?
Piece of shit!
Darn it!
Hey!
-You…
-I said I'm on it.
I just want to talk.
Oh, no, you don't.
No, you don't! Get away from me!
I don't know anything.
Let me go!
It's me, it's me!
Sheriff!
Now go! Get out, get out!
Hey, please stop! Freeze!
Shoot him.
Oh my God! Put the gun down!
Please!
Oh my God!
Shit!
-No, no, no!
-I got you!
Oh my God.
Shit.
Oh, fuck.
No.
Ow!
-Hey! I'm not going anywhere!
-Shut up.
Hurry the fuck up.
Hi, you've reached
Sheriff Pancho.
Leave me your name, number,
and I'll get right back to you.
Sheriff, it's Josey.
I need your help.
-They have Chase.
-I know.
What the hell is going on, Guy?
Don't bullshit me!
It's not good.
What?
I was gonna take these
motherfuckers out one by one,
Who are you?
-Enough with the mystery.
-Lucky them, their plans have changed.
They got Chase, so…
I need your help.
-Anything.
-Okay.
I need you to distract 'em
and take 'em over to the
Harrisburg Monastery.
Okay, I'll do it.
Josey?
No.
-Okay, I'm ready to talk.
-No, no, no, no.
I want you out of here.
I'll tell you where he is.
Josey.
My favorite history student.
And yet, if I'm being honest,
I think you're lying.
I'm telling the truth,
but I'm a businesswoman.
I'll send you his way
in exchange for the kid.
Oh boy.
Why don't you tell
us where he is?
Quick.
He's…
He's at the abandoned
Harrisburg Monastery.
And where might we find that?
Please just give me the kid.
10 miles north,
-outside of town.
-Right.
Okay, okay, okay. Okay.
Okay.
He's got a terrible
temper. I apologize.
What about the kid?
I'll tell you what.
You keep this between us,
you and that boy
will not end up dead
back in that lovely
little bar of yours.
Scout's honor.
Which should be burned
to the ground, so.
Seven of my men are dead.
What the hell is going on?
He's still alive, right?
He is.
-And if you'll just let me explain.
-No, I don't want to hear you
explaining ever again.
You're not hearing me, Ranish.
Do you understand that we
are running out of time?
And when I say we, I mean you.
Well, he's proven to be more resourceful
than we anticipated.
But we believe that with
a little bit of time,
-if you--
-Don't you talk to me
like a fucking politician!
I need him back here now!
Fucking now!
Mia, all set?
Make sure we got the shells.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, guys, let's go.
That seemed pleasant.
Let's just get home.
Wait, wait. Hold on, guys.
I'm losing signal.
Shit!
Where's he at!
Get down! No!
Where the fuck is he?
Come on, get him.
Are you shitting me?
He's shooting fucking arrows!
Split up.
Stop.
Goddammit.
Jesus. What the…?
Where the fuck are you?
Hey, there he is.
Why are you stopping?
Fucking move!
Shh!
Ranish, do you copy me?
Does anyone read me?
Sit the fuck down!
Clear.
Jack, just listen to me.
You know what they want.
They're prepared to
give you everything.
-Money, power, all of it.
-It's not a weapon.
Then come home and have
that conversation with them.
Just leave me the fuck alone.
But that's not what you
wanted 19 years ago, right,
when you were starting
out and you had nothing?
Am I not the one
that got you started?
And Jack, you like
game theory, right?
Play this out for me.
You got a half dozen
men dead in the woods.
Jack, this has
gotta be dealt with.
I never wanted to kill anybody.
I know that.
Come home, let Belcor help you.
I can have you back in
the city in six hours.
I'll help you.
I don't want your help.
They're gonna kill me, Jack.
No!
Stop!
Jack…
Don't feel so smart
now, do you, Guy?
Chase.
Fuck!
Fuck.
I never pulled a trigger, Jack.
I swear to God I'll put
a bullet in his head.
I'm so sorry.
-Wait, no, no. It's okay.
-I'm sorry.
Ranish, let him go.
This is not the kid's fight.
Is this a fight?
Christ!
I just want you to come home
and finish what you started!
Okay.
I'll give you everything.
-No!
-Wait! Wait!
-Hold on, Chase!
-No, you can't do that!
-You can't do that!
-Settle the fuck down!
I will give you everything.
I got full-scale
program completion.
It's sealed, but
it is completed.
I got multiple AutoCADs.
I got BIM, I got geographics.
I got everything
that Belcor needs.
I'm out of time, Jack.
I just need you to
tell me where it's at.
-No, please--
-Where is it!
You want the program?
You give me the kid.
I hate it down here.
And I blame you for it.
You didn't have to make these
last few days so unpleasant.
It's all inevitable, Jack.
Nobody hides from Belcor.
Did he tell you to say that?
I can't really blame the guy.
Expect him to let you disappear
with 15 years of technology,
is that what you thought?
I thought we wanted
the same thing, Ranish.
You sold your soul.
What's that taste like, huh?
Shit?
Always so self-righteous.
Everybody on the team, though,
is well paid, well compensated
and rewarded for our
work, including you.
Our work?
They wouldn't let you
run the HR department
if it weren't for me, Ranish.
None of this matters anymore.
We're gonna take you back
and you're gonna do
the work that's needed,
and then you can go disappear
in some other insect-filled cesspit
in the other end of the world.
Hey, you might want
to take the back road.
-What?
-The back road.
-Hey, sit down!
-Get off me, get off me!
Take the back road.
-Turn left! Turn left!
-Jack! Jack!
-You're gonna hit the fucking mine!
-Sit down, Jack!
-You're gonna miss the landmine.
-Jack, sit down!
Do you wanna hit the landmine?
Oh, goddammit!
Idiot!
What are you doing?
Jesus Christ!
What the fuck are you thinking?
-Dammit!
-Oh my God!
Chase, grab it!
Fuck!
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, this way.
This way, this way.
Come on.
-Come on. Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Come on.
Let's go.
This way.
Where are we going?
Hey…
There's only one
way out of this.
Hey.
It's time for you to go.
What are you talking about?
Look, wherever I go,
they're gonna follow me.
Alright? You gotta go.
You gotta go.
Alright? Come on.
Go.
Come on.
Go. Hey
Thank you.
Go!
Shit.
-No, put it down.
-Fuck him!
Put the gun down!
Put it down!
Seriously?
What the fuck are
you doing, Jack?
Where are you going?
Belcor will never
stop coming for you!
Yeah, you're right.
This has gotta end.
Right now.
Right here.
No. Oh, no.
No!
Hey! Don't shoot!
Goddammit!
Are you kidding me?
Shit!
Jack! Jack, get…
Get outta the fucking truck!
Get the fuck out of the truck!
Get the fuck out!
Get out!
Get your hands off me!
I wanna talk to Belcor!
Hey!
God.
So alone.
He's dead?
No, no. Belcor…
listen.
Listen to me, we don't need him.
Wow, great news.
So now you can do
it all by yourself?
-I can do this!
-That's fantastic.
I swear to God I can do this!
Well, I'm a generous man.
I'm gonna let you.
You're going to stay down there
until my project is completed.
No.
-Yeah.
-No.
Now, get to work.
No, no!
You're alive you…
you son of a bitch.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Hey! Hey! He's alive!
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
He's alive!
Hey, open this!
Belcor!
Look at you.
-You look cool.
-Yeah, it's the…
-it's the mustache.
-Yeah.
I can't believe I'm here now.
Yeah, I wasn't sure
I'd ever see you again.
Okay, I'm here.
Are you gonna tell me
how you got out of there?
Well, there was an old truck
that sat outside my place.
I built an escape
hatch under the truck.
Grade 10 low-alloy
reinforced steel.
Shockwaves spread
laterally. Right?
Explosions move outward, not downward.
-You got it.
-Wow!
You're here to give
me your research. Huh?
Yeah. When you're ready,
-we can talk about that.
-When I'm ready.
-Oh, hey.
-Alright. When I'm ready.
Somebody wants to say hi.
-Oh my God!
-Cheeky!
What are you doing here?
I'm with him.
USC! I'm so proud of you!
Time to make your
dreams come true.
-Here are some tacos al pastor too.
-Thank you.
-Alright, we should go.
-Where are you guys going?
We'll be around.
Oh, and that's for you.
So long!
Show a little mercy
Mother needs to keep me alive
Watch me disappear where nobody goes
I ain't never gonna sell my soul
Run wild, run wild
-Run wild, run wild
-Ain't never gonna sell my soul
-I ain't never gonna sell my soul