Yes, Mr. Lee.
Hey, Ji-eun.
Come to Gangnam Palace now.
Important investors will be here tonight.
They want to see you
after hearing about you.
Are you crazy?
Yes, I'm crazy.
Thinking about you
going to Lee Sumin's drinking party,
I just want to
keep you by my side forever.
[In the practice room at night]
[Training by Lee Sumin]
Wrong.
Yes, yes.
Yes, this part. This part.
Don't do this.
Bend your arms. Like this.
Not like this.
Bend your arms more, and do this.
Yes.
Ji-eun.
Shall we try this part together?
Yes, thank you, Mr. Lee.
OK.
Your right foot first.
When you do this, move forward a bit more.
Yes.
That's good.
Yes, this part.
Shall we do the demonstration together?
Yes, sounds good.
Thank you, Mr. Lee.
OK.
Mr. Lee.
Yeah?
Ji-eun's basic skills are not solid,
so she can't match the rhythm.
I'm just going through
the choreography with her.
Why are you so worked up?
Because she's my group member.
If you want a demonstration, I'll do it.
Mr. Lee, Yebin-unnie.
It's all for the choreography after all.
Ji-eun is still working on the basics.
I think it'd be best if you
do the demonstration with our leader
and let Ji-eun watch.
We know how skilled Yebin-unnie is.
Ji-eun.
Let's watch it at the side together.
Sure.
If Yebin wants to do it.
Let's start from that part.
Yes.
OK.
1, 2, 3, 4.
2, 3, 4.
Again.
OK.
But your arm movements...
should be faster.
Stop it.
Don't move.
If you don't relieve the tension,
your muscles will get stiff.
Whether it hurts or not,
it's none of your business.
What do you want from me?
Why are you so bossy with me?
Who I meet, what I eat,
and even what I practice.
What am I to you?
I'm in charge of you.
Your gaze,
your time, and your energy
are all for me
and no one else.
Absolutely not.
Kang Yebin.
What happened to you?
Kang Yebin!
There's nothing between us right now,
understand?
Why do you still want to control me?
Let go of me!
Today,
let's call it a day.
Unnie, here.
As always, I got the last salad today.
By the way, where is Ji-eun?
Aren't you two always together lately?
Where's Ji-eun?
Oh, she went to the bathroom.
Let's eat first.
You know,
Ji-eun has been working so hard lately.
She practices all night
and eats so little.
I wonder if she can hold on.
Mm!
I'm going to see Ji-eun.
Huh?
Yebin.
Aren't you eating?
Is this all you eat?
Yes.
Where's the lunch I gave you?
In my bag.
I'm going to...
to have it for dinner.
Get up.
Don't eat instant noodles.
It's bad for your health.
But I think
instant noodles are better.
No buts.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
To eat.
Wait for me here.
I'll cook for you.
Eat first.
Bin.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry I made you worry.
I didn't scold you
because you ate instant noodles.
I'm just angry because
you don't seem to take care of yourself.
From now on,
tell me when you crave something.
I'll cook all of it for you.
Cheers.
Do you know why I learned to cook?
In high school,
you always prepared my lunch for me.
When I was a trainee,
I was always hungry and stressed
with all the dieting.
At that time, I kept thinking
that if you were by my side,
I probably wouldn't
be so hungry.
That's when I started learning to cook.
I only knew how to cook congee at first.
Now I can cook a lot of dishes.
Now, I finally
get to cook for you.
It wasn't a dream.
It really wasn't.
All these years,
I've sent you many things.
I sent you daily necessities
and a lot of food,
but they were all returned,
stating the recipient
is not at this address.
You were there the whole time,
but I couldn't reach you at all.
Ji-eun.
You finally came back to me.
When you were away,
I always spent my birthday alone.
Happy birthday to me.
You might not like this,
but this pie is my absolute favorite.
So I brought it to share with you.
Here.
Happy birthday,
Kang Yebin.
Jung Ji-eun.
Actually,
when you were away,
I always spent my birthday alone.
I'm sorry, Ji-eun.
I won't let you get hurt again.
[Mr. Lee]
Lee Sumin?
Are you two in touch?
Why do you contact him?
Give me back my phone!
Answer me!
You're not answering?
Then I'll have to make you mine.
[Mr. Lee]
Hey, Ji-eun.
Come to Gangnam Palace now.
Important investors will be here tonight.
They want to see you
after hearing about you.
Hello, Mr. Lee.
This is Yebin,
Kang Yebin.
Yebin.
This is about work.
The investors said...
She can't go today because of practice.
I understand the company's difficulties,
but she's not ready
for a private party yet.
Also, if you need anything,
call her during work hours.
Also, if negotiations with the investors
aren't going well,
I can connect you to my dad.
Gosh, Kang Yebin.
You sure have a perfect personality.
A perfect artist who is extremely logical.
It's pointless to
lock horns with Kang Yebin.
The agency can't handle the consequences.
I guess I'll have to try Song Minah.
Only look at me.
Only think about me.
Are you crazy?
Yes.
I'm crazy.
Thinking about you
going to Lee Sumin's drinking party,
I just want to
keep you by my side forever.
Ji-eun.
You can only belong to me.
Ouch.
It hurts!
Here.
It really hurts here too.
Yebin.
You'll only remember it if it hurts.
Remember this.
Do I have to remember it with pain?
Don't you remember?
Three years ago,
when I caught a cold
and was totally out of it,
it was you
who
stayed by my side,
taking care of me
and protecting me.
Between the Yebin
who was by my side all night,
worried about me suffering,
and this Yebin who is
trying to lock me down with pain,
which one is the real you?
Or
have I been wrong about you all along?
No. No!
Both of them are me.
I just
love you so much.
I'm not doing the wrong thing, am I?
No.
This is not love.
Such possessiveness is not love.
What else can I do?
What should I do
to keep you by my side
without hurting you?
Tell me.
Yebin.
Even though I love you,
I can't give up everything of mine.
In my world,
I have friends, family,
and my dream.
But what you want now
is just a shadow who follows you around.
Ji-eun.
The me
when you first fell in love with me?
Ji-eun.
When I think of the days without you,
I can't think straight.
I feel so empty.
It hurts so much that I'm going crazy.
Can't you...
Can't you just love me?
Bin.
Let's take some time apart.
I'm not saying we should break up.
But we...
We can't go on like this.