(Lee Je Hoon)
(Jang Hyuk Jin, Bae Yoo
Ram, Kim Eui Sung, Pyo Ye Jin)
(Taxi Driver 3)
(This drama is a work of fiction)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Children and animals were
filmed under guidelines.)
We're meeting Im Dong
Hyeon today, remember?
Dong Su?
Mind if I ask what this is about?
The reason I started Deluxe
Taxi was all because of Dong Su.
What kind of justice is this?
We still haven't even found his body!
Don't die. Let's get our revenge together.
Since no one believed
Mr. Park Dong Su 15 years ago,
let's do the reverse. What
if we trust him completely?
Im Dong Hyeon who was
released 15 years ago.
Can you find out where he is now?
Sir, you had a phone call earlier.
The name was Park Min Ho.
Park Min Ho. You
buried him for good, right?
You want me to bury you too?
I think I've found the person...
Im Dong Hyeon was with
on that day 15 years ago.
He's Jo Seong Uk.
He had a poor record, but he
became a college coach, which is tough.
And he held that position for a long time.
But doesn't something seem off
with Im Dong Hyeon and Jo Seong Uk?
It's a big match.
Nothing's more important
than that for us, right?
This "something more
important" has to be kept secret.
So Im Dong Hyeon was here five
hours doing online sports betting?
No. Im Dong Hyeon wasn't gambling.
He was fixing matches.
With Jo Seong Uk, who's at the match.
(Taxi Driver 3)
(Episode 7)
(2025 NUVF College Volleyball U-League)
Nice!
- That was a tough one. So close.
- My bad.
- Focus! Stay in sync with the team.
- Yeon Tae.
- Focus.
- Right.
- Darn it.
- All right, focus up.
(2025 NUVF College Volleyball U-League)
It's short! Receiver to the
front. That's it, get in position...
Hey!
- You could've called for it.
- My bad.
It's okay, guys. Take it slow.
Let's catch up point by point.
- Yeon Tae. The receive.
- Got it.
All right, focus.
- Let's go!
- Darn it!
Hey! Focus, will you?
And what was that sign
the coach just gave you?
I've never seen that sign before.
What are you talking about? What sign?
Hey! Stop getting distracted
and focus on your own game.
- Get into your position.
- Yes, Coach.
Let's go!
(Jingwang University)
Hey, Jeong Yeon Tae.
We'll talk later in private.
Hey, Yeon Tae. Come in, have a seat.
What are the other guys up to?
They finished stretching
and are doing their own drills.
By the way, did you hear Ji
Hoon got another scouting offer?
His asking price went up again.
Yes, I heard something
about it from the other guys.
This business is so ruthless.
Others get a "salary" or "pay."
But they call ours "market value."
You know?
Yeon Tae.
I think this world is incredibly unfair.
Nothing else matters.
Perform well, and you're set.
Though we all work just as hard, you know?
Isn't that right?
The next game is critical.
You work hard and trust my
calls, no matter what they are.
You're the ace of our team.
This is your market value, kid.
Kid, you're worth more than Ji Hoon.
But, Coach.
Ji Hoon is suspicious of me right now.
He asked if we were
exchanging our own secret signals.
All right. I'll have a talk with Ji Hoon.
You just focus on the next game.
It's the last game of the season.
- Yes, sir.
- Okay, go on.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- Yeon Tae.
- Yes?
I'm counting on you.
- I'll do my best.
- Okay.
My goodness.
Just stay down.
I'm fine.
Have you seen
his face?
No.
Right.
Ji Hoon.
There's more to being an
athlete than just playing well.
How could you be so
careless during the season?
I'm sorry.
- No, Coach. I'm really fine.
- What do you mean you're fine, kid?
You think I don't know
what you're up against?
Consider it a bonus
from your coach. Take it.
It's fine. Everything will be fine.
So get the treatment you need,
and take your time coming back.
- Got it?
- Yes.
All right, I'm heading out.
Hey, that jerk Ji Hoon is still alive.
All right, that's 20,000
dollars after the hospital bills.
Go on, count it.
- Yes, what is it?
- Hey, Seong Uk.
There's a problem at the gym.
Let's meet up and talk.
(Closed for renovations)
The network line came from the
empty unit on the first basement level.
That's why nothing showed
up on the gym's network.
Why?
To spoof the IP and hide their location.
So, the main server is overseas,
but the encryption is block chain-based.
Which means it can only be
accessed from this computer.
The site itself is a rental.
I heard block chain
encryption is hard to crack.
So how did you break it, Go Eun?
It is hard.
That's why they just
wrote it here at the bottom.
So that's why he offered 20,000
dollars just to rent it for a day.
Look at all these betting categories.
This looks complicated.
Wouldn't it be easier
to rig with fewer options?
The system is simple.
The payout is divided proportionally
among those who guess correctly.
If a lot of people win, the
individual payout is small.
But if only a few people
win, the payout is huge.
That's all there is to it.
Second set, three
consecutive receiving errors.
Third set, three consecutive service aces.
Almost no one would bet
on outcomes like these.
I wouldn't bet on that either.
How could that even happen
unless it was rigged?
Oh, so it's rigged.
Im Dong Hyeon
bet on this and won 500,000 dollars.
In just three hours.
So Im Dong Hyeon tells Jo Seong
Uk which bets have the longest odds,
and Jo Seong Uk makes
them happen during the game.
That's how they've been fixing the matches.
It's 500,000 dollars for 1 fix.
They'll be back to rent the gym soon.
I'll take down the site for now.
No, leave it up.
Leave it up? And let
them keep fixing matches?
Yes.
We need to find Park Min Ho
using that site.
You're saying we can find Park
Min Ho who died 15 years ago
with this site?
Yes.
As long as
we have someone on the inside.
Seong Uk, look, I never intended
to put the gym up as collateral.
Wait. Just hear me out, buddy.
"Buddy?" Don't call me that, you scum.
Don't you know what that gym means to us?
- Why did you do this, you jerk?
- I messed up.
You get that gym back by tomorrow.
Got it?
And to think I called you a friend.
You darn gambling addict.
(Deluxe Taxi)
I don't care how angry he is.
Who beats up their friend like that?
Looks like he could
use a consolation prize.
Why did he throw the money? Darn it.
(Rainbow Taxi)
He used to be so nice back in school.
It's scary how money
changes people. Seriously.
This is nowhere near enough.
What am I supposed to do?
(Funeral Hall)
Thank you. We'll put it to good use.
Mr. Im. You look pretty wasted.
Hey.
Spot me some more.
The sun's about to come
up. You should go home.
Just give it to me!
How about you pay back
what you already owe first?
- I'm a VIP here.
- Sir.
My guys got hurt last time, and
we paid for hefty medical bills.
Can't you see we only tolerate
you because you're a VIP?
Was I the one who hit them?
- Was I?
- What did you just say?
If it's the bills, deal with
me. Why take it out on him?
It's him.
Instead of trying to pay me back,
you're in here gambling again.
And whose fault do you think that is?
Let's play one round.
(Collateral Agreement)
What's wrong? Don't you
want to win your gym back?
There you go.
You can't win if you
don't look at your hand.
Darn it.
A bust.
Take it.
What the? This isn't a
bust. It's a winning hand.
Hey, hold on a second.
You fought hard to win this
from me. Why just give it back?
What, you have a problem
with me giving it to you?
You must have a reason for doing this.
My motto in life is to
keep things interesting.
And being a gym owner
was just not interesting.
I don't think I ever got your name.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Park Min Ho.
Who?
Park Min Ho.
You can just call me Min Ho.
So we're clear. You just
gave this to me for free.
Don't try to take it back later.
Hey, you got it for free.
You owe me a drink, don't you?
Talking about drinking
this early in the morning?
Come on, let's go for Round Two.
- He's not dead!
- That's enough.
Honey.
You can't go into the
crematorium. It's too hot!
Crying like that won't bring him back.
- Stop crying.
- No!
- Let's give him a proper send-off.
- He's not dead!
- Let's go now.
- What do you mean
- he's not dead?
- He's not dead!
Let him go.
- I said he's not dead!
- Like he's coming back.
Park Min Ho. Why a dead
guy's name? What a jinx.
- What's that?
- What is that?
It's a ghost!
- Look!
- A ghost.
- What?
- It's a ghost.
Look at that.
My friend.
Hey, buddy. Time for Round Two, right?
- You can't fall asleep on me now.
- I know, right?
Gosh, my head.
Where am I?
Darn it, what on earth happened?
You drank too much, that's what.
Hey.
How did you get in here?
Why the surprise? You
brought me here, bragging.
I did?
I said the second round was
on me. And you brought us here.
How else would I have gotten in here?
Round Two was on you?
That does sound kind of familiar.
So then I
brought you here?
You even told me the passcode
and asked me to punch it in for you.
Five, three, seven, nine.
Gosh, seriously.
Three consecutive receiving errors.
Great idea.
It's brilliant!
To be honest, I was really
touched by your words.
What did I say?
You said you'd make me rich.
You said I was your
emotional baggage, didn't you?
I did?
My friend, CEO Im!
I always knew you'd be a big shot.
Hey, what do you say we come
up with our own secret handshake?
Could you just pretend
you never saw any of this?
Come on.
I'm not blind.
I saw what I saw. How
can I pretend I didn't?
I've got a killer nose for money.
The smell of us getting rich, CEO Im.
But what is that smell?
You smell that?
That's the smell of us getting rich.
Hey, this is a huge jackpot!
This'll make us rich! You get it?
How we'll grow this and cash in. Let's
meet up later and discuss it, okay?
Wait. We came up
with this handshake, but
how should we finish it?
Got any ideas? I know
it's a bit old-school,
but let's just go with this. Boom!
We do this. Got it? Boom!
We drank too much yesterday.
Right? Go get some hangover food.
Hey, great idea. This mirror.
Excellent. How clever.
Darn it. If Seong Uk finds
out, he's going to kill me.
(14 missed calls from Jo Seong Uk)
Darn it!
You're ignoring my calls?
I got the gym back!
I wasn't avoiding your calls on purpose.
I kind of blacked out.
Hey, Seong Uk.
What do you think about moving
our office somewhere else?
Why? Is something wrong?
No, it's just that the
ventilation isn't great and...
Dong Hyeon.
Stop rambling,
and just focus on checking the list.
You know I'm counting on you, right?
You're good at this.
Gosh, I'm completely swamped here.
Thanks, Seong Uk. Drive safe.
Park Min Ho, that little pest.
Yes.
Prepare a funeral altar for me.
(Closed for renovations)
Eight, one, three, seven, star.
- The passcode has been changed.
- Yes.
When this jerk arrives in five minutes,
make sure he's completely taken
out so he can never come again.
I've turned off all the
cameras, so you're clear. Got it?
The longer the hospital
stay, the higher the price.
Keep that in mind.
Just make sure you do a thorough job.
You should probably take that off.
Hey, don't you worry. We've
got a score to settle too.
Darn him.
(All in Gym)
We're on scene.
(Police)
- Excuse me. Sorry to interrupt.
- How can I help you, Officer?
We received a report of an
illegal gambling den at this location.
A gambling den?
Well, thanks for the consultation.
I'll come back when I'm ready.
- All right, take care now.
- We're going to take a look inside.
Of course.
Who in the world would
file a false report like that?
What is it, Officer?
What's the matter?
It seems it was a false report, after all.
I mean, of course. It's a gym.
There's no way you'd find that here.
- Thank you for your cooperation.
- Of course.
- Have a good day.
- Yes, thank you.
What?
He's one of your staff?
You should've said so.
Have a safe trip back.
Unbelievable.
(Bring a Friend to the Gym!)
Are they gone?
The cops. They're gone, right?
Don't tell me you're
the one who called them.
No way. I was too busy dreaming
about getting rich thanks to you.
I was getting all giddy.
I barely said a word to
my college buddy about it.
Gosh, but for him to stab
me in the back like this?
Just unbelievable.
You can't trust anyone
in this world, right?
You haven't told anyone
about this, have you?
Of course not.
CEO Im!
Come on!
Don't go around telling
anyone this, you hear me?
This is our little secret. All right?
All right.
Hey, we did this before,
remember? This one.
You want to go on top,
or should I? You go on top.
Slap, then grab.
Boom! Rich guy!
Come on, do it with me. Rich guy!
We're the only ones getting rich, got it?
Feel free to work out
here if you want, okay?
Let's give this place a complete makeover.
Why that little jerk...
Gosh, it's tough trying to
watch all of these at once.
Go Eun, can't you just
narrow it down for us?
No, sorry. You see the big picture
when you see them all together.
Watch closely again.
See? The coach, Jo Seong
Uk, subtly gives a sign.
And then they give up
a point. Then another.
The player acting on the sign
is the same one every time.
You're right. Number 17 was
the one who gave up every point.
Good! And that's our guy, Jeong Yeon Tae.
He's a Jingwang University
junior, playing libero.
Sometimes it's hard to tell if he
messed up or did it on purpose.
- What a coincidence.
- He wasn't going for the ball.
He was going for the player.
If he was going for the player,
that means he tried to injure him.
Looks like there was money in it for him.
Hang on a second.
(In-game injuries)
There's a betting
category. In-game injuries.
Darn. These jerks will
stop at nothing for money.
And their next game is
the last one of the season.
They'll try for one last big
score, since it's the finale.
That's actually perfect for us.
Let's get their guy on our side.
You want to get that corrupt
young star on our side?
Go Eun.
How about you go have a meal
with our "corrupt young star?"
Sure, why not? I can have a meal with him.
- What should I get?
- Give me a lot, please.
- Eat up, everyone.
- Just a little more.
This is delicious.
Hey, that's my phone.
- Can you unlock this for me?
- Hey, I said that's my phone.
I know.
I know it's yours. That's
why I asked you to unlock it.
She's gorgeous.
- I can't argue with that.
- Wow, she's so pretty.
You got a text.
Hey, I think she's trying
to get your number.
Goodness, dude. I
think you're getting hit on.
- You're the man!
- Hey, hold on.
So...
Do I know you?
Of course I do, Jeong Yeon Tae.
This was useful. Thanks.
Eat up. You've got to
work on your receives.
- Jeong Yeon Tae!
- Jeong Yeon Tae! Jeong Yeon Tae!
- Hey, cut it out.
- Clean up.
- Where are you going?
What's this?
"How are your psychic powers today?"
"New fortune-teller's shop opening?"
Wow, that's one way to get
a customer's heart pounding.
Today's psychic power, five stars!
(The trending beautiful fortune-teller)
She really is beautiful, though.
Darn it.
What's this?
That kid...
The fox provoked the tiger.
What are you saying?
It means Jeong Yeon Tae took the diary.
Gosh.
One hundred euros? How much is that?
Is one bill really worth
over a hundred dollars?
Yes! Score!
Is there any more in here?
What's this?
(Hwang Ji Hoon: Spiker, Scorer, Blocker)
Hwang Ji Hoon.
"Inconsistent receiving. One to watch."
Hey, I'm in here too.
"Player with the greatest
potential and is a very quick study."
"With great leadership,
he could be a huge asset."
"Could compete in the pro
leagues within 2 or 3 years."
Translated.
"Official Euro League agent, Lorenzo Kim?"
(Official Euro League Volleyball)
There we go!
Of course. Our little star must be curious.
Lorenzo Kim. Type that in.
(Official Euro League Agent Lorenzo Kim)
("First Asian Agent Lorenzo
Kim Takes Over Italian Market")
Who is this guy?
(Lorenzo Kim, following
an 11 million-dollar deal...)
("The Strategist Who Forged
a Win-Win for Player and Club")
Come on, aren't you going to click it?
Gosh, I worked so hard on this.
Click on the article! There you go.
(Sync in Progress)
Wait, is that Kim Yeon Koung?
(Errors occur frequently
during chance-ball situations)
(Jeong Yeon Tae of Jingwang University)
I'm the only five-star player here.
Lorenzo Kim.
Please try this on.
Our Driver Kim Do Gi really
is someone to be proud of.
I wonder if I'd look that good in that suit.
Chief Park, why don't you come with me?
Me?
Me too?
What kind of style are you looking for?
Something with a passionate,
romantic, European vibe,
but a bad boy with a fiery
heart who can't be tamed.
One anyone can fall for.
I know just the thing.
Okay.
Wait, am I getting a haircut?
But I can't grow a beard.
Hey, Do Gi.
- Mr. Jang, could I borrow a car?
- A car?
We have a whole fleet of
cars. You don't have to ask.
Wait a minute. By "a
car," you don't mean...
I'll take good care of it
and bring it right back.
No, wait, Do Gi. Hello? Do Gi?
There's a car coming.
You may pass.
All right, guys, let's go.
(Jingwang University)
Go ahead.
(Lorenzo Kim striking a pose)
(Kim Yeon Koung and
Lorenzo Kim posing for photos)
(Jeong Yeon Tae of Jingwang University)
Do you know him?
- No, not at all.
- Gosh, check out that car.
My gosh.
- Let's do it.
- Let's do this!
(Jingwang University)
Play.
Nice! Great.
Yes.
Play.
There you go. Great.
Driver Kim Do Gi, we
have a bit of a problem.
A problem?
It looks like he's here to see Jo Seong Uk.
Won't it be a problem if he runs into you?
I'm not the one who'll be in trouble.
Hey, rich guy.
I wondered what smelled like money.
Of course, it's our CEO Im!
What are you suddenly doing here?
What do you mean? I'm
here to see our coach too.
We're on the same team now, remember?
Why would you meet
him? You have no reason to.
That reminds me.
I was talking to a police officer I know,
and there's a reward for
reporting illegal gambling.
What?
With stakes your size,
the reward could be up to 300,000 dollars.
Or, if that's too much trouble, I
can report you, and you confess.
Then when the reward money
comes in, we split it 50-50.
A police officer? What did you ask them?
Hey, come on, Dong Hyeon.
Why are you still being so formal?
It kind of hurts my
feelings. Just use my name.
Park Min Ho.
- Okay, I got it. Park Min Ho.
- Yes.
Min Ho.
I'll set up a time for us to talk later.
You'd better set up that meeting. Got it?
We won't get rich by doing
nothing. You know that, right?
Look, I'm going to
set a few things up,
so you must keep the gears turning.
- We can't stop. You get me?
- Yes.
All right? We're doing this.
Let's go for it. Let's go!
We're doing this.
I love you so much. Let's go!
Hello.
My brother.
Please have a seat.
This is your itinerary for Korea.
He's the talent I've found.
Hello.
Magnificent.
I'm still in Korea.
I'm looking for a libero with potential.
It's time for your meeting
with the volleyball president.
We need to get going, Lorenzo.
I'm still in Korea.
I'm looking for a libero with potential.
The second Driver Kim left,
he frantically searched the Euro league.
How is he falling for this so
easily without any suspicion?
I guess it's because he's young?
Human psychology can be
conveniently simple sometimes.
- How so?
- People doubt info that's given,
but when it's information
they've dug up themselves,
they almost always believe
it without a second thought.
Jeong Yeon Tae figured out
who I am through his own efforts,
and he even did the legwork
himself to find out what I'm up to.
There's no way he'll doubt it.
After all, it's all information
he discovered on his own.
- So he trusts it completely.
- I see.
That's Lorenzo Kim for you.
You could call it the moment
the fake turns into the real thing.
Message received.
Now that we have someone on our side,
shall we start placing some real bets?
Isn't it a little public to be doing this?
Cut the nonsense.
Just take it.
I'll get on the site and
set it up by tomorrow.
It's the last match of the
season, so I'm going big.
So stay sharp.
Got it.
Rich guy.
I was over there ordering. I
swear the small of your money
was stronger than the smell of fries.
I had a hunch, and sure enough.
You're impressive, CEO IM.
Boom!
I'm kind of in the middle of something.
Nice catch!
CEO Im, you nearly gave up on that, right?
Or maybe not? Or was that my service ace?
Sit down.
I'm in an important
meeting. I'll call you later.
An important meeting?
I guess you hold important
meetings over burgers these days.
- I'll call you later, okay?
- Yes.
You're with someone.
Got it. Sorry for interrupting.
Hang on.
By any chance,
aren't you the coach of the
Jingwang University volleyball team?
I'm right, aren't I?
You are him!
I thought you looked familiar. I knew it!
Goodness, what an honor.
I've just been so obsessed
with volleyball lately.
Would you just leave already?
All right. But I'm a huge fan of the coach.
If you don't mind, I'd
love to treat you to a meal.
My treat. I'll take you somewhere nice.
After all, we'll be seeing
a lot of each other.
I'll let you get back to
your important discussion.
CEO Im, give me a call.
Take care.
Hey, Dong Hyeon.
Be straight with me.
Did you mess up again?
Mess up? No.
- I didn't.
- Just be honest with me.
The thing is,
I went to a gambling den.
That...
That guy...
He's the one who took my gym as collateral.
And he even found our secret room.
I'm sorry.
(Jingwang University
versus Hogyeong University)
Goodness.
The site's stakes are way
higher than we expected.
Gosh, how much is all this?
With that much money on the line,
I must be a big thorn in their side.
It's Im Dong Hyeon.
Rich guy.
Clear your schedule.
- My schedule?
- You wanted to see the coach.
Let's talk business over dinner.
Sounds great. Send me the address.
(CEO Im Dong Hyeon)
That arrogant jerk.
I'll get the car ready.
Hold on. We should take a different car.
At the address Im Dong Hyeon gave me,
there are no restaurants.
I knew it. He wasn't just
asking you to have dinner.
We still have those used cars
from Cha Byeong Jin, right?
Get me one that wasn't flood-damaged.
Why are they driving like this?
Driver Kim, construction
zone on your right.
So this is why they wanted to meet here.
Driver Kim, tow truck up ahead! Watch out!
Driver Kim, it's blocked! Turn!
(Construction Notice)
(Your vehicle has been safely towed.)
- Yes.
- What do you think?
We killed and burned the body all at once.
That's foolproof.
Make sure you wrap up well. No loose ends.
Okay, just wire me the money.
Let's wrap this up!
What did he say? Is it done? Is he dead?
You think he could've survived that?
He's definitely a goner.
By the way, do you know
what that jerk's name is?
Park Min Ho.
Do I need to know the jerk's name too?
No.
Tomorrow's D-day.
Let's see this through to the end.
Okay.
Driver Kim!
- Driver Kim, are you okay?
- Why ask? You know he's fine.
Jo Seong Uk.
I didn't expect him to
be so bold with his attack.
Now that they've made their
move, it's our turn to strike.
All right. Tomorrow, we unleash everything.
(D-1)
(D-Day)
(Jingwang University
versus Hogyeong University)
(Live Viewers: 12,583)
All right, listen up! It's the
finals. Everyone play safe,
and let's stick to the game plan. Got it?
- Jingwang!
- Let's go!
(College Volleyball U-League Finals)
(Gymnasium)
If it isn't the legend himself.
- Play well today.
- Yes, sir. We'll do our best.
Hello.
(Jingwang University)
Excuse me, Agent Lorenzo?
Do I know you?
Where did you find this?
I was just kicking myself for losing this.
Hello. I'm Jeong Yeon Tae,
the libero for Jingwang University.
- Jeong Yeon Tae. The player?
- I'm sorry.
I happened to see a
little of what was inside.
And I know why you're here, Agent Lorenzo.
I really do.
(2025 NUVF College
Volleyball U-League, Finals)
(Jingwang University
versus Hogyeong University)
(Hogyeong University)
To be honest,
I've never been drafted
into the pro leagues.
Why are you interested in me?
Because you stood out to me.
You have great court vision, Yeon Tae.
You were always right where I
thought a defender should be.
That's not something you
can learn from practice.
It's a natural gift.
You really think I have that kind of talent?
An Asian libero
has never made it big in the major leagues.
Do you know why that is?
No.
Because he hasn't gone yet.
I mean you, Jeong Yeon Tae.
Just cut down on the mistakes.
You make way too many mistakes per game.
Consistently.
You can't afford that.
I'll make up for it this time.
Just you watch!
Your hand.
Go out there and show
them what you're made of.
Let's make you the Son Heung Min,
the Ryu Hyun Jin of volleyball.
Right.
Yes!
Thank you.
Jeong Yeon Tae!
Get your head in the game! Come on, focus!
Let's go!
Cover!
Nice!
Darn, why is he suddenly playing so well?
Darn it. He's not doing what he's told.
- Hey, pass it back!
- Come on.
Nice!
Hey, Jeong Yeon Tae!
Why aren't you playing as you're told?
Gosh, why are you so good?
Who is this?
(Unknown Caller)
- Who is this?
- Hey, CEO Im.
It's me.
- What?
- Can you see me on TV?
Why... Why aren't you dead?
Park Min Ho.
How are you alive?
The tow truck.
- The tow...
- Let me share a secret, CEO Im.
That 50-50 split on the reward? It's off.
It's all mine now.
(2025 NUVF College
Volleyball U-League, Finals)
No way. The car blew
up, so how is he alive?
(2025 NUVF College
Volleyball U-League, Finals)
Yeon Tae. Jeong Yeon Tae.
Jeong Yeon Tae, are
you even trying to focus?
Coach, sorry, but can you please
just let me play for real this once?
What kind of nonsense is
that? You're a talentless hack.
- I do have skills.
- Who says?
Not a single team drafted you.
So who told you you're any good?
There might be a chance for
me in the major leagues in Europe.
You've really lost it. Hey.
How many Korean liberos do you
think have ever made it to Europe?
Not a single one. Not even one.
Then I could be the first, Coach.
Yeon Tae.
The next set is really important.
If you don't want to mess up your life,
just do as I say. Got it?
Good.
I'm counting on you. Now go.
Let's go!
Let's do this!
Yeon Tae.
You're doing great.
Play.
Nice one.
Nice!
(Invincible Jingwang's lucky
charm, Jeong Yeon Tae)
- Yeon Tae...
- Mine!
- Nice!
- Yes, that's it!
- That's it.
- Cover!
Go!
(Invincible Jingwang's lucky
charm, Jeong Yeon Tae)
- Jeong Yeon Tae!
(Jingwang University
versus Hogyeong University)
(Payout: 167,000 dollars)
Jeong Yeon Tae! Let's go!
Darn it.
Now that they've made their
move, it's our turn to strike.
All right. Tomorrow, we unleash everything.
For that one moment of wavering,
we have to focus everything.
(Park Min Ho)
Get the one in front! Cover!
How dare worthless trash like you defy me?
I'm holding a press conference immediately.
- What?
- I recorded everything you said.
Everything. From the very beginning.
Jeong Yeon Tae, you...
What do you want from me?
What is it you want from me, jerk?
What do I want?
There's definitely something I want.
Apologize to Park Min Ho.
What?
For that one moment of wavering,
we have to focus everything.
What?
What's going on? Park...
I thought you said Park Min Ho was dead!
Park Min Ho? What are you talking about?
The tow truck. You said it
flipped and, you blew it up!
We saw the pictures together!
You think he could've survived that?
He's definitely a goner.
Get out of my way.
But how is Park Min Ho still alive?
Hey, Park Min Ho... He's right here.
Get out of my way!
Hey! Who on earth are you?
Who on earth are you, you crazy jerk?
(Park Min Ho)
No.
It can't be.
It can't be. Park Min Ho is dead!
Park Min Ho is dead! Darn it!
No way. This can't be happening.
And the autopsy report?
Who did they ID the body as?
Park Min Ho, a volleyball
player of Jingwang University.
- Park Min Ho?
- Yes.
We're taking Coach Jo Seong Uk
of Jingwang University into custody.
How did they manage it with the body?
The body!
How did they do it?
Where did they...
This can't be right. Only
we knew about this. Right?
- Seong Uk, you need to calm down.
- But I just got here.
I'll go check for myself.
(The grave of Baek Seon Ja)
It's here!
Park Min Ho is here!
You had me so worried! Darn it.
Hey, I found him. Min Ho was right here.
I've found him.
Park Min Ho.
So you dug him up
yourself just to make sure.
No, that's not it.
Let's meet face-to-face soon.
It feels good to be outside
after being cooped up
in a hospital room, right?
Take a nice, deep breath.
The sky?
That's right.
Min Ho said he loved a
sky just like this, didn't he?
Come to think of it,
just as Min Ho said,
the sky really does look
like one giant volleyball court.
The sky is so beautiful.
Seong Cheol.
Yes?
(Special thanks to our
guest star, Um Mun Suk)
(Taxi Driver 3)
Someone else was involved
in Park Min Ho's death?
From now on, I'll take care
of your futures.
Cheon Gwang Jin. He thinks
without restraint and is dangerous.
Who are you?
Me? I'm Park Min Ho.
What are you talking about?
Park Min Ho's body was stolen?
- Min Ho. Long time no see.
- How about we meet and talk?
Be late, and you'll never
find Min Ho's bones.
You're too slow.