[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 16]
Mr. Ji.
Mr. Feng is the head
of the HSKP Department after all.
Making a decision
on his position all by yourself—
isn't that a bit too hasty?
Exactly.
You should at least
discuss it with Mr. Wei first.
So what you're saying is,
the hotel's general manager
can't make personnel
decisions independently?
Or do you think
I should present Mr. Feng's
record of dereliction of duty
directly to the board,
and let Chairman Wei decide personally?
Any other opinions?
Susan, please ask
the HR Department to hire
a new HSKP director as soon as possible.
Okay, Mr. Ji.
Meeting adjourned.
Don't drink in my car.
Zhigang, you have to help me.
How many times have I told you?
Clean up your mess when you do something.
Now that someone's got dirt on you,
how can I help you?
So...
So you're just going to
let that guy Ji Feng
walk all over you?
Stay calm.
He couldn't hold back
and went after my people first.
Don't blame me
for being ruthless from now on.
I've arranged for you
to work at a friend's hotel.
And as for your sister,
you know what to say, right?
I didn't expect Ji Feng
to be serious this time.
Kaixin really took a fall this time.
We both need
to keep a low profile from now on.
Mr. Qian.
What's up?
Can we talk in private?
Mr. Huang and I have something to discuss.
Come back later.
Okay.
Isn't she your subordinate?
Could she be working for Ji Feng?
She works for whoever pays her.
My subordinate?
She'll just use me and kick me away.
Anyway, be careful.
Don't let her set a trap for you.
She wants to play me?
She's a bit too green for that.
Come in.
Mr. Ji.
You took Marcos to the airport?
Yes, I did.
Ms. Lu didn't go?
She said she was busy
and asked me to take him instead.
Did Marcos say anything
before he left?
Nothing special,
just some words of thanks.
What exactly did he say?
He said our service
made him feel at home.
He also said he hopes his employees
can enjoy our service too.
Okay. Thanks for your hard work.
Go back and get some rest.
Mr. Qian.
Go ahead. What is it?
Ms. Lu.
Mr. Qian, I'll be straightforward.
I volunteered this time
not to suck up to the new leader.
On the contrary,
I did it to test the waters for you.
Ms. Lu, what do you mean?
I know the current situation
isn't what you hoped for.
But if you want to hold onto
the No.1 spot in sales,
someone has to step up
and take on this task.
I'm giving it my all
for our sales department's reputation,
not to work for Mr. Ji.
Mr. Qian, please believe me.
I'm definitely on your side.
I took the lead in this event
just to test the waters for you
and see how deep it goes.
I would never betray you.
With you explaining it like this,
it actually makes sense, doesn't it?
Otherwise, I was starting to think Mr. Wei
had sent me an ungrateful wretch.
Mr. Qian, I knew
you must have misunderstood me.
That's why I hurried over to apologize.
Mr. Qian,
I know you like game and wild goods,
so I had someone
custom-order these for you.
Look at you, Ms. Lu.
You're too kind.
We're on the same side here.
Here.
Then you should definitely accept it.
Fine.
Alright.
Seriously,
you never tidy up.
Look at how messy this place is.
We're busy with work,
and have no time to clean up.
What about weekends?
Are you busy on weekends too?
Today's the weekend.
Where's Zhenzhen?
She went to the hotel.
There's a reception at the hotel.
She had to be there.
I'm not saying she has to do housework.
But she's pregnant
and still running around outside.
As a woman,
how much work can she possibly have?
You know her temper.
She can't sit still.
She likes to stay busy.
If you made her stay home all day,
she'd get all anxious
and complain nonstop.
You can't just indulge her.
A woman's pregnancy lasts 10 months,
and every single month is critical.
She should stay home and rest.
She's carrying our family's child.
You can't be careless.
Understand?
Got it.
You have to take my words to heart.
Did you hear me?
Yeah, I hear you.
If it weren't for her
being pregnant at that time,
I'd never have let her into this family.
Look at her frivolous face.
She won't even stay home on weekends.
Mom,
you know, for a woman,
isn't it good that she likes to work?
Besides, I've told you,
she has some connections I can use.
Why should I go against her?
Isn't it better to play along?
Don't worry about your grandson.
I will definitely protect him.
You're back.
When did you come back?
I didn't hear you.
Just now.
Mom, Yucheng, what are you talking about?
Nothing.
I'm helping you tidy up the room.
Let me do it.
How could I let you clean?
Zhenzhen, you've been busy all day.
Go and get some rest.
You don't need to help me.
I'll be done soon.
Mom,
my colleague's looking for me.
I have to go.
Sorry I can't stay.
Are you going out to work again?
I got promoted.
My colleagues want to celebrate with me.
You got a promotion?
Congratulations.
I'll get going then.
Stay safe.
Take care on your way.
Look at her.
Hello, Mr. Cheng.
Nice to see you again.
You've got a good memory.
By the way,
this is our group's
North China regional head
Mr. Dai.
Hello, Mr. Dai.
Hello.
I've arranged a room
facing the sun for you.
It has a better view. This way, please.
But he hasn't checked in yet.
That's okay.
We can drop off the luggage first.
I'll have an attendant
come up and register later.
Perfect.
Let's go.
You can take a rest first.
The attendant will be up
to see you shortly.
Okay, thank you.
Get some rest.
Okay, bye.
Mr. Cheng, let me walk you down.
Okay.
Thank you so much
for introducing so many guests to us.
Rest assured,
our executive floor
will wholeheartedly serve them.
I trust you with them, of course.
By the way,
is the presidential suite
occupied right now?
We have a long-term guest in one.
But the other presidential suite
is vacant.
Whatever you need,
just let me know.
Here's the thing.
A friend of mine is Li Bingyan's manager.
Li Bingyan?
You mean the actress Li Bingyan?
Exactly.
She's
coming to Shanghai soon
to film a variety show.
Her manager asked me
to find a reliable hotel for her.
The requirements: a presidential suite,
and
absolute confidentiality
regarding her schedule.
Her personal life
absolutely cannot be disturbed.
So the first place
I thought of was your Purong Hotel,
and I thought of you.
I wonder if you're willing to take it.
Yes, of course we are.
But she's a celebrity
with lots of public attention and fans.
It's bound to come with
a fair amount of trouble.
You have to consider the pressure.
Don't worry.
We will definitely try our best
to meet all her needs.
I'll set up a group chat then.
Thank you.
Don't mention it. I should thank you
for always introducing such important VIPs
to our hotel.
It's all because of
the service you provide.
Please.
Ms. Lu.
Ms. Xu,
I need a presidential suite.
The VIP will arrive tomorrow.
Please arrange it as soon as possible.
I'm sorry,
but the presidential suites
have just been booked.
Then I suggest you figure something out
and clear one quickly.
This VIP has an agreement
with our hotel.
The accommodation must
be no less than a presidential suite.
[February 5, 2025]
I'm sure you understand who this VIP is.
If we fail to meet the VIP's needs,
will you be responsible
for breaking the agreement?
Whoever it is,
she's indeed a step late.
I'm sorry.
Xu Miyu,
why are you working against me?
Let me put it this way.
The room she stays in
won't be vacant for the next 2 years.
If this deal falls through
because of you,
can you afford
to cover the hotel's losses?
Don't worry about my personal matters.
But what I just said about
the presidential suite situation—
that's the truth.
Fine.
I won't make things difficult for you.
If Mr. Ji asks about it,
explain it to him yourself.
Who does she think she is?
[Reception]
Let me check.
[Room Status Center]
Come in.
Mr. Ji.
I have something to discuss with you.
Okay.
The Qiao Feifei account
is definitely an opportunity
for our hotel.
I won't say
how much effort it took me
to secure this order.
And then
Ms. Xu just shuts it down flat.
Does she even have that authority?
Alright.
I got it.
I'll look into the situation first.
Leave this to me.
Sorry to trouble you, Mr. Ji.
Not at all.
Actually,
I shouldn't bother you
with such a small matter.
But I'm doing this
for the benefit of the hotel.
If there's nothing else,
get back to work.
Okay.
♪Ah♪
♪Talking to myself♪
♪Playing pretend
that I've got it together♪
Stop watching.
Hurry up and clean.
The guest will be here any minute.
♪ That fleeting moment I tried to hold ♪
♪ Let it go when the glass runs dry ♪
Who's this?
You don't know Qiao Feifei?
♪ Unfinished longings ♪
You've never watched the show Star Maker?
I haven't missed a single episode.
♪ Drift like fading embers ♪
That's her hit song.
The VIP is arriving soon.
How's the cleaning going?
♪ Still longing for yesterday's glow ♪
Almost done.
♪ Yet sailing into
the ocean's depths at night ♪
♪ Questions without answers ♪
You two, stop watching.
Hurry and clean up.
The guest is arriving soon.
Hurry up, Jia.
Thank you.
Huanhuan.
Have you seen Ms. Li Bingyan?
I'm here.
Hello, Ms. Li.
I'm your butler. My surname is Xu.
Hello, I'm Li Bingyan.
Your name is Xu Miyu?
It's a really nice name.
You don't put on any airs as a star.
I'm not really a star.
Let's go.
This way, please.
I'll take it.
Thank you.
Li Bingyan?
Mr. Duan.
I... I'm your fan.
You must be Mr. Duan Jr.
Hello.
You know me?
W-Well, I'm so honored.
Can I have your autograph?
Sure.
Well...
Pen.
I don't have a pen, Mr. Duan.
How about a photo?
What a coincidence.
I'm sorry.
I'm not wearing makeup today.
It's not convenient to take photos.
Mr. Duan, the guest needs to rest.
I'm sorry.
Where is my room?
This way, please.
Okay.
-We could at least chat.
-Mr. Duan.
I'm sorry.
Xu Miyu.
I remember you.
Please come in.
This is your room.
If you need anything later,
just call the number on the bedside.
We're at your service anytime.
Thank you for helping me out just now.
I actually have a bit of social anxiety.
I understand.
The more public a figure is,
the more private space they need.
Thank you.
You're really sharp.
I'm flattered.
If there's anything I need—
well,
I don't sleep very well,
so I'm quite picky about
the living environment.
I'm especially sensitive to noise.
We'll keep the hallway
as quiet as possible.
Also, I could add some
begonia to your room's diffuser.
Begonia helps
calm the mind and promotes sleep.
And having floral scent in the room
will also make you feel relaxed.
Thank you, Ms. Xu.
You seem like
someone who's very considerate of others.
Please get some rest.
I'll go prepare it right away.
Okay.
Send the diffuser up now,
before the lunch break.
Okay.
Here.
Everyone, pay attention.
Ms. Li doesn't sleep well,
as I reminded you before.
So when we go upstairs to serve,
we must keep quiet.
Got it?
Yes.
Ms. Xu.
Ms. Lu is pushing
for the presidential suite again.
Got it.
Hello. Is Mr. Duan here?
Come in.
Sorry to disturb you, Mr. Duan.
I'm Xu Miyu.
There's something
I'd like to discuss with you.
We just saw each other.
What's there to disturb?
Here's the thing.
Our presidential suites
are fully occupied.
And now another VIP wants to check in.
So there's a bit of a conflict.
Sounds troublesome.
So what do we do?
Mr. Duan, that's why I wanted
to ask you...
To move out?
Not moving out.
Just to have you temporarily
stay on the executive floor.
And once this guest leaves,
you can move back in.
Then for such a big favor,
how will you repay me?
You're the financial backer
of Purong Hotel.
If the hotel's performance is good,
you can also get
a higher return on investment.
Enough.
Drop the corporate talk.
It's boring.
Can't you humble yourself a bit
when asking for a favor?
W-Why don't you ask me
what I want?
What do you want?
Then I have to think about it carefully.
What do you have to offer?
I...
Hello, Mr. Ji.
Where is Ms. Xu?
She's not here.
She's in the presidential suite.
Which one?
Mr. Duan's suite.
They're discussing the room swap.
Okay, thanks.
I'm not asking you
to get me the stars from the sky.
Doesn't she just live across the hall?
You go knock on her door
and introduce me.
Am I that unpresentable?
I don't mean that, Mr. Duan.
Take a step back.
I could knock on her door
and recommend myself.
And you're still trying to stop me.
Did she buy you out or something?
The guest across the hall clearly told me
that she didn't want
to be disturbed by anyone.
As her butler,
I...
You really think you're something?
You're her butler,
but you're not mine?
I don't care.
You have to ask her out for me.
I'm having dinner with her tonight.
I promise you!
The knight is here.
We were just having a good chat.
There is a lot to do
on the executive floor.
Tell me if you need anything.
Interesting.
[Qiao Feifei, Chinese actress, singer]
[Qiao Feifei, a new-generation
idol female star in China]
[Qiao Feifei's efforts and talent
have enabled her to rise rapidly]
[in the entertainment industry, leading
among the new generation of idols.]
[Chinese name Qiao Feifei]
[Alias: Feifei]
Mr. Ji.
The presidential suite has been vacated.
Have someone clean it up.
That's great, Mr. Ji.
How did you get Mr. Duan
to move out so quickly?
I gave him a ticket to the fashion gala.
He gets to walk the red carpet
with his idol.
Walk the red carpet?
Will Ms. Li cooperate?
That's not my concern.
We'll have to see what he's capable of.
I didn't expect
you had such tricks up your sleeve.
Your compliments are the greatest
encouragement for my work.
Thank you.
Are you playing tricks again?
I didn't expect
you held grudges like that.
Mr. Duan.
You messed with me?
What's wrong, Mr. Duan?
Didn't you have a good chat
with Li Bingyan?
Chat?
She kicked me away
as soon as she got on the red carpet.
We didn't even say hi.
That's really a pity.
I feel pity for you,
because our cooperation ends here.
I'm telling you I'm very unhappy.
Also,
compared to the ordinary
leather on this executive floor,
I prefer the genuine leather sofa
in my presidential suite.
Mr. Duan,
our deal is not over yet.
Do you know
who is currently staying
in Room 1816?
Who?
Zuo Qiang.
You know him?
He's your dad's right-hand man.
Everyone in the circle knows him.
Then... what is he doing here?
We don't know what he's here for.
But now that you've
moved to the executive floor.
Keeping a low profile
certainly won't hurt.
You don't want him
to snitch on you to your dad
that you spend your days
in Purong Hotel's presidential suite
having fun, right?
You knew this all along?
I just found out.
Well, since you're so thoughtful,
I won't embarrass you this time.
Thank you for your great support.
Don't get too cocky.
We'll have plenty of time
to deal with each other.
Thank you for going easy on me.
Welcome.
Qingping.
Get two more people down
to help with the luggage.
Stop looking. Let's go.
Wei.
You look even more handsome today.
Zhenzhen,
I'm only here as a favor to you.
You must take good care of our Feifei.
Thank you so much, Wei.
Feifei,
you're 100 times prettier
in person than on screen.
Besides, you're a top star
and a ratings queen everyone knows.
Our hotel will definitely provide
first-class service.
Please rest assured, Wei.
Otherwise, Feifei's fans
wouldn't let us off the hook.
Please.
Isn't this the concierge's job?
Ms. Xu,
why bringing the luggage over yourself?
Are you a fan too?
There's a lot of luggage
for the presidential suite.
The HSKP Department is helping out.
Any problem with that, Ms. Lu?
No problem at all.
You're quite right.
Helping guests is also your job.
Be careful, everyone.
Don't bump into anything.
You can't afford to pay
for such valuable items.
Ms. Xu.
Should we book the small banquet hall
or a private dining room for lunch?
The kitchen's asking
how many people
they need to prepare food for.
I'll let you know once I confirm.
Ms. Xu,
can you get someone from
the Engineering Department to come over?
We need to connect
some external equipment,
and check the voltage.
Okay, wait a moment.
Ms. Xu. Ms. Xu.
Can you help me ask
about the number of diners first?
Do you have a piano here?
Ou!
Ou, Feifei asked you to go in.
Tell her to wait a moment.
Ms. Xu!
There seems to be a problem
with their credit card.
Could you double-check for me?
Is this the right one?
Ms. Xu, the guest in the presidential suite
complained about the noise.
Got it.
Ms. Xu, that...
I've heard everyone's questions.
This is a public area.
Please don't make loud noises.
There are VIPs resting.
Go back to your rooms and close the doors.
I'll come find you in a moment.
You, you, and you,
go wait for me on the executive floor.
I'll come find you
after sorting out the luggage.
Okay?
Okay.
No problem. Dismissed.
Miyu,
I'll go get an autograph.
It's working hours.
Sort out the luggage first.
But my idol is right inside.
Work first. You'll get your chance later.
Ms. Xu, the presidential suite guests
sent their thanks.
Got it.
Let's go.
Right now, we have two celebrities
staying in the presidential suites.
Qiao Feifei and Li Bingyan.
As public figures, they naturally
have higher demands
for privacy and security.
I hope everyone will keep this in mind
and act accordingly.
Don't wait until their teams
come to complain
before we scramble to respond.
In that case,
it would be beneath Purong Hotel's
service standards.
Then what's the best way to handle this?
Should we send more people up to patrol?
The celebrities don't want
to be disturbed in the first place.
Sending more people to wander around
is just asking to be yelled at.
Ms. Xu,
I think the key to this issue
is to resolve the review mechanism
on our executive floor.
Everyone who takes the elevator
to the presidential suite
should be strictly registered.
This way, we can manage
the flow in and out
of the presidential suite
and ensure
the guests' privacy isn't disturbed.
That's a very good idea.
Qingping, I'm putting you
in charge of this.
Okay.
Also, if any fans come
looking for the celebrities,
we must remember:
no verbal conflicts
or violent eviction.
We're service staff.
Our job is to keep the executive floor
and the presidential suite
safe, smooth, and peaceful.
We cannot afford to cause any conflict.
Got it?
Yes.
Okay.
Get back to work.
As always,
I'll serve you two the Yan Du Xian first.
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
Is the gluten ball
stuffed with meat ready?
Yes.
How much longer
for the shredded pork and ham soup?
Almost done.
Chef,
a lot of tables
are asking for their dishes.
-Got it.
-Thank you.
Okay.
Where's Chef Yang?
I said, where's Chef Yang?
Chef Yang went to make soup.
Qiaoqi,
Ting from the restaurant just told me
that Professor Liu and his wife canceled
their reservation for next week.
Was it the food or the service?
They said there's a problem
with the taste of the Yan Du Xian.
When did this run out?
I don't know.
Why didn't anyone tell me
we were out of cured pork?
You didn't ask.
What kind of answer is that?
How do you make Yan Du Xian
without cured pork?
You...
Where's your name tag?
Why aren't you wearing it?
I'm not wearing it. So what?
You never call me by my name anyway.
Don't you always call me
"Hey?"
Baozi, say less.
Come help me.
Stop looking.
Get back to cooking.
Eight-Treasure Duck!
Four Joy Meatballs!
Braised Pork Intestines and Yan Du Xian!
Yan Du Xian again.
Use
air-dried pork for now.
Okay.
Excuse me, what meat is this?
Air-dried pork.
And what season
is the air-dried pork meant for?
Summer.
So you use summer air-dried pork,
mix in some leftover autumn ham scraps,
and slap together
a half-decent spring Yan Du Xian.
Is your Purong Hotel
trying to ruin its own name?
Don't our loyal customers' palates
deserve a little more effort from you?
I'm sorry, sir.
It's my responsibility.
[Soups] [Bamboo shoot soup
with fresh and pickled streaky pork]
When did the cured pork supply run out?
Last week.
They made it clear
they only work with Chef Jia.
But I'm already looking for new suppliers.
Please give me a little more time.
It will be difficult
during this special period,
but please hang in there, Chef Li.
I have faith in you.
I won't let you down, Mr. Ji.
We absolutely cannot
let our signature dish fail.
Let me know
when there's something good to eat.
You got it.
Xu Miyu!
Where are you going so late?
I'm going to the hotel.
There's something I need to do.
Is everything okay?
[Bund Tunnel]
You're here.
[Staff Only]
How is it? Smells good, right?
Makes your mouth water, doesn't it?
Miyu...
You scared me.
Why is it you?
I saw the light in the kitchen.
So I came to check.
Why haven't you left work yet?
Where did you get the cured pork?
Smells so good.
Let me taste it for the guests.
Is it for you?
-Qiaoqi.
-Then who's it for?
You're here.
You invited Xu Miyu?
Let's both try it. You go first.
Why are you here?
Mr. Ji.
Did you invite Mr. Ji?
No, no.
We ran into each other on the way.
Didn't I tell you to let me know
when there's good food?
This is just a test.
I don't know how it will turn out.
So I wanted Miyu to help me check it.
As an experienced foodie,
I can help with that too.
So can I.
Then let's all try it.
It smells so good.
Earthy from the clay pot,
a hint of charcoal,
with a little bit of smokiness.
Tomorrow we can use this Yan Du Xian
to blow the diners away.
It can definitely become our
new signature dish at Purong Hotel.
Keep bragging.
It's not up to you
whether the guests like it.
I'm really not confident.
After all, Chef Jia's Yan Du Xian
dominates Shanghai.
Many guests come here for its reputation.
Will the Chinese restaurant
really be ruined in my hands?
The quality of Yan Du Xian
must certainly continue to improve.
But does it have to be exactly the same
as Chef Jia's?
I don't think so.
Times change,
and so do diners' tastes.
Now that Chef Jia has blocked
all supply channels,
we can find another way.
Let's see if there
are other possibilities for this dish.
Okay, Mr. Ji.
Tomorrow, I'll keep looking
for cured pork suppliers.
I'll help you.
There are plenty of
cured pork makers
in the Yangtze River Delta.
We can definitely find a good source.
Leave it to me.
Stop bragging.
It'd be great
if you don't make things worse.
See?
You always put me down.
One last bowl.
Yan Du Xian.
Please enjoy.
Hello?
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Waiter, I'd like to order!
Hello, sir.
What would you like to eat?
One Yan Du Xian.
Anything else, sir?
No, thanks.
[Trending]
[Former Purong Hotel's Head Chef
Jia Shikun Joins Kuanli]
[Ji Feng]
[Photos and videos]
[WeChat]
[Chef Qiao]
Are things going well?
Is the Yan Du Xian's response good?
Watch the heat.
[Xue Rui]
[Is the Yan Du Xian's response good?]
Pretty good.
Move faster.
Okay.
Everything okay?
Qiaoqi, Qiaoqi!
A customer is causing trouble
in the Chinese restaurant.