♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my playful charm♪
♪Just to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for you♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 8=
=Plan to Rewrite Fate Begins=
Go get more people over here.
Let your guys have some fun first.
Yes, Ma'am.
So Mrs. Liu is doing this yourself?
So this Li family
isn't as classy as I imagined.
Because...
I just really want to
see you completely taken down.
Mrs. Liu, you really like thrills.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't be with Mr. Zhong.
What do you actually know?
Speak!
That day, in Master Li's study,
I saw how nervous Zhong was about you.
That's when I figured it out.
If Ye Lang dies,
it does Zhong no good at all.
But you're different.
If Ye Lang dies,
then your son, Li Hong,
stands to gain the most.
Let me guess.
If I vanish here today,
then the blame for your deal with
Zhong Minghui gets pinned on me?
Jiang Niannian.
Knowing too much
is exactly why you must die.
Since I'm about to die,
I have one last question.
Where is Jiang Xiaodi?
Where are you going?
Niannian is missing.
I received this.
You should take a look.
Brother, you should brace yourself.
Beauty...
What is this?
She's the shameless woman
you brought home.
Do you know
Zhong was bewitched by her
into hurting you?
She wanted you dead
and to seize our fortune.
Young Master.
Today, a servant
found Ms. Jiang's underwear
while cleaning
Mr. Zhong's room.
No way!
I think you've
lost your head over desire.
Give Niannian back to me.
That woman
has already been dealt with.
I think
you also need
to be taught a lesson.
Bring in the family punishment.
Stop!
I have evidence
which can prove
Liu Yexi worked with Zhong Minghui
to hurt Ye Lang.
(Audio Recording)
If Ye Lang dies,
it does Zhong no good at all.
But you're different.
If Ye Lang dies,
then your son, Li Hong,
stands to gain the most.
Let me guess.
If I vanish here today,
then the blame for your deal with
Zhong Minghui gets pinned on me?
Jiang Niannian.
Knowing too much is exactly
why you must die.
Father,
I had nothing to do with this.
That woman must've used AI
to fake mother's voice!
AI?
Since I'm standing here just fine,
then why not take a guess
who the woman in the video
really is?
Quick.
Bring her back!
Father.
Let me go.
Let me go!
Let go of me!
Next week is my engagement ceremony with Xue.
On that day,
there will be shareholders, relatives
and reporters from all over Manlong.
Given Mom's condition...
Lock her
in a room.
Not a single word
of what happened today can be leaked.
I use myself
to help you bring down Liu Yexi.
Young Master,
time to pay up.
Niannian.
Why do you need that much money?
Are you in trouble?
Just tell me.
I can help you fix anything.
(Who's using Xiaodi to threaten me?)
(Ye Lang.)
(Can I really trust you?)
Money, you know,
the more, the better.
Wait,
are you backing out?
(Transfer)
(Successful)
Thanks for your business.
Now come get your reward.
Niannian.
I don't need anything from you.
Ye Lang.
Do you really love me?
I have no good education,
no good background.
You got rid of Jiang Qingqing,
but another girl will appear.
Jiang Niannian,
there has never
been anyone else.
Only you.
(Past and present,)
(I only want you.)
(Ye Lang.)
(If you were the first I met,)
(maybe we would've had a story.)
(But sadly,)
(you weren't the first.)
(Ye Lang.)
(Once I find Xiaodi, I'll leave.)
(True love is too risky.)
(I'm scared.)
Thank you.
What is it?
One breakfast
makes you this moved?
Breakfast doesn't matter.
Who I eat with does.
(Thank you for staying.)
(Thank you for making me feel)
(we can have a happy ending.)
(He's threatening me again.)
(But I will never sacrifice Ye Lang)
(to save Xiaodi.)
The highway's jammed.
Take the service road.
It's fine if we're late.
(The one threatening me,)
(could it be her?)
(Jiang Xiaodi is safe.)
Bro,
what's wrong with you now?
Want me to dissect you and check?
I'm just being careful.
For your good.
Life and death are fate.
If I die, give my body to the hospital.
But if you die,
then you're mine.
You can't die.
If you do,
finish Jiang Xiaodi's treatment first.
I owe her a healthy brother.
This patient's surgery
is really interesting.
But...
Bro,
did you really have to
pick me up this early?
It's only one o'clock now.
(One o'clock.)
(The crash in my past life was at 1:15.)
(As long as I avoid that time...)
(Outpatient Lobby)
(1:20.)
(The time of the accident has passed.)
Ye Lang.
Are you questioning my skills?
With me on Jiang Xiaodi's case,
the success rate is at least 75.9%.
But that's still not 100%.
What if I can make it 100%?
I'll give you my body anytime.
Fine. Just wait.
(Previous Life)
How could this happen outside the hospital?
He's an Attending Physician here.
What happened?
Director Ye.
Dr. Zheng Lu died in a car crash.
He had a brain surgery scheduled today.
Without him,
we can't guarantee it'll work.
Zheng Lu?
Which patient's surgery?
Jiang Xiaodi.
All right.
Disperse.
Poor guy, he's still so young.
(In my previous life, Zheng Lu died,)
(so Xiaodi's surgery didn't happen.)
(He was later killed in the hospital.)
(Niannian and I became enemies.)
(In this life,)
(if Zheng Lu can do Jiang Xiaodi's surgery)
(and save Xiaodi,)
(then our ending can change.)
Don't worry.
If I die before dissecting you,
I won't rest in peace.
You can't die.
Come on.
I'll take you there.
You're really acting strange today.
Shall I cut you open for a check
before the surgery?
(Outpatient Hall)
Hello.
Excuse me, is Dr. Zheng Lu here?
Sorry, Dr. Zheng
has a surgery scheduled today.
Registration and consults are on hold.
Watch out!
What's going on?
Ye Lang.
Knife!
- Quack.
- Ye Lang.
Stop hurting people!
Niannian.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Your hand.
Stop the bleeding first.
Does it hurt?
How could you block it with your hand?
It doesn't hurt.
You put your hand on mine,
then it won't hurt.
You're still grinning?
Did you hit your head too?
Nurse, please help stop his bleeding.
Director Ye, please come with me.
Mm.
Miss, please don't worry.
The nurse will handle it.
(Zheng Lu)
You are...
Zheng Lu, Dr. Zheng?
Yes.
Thanks for saving me.
I'm Chief Neurosurgeon at Renxin Hospital,
Zheng Lu.
Dr. Zheng.
I'm Jiang Niannian.
I came to see you today.
Me?
Yes.
Have you treated a patient
named Jiang Xiaodi?
A brain tumor patient.
I see lots of patients.
I don't recall.
Jiang Xiaodi is your...
My younger brother.
We only have each other.
But now he's missing.
Dr. Zheng.
I'm not asking to repay a favor.
If I find Xiaodi,
could you treat him?
Don't worry.
Saving lives is a doctor's duty.
Thank you.
(Ye Lang.)
(You owe me again.)
(What went wrong this time?)
(I avoided the time of the accident,)
(but a car still nearly hit him.)
(And there was even a stabbing,)
(something that never happened before.)
(So the fate can't be changed?)
Didn't you go to the pre-op meeting?
Jiang Xiaodi's exam report.
(Basic Info Jiang Xiaodi)
Some indicators are unstable.
And his blood type
is rare.
I checked the blood bank,
insufficient supplies.
Even if you volunteer as a blood donor,
the surgery still has to be delayed.
(Zheng Lu survived,)
(but Xiaodi's surgery still fell through.)
(No.)
(It feels like someone's behind this.)
(Could someone else have had a rebirth too?)
Useless fool!
Why didn't you kill him?
How could you miss?
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪