Subtitle Provide by Kisskh.Asia Translator [ Admin Qari ]
Thame is tearing up the last page
and rewriting the whole thing with you.
Since we're all crappy people,
let's get back up
and move forward together.
Thank that person for me.
Do you have anything to say to Po?
But if you don’t like him,
then you’re seriously
hurting his feelings.
Tell me what I have to do
to find out if I like him or not.
If you hear your heart
beat faster than usual…
…that’s what’s called love.
Are you…
trying to prove something?
Well…
I just want to make sure
that all this time, I haven’t hurt you.
And… how does doing this help?
Well…
It does help me understand something.
What do you mean?
My feelings.
I got to realize that…
I’m sorry,
but I booked a ride home.
Can you cancel it, and I’ll walk you home?
Well, I’m sorry,
but I would like to cancel my booking.
But…
take the money, please.
But is it too far to walk there?
Will you feel achy?
I won’t.
I’m good at walking, you know.
Baifern even complained that
she doesn’t want to walk with me
because I walk fast.
But I think you walk slowly.
Well… Hmm?
I’m home now.
Well done.
While we were walking home together,
you mentioned the movie
you wanted to watch.
What is the name again?
It’s Love You to Debt.
They’re hosting a special screening
in the cinema again.
Why?
You’re not in a rush
to go watch it, right?
Uh-huh. Why?
I was just asking.
THERE'S A SPECIAL SCREENING
AT THE CINEMA AGAIN
WHY?
YOU’RE NOT IN A RUSH
TO WATCH IT, RIGHT?
- UH-HUH. WHY?
- I WAS JUST ASKING
Hey!
Ouch!
Well…
Why, huh?
Can’t you just walk to me
and talk properly?
This way, it's more exciting.
It’s scandalous.
Yeah.
So, what’s your business?
Tell the company we’ve
successfully united the group.
Also, tell them
I’m behind this whole thing.
This is such an easy task.
You can do it, right?
Hold on.
What again?
They’re trying to find out
who the traitor is, aren’t they?
Also, you’ve spent time with us the most.
If you have nothing to share with them,
they might end up suspecting you.
I’m sacrificing myself to save you.
Feeling touched, huh?
I’m trying to figure out what you want
as you’re offering yourself
to help like this?
Come on.
Why do you see me as that kind of person?
And you aren’t?
I am, actually.
Let’s talk about that later.
That’s it for now.
It’s my fault
for proposing that camping trip idea.
Well, previously,
Jun often sent me
this type of show to watch.
MARS used this opportunity to clear
the air and understand each other better.
Jun?
But Jun said he would help us.
When does the music show
Jun appears on air again?
Music show? Please give me a second.
Music show?
It’s not on the schedule.
What?
How could Jun lie to us
through a straight face like that?
I’m sorry.
Just forget about it.
When you said it’ll be
the five of them together,
does that include Pepper?
Yes.
If that’s the case,
it wouldn’t count as every member.
Per.
Yeah?
- I want to ask for some advice.
- Yeah.
Well,
I already understood what’s going on.
And I think I…
Where’s the damn one who told me
to hurry back for the meeting?
Where did he disappear to?
And where the hell have you been? Come.
People have been waiting for you
since this morning.
Look. Nano is already sleeping.
I’m not. I’m just resting my eyes.
I've got my own stuff to do,
you know, meeting people.
Who’s like you,
just stuck in a room all the time?
At least I'm being useful
to the group, all right?
I'm working on arranging the song.
I’m more useful than you, man!
I went to be a pawn
and turned the enemy’s pawn
into a favorite.
- It’s so damn fun!
- I’m confused.
Pawn?
Did you just come back
from a pawn shop, Jun?
Enough.
It’s good we’re all here now.
So, what’s our plan now, Thame?
I think the way to prove to the company
that we can continue as MARS is our song
to show that
we still have enough potential
to earn them money as a group.
And this is everything we have to do.
LYRICS
MELODY
CHOREOGRAPHY / MV
MV SHOOTING / MV RELEASE! / PROMOTION
I think we must complete all these
before the day of our concert,
so we can change
the concert pattern in time.
So, we have three months left.
But if we look back at the timeline,
we’ll have about one
to one and a half months
to show the company
the amount of profits we could make,
and that means
we have around one month
to produce the song.
Our MV must be finished
one day before the release date.
How long do you think it will take
to design the performance
and the MV, Nano?
As for the performance,
I need around one week
to design the choreography
and one more week for practice.
I think we can work
on the MV parallel to that,
so we’ll have roughly three weeks.
Thame and Dylan,
you need to finish the song
and melody within three weeks.
Think you can do that?
Nano will be in charge of the choreography
and the dance challenge,
but you also need to practice
your singing more
because you will have
more lines this time.
Thame and Dylan
are in charge of the song together.
I won’t be designing
the MV concept, though.
Let me go mess with the company
and make them stay away from you all.
It’s way easier for me.
I don’t trust you from the start,
you know.
If I assign you to design the MV concept,
I have no clue how your idea
will turn out.
But you picked the right task
for yourself, though.
I’m deciding who should be
designing the MV concept.
Thame and Dylan in charge of the song
or Nano in charge of the performance.
I bet you three could come up
with an idea.
How about you, Per?
What do you think he’ll do?
He must be supervising all the tasks
to go as planned, of course.
All right, it's settled then, Per.
I’ll get going.
Are you messing with the company?
I’m off to bed.
Cool.
Then, let me write my plan
and insert it into the schedule.
I’ll schedule the date for us, Thame.
SHOW THAME DANCE CHALLENGE IDEA
AND THE PERFORMANCE IDEA ROUND 1/2
THAME CHECK BOTH TO MAKE SURE
THEY'RE IN THE SAME DIRECTION
COMBINE LYRICS + MELODY
ADJUST IT ROUND 1/2
BRAINSTORM THE DIRECTION WITH THAME
REFINE THE DETAILS
MEETING FOR REVISIONS
Are you looking for a day
for your movie date?
This is what I want to talk to you about.
Let’s go play basketball and talk.
Yeah.
Did you really have to bring me here
to tutor me on dating?
Is it that difficult?
You know what?
I asked you to reflect on your feelings
because I wanted you
to come back and tell me
you don’t have feelings for him.
I didn’t expect you
to come back with movie tickets.
Why?
Did you forget
idols aren’t allowed to fall in love?
That’s why I decided
not to take charge of anything
for this single.
I don’t think I can be
a part of MARS anymore.
Well, I’m in a relationship now.
What?
You heard it right.
But you were one of the first to join us.
I just wanted to support,
so you guys could keep the work going
because I guess I can’t continue anymore.
As for you,
if you’ve already realized your feelings,
it’s still not too late
to stop yourself now,
but… between the two of us,
there have been so many things,
too many for me to just walk away.
But MARS has always been five of us.
Aw, there, there.
MARS doesn’t need to have five members.
With four members,
MARS can be perfectly complete.
You’re the main vocalist.
Jun is the sub vocalist.
Nano is the main dancer.
Dylan is the main rapper.
See?
It’s complete, really.
Come on. Teach me singing, okay?
Ugh.
Please.
Wait for Thame to come back and teach you.
He isn’t back yet.
Since you’re here now, teach me.
I don’t want to. I’m lazy!
How much longer
are you guys going to be so loud?
I’m trying to focus here.
Oh, come on.
Please.
No!
What?
When you asked me to join the group again,
you said you would teach me, didn’t you?
I didn’t say that.
Let the person
who said that teach you, okay?
He isn’t here.
Help me, okay?
See? He’s back.
Let him teach you.
Fine.
Bro.
Thame.
What are you doing?
I’ve got something on my mind.
What is it?
JUN MARS
- What?
- Why are you being so rough, babe?
Babe, my foot!
- What’s up?
- What do you want to eat tonight?
I’ll treat you to cheer you up.
Why?
Did you betray me already?
Did you already tell Miss Pemika
I’m a traitor?
No, of course.
It’s not about work.
Yeah?
PEPPER MARS
ARTIST
We haven’t figured out who Per is dating,
but I guess it’s probably someone close
because he told Thame
it’s the person he met often during work.
That person makes him feel more
meaningful than when he’s with the group.
Maybe it’s because that person
always has him in sight.
No wonder Miss Pemika asked
if Per would be part of the group reunion,
saying if we counted him in,
the reunion couldn’t really happen.
You see now how serious it is, right?
That’s why I told you,
between Thame and you,
it can never be possible.
THAME
Uncle Joei isn’t here?
He went upstairs to sleep already.
You…
knew about Per already, right?
Yes.
This is what
I want to talk to you about.
I want to tell you in person.
I think between us…
Are you saying you saw him touch the ring
while talking about this?
Yeah.
The first time I saw him wear this ring
was around three months ago.
Why did you say that before I did so?
- Eh?
- I saw it, so I must talk about it.
But seriously,
if they gave each other the rings,
it means they must have been
dating before that, right?
See? Look at this.
The photos he posted
are all about his MC jobs,
variety shows, events, and dinners.
- Hold on.
- Hey.
Show me that IG account.
But seriously, I just don’t get it.
What’s the point of finding out
who Per is dating?
It’s useful for us because
that person will make us understand him
the way we haven’t before.
Otherwise, he wouldn’t have said
he’s not important to MARS.
Jun, whose IG account do you want me
to show you again?
I think there aren’t
many possible choices left.
If it’s someone who has seen him
all this time…
Ugh, my head hurts so much.
I’ve submitted the work twice already,
but Miss Gam won’t approve it.
This time, I even went to pray for it,
you know.
Let’s try again next time.
Fine.
Help me pray in case my energy
doesn’t reach the divine forces.
Annyeong.
What is it again?
MARS keeps causing trouble, huh?
What are you talking about?
I have no clue.
By the way, Ming,
lend me some coins to get some water.
Wow, now, they're asking for money.
Two of you came, and no one has money?
Come on, Ming.
The whole group’s been put on pause.
How are we supposed to have any money?
If you don’t have any coins with you,
please lend me your phone to scan and pay.
Fine.
I’ve got some change with me.
Here.
Hey,
- go already.
- Just go.
Thank you.
I’m stressed out, come on.
It’s not her?
But seriously,
Per didn’t mention if he’s dating
a woman or a man, right?
- …on 10th.
- Hey, can we have more coins?
Whoa. Stop it already.
We just saw you use your phone.
Scan and pay, okay?
Why are you asking us for money, huh?
We’re broke!
Come on.
You know we can’t compete
when it comes to luck.
Now, let’s not compete
with who's more broke, okay?
Come on, Jun.
I literally have no more left.
Like, I’m broke.
If Ming doesn’t have any,
how about you, Tae?
Listen up.
Why do you want so many drinks, huh?
I have to join the meeting real soon.
WHATCHA SMILIN ABOUT?
MOTTO - WITH GREAT POWER
COMES GREAT RESPONSIBILITY
Come on, Tae.
Don’t be mean to me.
We’ve been working together for so long.
Won’t you be kind to me a little?
Ming just gave you some.
Spend your own money, okay?!
I’ll head to the meeting now.
I can’t stand this anymore.
Let’s go.
- Now.
- You’re right.
Come on, Tae.
It’s only 10 THB.
I'm begging for the last time. Please.
Don’t touch me. Enough.
I need to go now.
Take it!
Here you are!
Gotcha. Why did you buy
the same ring as me?
Eh? You saw that it looks good on me, huh?
- It’s you who bought that after I did.
- Oh, wow.
- I bought it before you.
- Nope. You bought one after I did.
- It was a buy one get one free promotion.
- Exactly.
- The client…
- Our client has arrived.
Hello.
Here she is,
the one who got me stressed out.
Ouch. I’m about to faint.
Hey.
I figured it out now.
It’s Gam.
You still aren’t allowed to come
to the company, are you?
That’s why I have to secretly
come here at night.
When you guys found out it’s me,
I thought all four of you
would come and talk.
I wanted all of them to come,
but I preferred talking to you alone.
There are many things
I want to understand and beg you.
Is that because you still
can’t decide which way to choose?
I’ve already made my decision,
and I want Per to make the same decision.
One game, okay?
You talked to Gam already, right?
Yeah.
So, what’s your answer?
All I could think was, "Really?",
both about your decision
and you saying I’m important to the group.
An all-rounder is supposed
to fulfill every position.
If you can’t sing,
I must do it.
If Nano can’t dance,
I must do it,
or if Dylan can’t rap,
I must be able to do it.
I think I’m not that type of member.
To me, an all-rounder can be defined
in two ways.
The first one is exactly what you said,
and the second one is who you are now.
Someone who can take care
of the other members.
It’s true I’m the leader,
but what I do is to represent you guys,
talking to the company
and determining the vision with them.
But the person who can
take care of our members
has always been you.
I believe that
if MARS could pick the leader themselves,
it wouldn’t be me.
You should have been in this position.
I can only set the goals,
but the one who can work through the steps
is you.
You said MARS doesn’t need you.
That’s totally not true.
MARS needs you the most.
You also said
you couldn’t do all those things.
That’s not true either.
You can sing,
rap, and also dance.
Most importantly, you excel at them.
Even if
Gam and I are a ticking time bomb
for you guys?
I have my own ticking time bomb, don’t I?
Per, trust me,
don’t break up with her.
I know you can’t ask for a breakup
because when I was about to tell him
that I could no longer like him,
I turned speechless too.
That’s why I think
we’ll just keep going together like this.
I believe that we can both work as a group
and like someone at the same time
because both are part of our lives.
You’re madly in love with him, aren’t you?
All right.
From listening to me,
are you now convinced
to become MARS again?
Well, I have a question.
What is it?
Can I take her to our group’s house too?
I’m sick of those crazy in love, man.
Come on.
You aren’t different from me.
Blue.
Guys,
this is Gam, my girlfriend.
- Hello.
- Hello. Hello.
I think you all know each other already.
I bet you have something
to talk to her about.
I’m sorry that
I used to be flirty with you.
Well,
I didn’t know you’re Per’s girlfriend.
When?
All the time.
- Per.
- Jun!
Don’t touch me.
- Per.
- You did that all the time, huh?
That’s what I always do, you know.
But she’s my girlfriend.
- Per.
- You shouldn’t have done that.
- Per, relax.
- Jun!
- Per. Per.
- Let’s fight.
- Don’t.
- You know what I’m like, don’t you?
- Run.
But she’s my girlfriend!
- Run. Run now.
- Hurry up.
- Hey.
- Jun.
Per!
Jun.
- Come here.
- Per.
Just jump over it.
Po, I have something to talk to you about.
Can you come to the group's house?
I thought he would come.
I also wanted him to come.
Why?
I just don’t get it.
Well, let me ask you something.
When you were about to say
you would stop your feelings for him
and then you didn’t say it,
what did you say instead?
I just want to tell you
to take good care of yourself.
I want him to take good care of himself,
so that we can fight
on this journey together.
You know what?
That could be interpreted
in the other way.
What is it?
Stop feeling for each other
and take care of yourself.
Huh?
You're dumb.
I’m not surprised he didn't come.
He must be lying there
all sad and mopey now.
Thame.
You need to get good at laying low.
One more thing you need
to be careful of is the distance.
If you don’t want anyone to catch on,
when you’re outside,
keep a five-meter distance.
Gam and I have been using
this distance all this time.
Thanks.
Hey, if Mr. B told Mr. A
to take good care of himself,
what did that mean?
It’s this clear,
but you couldn’t figure it out?
He dumped you.
When I told you to take care of yourself,
how did you interpret it?
Huh?
You didn’t think
I told you to take care
of yourself alone, did you?
Well…
You did?
So, what did you mean?
Anyway,
I’ll tell you about Per and Gam.
Per and Gam?
Which Gam are you talking about?
- You mean, Miss Gam?
- Yeah.
Huh?
So, you told Pepper
they could do both things
at the same time?
So, when you told me
to take care of myself…
Oh.
I meant, be careful.
Well, it won’t be good
if others know that…
Well,
I might get fired, right?
You aren’t walking fast as Baifern said.
Well, you’re walking at this speed.
Try walking at your own speed then.
But…
Come on.
Next time, don’t follow my speed, okay?
Just be yourself.
I want to adjust myself
to your rhythm too.
How about we find a balance
to see which speed suits us best?
That sounds like a good idea.
I’m heading inside.
Thanks for walking me home.
Yeah.
You should go back now. It’s already late.
I know.
Why haven’t you left yet?
Why did you come back and check?
I just wanted to know if you left already.
Just go.
You haven’t left?
Come.
Walk me to the bus stop.
Which bus number are you taking?
Seventy-seven.
Hey, it’s here.
Eh? You aren’t going?
Can I walk you home again?
Po.
Can you walk me there again?
Can I walk you home one more time?
You don’t feel achy at all?
You do?
No.
Well, then…
I bet neither of us will arrive home.
You’re right.
Pepper told me that
when we’re outside,
we must keep a five-meter distance,
so we won’t get caught.
Caught for what?
Caught for…
Forget about it.
And…
do we need to keep that distance?
Well,
I think we should,
but…
since we have time,
we should have watched the movie,
but we can’t make it in time now.
Anyway,
can we watch it next week?
Um…
Let’s not keep a five-meter distance
because even five centimeters
feels too far apart.
We can start working on our MV now.
So, we’re going to be busy
both day and night, right?
I will handle the MV.
Do you want to get to work
right beside him?
You’ll have to give it your all, though.
If you slack off,
Thame will definitely get mad.
Why are you putting
so much pressure on me?
If you want him to love you,
why not do something he’ll admire?