Do what's best for you.
Because that's what's best for me.
They're all dead.
Madam Ju,
Mom, and Dad.
Everyone I've ever loved is dead.
And you'll die…
because of me too.
I don't care.
Your wound.
It shouldn't get wet.
You…
Your powers…
My powers…
are back.
EPISODE 9
THE UNMASKED TRUTH
Is this why…
humans willingly become foolish?
What's wrong?
When did you wake up?
A while ago.
Was I snoring?
- I wouldn't mind worse things than that.
- So I was?
- No, you weren't.
- Are you sure?
Yes. So let me see your face.
No.
Why not?
I don't know. I'm feeling a bit shy.
Let's go out. I'm hungry.
I thought a cup of pour-over coffee
was all you needed.
I know. Maybe it's because
I'm almost human now.
You didn't book the whole place today.
I realized
it might not be a bad idea
to eat among humans.
With so many of them around,
it's nice and lively.
One couple set, please.
I'm afraid that's only available
during Christmas, sir.
But that's the whole reason we're here.
Can't we just consider today as Christmas?
To commemorate my mingling with humans.
We don't have the ingredients, sir.
Is that right?
Then let's find another place
that serves couple sets.
We'll just have two of these, please.
Yes, ma'am.
Isn't this discrimination against demons?
Why are couple sets only available
on Jesus's birthday?
Let's come back on Christmas
and celebrate with your favorite cake.
Are you telling a demon
to celebrate Jesus's birthday?
So you don't want to?
No, I don't mean that.
It's not that I don't want to.
I was just saying.
But why does everyone
make such a fuss over Christmas?
Christmas somehow makes you excited.
As if you were a kid again.
Now I see
why everyone gets so noisy and rowdy
during Christmas.
I'll do my best as my name suggests.
I don't mean to brag,
but I once got set up with a chaebol.
The famous heiress
fell in love with me at first sight
and kept pestering me
to register our marriage.
But I told her,
"I refuse to become a chaebol's dog."
"I shall become
a hunting dog for the public."
I coldly and resolutely turned her down.
A hunting dog?
Is that why you try to smell everything?
How about another round someplace else?
Love at first sight, my foot.
- Give me your wrist.
- What for?
I'll teach him a lesson
so he won't run his mouth about you again.
Since he wishes to be a hunting dog,
I could give him the nose of...
Forget it.
I'm the one who suggested
registering the marriage and bailed.
Why are you taking that sleazebag's side?
This is so annoying.
By the way, did I tell you?
Tell me what?
I'm not going to work today.
It's the company's anniversary.
Really?
What on earth is going on?
Why is Director Jeong unhappy about
Do Do-hee's withdrawal?
Shouldn't he be happy now that she's safe?
Goodness.
Is he still asleep?
I love not going to work.
I thought you loved going to work.
I thought so too
until I fell for a demon.
So what do humans usually do on a date?
They usually grab a bite and have coffee.
That's about it.
How insignificant.
Even if it's with me?
What is it?
I'm outside your door, Director Jeong.
Open up.
I'm not home right now.
Where are you then?
We're at the Han River.
That's right. We're on a date.
- In your condition?
- I'm fully recovered.
CALL ENDED
DIRECTOR JEONG
What did I miss?
I've been wondering.
What are those
insignificant-looking things?
- Those?
- Yes.
They're tandem bikes for couples.
Couples…
For couples?
Let's try one of those!
It'll be extremely insignificant.
I love insignificant things.
Let's go.
- What?
- Come on.
Where are we going?
- Let's get on one of those bikes.
- But…
Why are you sitting in front?
Hold on, look at that!
- What?
- Over there!
Let's try that insignificant thing too.
Is everything for couples these days?
Shall we?
- Sure, let's go.
- Let's go.
- Here we go.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- I'm lifting my feet.
Here we go.
- Higher!
- I said higher!
- Up!
What could it be?
- Higher!
- What would be the most effective way
for her to screw us over
while our guard is down?
- Higher!
- Could it be…
- No way.
- Even higher!
Then what about…
No, that's not it either.
My head is splitting, for crying out loud.
I remember my IQ being pretty high,
but have I been drinking too much?
All my brain cells seem dead.
Whatever.
I'm more of a doer than a thinker.
- So cute.
- I like this place.
Nothing is more beautiful
than man-made landscapes.
Isn't it usually the opposite?
I prefer human creations to those of God.
That's why I'm more of a collector
than a traveler.
Do you not like God?
Does anyone like their boss?
Even though I've never met God in person,
I can't seem to get attached.
Watching the world deteriorate
for 200 years didn't help either.
I wonder what your life has been like
for the past 200 years.
An insignificant human being
could never fathom a demon's existence.
I'm not trying to fathom you.
I just want to accept you the way you are.
Apparently, demons used to be
the guardians of mankind.
Is that true?
Daiomai.
It's an ancient Greek word meaning
"to share the same fate."
The word "demon" comes from that word.
"To share the same fate."
So I was right about us
sharing the same fate.
Then how did they end up becoming evil?
Let's say I gave in
to the hardships in life.
Humans turn to the dark side
after just a few years of work.
I had to do this for 200 years.
I guess you're not too bad.
Then you're back to being
your original self.
You're my guardian.
Let's go.
Okay.
Customer number 82, your couple drink set
and complimentary plush toy are ready.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
I'm starting to think
humans are insignificant
yet adorable at the same time.
It's as if I took in a kitty
and ended up caring about
every stray cat on earth.
Who would've known
affection could be this contagious?
Are you now comparing me to a cat
instead of a longhorn beetle?
What do you want, babe?
Whatever you're getting, babe.
If you don't like being called kitty,
then what about "babe"?
No.
Or you could call me hubby.
You must be crazy.
What do you mean?
I am your hubby.
- Let's just go with kitty.
- No.
Look, it's beautiful.
It is.
Seriously, nothing ever gets past her.
My goodness.
Nice.
This one's nice too.
Every single picture looks flawless.
They're so photogenic.
Goodness, what on earth am I doing?
I'm not their photographer or anything.
Get it together, Noh Su-ahn.
You're here to dig out the truth.
She may fool everyone else, but not me.
Do Do-hee, it's time for you
to reveal your true, horrific colors.
Why did you refuse
to go on that insignificant ferry?
Later. We have all the time in the world.
Later when?
Let's fix a date.
Otherwise, I might have to wait
another year…
Hello?
Hi, sweetie. Mommy's almost home.
Okay. See you soon.
Do Do-hee.
What a jerk.
He ruined such a great song, didn't he?
Let's go.
I don't like this music.
Why not? I like it.
I want something to dance to.
Shall we?
No, I have two left feet.
Just follow my lead.
You must trust your partner
when you slow dance.
This is our song now.
What happened?
What the hell?
What is this?
I'm out here breaking my back
while they're enjoying themselves all day.
I quit.
It's not like me to work my butt off.
I'm more of a thinker
than a doer after all.
That's right. I should go.
Next week is the earliest we can hold
the special stockholders' meeting
to elect the new chairperson.
Make it this week.
That's going to be a challenge.
There are procedures to follow when…
I'm paying you all that money
for you to deal with challenges like this.
Let's speed things up as much as we can.
Once you become the chairman,
I suppose your son
will be leading Mirae Electronics.
There's something I learned
while I was under my mother
for over 20 years.
The importance of deprivation.
Deprivation leads to growth.
That's what I plan to teach my son.
Good shot!
17 YEARS AGO
I'm here, Mother.
I have to wash it away.
Yes, I have to.
I have to wash away
all my filthy sins.
If I don't…
Do you know why
my mother turned her back on us?
I guess she didn't like us.
It was self-hatred.
She despised us
because she despised her own blood.
Surely even someone as thoughtless as you
must realize we're at a critical juncture.
We must convince the public
that we have
a solid and stable succession plan.
I understand.
I'm not like my mother.
I intend to fix you up and use you.
I can never trust anyone
who isn't of my own blood.
MESSAGE
Do you have a second phone?
It's just…
It's for girls.
Don't worry. I'll sort everything out.
ENFORCER
Why haven't I heard from you?
Don't tell me you're bailing out.
What a peaceful morning.
It's been a while.
I ended up doing
what's best for me, Madam Ju.
I always thought happiness was fake.
You're up early.
I have to go to work.
I've been thinking.
Why don't we say yesterday was the eve
and have today
as the actual company anniversary?
No. Are you trying
to take the whole year off?
An anniversary deserves
at least two days' celebration.
You seem to have less affection
for the company than I do.
Affection for the company?
Hello, Ms. Shin.
Ms. Do, we received a document
from Mr. Noh Suk-min.
You can't sign it.
Everything's already over.
We need to catch the bastard
who tried to kill you,
find out who was behind him,
and make sure they leave you alone.
I don't want to.
Why not?
I'm fully recovered now.
I don't want to restart the whole thing.
I like the peace I have now.
RENUNCIATION OF INHERITANCE
BENEFICIARY:
DO DO-HEE
DECEDENT:
JU CHEON-SUK
What's best for you
has become what's best for me.
I decided to let go
so that everyone else would find peace,
but I'm the one who ended up happy.
You said nothing's free in this world.
Happiness requires sacrifice.
And I think it's well worth it.
Do Do-hee.
Are you really going to give up like this
without even knowing his face?
If you give up now,
you'll live the rest of your life in fear.
You can't maintain peace
by covering things up.
Let's just go see his face.
After that,
I'll do as you say.
All right.
I'll see his face and that'll be it, okay?
I've been by your side all day.
Why am I not recharged?
Let's try again once you've charged up.
Mr. Ju Seok-hoon is here.
Why does Ju Seok-hoon
keep showing up here?
Something's fishy.
It just doesn't make sense.
What do you mean?
Mr. Jeong… No, I mean Director Jeong.
He's only recently survived
a deadly attack.
So how could he have recovered so quickly?
Now that you mention it,
something's definitely off.
Let me see.
I'd say the heavens helped him.
Or his ancestors did.
You and your superstitions.
Maybe he has a secret.
A secret?
Maybe he's been hogging
something good for himself.
What?
A secret, huh?
This is nice.
Since I missed the board meeting
and everything,
I wanted to see you.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm doing a lot better than I expected.
That's a relief.
Do you remember going
to that tattoo parlor with me in the US?
You said
you were scared of needles
and that you'd never get a tattoo.
I was drunk for this one.
I didn't even feel a thing.
You've been acting out of character a lot
since you met Mr. Jeong.
Do-hee.
Don't you…
regret your decision at all?
No, I don't regret it.
Thanks, Seok-hoon.
And I'm sorry.
Mr. Jeong.
Can we talk?
He likes me too much.
How are you?
Good as new.
You seemed to be in critical condition.
I tend to recover fast.
Vampires stay young
by consuming human blood.
What's your secret?
Again with that vampire nonsense?
Are you that interested in the occult?
It's not the occult
that I'm interested in.
I'm interested in you, Mr. Jeong.
You're smitten with me, aren't you?
Are you into men?
Mr. Jeong.
What do you get
from your relationship with Do-hee?
I don't see how you'd benefit
from being her husband and bodyguard.
I need her.
If that were true,
you wouldn't just be sitting back
as she gives up on something important
because of you.
We're finally on the same page.
I don't plan on just sitting back.
Are you happy now?
The secret to my recovery
is a thirst for revenge.
I couldn't possibly die
without paying back
the one who did this to me.
DO DO-HEE
I'm free now.
I can finally go outside
without a bodyguard.
Congratulations, ma'am.
Why don't we grab a drink to celebrate?
I forgot what a goody-goody you are.
Let's do it.
Just one drink though.
MIRAE GROUP TO ELECT CHAIRMAN
AT STOCKHOLDER MEETING
It seems like
Ms. Do has officially given up.
I don't think things should end this way.
Something doesn't feel right.
Exactly.
Speaking of which,
can you draw a sketch of half a face?
What do you think?
Hey, you're quite talented.
A lot more so than you look.
How do I look?
Now, mirror it.
The hide-and-seek is over.
SUNWOL FOUNDATION
This is the boss's workplace.
Let's keep it safe and clean ourselves.
Stay in line!
Make sure the boss
doesn't breathe in a speck of dust!
- Move along!
- Yes, sir!
Who are you?
- I'm the assistant director here.
- Are you sure?
Look, the bags under my eyes
are the proof.
- Pass!
Director Jeong.
I need you down at the theater.
Please come and kick these mongrels out.
The boss is here.
Hello, boss.
- Hello, boss!
I said I wasn't your boss.
What's with the illegal occupation?
Oh my. You're all working so hard.
Please have a drink. Great job.
Kick these mongrels out.
The performance is coming up.
They'll scare the audience away.
Thank you so much for your hard work.
So you call yourselves Deulgaepa,
as in "wild dogs"?
Yes, boss.
- Yes, boss!
You know what your name also sounds like?
Deulkkaepa,
as in perilla seeds and scallions.
My goodness.
You're funny, boss.
Our name, the Wild Dogs,
symbolizes our fearlessness
and doggedness…
Hereafter, we will be known
as the soul of Korean cuisine,
the Perilla Seeds and Scallions!
- The Perilla Seeds and Scallions!
Anyway,
I have a task for you.
If you fail,
I forbid you to show up
in front of me ever again.
We're ready to risk our lives, boss!
- As you say, boss!
Let's go!
- Let's go!
Director Jeong,
I guess you sorted everything out.
You quit being
her bodyguard and husband, right?
I warned you, didn't I?
After all I've said,
do you really want to become
an insignificant human?
Do you know what it's like to be human?
Every day feels like walking on thin ice,
and we use that as an excuse
to prey on each other.
Humans are the most cowardly
and despicable beings in the world.
You were perfect because you were a demon.
Death, love, fear…
You were who you were
because you were free from those things.
Stop it.
I'm not giving up on Do Do-hee
no matter what.
And I'm not giving up on you.
I can't just watch you
jump into this fiery pit.
This is your last warning, Jin Ga-young.
Don't cross the line.
What's so special about her?
What makes her worth
putting everything on the line?
Star Jin.
How about
we wish the two of them happiness?
If the price of their happiness
is this high,
it can't be true happiness.
Let me do it.
No, I'll do it.
Cheers.
It's so nice
to be drinking in the open air.
I'm glad it's to your liking.
My journey has finally come to an end,
although it ended in an unexpected way.
Letting go turns out to be
easier than I thought.
It makes me wonder
why I've been holding on so desperately.
Sometimes, we bet everything on something
without even knowing why.
Maybe we only find out why
after the journey has ended.
What could be the reason for my journey?
I'm not sure.
Ms. Shin.
How was your marriage?
My ex was incredibly lame.
I didn't know it was possible
to love and loathe someone
in such a short span of time.
But now that I've come out the other side,
I understand myself better.
Had it not been for him,
I would've never known
the pathetic, shameful,
weak, and strong parts of myself.
That's what my marriage meant to me.
I didn't know
you had such passion within you.
Neither did I.
I've never loved anyone
before or after him.
I've been lukewarm all my life,
neither hot nor cold.
But I have no regrets
since I've boiled once.
That must be the reason for your journey.
That's right.
Growth can only happen after destruction.
Cheers.
Come on, raise your glass.
Bottoms up.
DO-HEE THE NUTJOB
Where are you, hubby?
Do Do-hee, your hubby is…
Do Do-hee's happiness train
is now departing!
The real mongrels were here.
What's wrong, Do-hee?
- Da-jeong.
- What?
I'm sorry for making you work
so late all the time.
It's okay.
You pay me a lot anyway.
I guess I do.
- Here.
- Do Do-hee!
You better
get your act together.
Hold on.
What is it?
Why are we laughing?
No idea.
- Cheers!
My wife is being embarrassing.
Why don't we go home now?
The sun is up.
It's so blinding.
The sun is up
Twinkle, twinkle…
Da-jeong! Where do you think you're going?
- Let's have another round.
- I have to get to work.
It's 9 a.m. I'm late.
I'm late!
Huh?
All humans are obliged
to get drunk on happiness!
Let's go!
Okay!
It's not alcohol that we're drinking.
It's happiness.
Stop drinking!
Jeong Gu-won!
You better
get your act together.
You shouldn't throw up your happiness!
Wait, stay seated.
Mr. Park, someone needs your help.
Hurry over here.
Are you okay?
Bottoms up.
Park Fork-you.
You better
get your act together.
My name's Bok-gyu, not Fork-you.
Fuck-you.
We're off.
That's enough.
Hubby,
give me a piggyback ride.
Just how much did you have to drink?
I'm feeling super happy.
It's like a huge weight
lifted off my chest.
I feel so free and happy.
And that makes me feel bad.
Because I'm the only one who's happy.
I feel so sorry for Madam Ju.
- Hubby, how about one more lap?
- Yeah?
Sure, but do you know
how many laps we've done?
Beats me.
Just one more lap, please?
Are you sure?
Can't you do that much for me, hubby?
Fine.
- Let's go!
- Run!
- Okay, should I run?
- Here we go.
- Run, demon, run!
You and your diligence.
You're even diligent in giving up.
Look.
Just where is your place out of all these?
Tell me exactly where you live.
Why do you want to know where I live?
To take you home.
What is it?
What's that look?
You're a kind man.
I'm just following
Director Jeong's orders here.
You're also responsible.
You've got to be kidding me.
You look cute when you smile.
That's all true,
but tell me where you live.
Where are we?
What do you mean? This is where you live!
This isn't where I live.
Seriously?
When did the moon get so fat?
There are still two more days left
until the full moon.
That's a relief.
Ms. Shin!
My goodness.
- These are from the boss.
- Yes, sir!
- Stay alert, okay?
Let's do this!
Memorize his face.
Memorize it. We can do…
That stings! Your stupid necklace!
- Gather up!
- Yes, sir!
Savory and spicy!
- Go, Perilla Seeds and Scallions!
- Go get him!
- Yes, sir!
Look at me!
- Stop eating.
- Show me your face.
These are women!
- Let's go in!
- Yes, sir!
This is our chance to impress the boss.
Find him!
Who are you?
ABRAXAS HAS ENTERED THE ROOM
It might become troublesome later,
so let's nip it in the bud.
What?
I think it's him.
NAME: GI KWANG-CHUL
BLUE NIGHT THEATER
You're here.
The most suitable ending
for the devil that I could think of
was hellfire.
It comes up in the book too.
Spontaneous combustion.
I'll be doing the Lord's work.
Let me tell you,
I'm not a murderer but an artist.
Do you know
what makes humans
greater than the devil or God?
Humans
can become anything.
Be it the devil, God,
or even something more than that.
Noh Suk-min, you son of a bitch.
Did I ever tell you this?
Thank you
for getting me out of prison.
I didn't know
I'd be repaying you this way.
Damn.
You'll be killed
by the devil you set free.
Shit!
Open the door!
Noh Suk-min!
This can't be happening.
Noh Suk-min, this isn't right.
Open the door.
Hey!
Open the door!
You killed someone
on top of all your dirty tricks?
You brought this upon yourself, Mother.
I REALIZED I'D GIVEN BIRTH
TO THE DEVIL'S SPAWN…
PERHAPS I'M AT FAULT…
YOU PAY FOR YOUR SINS
AND I'LL PAY FOR MINE
CEO DO DO-HEE
My head is killing me.
Here.
Thanks.
Nothing happened, right?
Madam Ju always made sure
I behaved while drunk.
Jeez, that old woman.
DETECTIVE PARK KYUNG-SOO
Yes, Detective?
We found the culprit, Ms. Do.
We got him, boss.
Your Perilla Seeds and Scallions
found him.
We found his hideout.
His name is Gi Kwang-chul.
He has countless charges
of murder and assault.
He's currently on our wanted list,
so we'll be able to track him down soon.
BLUE NIGHT THEATER
He looks more ordinary than I expected.
This seemingly ordinary man
had killed countless people.
How did he die?
It was arson.
What's strange is that
his corpse was abused.
Someone stuck a 20 cm-long knife
into his heart
after his body completely burned.
As if to leave a message.
It hurts, doesn't it?
See you in hell.
Well then…
Do-hee.
So the culprit's dead?
- Yes.
- What happened, Detective?
Well…
I need to go check something.
Could you go home with Ju Seok-hoon?
I heard the culprit got caught.
What are you looking for?
Now that the culprit is dead,
it's all over, isn't it?
What's that?
Is that a bug?
I was right.
The culprit got killed
because I saw his face.
How would anyone know
that you can find people with faces?
It's not even written in the…
Is that how you figured out
we were bugged?
I finally saw the culprit's face,
but the real culprit…
went hiding behind the dead one.
- Excuse me.
- Yes, ma'am?
Just a second.
You just woke up?
Another golf outing?
I have a lot of people to see
before the stockholders' meeting.
That sounds tough.
- Please continue.
- Yes, ma'am.
You must've been shocked.
Yeah.
I didn't know my invitation to end the war
would be met with this response.
So what does it mean?
I guess the war is over.
They've eliminated their weapon.
Do you really think this is the end?
It has to be.
It has to be over.
The secret to my recovery
is a thirst for revenge.
I couldn't possibly die
without paying back
the one who did this to me.
How did you find the culprit?
You didn't know his face.
Gu-won saw his face
when he got attacked.
So he's the one who found him.
Do-hee.
How much do you trust Mr. Jeong?
What do you mean?
Don't tell me you're suspecting him.
He would never.
- But Do-hee…
- Seok-hoon.
Gu-won
had always been there to protect me.
It's all over now.
Let's stop talking about it.
See if this can lead us
to the real culprit.
Director Jeong,
I suggest we lie low for now.
The knife was clearly a warning.
If they've been eavesdropping,
they must know your powers are acting up.
If you act rashly, you'll get hurt.
Also, there will finally be
a full moon tomorrow.
You can go back to
being your perfect self.
So wait just one day and…
The clocks…
What about them?
They've stopped.
SEOUL HANSE MEDICAL CENTER
I'm here to visit Lee Yeon-seo
in the pediatric oncology ward.
You mean the Yeon-seo
who already got discharged?
I heard she's back in the hospital.
That can't be.
She's our hospital's symbol of miracle.
- It's dropping.
- What's her oxygen level and temperature?
It's at 95%,
and her body temperature is 30°C.
- Mommy's here, Yeon-seo.
- Let's raise the body temperature first.
Hang in there, sweetie!
Yeon-seo!
Oh no…
So your name's Yeon-seo?
Do you have a wish?
I hope my parents
won't have to suffer because of me.
That's my wish.
My powers weren't just flickering.
They're completely gone.
No.
JESUS CORP.
DAEGUK BANK
What?
You know something about me, don't you?
You've become completely human.
What on earth is going on?
Tell me.
For free?
Long time no see.
- Let me show you to your table, ma'am.
- Sure.
- It's been a while.
- You're looking good.
- Hi there.
- Hi.
- Long time no see.
- Have fun.
I'll have my usual, but make it two.
Understood, ma'am.
Have a seat.
Are you a regular here?
Humans tend to judge others
by their appearances.
How come they treat you so nicely?
It's as if they were under hypnosis.
I'm not sure.
They must be able to recognize
my true worth beyond my appearance.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Is this really the right place
to discuss something like this?
Is that so?
What?
Not up your alley?
I suppose this isn't quite your style.
Who…
are you?
Why are you so surprised?
I can do everything you can.
Because I gave you those powers.
SUNWOL FOUNDATION
Are you…
God?
That's one name I have.
Some call me the universe.
Others call me time.
You know what they say.
"God is everywhere and in everything."
To me,
that sounds like God is nowhere.
Just as defiant as a demon should be.
To think we've traveled
halfway around the world
for blasphemy.
I believe you,
so give me back
my powers.
I can't do that.
- What?
- Even though I gave you the powers,
I didn't take them away from you.
Did this happen
because I haven't made a new deal?
Can I get my powers back
if I make one right now?
Deals won't change anything.
Since the powers are in the wrong body,
it's only natural for them to fade
until they're completely gone.
Then I'll…
That's right.
You're dying as we speak.
You seem to care about Do Do-hee a lot.
Few people would go to these lengths
even for their immediate families,
much less for their cousins.
Do-hee is more than family to me.
We have something in common.
So tell me.
Why did you want to see me?
I assume you know
Mr. Jeong's true identity.
Then how can I get my powers back?
There must be a way.
It's simple.
He's a demon.
Also known as the devil.
You can get your powers back
once the woman dies.
He brings misfortune upon humans
and leads them to hell.
At the full moon,
the roulette wheel will come to a stop,
and the game will end one way or another.
Let's stay up all night tonight.
I just feel like
it'd be a waste if we slept tonight.
We never went on our honeymoon.
This can be it.
What scares me is a world without you.
Like I said, I'm going to fix you up.
The only thing you can do for him is die.
You mean nothing to me.
I won't give up on either one of us.
I'm choosing both me and Do Do-hee.
Let's make a bet.
Subtitle translation by: Min-jin Kim