KING THE LAND
- Thank you.
Goodbye.
Thank you, Mr. Yoo.
- Is this enough beer?
- I think so.
We can always get more. We make money.
Hello, sir.
I'm sorry we're late, Mr. Yoo.
- Hello, Ms. Gang.
- Hello.
Thank you for coming at such short notice.
You're still in uniform.
We got your call at the airport
and came straight here.
Where's Sa-rang?
She won't pick up.
What about Mr. No?
He won't pick up either.
Let's call them in the car.
- Okay.
- Are we taking this?
- Let's go.
- You can sit in front.
- Goodness.
- I'll take that.
Thank you.
MR. NO
The person you have called is unavailable…
Mr. No is free today,
but he won't pick up.
It'll be the four of us today.
The Bangkok crew will get together soon.
- Okay.
But why won't the two of them pick up?
Maybe they're hanging out
behind our backs.
Have they finally become an item?
Really?
Gosh, he's amazing.
I knew he had it in him.
Have what? He's got nothing.
You say you're friends,
but you don't know anything.
What do you mean?
Things are already over between them.
What? Since when?
Were they ever together?
It ended before it began.
They went out by themselves
in Thailand, remember?
He asked her out on that day,
but I think he was turned down.
Really?
Did he tell you that?
How could I ask him?
It would only hurt him.
Yeah, it didn't seem like
things worked out.
I knew it would never work out.
I know Mr. Gu…
I mean, Mr. No very well.
It's not in him to date anyone.
I'd give him one-on-one lessons
on the best tips for dating,
but he couldn't keep up.
Basic skills are everything for dating.
Were you in lots of relationships?
Me?
Well, many women were into me.
But nobody ever asked me out.
I'm not that hard to figure out,
but they all feel like
I'm too good for them.
So are you saying
you've never dated anyone?
I'm telling you. I'm very popular.
But nobody can find a way to ask me out.
You can ask them out first.
No. Ladies first.
A gentleman's duty. Don't you know?
That's why you have no girlfriend.
May I have some snacks? That one.
- Here.
- Thanks a lot. Thank you.
Anyway, he must be heartbroken
to be turned down before they got to date.
I should grab a drink with him later.
Have some snacks too.
- Thank you.
- Do you want to see something funny?
Magic!
You're hilarious. I want one too.
Thank you.
- Did you paint the stairs yourselves?
- How did you know?
It didn't look professional.
Come on in.
- Okay.
- Welcome.
- What are these?
- What?
Why are there men's shoes?
EPISODE 12
What's going on, you two?
Since when?
It hasn't been that long.
You insisted that you two weren't dating.
Sorry.
Well, things happened.
Why weren't you honest with us?
Why did you fool us?
We weren't fooling you.
We just chose not to tell.
That's fooling us.
What's with the mood?
We should celebrate
instead of getting mad.
We're not mad. We're just in shock.
We used to share everything
without keeping any secrets.
That's why I'm telling you now.
Please go easy on us.
Put your cutesy act away.
How dare you try to get away with this?
Congratulations.
You two make a great couple.
Thank you.
You have great judgment.
Anyway, is there anything else
you've lied about?
We weren't trying to hide anything.
If you fool us once again,
the six of us will disband.
Even if you tell us later that you're
an illegitimate son of the chairman,
we aren't going to excuse you.
No.
I'll tell you everything honestly.
I'm actually not an illegitimate son
of the chairman.
Of course you aren't.
It was just an example.
I'm just a son.
I know. We're just daughters.
- Whose son?
- He's right.
He's the chairman's son.
Come on. That scared us.
How can you make up such a lie?
Our chairman's last name is Gu,
and yours is No.
You're right. Come on.
I almost fell for that.
Yes, the chairman's son
is the head manager, right?
I hear he's a jerk
who has a rotten personality.
That rude nepotism guy
and our Mr. No here
are on a completely different level.
I'm that rude, rotten nepotism guy.
I'm sorry for accidentally deceiving you.
I'm Gu Won, the head manager.
The guy who's staring at the wall
isn't Department Manager Yoo.
He's Manager No Sang-sik.
Sa-rang, is this true?
Let me make a formal introduction.
He's Head Manager Gu Won,
and that's Manager No Sang-sik.
I'm Manager No Sang-sik.
Nice to meet you.
Are you serious? Wait.
Really? That's crazy.
Do you think that went all right?
Sure, I think so.
What a relief.
Mr. Gu.
The floor is quite cold.
Please sit on this.
- No, it's warm here.
- Please sit comfortably.
I'm very comfortable.
We don't have much to serve here.
A sitting cushion? Escort him to the sofa.
- Mr. Gu, please sit here.
- No.
I'm really comfortable here.
- I'm fine.
- Sit up here.
You're making us feel awkward.
That's enough.
We kept it a secret
because you'd feel awkward.
Of course it feels awkward.
He's the chairman's son.
It'd be weird if we were at ease.
This is even more awkward.
Please sit comfortably.
Why are you kneeling?
- Sit at ease.
- Please.
Well, Mr. Gu.
If I misbehaved in any way,
please show me your mercy.
No, you didn't misbehave in any way.
Da-eul, please treat me
as recklessly as you did before.
- It's easier for me.
- Oh my.
- Did I treat you recklessly?
- Yes.
No way, I wouldn't do that.
You did. You were absolutely reckless.
You tried to put him in his place
in Bangkok,
and even threatened him once.
I did? When did I do that?
"Mr. Exclamation Mark!"
"Back there."
Don't you remember saying that?
It's okay, really.
I know you were looking out for someone
just starting his career.
It's all right.
I'm so sorry.
I deserve to die.
I deserve to die!
I'm so sorry.
- I'm so sorry.
- What's with you?
- What?
- I'm so sorry.
You're going overboard.
Well,
Mr. Gu.
I'm so sorry,
but please excuse me for a moment.
- Where are you going?
- Me?
Over there.
Sure.
We need to talk.
We can talk here in peace.
Come on out.
Okay.
I mean,
why did you have to take things that far?
Why would you do that to your colleagues?
It's not like I have any power.
I also had to do as I was told.
Even so, you should've tipped us off.
How could you do that as a peer?
You know what it's like to be powerless.
And consider how I felt
when I couldn't call him Mr. Gu.
At the airport,
I was going to explain that I was Mr. No,
then I…
I'm sorry.
Here you go, sir.
You treated me like a friend
up until five minutes ago.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
I don't have any brothers
or close male friends,
so I'm not sure
if I'll make a good friend,
but I'll do my best.
Let's be good friends.
Okay, Won.
Pyeong-hwa, please treat me like a friend.
Please sit comfortably.
Yes, of course, Mr. Gu.
Would you like more beverages?
Please don't do this.
I'm not the head manager.
I'm Sa-rang's boyfriend.
Yes, Mr. Sa-rang's Boyfriend.
If I can help you in any way,
I'll help you no matter…
Would he ever need my help?
Staying quiet would help.
Stop blabbering.
Okay.
Anyway, let's overcome
this state of affairs wisely…
- What am I saying?
- Pyeong-hwa.
Yes.
Anyway, I'll go get Da-eul.
You can stay. I'll go.
Wait.
I'll take responsibility
for this state of affairs and bring her.
- Please sit.
- But still…
- I'll go.
- Please sit.
- Please sit comfortably.
- But…
Yes, Mr. Sa-rang's Boyfriend.
What are you doing?
How could this happen?
What do you mean?
You were never as popular as me.
How could you start dating first?
How does this make any sense?
I have
absolutely no idea.
No idea about what?
About what makes you think that.
And why didn't you tell me
you two were dating?
How could you hide it from me?
Goodness.
My gosh.
When did it start?
- No Sang-sik.
- Yes?
- You can cry.
- Okay.
You can cry. Was she really mad?
- Yes.
- You can cry.
Goodness.
I'm sad we're not going to Dubai.
It's empty.
I'm sad it's empty.
What are you two talking about?
Are you mad because I didn't tell you?
No, we get it.
We can understand that much.
Then what? Are you worried about me?
That I might get hurt?
Why would you get hurt?
Is Mr. No that bad?
Mr. Gu.
Yes, right. Mr. Gu.
Is he the bad boy type?
No, he's far from it.
I wouldn't be dating him if he were.
Then why? Why would you get hurt?
Well, you know.
I thought you two might be worried
about the difference in status.
Hey.
People are all the same.
Difference in status? As if.
She's right.
There may be a difference,
but it's nothing before love.
Then what were you two
discussing so seriously?
We were having a serious discussion
that you may have made a rash decision.
It wasn't a rash decision.
I thought about it for a while.
He's a great guy.
What do you like about him?
He's someone I dreamed of.
He doesn't make me anxious
or disappointed.
And he's always by my side
when I need him.
He really showed up almost magically
whenever I was in trouble.
Mr. No is more lovey-dovey than he seems.
Mr. Gu.
Whatever. "Mr. No" has already stuck.
Anyway, he seems like a great guy.
Congrats.
I hope our Sa-rang will be
dearly loved in this relationship.
Thanks, guys.
Now, we have a reason
to party hard all night!
Sounds great!
Weren't we partying this whole time?
- No.
- What?
We haven't even gotten started.
- Let's party.
- All right. Time to get started.
It's time to begin
My gosh.
"King Hotel became the first Korean hotel
to win the World of Best Talent,
surpassing many major global hotels."
"King Hotel gave all the credit
to its staff
for 100 years of its history."
"They showcased the class
of the best hotel in Korea to the world."
The class of our hotel skyrocketed
because I stepped up
as our representative.
You represented us?
- Since when?
- I welcomed the guests.
The first person to greet people
is the representative of the hotel.
And I carried out that difficult task.
You're right.
You successfully carried out
such a difficult task.
Great job.
You're the best.
You say that with such a mad face.
You've done well too.
If you keep this up,
you'll be in charge soon.
Stop talking nonsense.
The situation has already turned.
Slowly take over the Hotel,
Air, and Distribution.
The world is now yours, Mr. Gu.
It doesn't matter
who the world belongs to.
Let's wonder if it's worth living in.
It'll be worth living in
if you take over the group.
I'll cover every step of your journey
with flowers from now on.
Put your trust in me.
Seriously.
That event was quite touching.
I began to think of our old days.
I almost choked up.
I got to see Mr. Gu in a different light.
I honestly thought he'd ruin this event,
but it was a great success.
We just saved a fortune on marketing.
Other global hotel chains
have requested the video of the event.
And World Luxury Travel Guide
also asked us for an interview.
You all sound very satisfied.
Yes, our staff is satisfied,
and their spirits have gone up too.
I must have overestimated all of you.
I can't believe you shed tears
at that overly sentimental show.
Who should I put my trust in
as I lead this company?
Preying on people's sentiments
can win praise easily.
But will it bring us any money?
How does this help us
overcome the management crisis
faced by the group?
Is now the time to manage
with our emotions?
Other groups are discussing
going into survival mode,
not just contingency plans.
I also spoke
to the chairman a few days ago.
That I cannot trust him.
Don't make me lose my trust in you too.
I won't drag this out.
Only those who will follow me
are to attend the meeting today.
I'd like to commend you
for the 100th-anniversary event.
Anniversaries were usually excuses
to invite people who could be useful to us
and to treat them.
But this time, it was truly our occasion.
Head Manager Gu, great work.
Don't mention it, sir.
It's all thanks to our staff.
Well, the event may have ended well,
but it's too early
to open the champagne, sir.
What do you mean?
As a group,
our sales, profits, and stock price
are stagnant.
Don't you think we're doing well
in this time of recession?
If you consider inflation
and the increase in interest rates,
I wouldn't say we're stagnant,
but retrogressing.
What do you think, Ms. Gu?
I agree.
Six groups among the top ten corporations
have entered contingency management.
We must declare the same
before it's too late
and restructure our group.
What about others?
It looks like you're all on the same page.
You came thoroughly prepared.
At least I should keep it together.
We're already late.
I don't think now's the time to do that.
Contingency management is all a show.
It's an official threat to the staff
that they must tighten their belts
because we're in a crisis.
Don't you know cutting costs
is the most effective way
to increase short-term profits?
I do.
And that it's a move we always use
to pile up money in our company account.
Do you all agree with Ms. Gu?
Is this normal?
Mr. Gu, as you already know,
cutting costs isn't the biggest issue
just for us, but for all corporations.
You all wish to make King Group
into a world-renowned company,
yet all you can talk about
is extorting our employees.
Luxury brands exist
because history lies within their value.
If we wish to become
a world-renowned company,
I believe we must be equipped
with a worthwhile history.
So…
do you wish to write the story
of chasing after short-time profits
by extorting the staff?
If we want to make history,
we must survive first.
The dead don't get to tell a story.
How will we live?
That's more important
than survival itself.
It's concerning
that you're in management
with that attitude.
Father.
If you can't decide, I will.
Is cutting costs the only way
of improving our business?
Yes.
Are you confident that we can do better
without cutting costs?
Yes, I am.
This is great news.
This means we're going to do well
whether we cut costs or not.
At the next meeting,
bring me reports on what you'll do
for the future of King Group.
You.
And you. Both of you.
Yes, sir.
The war has finally begun.
She has a million people on her side,
whereas you
only have me.
It's not just you.
It's you and me both.
Yes, you're right.
It's always been the two of us.
You're right.
What's with you?
Come on.
Mr. Gu,
please remember this.
That I'll always be by your side.
Even if we must face a million
or ten million foes, we'll be fine.
Because we are…
one.
I'd be better off alone.
You liar.
Today is my last flight.
I'll be working at headquarters
starting tomorrow.
I'll always remember
these beautiful flights
I shared with all of you.
Thank you for your hard work, Ms. Yoo.
I prepared this for you.
Gosh, you didn't have to.
Mi-na, you're the best.
Please take good care of our team,
Purser Hwang Mi-na.
I'll do my best, just as you taught me.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you so much for your service.
Thank you, everyone.
Hello?
Hey, did you see how my team
topped in-flight sales?
Yes, isn't it amazing?
I got promoted and got moved
to headquarters thanks to that.
Really?
Hey, one sec. I'll call you back.
What? Do you have something to say?
Don't you?
No.
At the very least,
you should have said sorry.
Why should I?
Do you even have to ask?
You weren't going to promote me
to purser anyway.
You took advantage of me
to increase sales.
You've been working long enough
to increase sales
without promotion at stake.
And you already know
it'll be tough for you to become a purser.
What?
Did you think
I didn't know about your divorce?
Everyone worries that divorce
could affect their performance reviews,
so they hide it.
Sure, that's fine.
However,
at the very least,
you should know your place.
The only reason I'm not blowing this up
is because we're friends.
I hope you do well.
Good luck.
REQUEST BY: OH PYEONG-HWA
MARRIAGE CANCELLATION APPLICATION
It's impossible.
Come on.
Her ex registered the marriage in secret
when she broke up with him.
But I can't help you
since it has been registered.
Why can't you help her?
This is total fraud!
That's the law.
You filled out the marriage form yourself.
Well, he wanted to write it up as a joke
for our 100th-day anniversary.
You shouldn't have signed
such an important form.
Anyway, your marriage registration
cannot be canceled.
Then what am I going to do?
Well, you can file for annulment,
but that's basically impossible.
All you can do is file for divorce.
- Divorce?
- What?
They weren't even married.
What do you mean?
Please cancel this registration.
Please cancel it.
There's nothing more I can do for you.
You should go find an attorney.
What am I going to do?
Please help her this once.
- Just once.
- Please look over it.
She's too young to get a divorce.
- Come on.
- Please help me.
What am I going to do?
You'll now become a divorcée
because you weren't careful enough!
You were the one who invited me.
And it wasn't just an invitation.
I came by because
you begged me to make a speech.
But to be humiliated like that?
I didn't know things
would play out that way.
Who could have known if you didn't?
I couldn't face my subordinates
after the humiliation that day.
You never mind
what your subordinates think anyway.
I'll continue to make it up to you
for the mistake that day,
so please don't be upset.
This is the finest premium
Jamón 100% Ibérico de Bellota,
made from the top 5% of pigs in the world.
Hey.
Why do you keep serving food
on this side and that side?
It's very distracting
as you go back and forth.
I'm sorry, sir.
Which side would you prefer?
I just asked why you distracted me
by going back and forth.
How is an apology your answer?
Are you deaf?
Don't you get it?
The serving ritual here at King the Land
follows the European royal families.
We serve wine and beverages on the right
and other dishes on the left.
If you find this inconvenient,
allow me to serve
from the side of your choice.
Oh my.
You really are something.
Very high and mighty.
All you had to say was sorry!
Are you trying to educate me?
Was that a lecture?
No, sir. I'm sorry.
Saying sorry won't cut it!
Ms. Gu, how come
your employees aren't trained?
Wasn't it enough
that I was humiliated by you?
Now I have to be belittled
by the likes of her?
Fire her!
If you don't, I'll never see you again.
Yes, ma'am?
Make sure everyone here is retrained.
And get rid of her.
- Sorry?
- Get rid of her.
Yes, ma'am.
Get rid of what?
Our staff aren't objects.
This isn't for you to meddle with.
I think it is.
Hello.
My name is Gu Won, head of King the Land.
Yes, and?
Sir.
Dining etiquette was formed
in the 19th century,
during Queen Victoria's reign.
It's what we usually call table manners.
A knife is a miniature version
of a dueling sword,
so the blade should be held
away from others.
Throwing a handkerchief means
you wish to fight the other.
So the napkin,
used here in place of a handkerchief,
should not be thrown.
Manners are unlike the law,
so it isn't compulsory to abide by them,
but it does display a person's worth.
Mr. Park, please show manners
appropriate for your position.
You aren't a man who's built for business.
King Hotel
has made many grave mistakes against me.
Let's meet again another time.
This is too humiliating
before my subordinates!
Too humiliating!
Mr. Park.
How dare you do this to me
to protect a mere employee?
Don't you realize how important
Assemblyman Park is to us?
She's not a mere employee!
She's a valued member.
I'll protect my own people
as long as I'm in charge here.
Is she just an employee?
Not something more?
What do you mean?
Blood never lies, so just in case.
You deployed the helicopter to save her.
I'm sorry. It was my fault.
No, you've done well.
If something similar happens,
protect our staff first.
That's your duty as the manager.
Yes, sir.
Do that in every situation.
I'll take responsibility.
It was such a tough day.
Yes, let's wrap up and go home.
It wasn't easy.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't your fault.
You can't deal with someone
who's trying to pick a fight.
Assemblyman Park is the worst.
He took it out on you
after Ms. Gu ticked him off.
But we were all saved thanks to Mr. Gu.
Remember how Mr. Park got drunk
and made a scene last time?
How could I forget?
We were all told to line up,
and he droned on for over an hour
about staff discipline.
It's that easy to pick on us.
Anyway, he's such an eyesore.
Don't even bring it up.
I don't even want to remember.
Hey, let's just call it a bad day
- and go out for a beer.
- Okay.
It was a bad day,
so let's chug it away with beer.
I'll wrap up here, so you can all go.
Aren't you coming?
I'm invited?
You're a part of our team.
Let's wrap up together and leave.
- Okay.
Sa-rang.
That Thai medicine you got me was great.
I've been in less pain.
I'm glad it was effective.
You're too nice.
If it were me,
I wouldn't have bought gifts.
Exactly.
We were quite mean to her.
Hey, it wasn't us. It was especially you.
What? So you're feigning innocence?
- You did it too.
- You were mean to her.
- That's enough.
- Seriously…
To be frank, I didn't like you.
We worked very hard to get here,
but you were promoted immediately
with one word from Chairman Gu.
But after spending time with you,
I realized you deserved to work here.
Thank you for being a competent worker.
Don't mention it.
You've always had a certain set of rules,
so I understood how odd it must've been
for me to suddenly join you.
That's why I worked very hard
to be worthy of this position.
You've done more than enough.
You're doing great.
Thank you.
Raise your glasses.
Okay.
- Cheers!
Anyway, wasn't Mr. Gu
really amazing back then?
I never imagined
an executive would take our side.
Right?
We've always been told to beg
for forgiveness when guests got mad.
I was honestly surprised.
I can see something
like sincerity in Mr. Gu.
Did you check your bank accounts?
No, why?
We got a bonus for our 100th anniversary.
A million won each.
But we normally get vouchers
for the hotel or the buffet.
That was the norm,
but Mr. Gu sent out a survey
to see what we actually wanted.
Cash was the overwhelming first place,
so he gave it to us.
The hotel never gave us
something we really wanted.
I thought the survey was a show
just as it always had been.
Right?
The world changes
now that we have a new boss.
Let's all make a toast.
For Head Manager Gu Won!
- For Mr. Gu!
Gosh, that's nice.
- It's pouring.
- It really is.
Oh no.
There's the taxi.
- Bye, Sa-rang.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
I'm this way. See you tomorrow.
- Bye, Sa-rang.
- Goodbye.
How will you get home?
I'll take the bus.
We'll go too.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
How did you find me?
It began to rain,
and I heard you were still here.
You should've called.
I couldn't ruin your fun
just for my own happiness.
Did you have fun?
Yes.
It felt like I was finally
accepted into the team.
It was great.
I'm sure they already accepted you.
It just took more time to break the wall
even after they decided to take you in.
I was grateful to everyone.
And I think they organized this dinner
because of me.
Anyway, are you okay?
Ms. Gu looked really angry.
So what?
If the customer is king,
he should act like one too.
Our hotel is way too classy
to show courtesy
to someone as rude as him.
Shall we?
Here.
Did you see how quick I was?
Oh no.
What? What is it?
What is it? What's going on?
What? What now?
What? Why?
- What's going on?
- What?
I was just startled while watching TV.
Right.
So why did you come out half-dressed?
You surprised me.
Well, I thought…
I heard you scream, so I rushed out.
I'll make tea.
You should dry yourself off first.
Buttons.
Shirt off?
Fasten them.
You already saw everything.
Why are you acting so shy?
I didn't even see anything.
Go dry off. You'll catch a cold.
Why are you being so shy?
You're too cute.
I'm not.
I can't leave you alone
if you're this endearing.
It's your fault.
- Please relax and have some.
- Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
You must be wondering
why I called you.
Yes.
May I ask why?
I hear you're an ambitious man.
Career-wise? Yes, very much so.
That's why I work for Mr. Gu.
And I'm the only one
who can deal with that personality of his.
Mr. No, you're with me from now on.
Make sure you report
everything related to Mr. Gu to me.
Then…
what do you mean by everything?
Everything.
From his professional life
to his personal life.
Report everything back to me.
Do not leave anything out.
Let me have another sip of coffee.
In that case,
how high can I go
by helping you?
Hello.
- What are you doing?
- My gosh.
Make some noise when you come in!
I have to go to a reunion,
so I came to find something I could wear.
What do you do with your paycheck?
Don't be so cheap and buy some clothes.
These are ancient. My gosh.
Why are you going through my closet?
Family is supposed to share.
Family is supposed to have some privacy.
Mom, I'm hungry.
Auntie Da-eul will make something.
Da-eul, please make a snack for Tae-ri.
What?
- Here.
- You work at a duty-free shop.
They don't have to be name-brand,
but none of these are good enough.
I'll just wear these.
- Bye Da-eul.
- What?
Hey, wait.
What about Tae-ri?
Aren't you going to take him?
You're here. Why should I?
I'll be late.
Don't wait, and put him to sleep.
What? Bo-mi!
You're going to wake Tae-ri.
Bo-mi went too far this time.
You need to talk to her.
She snuck in here quietly
and took my clothes, shoes, and bag.
And the room was a mess too.
Hey, family is supposed to share.
Just share with her.
There are manners
between family members too.
Don't be so cold-hearted.
It'll all come back to you.
"Cold-hearted"?
Has she ever babysat Cho-rong before?
Or has she ever even bought her a toy?
Your parents never gave her
pocket money or bought clothes for her.
Why do you want so much from people?
You'll be punished.
Punished, my foot.
Tell her to do as much as I do.
"Tell her to do as much as I do."
I want dinner.
Do I owe you dinner?
You can cook for yourself.
Goodness.
My son, I'm home.
You're home.
- Grandma!
- Hey.
Start cooking. I'm hungry.
We have beef, right?
Grill some of that.
And if we have mackerel,
grill some of that too.
I don't have an appetite these days.
Make some spicy soybean paste stew too.
Okay, coming right up.
Have you had dinner?
I'm starving.
Oh dear.
Go lay in bed. The floor is cold.
I can't be bothered.
I don't want to move an inch.
Don't you ever get married.
You always nagged me to get married.
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
Just date and enjoy your life.
You have no idea how precious it is
to have the freedom
to eat when you want,
to lie down when you want,
and to do nothing at all.
What's wrong?
I went and checked myself,
but it wasn't in the room.
Could you please check one last time?
My daughter can't sleep without that doll.
I'm so sorry.
If we do end up finding it,
we'll call you immediately.
If it's all right with you,
may I look one more time?
If the room inspection team says
it's not there, then it's not there.
It could've been tucked away
in the sheets,
so I'll visit the linen room.
Will you really do that?
Yes, but it might take some time.
Is that all right?
Yes, it's fine. We can wait.
What does the doll look like?
She's Jenny.
She's my friend.
Please find her for me.
She's a stuffed rabbit.
Yes, I'll try to find it
as quickly as possible.
Who's she?
She's from King the Land.
She's looking for a doll
a girl lost in one of the rooms.
What about room inspection?
They said they didn't see it,
but she's been at it for half an hour
trying to find it.
Excuse me.
Hello.
I was wondering who you were.
How are you going to find that here?
Room inspection searched for it,
so tell her you'll call
if we find it later.
She said the doll is her dear friend.
Please let me look just once more.
Ms. Kim.
There was a question I wanted to ask.
Could you grant me your time
whenever you're free?
Sure.
Thank you.
- Jenny!
- Ta-da.
Thank you.
Sure.
You must know that
you shouldn't make promises to guests.
What if you can't find it
after saying you will?
How will you deal with that?
It seemed weirder to avoid looking at all.
I wasn't saying you were wrong.
It's just that I see hard workers
get in trouble more often than others.
It's not like anybody appreciates it.
But I know
if I gave my best or not.
What did you want to ask me?
Right.
There's a staff member
who worked here a long time ago,
but her personnel record is gone,
and nobody seems to know her.
Her name is Han Mi-so.
You know her, right?
She was my closest friend.
What was she like?
She was braver than anyone.
Such a beautiful woman.
She was a great person.
What a relief.
Did you hope she would be a great person?
Yes.
You seem like a great person too,
Ms. Cheon.
Thank you.
My gosh.
Did I keep you waiting?
No.
Did you run here? Where's your car?
There was too much traffic, so I ran.
You must be tired.
Is something going on? You look happy.
Of course I'm happy.
It's the first time you asked me out
and waited for me.
- Is that so?
- That is so.
I always waited for you.
I asked you out to dinner first
and suggested we go somewhere first.
That's why I'll ask you today.
I want to go somewhere.
- Let's go.
- You won't ask where it is?
It doesn't matter where.
Where are you going?
To get my car.
I'll go with you.
Should I step on it?
Sounds great.
Did you want to see the sea?
No.
I wanted to see my mom.
I came to the sea with Grandma
whenever I missed her.
It felt like my mom was there
at the end of the horizon.
It breaks my heart to think…
you came here with that heart.
It's all in the past.
One day, that wind turbine
was suddenly installed there.
I was a young girl then,
so it looked like a huge pinwheel.
I thought it'd be big enough
to fly me to where my mom was.
But it wasn't like
I could walk on the sea.
So I was about to turn around.
Then suddenly,
a trail appeared between the sea,
just like now.
It felt like my wish came true.
I couldn't actually meet my mom,
but after that day,
this trail forever became
the trail that leads to her.
Will you come with me?
Yes.
They say you can go anywhere
if there's a trail in your heart.
Ms. Kim Ok-ja
who works in the linen room
was her old friend, and she gave it to me.
I heard she was a brave, beautiful woman.
And she was a great person.
You should meet Ms. Kim
once we get back to Seoul.
I don't want you
to have any regrets like I do.
INTERNATIONAL ARRIVALS
UNCONTESTED DIVORCE FORM
SIGNED: YOON SEONG-HUN
I told you to stop.
Avoiding it won't make it go away.
I never avoided it.
It's just not worth my while.
Go now.
I'm busy.
Let's not turn this into a lawsuit.
The news won't do us good.
I said not now.
Well, it has to be now for me.
Do you have to do this?
Please sign it.
JI-HU
Mom's busy right now.
I'll call you back.
What?
- Ji-hu.
- Mom!
Why did you come?
Because I missed you so much.
This is an important time.
Why are you adding to this too?
At the very least,
can't you not worry me either?
Is that so difficult?
I'm sorry.
If you're sorry, go back.
Go back and live your life.
That's what you can do for me.
Okay.
These look great.
My friend got these on her flight,
and they were delicious.
I asked her for another one to share here.
Try some.
You're so considerate. Thank you.
It's good.
Yes, it's not too sweet.
It should be perfect with coffee.
Right?
Take a seat.
Sa-rang.
Have you heard of the Dream Team?
No, I've never heard of it.
What's the highest position
a concierge can hold here
that you know of?
Us, King the Land.
The Dream Team is above that.
Really? What does that team do?
That team carries out
Chairman Gu's personal events.
It's basically a fancy catering service
at his command.
How do you always phrase it
to sound more vulgar?
Why? I'm right.
Only the best among the best are chosen.
While most don't know such a team exists,
for those in the know,
it's a dream to join.
Hence, the Dream Team.
He has an event this weekend,
and his secretary called
asking you to join.
Hey, Sa-rang.
It's your debut in the Dream Team.
You're a big shot now, Sa-rang. Congrats.
Thank you.
I'm still not sure what this is,
but I'll do my best not to be a nuisance.
- Congrats.
- I'm happy for you.
Where are we going?
Are you Cheon Sa-rang?
Your first time?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm with the secretary's office,
the manager of the Dream Team.
You must abide by your NDA.
Don't ask questions or get curious.
Let's keep it classy.
Yes, ma'am.
The aprons look insane, right?
I'm afraid I might get
a kimchi stain on it.
I'd be grateful if it got splashed on me.
What if it splashed to the chairman?
The thought alone is terrifying.
It does look quite classy,
but it somehow reminds me
of a maid's attire.
Dresses won't turn us into princesses.
Let's be grateful
that we get to put on expensive aprons.
Do you know why we're the Dream Team?
- Yes, ma'am.
The Dream Team
has never made a mistake in our service.
And of course,
that will also be the case today.
Keep your faces classy
and your acts elegant.
We create our own dignity.
Now, let us get started.
- Yes, ma'am.
We're in a war,
so you either eat or get eaten.
We have no time to look away.
Stop talking nonsense.
Do you want to make a bet
and see if this is nonsense or not?
Goodness.
Dad.
Oh.
Let us serve the meal.
Yes, sure.
It's Ms. Best Talent.
It's been a while.
Hello, have you been well, sir?
If she's titled the Best Talent,
she must be very talented.
Not at all.
He's just being generous.
Then let us serve the soup first.
Yes.
It's already been decided,
so there's no need to drag this out.
Won, now that your position is settled,
marry Yu-ri within the year
before it's too late.
KING THE LAND
The person you have called is unavailable…
I'll keep this short. End it.
It's going to be a head-to-head battle.
Is there a reason
why you can't give up on the hotel?
You will be on special duty.
You won't be working
in King the Land for the time being.
I'll take care of it.
It's my problem.
It's up to me to decide my future.
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon