[Yuseong Technical High Bulletin Board]
[A year ago]
What's the disciplinary meeting for?
Hey.
Move, you bastards.
Geez, what the f***...
[Notice for a disciplinary meeting]
[Subject: Bang Sang In, Chu Jae Hwang,]
[Ma Min Hwan, Pi Han Ul]
Geez, how embarrassing.
Oh Jeong Hwa did this, didn't she?
Did that bitch go senile or what?
[Proposed by Oh Jeong Hwa]
I heard there's a disciplinary meeting on you.
Is it that hard to graduate without issues?
I'll make sure to take care of it.
People are animals motivated by their gains.
Are you scared?
I don't think anyone was born bad.
So, you can change, too.
Hey.
You think you're the first high schooler
who acts cool with dead eyes?
Ms. Oh,
you don't just fix people.
Pi Han Ul!
That woman is...
also just using me to be a good teacher.
No! Stop!
Mom, Mom!
The woman who was stabbed to death
in an alleyway in Dong-gu, Ancheon
turned out to be a high school teacher.
The suspect is a teenage boy named Song.
He turned himself in after the killing.
The police believe
Song could flee while being investigated.
Thus, they requested an arrest warrant.
The disciplinary meeting was canceled, Han Ul.
Okay, let's all check our phones.
[The only way to join the Yeonback Family]
Download the app and prove yourself.
Then, you'll join the Yeonbaek Family.
Ready, go!
[10th grade ranking]
I will turn...
this school back to normal.
Regardless of who my opponent will be.
What's this?
What?
[Today]
I'm sorry.
The disciplinary committee is on you now.
Keep your neck clean until then.
[Study - Join if you want to study!]
[Hwang Min Hyun]
[Han Ji Eun]
[Cha Woo Min]
[Lee Jong Hyun]
[Shin Su Hyun]
[Yoon Sang Jung / Gong Do Yu]
[Study Group]
[I create opportunities even in hellish situations]
- This.
- We're doing it ourselves.
The school feels different these days.
Right? I felt that, too.
There hasn't been any ranking update today.
This never happened before, right?
The Yuseong kids quit fighting?
Wow, is this for real?
It's all thanks to Ms. Lee.
And...
Yun Ga Min, also.
What are you doing?
Don't hold the disciplinary meeting.
What?
I told you last time.
A fair punishment.
Don't believe in stuff like that.
You've told me once...
that I remind you of your late mother.
I've always wondered...
what you meant by that.
I found out while investigating the case.
The Late Ms. Oh's son attends Yuseong Tech High.
I'm sorry.
I should've known and cared for you more.
By the way, Geon Yeop,
what does Ms. Oh's case...
have to do with Pi Han Ul's disciplinary meeting?
Because the bastard who killed my mom
was Pi Han Ul.
The culprit in the case was caught.
Were you so naive to believe that?
He was just Yeonbaek Gang's minion serving time.
You know what Pi Han Ul is like, too.
You think he can't do the same thing again?
- Geon Yeop-
- Please...
just stop now. I beg you.
I guess the substitute teacher...
has been only focusing on Han Ul.
She prepared a ton of materials for the meeting.
I tried my best to stop her, but...
You!
I didn't know you were this unreasonable.
Why would you sign this stuff?
Why would you get me involved, too?
The Office of Education will inspect, too.
There's no choice, sir.
Pi Han Ul's disciplinary meeting...
can't be avoided now.
Han Ul might need to be expelled.
Oh, Han Ul.
I wanted to tell the Chairman something.
Leave if you're done.
Huh?
Okay, I will.
I-I'll be in touch, then.
- Just go overseas-
- The meeting won't happen.
Don't worry.
I can take care of it.
Last night, a fight broke out
in a building in Ancheon
and the videos are going viral.
Based on the report,
some 10th graders from a high school in Ancheon
wore a different school uniform in disguise
and broke in to steal business equipment.
[Ambushing the viral thug school]
Hello, subscribers.
I'm at the infamous thug school,
Yuseong Technical High School.
The student who was on the news yesterday
is apparently a study group member here.
Let's get to the bottom of it.
She's from the Heemang Orphanage.
Along with her twin brother Lee Hyeon Wu,
she's an infamous thug.
What are you doing? Move!
Choi Hee Won, you were a bottom-tier loser,
but you leech off the thug friend, Lee Ji Wu.
- What are these fruit flies doing?
- Move it!
You're a student here, right?
They say there's a gang in the school.
Is that true?
Pardon?
- Hold on. The redhead.
- The redhead.
- It's him.
- By chance, are you...
- Yes, the redhead.
- Hey, hey! It's him.
Hold on right there!
Lee Ji Wu!
Run, run, run, run!
The redhead!
The redhead! Wow!
Vice Principal.
You want a disciplinary meeting for Ga Min?
What do you mean by that?
Haven't you seen the news?
There must've been a reason.
I guarantee my students aren't bullies.
I barely managed to stop the reporters
from entering school.
I'll assess the situation first and-
It's too late now.
You did this, Ms. Lee. It's your responsibility.
Get Yun Ga Min and his whole gang
expelled through a meeting or
cancel Pi Han Ul's disciplinary meeting.
- Pardon?
- Right.
Shutting down the study group should come first.
Vice Principal.
Get your resignation letter ready.
We agreed you'd be dismissed
if the study group failed.
Remember, right?
You must be shocked.
I'm sorry, Ms. Lee.
It's my fault.
I heard from Detective Na.
You tried to save one of our students Sun Cheol.
It's bad you endangered yourselves behind my back.
But the gesture wasn't wrong.
Instead, don't do anything dangerous from now on.
Promise me.
- Okay.
I'll correct the news and the disciplinary meeting.
That's my duty.
So, trust me, and wait a bit.
Don't let anyone provoke you, either.
Especially,
Ga Min.
I know it's not fair,
but please hang in there a bit.
I beg you.
Okay.
What will Ms. Lee do?
I know.
We're in trouble, but she's about to get fired.
That can never happen.
Geez, we need to beat up that bastard.
He fabricated everything.
Huh? What the f*** is this?
What's wrong with you?
Just now, the ranking app-
What?
Special notice.
Whoever moves up in ranking in an hour
will each be awarded a million won.
Whoa.
Yuseong Tech High is so full of fighting spirit.
Crazy bastards.
Fight him. Kim Se Hyeon is a loser.
You might win if you attack him first.
Kim Se Hyeon, you f***er!
I need a million! Fight me!
Shit.
It's okay.
I'm fine. Go inside.
Let's go in together.
What if...
our efforts don't change anything?
Huh?
Even if we studied hard and went to college,
but if society were like this school...
That wouldn't be the case.
I thought things could change.
But...
dream...
Having a dream is so hard.
[Father]
Hello?
Hey, here they are.
I enjoyed the news.
Give me your autograph.
It's all fake news.
The truth will eventually come out.
A plausible story with a hint of truth
makes anything true these days.
They'll go after you and get sick of it quickly.
You'll be remembered
as a gang regardless of the truth.
Yun Ga Min,
are the students here really worth it?
No matter what you do,
Yuseong Tech High won't change.
I can give them what they want.
Whether that's money or connections.
But what can you give them?
Dream?
Hopes?
Would the scums who only live a day want that?
Wake up.
I represent the reality here.
Make Lee Han Gyeong cancel the meeting.
I'll let you graduate, then.
Move, move, move.
What?
What are you bastards doing?
Oh, I forgot.
I don't think you'd need the room anymore.
Until the disciplinary meeting,
I heard you disqualify as a club.
Hey, tear it apart!
You promised Ms. Lee.
Ga Min, I know it's not fair,
but please hang in there a bit.
I beg you.
[I create opportunities even in hellish situations]
Stop that!
Move!
What? What? You bastard.
You think you could just say anything?
I called him a thug because he acts like one.
Is he a teacher, then?
Did you see him?
Did you see my son acting like a thug, bastard!
Damn it!
Why would you defend a kid like him?
What did you say, you bastard?
Come here! Come here!
Come here, you bastard!
You bastard.
Are you really a thug?
Why can't you answer?
Are you really a bully or something like that?
You bastard.
You said you'd only graduate high school.
You made such a fuss about it.
But is that what you've been up to?
You're old enough,
but you can't fend for yourself. Even so,
you shouldn't be a thug, at least, okay?
I'll come to work.
What?
I'll quit school...
and make money.
Geez, look at them.
Is it them?
Lee Ji Wu...
Her brother stabbed a teacher, too.
Geez, you can't help where you come from.
What hopeless siblings.
Lee Hyeon Wu is in juvenile jail right now.
Blood is thicker than water.
Their parents must've abandoned them, too.
Hey!
Geez.
What...
Let's go.
They weren't wrong.
But still. They can't insult your parents.
Those bitches don't know anything.
Choi Hee Won, you're a bad kid now.
You swear so naturally.
I'm not a bad kid. I'm your underling.
My parents work at KEPCO,
I live in a luxury apartment, and I'm loaded.
That's why I bribe you to survive.
Sorry, they found out where your parents work.
I don't care.
They aren't that interested in me, anyway.
Choi Hee Won!
Mom?
Dad.
I told you to come home right after school.
- Get over here.
- What are you doing?
Take care.
Seriously. You don't listen.
Are you okay?
[Yuseong Tech High Study Group]
Today was kind of rough.
You'd better stop ignoring me.
We aren't going down, are we?
I started enjoying studying a little bit.
F***. Are you all dead?
Why are you ignoring me?
♫ On these narrow streets, my days are ♫
[Yuseong Tech High Study Group]
♫ filled with my dried-up dreams ♫
[It's okay]
♫ If I look at you silently ♫
[Still, we...]
[Kim Se Hyeon left the chat]
♫ I sit blanking out and shed tears ♫
♫ In a painful memory, I close my eyes ♫
♫ I fall asleep after wandering a while ♫
♫ All by myself ♫
♫ As long as I can open my eyes ♫
What if our efforts don't change anything?
Dream...
Having a dream is so hard.
I can give them what they want.
Whether that's money or connections.
But what can you give them?
Let's eat.
♫ Even the warmth is gone ♫
What? Is something wrong?
♫ Some days pass by as if they're mocking me ♫
I think the study group...
will fall apart.
We just...
wanted to study.
♫ I close my eyes while being paused ♫
Ga Min,
do you know why I let you stay in Yuseong?
Because you looked...
happier than ever.
♫ As long as someone could hear it ♫
[I create opportunities even in hellish situations]
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
How did you come up with this?
Here. This question gets two stars.
You sound just like Ms. Lee.
Here are minerals.
And this is Omega-3.
One, two, three.
And here.
This is egg yolk lecithin.
- Really?
- Yes.
All of this is good for brain cells.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Your body might not rot after taking all this.
Hey, Yun Ga Min.
You look so red.
Look at your cheeks.
Why are your cheeks so red?
They're the same color as Jun's hair.
Why are they so red?
Try this. Try this.
[I create opportunities even in hellish situations]
[Disciplinary Committee Meeting for Pi Han Ul]
Kim Sun Cheol is the witness.
He was involved in the case
and a Yuseong student.
His testimony won't be so trustworthy.
If so,
will my students be framed like this?
I'm sorry, but we should keep an eye on it.
Insisting on the meeting can get Ga Min expelled.
You should give up.
But, sir...
Nothing can be done.
It's just how this school is.
I know how hard you tried.
Let's stop now.
[For Pi Han Ul's disciplinary meeting]
[Trash]
[Will you delete this file?]
[Yes]
[I create opportunities even in hellish situations]
Memorize the cube formula no matter what.
(a+b)³=a³+3a²b+3ab²
- +b³.
Repeat three times.
(a+b)³=a³+3a²b+3ab²
Next. (a-b)³...
a-...
Ms. Lee.
Should we tidy up?
What's with you?
Why are you here?
So, you'll be here instead of
Mr. Kim from now on?
Yes.
I can't replace Father immediately,
but I'll do anything.
Who are you?
We come as a set.
Seriously.
Just leave now.
I'll leave if you do.
I'll study and go to college with you.
What? Bricks? Put them here.
Okay.
- Are you okay?
- I told you to leave!
Working together makes it go faster.
There isn't a set amount of work.
It won't go faster.
I'll study and go to college with you.
Seriously.
Hey, Yun Ga Min.
Please leave now.
I don't want to study, I said!
I won't go to college, you crazy bastard.
What?
Wait...
I'll study with you and
go to college with you.
- Did you smile?
- Yes, let's.
You want to? Really?
Yes, you parrot.
Hold on.
Let's go.
Huh? What?
Gosh.
I thought you weren't coming, but you came.
Where are you going? It's still work hours.
Excuse me, sir.
Father,
thank you for raising me all these years.
Now that I'm here, I realized...
how hard you've been working.
But...
I really want to study.
Please wait just three years.
I swear I'll try my best.
I'll become successful...
and make sure you don't regret this.
Just wait and see, sir.
Se Hyeon...
will own a building like this.
Let's go.
Hello.
I...
am the top student of this school.
Yes, the top student.
Her grades went up because of the study group.
You think we're bullies, but you're mistaken.
The thing is, we're...
very worried. We're considering a transfer-
No.
Specialized admissions allow
many at our school to go to colleges in Seoul.
You didn't know, did you?
- I-In Seoul?
- Yes, in Seoul.
If you let me, I'll be her study-mate
and make sure she goes to college.
By the way, what's that?
We were taught to bring something
when you visit a friend.
I see.
But why blueberries?
Blueberries are
a superfood that activates your brain.
Oh, brain?
Yes.
They must really care.
I want a friend to go on group blind dates with me.
I won't make friends in college since I'm a loser.
And no group blind dates, either.
Geez, how sad.
Aigoo...
It'd be so fun to hang out with our boyfriends.
We have different ideal types, too.
You care about the face,
and I care about the physique.
I don't get to go to college or have a boyfriend.
Why not? There's nothing wrong with you.
Yes.
Let's say I go to college and go on blind dates.
How will I introduce myself, then?
I'm an orphan who was born with nothing.
I have a twin brother, but he's in jail.
I work to death to feed him in jail.
Do you want to visit him with me?
Should I say that?
I suppose you have a point.
But someone might think this.
"She's an orphan who struggles...
and her brother is in jail, but...
she works so hard and goes to college.
She even takes care of her brother. She's really
cool and impressive."
If you marry him, I'll...
catch your bouquet.
[Yuseong Tech High Study Group]
[Yun Ga Min invited Kim Se Hyeon]
What? Where have you been, Kim Se Hyeon?
I was cooling my head a bit.
You insist on the disciplinary meeting?
Yes.
After the transfer of duties and the meeting ends,
I'll leave the school.
You don't mind the study group getting hurt?
If you're a true teacher, you should protect them.
My students aren't just those in the study group.
I promised to protect Pi Han Ul's victims.
I still think
Yuseong Tech High needs to change to do that.
Ms. Lee Han Gyeong!
If the study group students were at fault,
I'll make sure they get punished and apologize.
But...
I won't stand by and let them get framed.
♫ I... ♫
♫ This is my world. I have a question. ♫
♫ What about this, boy? ♫
♫ Guess who's back? Tell 'em I'm back. Bring a lot. ♫
♫ Bring anyone. Do your best. ♫
♫ My name on top ♫
♫ Parking lot, backyard, rooftop ♫
♫ I turn them into my stages by standing there I'm yawning ♫
♫ I'll let you sleep soundly as if you're on vacation ♫
♫ I go after my goal with a pure look ♫
♫ I don't want to see a loser in the mirror ♫
♫ Make more plans ♫
[Study Group]
♫ Looks like you don't get it ♫
♫ Look at my grades, I bet everything ♫
♫ My growth rate is high ♫
♫ I throw a fast-breaking ball, slider ♫
♫ Yeah, I'm a rider ♫
♫ When I go low, look down ♫
♫ Or keep your mouths shut ♫
♫ I'll sink a goal like in football ♫
♫ I enjoy pain, I'm addicted now ♫
♫ I'll embrace it and go further like a bulldog ♫
♫ Cut it off, please ♫
♫ Set me oh, free ♫
♫ Just bring me closer and closer ♫
♫ Run it off, I got my hoodie on me ♫
♫ Let me go, let me go, let me go ♫
♫ Cut it off, please ♫
♫ Set me oh, free ♫
♫ Just bring me closer and closer ♫
♫ Run it off, I got my hoodie on me ♫
♫ And imma make it up from this hood ♫
♫ From this hood ♫
♫ Go on and poke me, it's your loss ♫
♫ Take it, pass out instead of breathing in and out ♫
♫ I'm not interested in a childish fight at all ♫
♫ To touch me, you'd better think twice ♫
♫ Because my life is a mountain of my assets ♫
♫ Forget it if you don't get it. Never stress out. ♫
♫ I'm flying outside the big bird cage ♫
♫ I fly high and ask you, looking down, "Como estas?" ♫
♫ Life is like a fiesta ♫
♫ I live for myself ♫
♫ And I be see signs ♫
♫ I chase you like the CSI ♫
♫ Intuition. I have no worries later ♫
♫ I wear designer clothes ♫
♫ Throwin' up that peace sign ♫