QUEEN OF TEARS
Well, I…
So what…
Yes?
…I wanted to say was…
I…
-Yes?
-"I'm sorry."
"About today
and everything that I did until now."
"It won't happen ever again.
I'll treat you better from now on."
That's what I wanted
to say.
But you only have three months to live?
How's that possible?
How can I live without you?
How is that possible?
I'm so dumbfounded
that I don't know what to say.
Are you serious?
Yes, you fool.
I love you, Hong Hae-in.
I love you.
If you can't live without me…
Yes?
Do you want to die together?
What?
You said you couldn't live without me.
I didn't mean I was certain
that I couldn't live without you.
I was simply wondering
if it was possible to do so.
I was curious.
Exactly. Then we should just die together.
It was an official thing back in the day.
It was called sunjang.
They buried you with your spouse.
Right.
Sunjang.
Yes, sunjang.
You can treat me better in the afterlife.
It's not bad.
You've always been good
at making terrifying jokes
with a straight face.
Do you think I'm joking?
You're serious?
I'm saying don't be dramatic.
Tell me.
What exactly did the doctor say?
Where are you hurting?
Did the doctor really say
that it'll only take three--
That you had only three months to live?
Hello, Professor.
The test result?
Can you e-mail it to me?
I don't have time to go there.
We need to go somewhere.
You're free today, aren't you?
The car is waiting downstairs.
I'm not going.
-I didn't even tell you where we're going.
-It doesn't matter.
I refuse to go anywhere with you.
Where are you going right now?
I don't know.
I have no idea where I'm headed.
SUNGMIN UNIVERSITY MEDICAL CENTER
Unlike normal tumors,
these fuzz-like tumors are scattered.
Hold on.
When did I get here?
Sorry?
I remember being in the lobby.
So how am I already here?
It's like I teleported.
Has this ever happened before?
I told you last time.
Sometimes, I had headaches
and was often forgetful. And sometimes…
Our VIPs loved the art class
we held in the first half year.
We invited famous artists…
Restea will be joining us.
These days, sleep quality…
Ten minutes? Thirty minutes?
Sometimes, I couldn't remember
what I did for the past several hours.
Ms. Hong.
I thought you had canceled your plans
to meet with Director Baek Hyun-woo.
Why are you still here?
I even missed an important appointment.
Why didn't you visit me sooner?
I just thought
I had dozed off or zoned out
due to exhaustion
I didn't feel any physical pain.
So…
is there something wrong with me?
You have Cloud Cytoma.
It's a very rare disease.
There aren't many cases worldwide.
It's safe to say
that you're our first Korean patient.
-Do I need surgery?
-No.
I see. It can be treated with medication.
Your case is a bit more complicated
because it's different
from regular tumors.
It's not a clear lump of tumor.
The tumor cells are dispersed
throughout your cranial nerves.
They're spread over a wide area.
It's the most concentrated
near your temporal lobe.
I believe this is the cause
of your temporary memory loss.
It's a rare disease.
The symptoms are nonspecific
and differ from case to case.
If it worsens, you could suffer from
hallucinations or personality disorders.
The problem is that
taking medication won't help much.
And it's too dangerous to receive surgery
since the tumor cells
have spread too much.
Ms. Hong?
Are you okay?
-Okay.
-Pardon?
So that's the case for ordinary people.
I get it.
Now, tell me what treatment I can get.
I want to know about my case, not theirs.
I heard you're raising money
for a new children's hospital.
I can take care of that.
So tell me
how I can get rid of them.
To my knowledge,
there's no medical solution
for this as of now.
The best we can do is give you medication
to alleviate your headache
and temporary memory loss.
However, it's impossible to cure
the disease itself for now--
You've been insinuating
that I'll be dying soon.
Fine. Tell me.
When will I die?
Judging by
the spreading of the tumor cells,
I believe you have about three months.
What does he know anyway?
He knows best as a doctor.
I know my own body.
You're talking like a stubborn, old woman.
Have you ever seen me
eat instant or junk food?
-No.
-Exactly.
I've never drunk soda in my entire life.
Do you think I enjoyed drinking
vegetable juice and watching what I ate?
I meditated in the morning and did yoga
at night for my stress.
I watched my breathing
if there was no oxygen concentrator.
I've tried to stay healthy
since the moment I was born.
I get it.
Calm down.
Even people who harm their bodies
by drinking, smoking,
eating whatever they want,
and not minding their breathing
aren't subjected to this disease.
So why me?
I don't know either.
Fine.
I get that I'm sick.
But why can't they fix me?
People travel to the moon,
and cars drive themselves.
But they can't remove
a tiny tumor in my head?
That's ludicrous.
How about
we go to the hospital tomorrow
and check again?
What for?
We need to be sure.
What do I do if it's a misdiagnosis?
What do you do if it's a misdiagnosis?
I'd be ecstatic.
So let's go and reconfirm everything.
You're on edge right now.
Just forget everything and rest up…
Do you think I can sleep?
Right.
I'm too shocked as well.
I don't know if I can sleep tonight.
It sure feels different
compared to yesterday.
Humming? Really?
Do you want to get buried with her?
I'm sad.
We'll be parting ways.
We'll be parting ways
in three months even without a divorce.
No.
Don't smile.
Go down.
Hae-in?
Wait. She never sleeps in.
What's going on?
Hey.
It's past 7:00 a.m.
What?
What is it?
Morning kiss.
Good morning.
You must be in a good mood to say that.
Even your skin looks better.
You must've slept well.
I tossed and turned all night.
Me?
My skin?
You're wrong.
No, that can't be.
Let me warn you.
You're the only one who knows about this.
So if anyone finds out, it's your fault.
I understand.
But will you keep this a secret forever?
Yes.
Shouldn't your family know?
Of course not.
They should be the last ones to know.
But I think--
I'm very close
to joining the One Trillion Club.
You know what Grandfather said
when he gave me the department store.
"I will choose you over your father
if you make
over one trillion won in sales."
And you want me to ruin that?
When I'm this close?
That's why you won't tell them?
Hong Soo-cheol
is the type who calls my doctor
to confirm if I really got the flu.
Do you think my mom
would be any different?
If they find out about my illness,
I'll be kicked out of the house.
They'd fight over who would get my assets.
I won't allow that.
Over my dead body.
Why do you think Grandfather wants
to see me prior to having breakfast?
Does he want to give me
an earful and get it over with
before eating breakfast?
Any ideas why he wants to see you?
Maybe it's about
how I wanted to launch
that organic New York coffee brand.
The one that you were confident
about launching?
Yes, but I was wrong.
Those scumbags put one over on me
and decided to work with Yeom Sang-jin.
Why is this world
full of immoral scumbags?
Do you think Grandfather knows?
Even I found out only recently.
Risks are required to run a business.
Don't be afraid. It was only force majeure
that the deal fell through.
Yes, you're right. It was only force…
The deal only fell through
due to force majeure.
But I'm still worried that he'll get mad.
He's your grandfather, not Satan.
Be confident and tell him.
-I should, right?
-Yes.
How are you so incompetent?
Grandfather, this deal only fell through
due to force majeure--
What? A deal fell through?
What deal are you talking about?
The launching
of the organic New York coffee.
Isn't that what this is about?
I'm talking about how
you overpaid eight billion won
in corporate tax!
-What?
-Hyun-woo's Legal Team
found out about it
and will file a rectification claim.
That money would've gone down
the drain had it not been for him!
Isn't your brother-in-law
the finance director?
-Fire him this instant!
-But--
Also, you were so confident
about that coffee deal.
Did that go down the drain too?
-No--
-Answer me!
Why can't you do anything right?
Haven't you learned anything from Hae-in?
-Haven't you?
-You see--
Say something, you scumbag!
Talk, you scumbag!
Make use of that mouth of yours!
-I--
-Answer me, you idiot!
I want to reply, but I can't--
Then talk!
I can't breathe.
What?
Get up!
Doctor Jeong thinks he has panic disorder.
Goodness.
You must've been
so stressed out by your grandfather
This is Hyun-woo's fault.
Why is he so good at his job?
I'm sorry, Mother.
It's my brother's fault.
Honey, that's ridiculous.
Your brother worked hard
and just made a mistake.
Eight billion won isn't that serious.
Eight billion won?
Is all of this just because
of eight billion won?
Where's Hyun-woo?
I'm truly sorry,
but the results are the same.
Do you mean
she really has three months left?
-Exactly three months?
-I can't say.
That's an irresponsible answer.
You've been a neurologist for 30 years.
Please be exact with the percentage.
Please give us the exact number.
That's enough. Let's go.
No, Hae-in. I need to hear this.
Fine then. I'm leaving first.
Sir.
I'd appreciate it if you could be exact.
My life is on the line here.
This is ridiculous.
I'm different.
Why are you here?
Why isn't Hyun-woo picking up?
Is he in his office?
I asked why you were here.
So what if Soo-cheol overpaid
a few billion won?
Hyun-woo could've taken care
of it quietly.
Your grandfather was livid with Soo-cheol.
He must've found out somehow.
Hyun-woo wouldn't do that.
What do you take me for?
I know you were behind it.
I have no time for that. I'm…
a bit distracted by a serious matter.
Soo-cheol had…
a panic attack today.
I see.
You must've been startled.
But, Mom,
I just told you
that I had a serious matter too.
Aren't you curious?
You always know what to do
whether it's big or small.
Right.
I'll take care
of my business.
You should go. This is my workplace.
Hey, don't mind me.
I'm here to see Hyun-woo anyway.
Stop provoking us.
Or I'll torment your son
until the day I die
no matter how busy or distracted I am.
-What?
-I'll torment him forever.
Is that so?
Do you think I'd just sit and watch?
Bring it on.
Why did you want to eat here?
Hey, I don't even feel safe
in our law firm's meeting room.
A public place like this feels safer.
Why is that?
Because I'm risking my life
to go against Queens.
Why would you?
I thought long and hard
after seeing you cry.
I'll help you. Let's have the divorce!
-About that--
-This wasn't an easy decision.
I'm risking my job.
Okay, but don't do it.
Why not?
I'm not getting a divorce.
No? Hey, didn't you tell me
that it was too unbearable?
Well…
I said that because I saw no end to this.
But now that I see one,
I think I can endure it.
What do you mean? What end?
Well…
God granted me a safe parting.
Let's just say that.
Explain in layman's terms.
Come to Hangang Jamwon Parking Lot
Section One in 30 minutes.
What are we doing?
What I'm about to tell you
is confidential.
-So if anyone finds out, it's your fault.
-Come on.
What's this about?
Are you serious?
She told me when I was about
to give her the divorce papers.
That she had three months left.
I met with her doctor today too.
Gosh, Hyun-woo.
Hey.
This is insane. What am I supposed to say?
First…
-Let's shake hands.
-Don't.
Right, you shouldn't show your happiness.
Let me be the scumbag.
So Lady Luck is on your side.
You would've left her
without a single penny to your name
had you gotten a divorce.
Those few seconds saved you.
What? Does this mean
you'll take over Queens?
Do you think
-they're that dumb?
-What do you mean?
Did she sign a prenup or something?
About not dividing her assets?
You know it won't matter
once you file a suit
unless she wrote it in her will.
Yes, she wrote it
in her will.
Seriously?
Yes.
It happened before we got married.
She refused to give anything to me
and even got the will notarized
before we got married.
Conglomerates sure are different.
They're extremely thorough.
It's okay.
I'm just happy
that I can escape from them
safe and sound in three months.
But think about this.
Why did God give you those three months?
Hyun-woo.
Attorney Baek.
Let's talk professionally.
You know she's free to revise
her will in those three months.
You just need to win her over
in the next three months
so that she'll think,
"Gosh, he must love me so much."
"I should hand over my beloved
Queens Department Store before I die."
What are you saying?
Three months is nothing
after serving two years in the military.
Consider that and it'll be easier.
Put your heart and soul
into loving her.
You.
Do you seriously think…
I'm that materialistic?
What's that for?
Today is our wedding anniversary.
So?
I had made a reservation
and prepared a surprise two years ago.
But you got very upset
and told me not to make a scene.
-So?
-So I didn't prepare anything last year.
But you still got mad
that I actually listened
and asked if I would die
if you told me to.
Are you here to nitpick
about my inconsistency?
No, of course not.
What kind of person
brings flowers to nitpick?
Then has our marriage ever been
so lovely that you'd bring flowers
on our anniversary?
To be honest,
I can't say yes to that.
But we could always
make it lovely, can't we?
Happy…
wedding anniversary.
Bring me a vase.
How are things?
Did they fight or anything like that?
No, they didn't. Rather…
-"Rather"?
-They've gotten closer.
-"Closer"?
-Yes.
He takes great care of her.
It's very unlike him.
Has this table always been for ten?
Twelve.
It's always been just the two of us.
But we sat so far apart.
What's wrong with you?
From now on,
I'll be sitting here.
There are too many cons in the contract.
We need to provide
the store's renovation fee.
I don't think
it's that big of a loss on our part
given the popularity of the brand.
Correct, but they're not required
to stay for a certain amount of time.
Let's say we spent five billion won
to bring them in.
We have no right to stop them
if they want to leave after a year.
We're also required
to pay a penalty if they find out
people are selling counterfeit products.
Are you okay?
Hold on. I'm okay--
Don't talk. Let me.
-Please call the ambulance.
-Sorry?
I'm fine.
Are you really?
I just choked on some water.
-Really?
-Yes.
So?
Can we resume?
Yes, sir.
No need for the ambulance.
What's gotten into him?
He's just trying to survive.
Goodbye, sir.
I'll call you later. Goodbye.
Had he stayed still,
she would've been furious
that he didn't do anything.
I really feel bad for him.
It's cold. You should just wait inside.
You're freezing.
What if you catch a cold?
Jeez.
Why are your hands so cold?
Secretary Na, is the car coming soon?
Well, yes.
Will you be okay?
Should I call an ambulance?
There it is.
It's okay.
Gosh.
They should just argue instead.
What's gotten into him?
Didn't I tell you?
Don't be dramatic.
Hae-in, I don't know how to be dramatic.
This is being dramatic.
Sorry.
I don't know why
Hyun-woo reminds me of Grace Kelly.
Didn't she get married to a king?
-He reminds me of Diana.
-That's wrong.
Those two got divorced.
-Sorry.
-Mi-seon.
I came here
to get my hair done, not pulled out.
I said I was sorry.
Maybe it's because we're housewives,
but you really don't treat us well.
-I agree.
-Be honest with us.
Does it annoy you
when we talk about Hyun-woo's looks?
Hyun-woo has always been good-looking.
It's not like that.
Right.
Did you hear?
-About what?
-The daughter of the electronics store.
-Whose in-laws are doctors?
-Yes.
-They're getting a divorce.
-Really?
-Seriously?
-Yes!
-Goodness.
Jeez, that's not a big deal.
Divorces are common these days.
There are even TV shows
that feature divorced couples.
It's not a shame
to be divorced these days.
Her mom must be so humiliated
to see her neighbors.
She used to brag all the time
about her son-in-law being a doctor.
I thought she was a doctor too.
She always gave advice
to others if they were unwell.
-Tell me about it.
-Why are they splitting?
They're too different.
I told you before.
The marriage won't last if the wife
and the husband are too different.
But I'm not saying that's always the case.
Is Hyun-woo happily married?
Of course, he is.
But you know what they say.
Those in Seoul look down
on people like us.
Right.
And Hyun-woo is married
to a conglomerate family.
My sister-in-law is not like that.
Right. I'm sure.
Then why didn't she attend
your dad's 60th birthday?
People started gossiping afterward.
-Saying?
-That they're not on good terms.
They think Hyun-woo isn't treated well.
Only those who don't treat
their in-laws well
attend birthday parties
and pretend like they do.
But people like her
who are good to their in-laws
don't need to do that.
I see. But are you mad?
Why would I be mad?
Then loosen up those fists,
or you're going to land a punch.
-I have a headache.
-What's wrong with her?
-She's mad.
-I see.
My entire body is sore today.
Don't throw things.
Pinky is watching, you know?
Hyun-woo, that idiot.
I get it. Studying law at SNU
probably made him arrogant,
so it must've been difficult
to brown-nose a conglomerate family.
But wouldn't it be better
to brown-nose them, if anything?
Of course.
I brown-nose middle-schoolers every month.
-Why?
-So they register for the next month.
Hey, it's not my hands
that keep me in business either.
Not at all. It's my mouth.
"Gosh, you're so beautiful today.
Your skin is glowing!"
"You look ten years younger
with this new haircut." That's what I say.
I wish Hyun-woo could be like us.
Gosh.
I doted on him too much.
Mom, shouldn't you do
something about this?
-He might actually get a divorce.
-A divorce isn't a big deal.
Honey.
People divorce when they think
they're on the brink of death.
It's better to divorce then.
The noodles are tasty.
More sesame oil?
Yes, add more.
I prepared different meals for each of you
based on last week's blood test results.
As for the vice-chairman,
I prepared a low-FODMAP diet
for your irritable bowel syndrome.
Thank you.
Where's Grandfather?
He needs to fast
for his medical checkup tomorrow.
I bet he'll live up to 120 years of age.
Mine doesn't have any meat.
It's because of your cholesterol.
Hae-in.
Yes?
You'll receive
a certification of contents tomorrow.
I'm going to file a suit
for how you built your department store
over my land in Gwanggyo.
We already talked about this
when the construction began.
And it wasn't that much land.
Listen. All wars began
because one party stepped over
-another party's land.
-You gave me your permission.
I did, but Attorney Shim was against it.
Rumors might spread about how
I gave you special treatment,
and I might have to pay a gift tax.
So you're going to file
a suit now that the building
has already been built?
You haven't opened yet.
I see. Then should I just demolish it?
Hae-in, she doesn't want
to prolong the case.
She wants to negotiate.
-Hyun-woo.
-Yes, sir.
Look over it with her
and come up with an appropriate measure.
"An appropriate measure"?
What does that mean?
Should I be afraid and back off?
Is this what you meant
when you said bring it on?
You're threatening me with that lawsuit.
What I'm saying is--
I think…
Hyun-woo.
Did you just cut me off?
I apologize.
But since
you've already filed a complaint,
we'll look over it and give you our reply.
However, the press
will learn about this in the process.
And that could cause
a fall in the stock price and more.
I'll have to inform her grandfather.
I'll do that.
Yes, ma'am. Then that'll be all.
She's feeling a bit unwell.
Please excuse us.
You wanted to keep it
a secret from your family.
But?
But wouldn't they suspect
that something's up
if you're all tense
and your fists are trembling?
Right. I know I was acting
out of character.
But what about you?
You interrupted my mom and sided with me.
You also looked me in the eye lovingly.
You were the most suspicious.
Just act like you always have.
When did you ever peel shrimp for me?
It just won't work for us.
It's impossible.
How can we change
after years of living as strangers?
But wasn't that the case
-three years ago?
-What was?
Weren't you in love?
-That was--
-You were both head over heels.
She visited you on a helicopter
and disobeyed her parents. You too.
You weren't sane back then either.
You were crazy in love.
So wasn't that love?
That was years ago.
Yes, you're right.
But let me give you an example.
We learn how to survive in water as kids.
Then we don't swim for decades.
Even if we end up in water again,
we'll still float.
You may think you forgot it all,
but your body remembers.
It's the same with love.
You may think you forgot how to do it,
but your heart remembers
once you get into it.
But this isn't like swimming.
Of course, it is.
Being in love isn't special.
It's strange, isn't it?
We get married because we're in love.
So why does that love disappear?
As a divorce attorney,
I think the problem
is that marriage is exclusive.
Couples don't find the need to try.
So they get disappointed and fight.
Then they come to me.
Marriage just makes it impossible
to stay in love.
-Do you think so?
-I think it's best not to marry
if you want to be in love for a long time.
Please accept this
as a token of my love and loyalty.
Honey.
Are you crazy? She's not your honey.
Long time no see, Secretary Kim.
Hello, ma'am.
You're getting married? You two?
And in Korea at that?
Right.
You must've heard that I was in jail.
That's why you came back.
But what a shame.
I got out.
Calm down, honey.
What did I tell you?
I said I'd spare your life
as long as you left
the country and lay low.
-Right.
-So how dare you
get married in front of all your relatives
when you cheated on me?
Honey.
Honey!
Ma'am, you have blood--
It's not mine.
-Where?
-On your cheek.
You shouldn't do this
when you're on probation.
You could get aggravated punishment
for assault and defamation.
Defamation? What I've done so far
to those cheaters is far from that.
Should I show you
what true defamation is like?
You could be behind bars
until you're 60 if you do that.
Will that be okay?
I've settled with their attorney.
How much?
-Do you want to know?
-Forget it.
It'll be enough
to build a pool in their house.
You shouldn't have done that.
Do you still resent them?
Do you smoke?
-I quit.
-Because I do.
I learned how to smoke
because all my ex-husbands cheated on me.
You can't smoke here.
Let's go.
Go? Where?
Damn it.
I was dying to get out of jail.
But now that I'm out,
there's nowhere to go.
You should go home.
The chairman is waiting for you.
Beom-ja.
I heard you didn't eat all day.
What's it to you
if I starve to death or not?
You put me behind bars
because you didn't care.
Gosh, it wasn't me who did that.
You assaulted an innocent woman,
so you were punished for your actions.
I see.
The woman who killed Mom
and became the madam of the house
is completely innocent.
She's not the madam of the house.
She's not in our family register.
All I did was gently grab her
by the hair, but I'm the sinner here.
You can't say it was gentle
when her disc slipped.
Exactly! So mind your own business
and let me die for slipping her disc!
Hey, Beom-ja.
You have the wrong idea about her.
Seul-hee doesn't want anything from us.
She's not interested
in fortune or becoming family.
That's even scarier.
What grand plan could she be scheming
to live with you and not want anything?
You're just a geezer with tons of money!
Hey!
Gosh.
I wonder when she'll wise up.
I shouldn't have hope
since she's already in her fifties, right?
Don't let it bother you.
By the way, I know I'm no match for you.
But you're not focused on the game at all.
What do you mean?
-Goodness.
-Staring at the board won't help.
You need to see the bigger picture.
You're right.
You'll get caught if you run away in fear.
But if you try to catch the tiger
without being prepared,
you'll lose everything.
Goodness.
This is why janggi
can teach you life lessons.
I took over your palace.
Where will the king flee to now?
Checkmate.
Did you see this coming?
Or were you just lucky?
I'm not sure.
You need to grant me
one favor since you lost.
What is it?
I'll tell you when I have one.
Honey, did you see that?
I think I just saw a shooting star.
I didn't know I could see them in Seoul.
You dreamed of shooting stars
before having Hae-in.
Did I?
You were excited because you thought
you'd be having a baby girl.
I'm not sure. I don't quite remember.
Honey, don't be so harsh on Hae-in.
What did I do?
How long will you let your past haunt you?
You should let go and move on.
That's what you said back then.
Your father didn't want any issues,
so you obliged.
I still don't understand
why Su-wan had to die.
It was just an accident.
No one is to blame.
You're right. It's no one's fault,
but Su-wan is gone.
I'm still upset and in pain
every single day.
To others…
To you, it's just a past event.
But I relive that moment every day.
I'm haunted by the day
when I lost my child.
So don't expect me to be reasonable.
Why hasn't she come home yet?
Is she really sick?
She has great stamina.
To be honest,
her chance of survival is very low.
But miracles do happen.
Sorry?
How often do these miracles occur?
Do they happen often?
During my 30 years as a doctor,
I've witnessed many patients
recover miraculously
from even less hopeful illnesses.
Don't lose hope.
CLINICAL CASES FOR BRAIN TUMORS
MALIGNANT TUMOR
DON'T GIVE UP ON TREATMENT
"Given three months to live
but still alive after 30 years."
Thirty years?
Seriously?
I didn't know it was this common.
I guess a doctor's prediction
isn't always correct.
This is-- Gosh.
This is unlike the dramas.
"The tumors disappeared after waking up.
A medically impossible case."
How could it be medically impossible?
Is this the reality
of modern medicine? Really?
TERMINALLY ILL PATIENTS CAN STILL RECOVER
GIVEN 3 MONTHS TO LIVE,
BUT STILL ALIVE AFTER 30 YEARS
THE MIRACULOUS HEALING
OF MY PANCREATIC CANCER
THOSE WHO CLING ONTO HOPE
Hey, Hae-in.
When did you come in?
Why are you sleeping here?
Sleep on the bed.
Right, I should.
You should too.
Good night.
Hyun-woo.
Yes?
To be honest,
I suspected you.
What?
I thought you'd be happy
to hear that I was dying.
I thought that was why
you were being so good to me.
I also suspected that you had
an ulterior motive.
I admit.
I was a bit suspicious.
I didn't know
you had looked up those things.
These miracles happen
more often than you think.
What…
You don't have to come here.
Don't worry. I will live no matter what.
I acted tough,
but I was shocked to hear my diagnosis.
I was dispirited.
A part of me didn't care
about what would happen to me.
"But if I really had only three months,
would receiving treatment even help?"
"Should I just give up?"
"No one would mourn my death."
"Not even my family."
I had all sorts of thoughts.
I see.
But there's one person.
You of all people want me to live.
Me?
Yes. Of course.
Yes, I do.
It had been tough for me.
It was too much to handle,
but seeing you gives me hope.
I did my own research.
Unlike in Korea,
there were similar cases abroad.
There are many labs out there
that are developing new drugs.
They'll be able to speed up the process
as long as they have the funds.
I'm going to actively look
into supporting them.
Really?
Are you that happy?
Yes.
Of course, I am.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to die
that easily for your sake.
Is this for your social media account?
What if it's just a part of your face?
I really want the world to see you.
But the media will post articles about me.
And your parents don't want that.
I don't want to worry them.
You're really…
All right.
Also,
Jun-ho told me to keep it a secret
since it wasn't confirmed yet.
Our finance director? About what?
He feels terrible
about the eight billion won.
It's totally fine.
Still.
He's trying to hook you up with someone
to make up for that.
-Who?
-A private equity fund investor.
He was the one
who invested in the organic coffee deal
for Yeom Sang-jin.
Really?
His name is David Yoon.
He's Korean-American.
He recently came to Korea.
He has control
of Middle Eastern oil money,
and he's here to find new investments.
He's looking to invest
at least a couple trillion won.
Hae-in has been trying
to bring Hercyna into her store.
And David is the reason
why the brand could launch
their first Asian flagship store in Seoul.
Hi.
Congratulations. I'm loving
your food section's new renovation.
I eat at your food court often these days.
Right. I heard you came by often.
Anyway, Royal still has
a long way to go to be on your level.
Our desserts need some tweaking.
We have a lot to do.
Once the fountain plaza is built
on the first floor,
we're going to bring in Hercyna
and we'll work from there.
No, we need to work harder.
So what if our food section is great?
A department store without Hercyna
is just a big restaurant.
We also have space for Hercyna.
Do you want a tip?
Sure, if you want to give me one.
Okay.
I'm sure you know that Mr. Hermann
puts company value and mindset
before anything else.
He believes that those
who form good relationships with others
are the best business partners.
That's his belief.
-So?
-Look around you.
Everyone here has brought
their spouse, lover, or family members.
You're the only one here
who came alone.
What?
You impress me.
Everyone knows that you have no friends,
but how could you think of coming here
of all places by yourself?
You're the only lone wolf here.
It's just you, Hae-in.
Poor you.
BAEK HYUN-WOO
-Where are you?
-I'm in a trial.
What did he say?
What do you mean?
You were frantically calling
your husband for help.
Is he not coming?
-He's in a trial.
-How fitting.
-What?
-What can you do?
You can't tell him to bail.
I think that was a fitting excuse.
It's not an excuse.
He's really in a trial.
Why are you so serious?
I was just kidding.
Hey, don't mind the rumors.
I don't believe them.
-What rumors?
-I'm sure you heard.
That you two have separated
and will divorce soon.
That he only married you for your money.
I don't even want to talk about them.
But you have.
I've barely begun.
You should've had an ordinary marriage.
Even gossipers wouldn't have much
to talk about had you married someone
on your own level.
I've realized something in life.
Marriage is about finding a life partner
who looks in the same direction as you.
My past four years of marriage
have been nothing but peaceful.
And that piqued my curiosity
about couples who couldn't get along.
How does it feel?
I've never been mad at my husband before.
Why are you asking me?
You shouldn't take your anger out on me
for not being loved by your husband.
You should've just married Yoon Eun-sung.
Why would you suddenly bring him up?
You don't know anything, do you?
He's Mr. Hermann's right-hand man.
He's the key to reaching Mr. Hermann.
What?
Hey, he became really successful.
He's not the same guy from university.
He's in charge of managing
sheikhs' finances now.
That's why I went
to greet him at the airport.
Eun-sung.
It's been a while.
You should've let me know
if you were back in Korea.
Don't you remember
the last thing you said to me?
To not contact you.
-I did?
-Yes.
I doubt that.
"Let's continue to stay in touch."
Isn't that what I said?
You're right. I told you
not to reach out to me ever again
because you kept crossing the line.
Right. But now,
it seems like you have something to say.
I'm sure you already know this,
so I'll just say it.
Ye-na and I are in a brutal competition
to bring Hercyna into our stores.
It seems like you have
a good relationship with Mr. Hermann.
So tell me.
-Can you help me?
-Me?
Why should I?
To be honest,
I don't remember much of the past.
So why don't we just say that we broke up
on good terms?
When will the trial end?
Is it almost over?
-What about the trial?
-I won.
I won quickly to come here.
Here you go.
One non-alcoholic cocktail, please.
What did you say marriage was again?
Finding a life partner who looked
in the same direction as you?
I didn't get it at first,
but seeing your husband made it clear.
What do you mean?
You see,
I'd rather look at my husband
than elsewhere.
He's that handsome.
Here you go.
Honey, have you tried this yet?
It's really something.
-Did you come here to eat?
-What?
I don't want to see it.
I'm talking about your face.
Go away.
A heart? You little…
Here.
Thank you.
I thought of Hae-in now and then.
So it feels odd
to meet her husband.
Sorry?
Well, Hae-in and I
had a good relationship in the past.
I see.
Hae-in isn't the type
who has had
many good relationships in her lifetime.
That's quite impressive.
To be honest,
I liked her a lot.
I see.
It doesn't bother you?
Sorry?
That only means one of two things.
You trust her completely,
or you just don't care.
Is it the latter?
I'm just kidding.
Mr. Yoon.
Coming.
Goodbye.
That bastard.
How did he know?
I'm offended.
How ridiculous.
To be honest, I liked her a lot.
If he truly
liked her a lot,
then he should've worked hard
and married her.
Then he would've saved my life.
What's the point of telling me
about his feelings now?
Is he teasing me or what?
What an annoying scumbag.
Hello.
-We meet again.
-Hello.
Gosh. Isn't this place teeming?
You're right.
More than half of these people
came to see him.
They want to meet him.
What does he do?
He's a tycoon.
Even the wealthiest people
from Wall Street
borrow oil money from him.
Even Chairman Yeom is dying to meet him.
Soo-cheol is trying to meet with him too,
but it's not easy.
And this Yoon Eun-sung attended
the same university as Hae-in?
Yes.
I don't know
what to say to you at times like this.
Why would you feel bad?
I should've introduced
someone like him to Ms. Hong Hae-in.
What can she do? She dug her own grave.
Still, I regret not trying harder.
To do what?
I think you're mistaken.
I'm always grateful
that you didn't try harder.
I'm truly thankful
that you excluded me from your list
of marriage candidates.
So spare yourself that useless guilt.
Why did you call?
You overheard us.
Invite Yoon Eun-sung to our family hunt.
Right. I can guarantee
that he'll come if I tell him to.
But why should I do that?
I have no reason to.
I'll withdraw…
the lawsuit.
Hae-in.
Here is the number of preys you can catch.
There's no limit for magpies and crows.
As for boars, water deer, and pheasants,
you can each catch a maximum of five.
An accident might occur
if you get in each other's way
and mistake each other for an animal.
So make sure you stay in your course.
You should not hunt boars by yourself.
Do not aim or turn your back on them
if you're alone.
Can we let her use a firearm?
As you already know…
What can we do? She chose to carry one.
What if she commits murder?
Look at that murderous look.
She should've gone
to a mental hospital, not jail.
Let's go.
Aunt, we need to move.
Over here.
Don't hold the firearm like that.
Did I hit it? I can't see very well.
You did, Father.
The biggest one fell. Gosh.
I saw it too, Grandfather. Gosh!
Did you? I believe I did as well.
You did.
Did you really get it?
I don't think any of them fell.
Hyun-woo, are you a Native American?
Or a Mongolian hunter?
Is your vision that great?
I think it fell into the woods.
I'll tell our men to get it.
What if Hyun-woo goes home
empty-handed this year as well?
Right.
He's right.
You've never caught anything on our hunts.
We come here every year. You should learn.
Are you afraid of guns?
You served in the military.
So? Should I teach you?
That's okay.
You should worry about yourself.
I'm already good at it.
That's why I offered to teach you.
What about you? Are you any good?
I'm not sure.
I doubt I can hold a candle to you all.
He's humble in every way.
Right.
Let's see who'll catch the pheasants
for this year's dumpling soup.
Let's begin.
Let's go.
-Let's go.
-All right.
Catch something for once.
There's a reason why
my grandfather brings us to this mountain
to hunt every year.
What is it?
Does he want us to pretend
like he successfully shot a duck
and praise him?
Stamina is important when hunting,
but quick judgment
and objective decision are also required.
And those are all virtues
that those who do business should have.
Is that why you catch so many every year?
To prove to him
that you're a worthy businesswoman?
Of course.
And I'll catch the most this year as well.
Take your time.
Yes, it's ready.
It's near the middle
of that course.
WILD BOAR HABITAT
RESTRICTED AREA
PROPERTY OWNED BY QUEENS
Where in the world is she?
Your call cannot be connected.
Darn it.
Sorry. I thought you were a water deer.
Why are you here?
This isn't your course.
Is it not? This is my first time hunting.
Don't you know it could be fatal to invade
someone else's territory when hunting?
I didn't know that.
I look forward to learning more from you.
You shouldn't do anything
in other people's territory.
You wanted me to teach you, didn't you?
What's wrong with me?
That's just a dumpling.
That's just pheasant soup.
It's a pheasant dumpling.
Pheasant soup.
Don't fool yourself. This isn't real.
Snap out of it, Hae-in.
Snap out of it.
What do you say?
I'm dying. I have three months left.
I love you, Hong Hae-in.
I love you.
Are you okay?
You refused to date
that civil servant or that music teacher.
Why do you suddenly want a housewife?
Didn't you say
that intern was going to get fired soon?
Someone who's jobless?
I don't want to pressure you, but how
will you save up money to buy a house?
I agree.
I didn't expect a wealthy daughter-in-law
just because you studied law at SNU.
I just hoped
she wouldn't be poorer than us.
That's all.
-Exactly.
-I've never felt this way before.
She's always
on my mind.
I wonder why her clothes
always have holes in them.
I'm worried
that she'll go around kicking things.
I'm worried that she'll get scolded again.
I think of her when I eat tasty food.
I want to bring her some.
I'm so distracted
because of her.
She'll be the death of me.
Then marry her.
-Honey.
-Mom.
Marry her if it's that serious.
It's better than dying.
Yes, that's true but…
Yes, I will.
We're going to get married.
And I'll protect her forever.
QUEEN OF TEARS
Are there women whose hearts still race
when they see their husbands
despite being married
for over three years?
No way.
I noticed that the fence was pried open.
You actually believe that he loves you.
Yes, I do.
I've never been this annoyed
at someone's smile.
I'm going to kill
every single scumbag who betrays
and stabs me in the back.
Don't be afraid.
It was because I was scared.
That's why my heart was racing so much.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim