(Wooju / Barcode Tinnasit)
(Raon / Jeff Satur)
(Woo-hyuk / DION)
(Q / Q)
(Hachi / Jason) (Air / Alpha)
"Wooju Bakery"
(Episode 1)
"Here we go."
(Wooju Bakery)
Nice work.
Hello, everyone.
We're opening tomorrow.
We hope you'll come visit.
Wooju Bread.
We're counting on your support.
Wooju.
Hyung.
Wooju, you're amazing.
This bread looks beautiful!
Here, try some.
It's just a test batch.
This... tastes a little...
Did I add too much salt?
Or is it the yeast?
How can I open a bakery like this?
Wooju, has your sense of
taste not come back yet?
Don't worry.
We still have Dad's recipes, right?
Just follow the recipe book.
Can I really do this?
Of course you can. Let's
get ready for the opening.
Are you hungry?
Me?
I'll just eat the bread.
Didn't you just say it tastes weird?
But you made it. I'm heading out.
See you later, hyung.
Is this where they sell the most delicious
and beautiful bread in the universe?
Welcome.
This is "Wooju Bakery."
I'm sorry, but...
All the bread in our shop...
is already sold out for today.
I came all this way just to try it.
It's such a shame I can't have any.
(Closed)
(Open)
Dad, where do stars come from?
Stars come from a
faraway "universe" [wooju].
Wooju, isn't that my name?
That's right.
And the universe is
full of delicious bread.
Wow, it looks so delicious!
Huh?
Dad, where did you go?
Wooju, it's okay. Don't worry.
Dad will always be by your side.
Dad?
Dad!
Don't be afraid.
When stars are first
born, they always tremble.
My Wooju, let's meet again!
Dad, where are you going?
Dad, take me with you! I'm scared!
Dad!
My home!
You guys!
Look!
Earthling!
Don't be alarmed.
This is just a regular landing accident.
Who are you people?
Can you understand me, Earthling?
Hachi! Is the translator broken?
No, it is working well.
Then why are you speaking
a different language?
I like this language.
I can speak Thai and English.
Stop messing around.
Who on earth are you?
My name is Blablalis
Romoromorian Ardi Raon.
We're from the planet Kauncilion.
I don't care who you are.
You're the ones who wrecked
my bakery, aren't you?
How are you going to pay for my bakery?
Earthling, your body's
chemical levels are surging!
You should lower your blood pressure.
Hachi, how do you say
that in the local language?
Take it easy!
Hey!
How can I be calm?
The grand opening is tomorrow, and
you crash into my shop and set it on fire!
What do you want me to do?
It was just a regular landing accident.
Anyway, don't worry.
It'll be covered by our
space travel insurance.
Insurance money?
When will I get it?
For them to investigate this far...
In Earth time, it would be about...
A year?
A year? Are you kidding me?
I have a bakery to open tomorrow!
Let's go to the police station.
The police?
The kind that lock us up and dissect us?
Is that an Earthling custom?
- Hey!
- Let's make a deal.
What kind of deal?
We have money in our spaceship.
I'll go exchange it quickly.
I'll give it to you before the
insurance money comes through.
What kind of nonsense is this?
That piece of junk is a spaceship?
Yes, a spaceship.
That's a car.
Where the hell did you learn Thai?
Hachi! This Earthling's
adrenaline is through the roof.
He might get too excited
and start screaming.
Stabilize his nerve cells, quickly.
You maniacs!
Prince.
Hachi.
Why did you shoot him?
I didn't kill him.
Let's get out of here first.
So you're saying there were
strange men here just now?
Are you sure you didn't see things?
Dong-myeong is here.
Dong-myeong...
Wooju!
Are you hurt?
Are you okay?
You're not even in night shift today, though.
Yes, sir.
But you know the owner of this bakery?
We've practically lived
together since we were kids.
He's like a real brother to me.
Wooju, are you all right?
It's the rescue team, right?
I think it's the rescue team?
What kind of rescue team is this sloppy?
It looks like a crash landing.
Bro, what should I do?
The shop was supposed to open tomorrow.
It's all ruined.
It's going to be okay.
There's a lot of smoke, but
not much actually burned.
Though the walls are a bit cracked.
Let's clean this up first, and
we'll open tomorrow as planned.
Hyung, we have to find them.
I've never seen those two Thai guys before.
But I'm sure of it.
They're definitely the culprits.
Thai guys?
Got it. Wooju, wait here for a second.
The rescue team's investigation
came to the same conclusion.
It was just a lot of smoke, not a big fire.
The owner here said a car crashed
into the shop and started a huge fire.
As you can see, there are
almost no signs of a fire.
He was probably drunk
driving. That's got to be it.
It looks like he just
crashed straight into it.
He said that when the fire started,
there were two Thai-speaking men here.
There are no signs of a break-in at all.
We have our conclusion.
The car crashed, creating sparks.
Then it hit the gas tank, "Bang!"
That matches the explosion
the residents heard.
But there are no signs of a gas explosion.
Just write what I told you to write.
No one's going to check anyway.
You guys, don't run!
Hey, stop!
Stop right there!
Don't run.
Hyung! Hyung!
Wooju!
I really saw them.
I saw them clearly.
I saw both of their faces.
What did they look like?
One was wearing a sparkly stage outfit.
The other was in a dog onesie.
They were both weird.
Hyung, tonight...
Can I sleep at your
place? I'm a little scared.
I'm really scared. Please let me stay.
It's not like we didn't have
sleepovers when we were kids...
Who are you, and what are you doing here?
Just as I thought.
Humans have such bad memories.
I'll say it again.
My name is Blablalis
Romoromorian Ardi Raon.
You can just call me Raon. This is Hachi.
Are you guys real?
I'm not seeing things, am I?
From a quantum mechanics perspective,
particles also have the properties of waves.
And waves have the properties of particles.
So determining if something truly exists
is not that simple.
"I think, therefore I am."
Then what are you?
Walking around in a dog costume?
What Hachi is wearing is special equipment.
It's the uniform of the kingdom's
top astronaut and engineer.
It can also transform into a humanoid form
during long voyages to save energy.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Who are you, and why are you here?
From the perspective of Earthlings...
we're aliens.
What? Aliens?
What do you think you're doing?
You lunatics.
You set fire to my place
and think you can just run off?
What on earth is going on?
Barging into my room...
Are you trying to end up in jail?
Jail food?
You mean that stuff that
was just made downstairs?
That stuff was disgusting.
If we get locked up and have to eat that...
it would be miserable.
It was terrible.
What... are you people talking about?
Who's this guy?
(Wooju Bakery)
There's one over there.
And another one there.
This is unacceptable!
Clean this mess up, you freak!
Looks like you're the freak here.
We... didn't order jjajangmyeon, though.
Is that the rescue team?
Who are you?
I'm Jirol. I transport
the galaxy's food supply.
The galaxy's food supply?
So it really was a crash landing.
I thought it was the rescue team.
I got my hopes up for nothing.
You'll have to bite the
bullet and stick it out here too.
But we'll be going back soon.
That's what I thought,
that I'd be back home soon.
But in Earth time...
it's been a hundred years. A full century.
We're from the House of Blablalis.
What? A prince of Blablalis?
The prince from the Kauncilion?
Old man!
See? I told you I was right.
That guy! He's actual royalty.
Blablalis?
Doesn't that make him the Crown Prince?
It looks like they really did crash-land.
If he's the Crown Prince, a
rescue team is sure to come.
Get closer. Stick with them.
If we want to get out of here with
them, we need to get on their good side.
The House of Blablaris...
is the supreme royal family that unites
hundreds of thousands of alien species.
Without them, the galaxy
would be in total chaos.
A rescue team will definitely come for
the Prince of Blablaris.
And that means...
after 116 years, 8 months,
and 37 days on Earth...
I can finally go home.
Are you wondering why
an alien looks so... normal?
What, you thought we'd
look like this? Or maybe this?
You Earthlings have
such a poor imagination.
Is it all the oxygen you breathe?
Aliens don't have a fixed appearance.
We just take this form
to blend in with you.
So while we wait to be rescued...
some of us open auto repair shops,
some become fortune-tellers,
and others get into pyramid schemes.
Me? As you can see, I just play the
fool and hang around the neighborhood.
What, you still don't believe me?
You want proof?
Then put on some music with a beat.
Ah... I can't stop!
If they dance, they must be an alien.
We can't help but move when we hear a beat.
Okay, shh! Don't get too friendly.
We've been living among you all along.
Mwahahahaha!
About what happened yesterday...
The victim said they saw a stranger.
Sir.
This is a metal fragment we
found at the scene yesterday.
It's not any metal found on Earth.
Hello, is this the psychiatric hospital?
I'd like to bring someone
in for an appointment at two.
Okay.
He said to come by at two.
Take this with you.
I don't need a shrink,
this needs to be sent to NASA.
Just get back to work.
What are we going to do with this car?
That's not a car. It's a spaceship.
It just took a form that
would be familiar to Earthlings.
Cut the crap. What are
we doing with this thing?
Let's just leave it here for now.
It'll be a nice tourist
attraction for the Earthlings.
Why do we have to put everything back?
Is that a rule on Earth?
The grand opening is
delayed because of you.
Didn't you say you'd pay me back in cash?
Then give me the money now!
Right now...
I don't have any...
money.
"Currency Exchange - Earth
Branch 16 / House of Blablaris"
What's that?
Isn't that just a kid's marble?
This is money where I come from.
And it's very valuable.
It's just been shrunken down to this size.
It just looks like a marble to me.
Hold on.
(Incantation)
What is that?
See?
(Incantation)
What is that?
Is that an Earthling?
Why did you bring an
Earthling to an exchange?
That's against the rules.
We just crash-landed yesterday.
We don't know the rules.
Sorry.
The signal is weak here on Earth.
So foreign currency is almost worthless.
Do you still want to make the exchange?
Be honest with me.
You're a con artist, aren't you?
This isn't even enough to
cover the repairs for my shop.
Let alone be enough for compensation.
Oh, really?
So...
what can you do with this much money?
Maybe where you're from,
this is a month's salary.
But here, you can earn this
by working hard for 15 hours.
What?
Fifteen hours?
Hold your hands up.
This is...
What are you doing?
I'm putting you to work.
So I don't have to pay you?
What are you talking about?
Of course you have to pay me back.
Then I don't want to work.
I'd rather just pay you the money.
This is unbelievable.
You're not even a
little bit sorry, are you?
Don't you see all this burnt equipment?
And the power outage?
I'm trying to cut you some slack
since you're stranded on Earth.
I'm not holding it against you.
Sign your name here.
What's this?
It's a contract.
You'll work for me for 10
years until you pay off your debt.
That includes repair costs and interest.
Oh shit! Prince, the police are here.
You called the police?
I'll work at your bakery
to pay off the debt.
Please, don't call the police.
(Wooju Bakery)
We just arrived on earth with the princess.
We plan to rescue the prince by searching
the place where the prince is presumed to be.
The princess has a question.
If we've found the prince,
will the King keep his promise?