[If you don't turn yourself in,
your limbs will rot and you'll die]
[All characters and events are fictional,
and any resemblance is coincidental]
[Scenes with children and animals were filmed
safely under professional supervision]
[Establishing Law and Order]
Mr. Lee Yong Woo, have you been well?
[Compliance Required]
Why didn't you come yesterday?
Something urgent came up.
Were you waiting for me?
Something urgent?
[Confession is the beginning of forgiveness,
and forgiveness opens the door to salvation]
Guess this isn't all that urgent to you.
Well, why would it be?
The statute of limitations
has already expired anyway.
Right, nothing urgent about it.
The more important something is,
the less you should rush it.
Important?
This is
like my life's mission.
"Mission", huh?
Sounds impressive.
What do you mean?
A life's mission?
People like me don't have anything like that.
How did you end up getting into that,
your life's mission?
What got me started?
Calling won't wake her up.
Go get questioned.
On what?
[Episode 3]
The assault on Jeon Kyeong Ho.
That's my jurisdiction.
Are you seriously
going to lock me up over that?
You think the case is going
to be handed to you now?
It's already mine.
What?
I told you.
I'd take it back.
You,
and the case.
Hey.
Forget about petty things
like asking to make a phone call.
Just for once,
say, "Please help me."
Jeez.
Then I'll take care of everything.
Tae Joo.
Kang Tae Joo.
We can
take that punk down together.
You and me, we do this together.
Didn't I already tell you?
Cut the "we" crap.
I don't want anything to do with you.
You're gonna help me?
You?
What a joke.
Prosecutor Cha Si Young.
You really wanna help me?
Get your face
out of my sight.
If that's what you want, fine.
[Police officer arrested]
The victim needs eight weeks to recover.
What are you going to do about this?
Is there
any way to handle this quietly?
I even considered indicting him immediately,
but with the recent serial murders,
public trust in the police is at rock bottom.
It just didn't feel right.
That's right.
Let's just take his resignation
quietly and end it.
Yeah, that sounds best.
- Do that.
- Chief!
You still don't get it even now?
Eight weeks means jail time, no question.
And jail time means dismissal anyway.
Why aren't you answering?
Please have Detective Kang questioned.
What?
He's still a police officer.
He even saved a woman
from the suspect this time.
So you're asking me to let him off?
No, what I mean is
he's done his job properly
for over ten years.
If you throw someone like that out,
morale among the others will drop.
Chief, honestly,
who'd even want to be a cop then?
Please show some leniency.
Fine, let's do that.
If it makes you uncomfortable
to fire your colleague,
what can we do?
Just follow procedure.
Anyway, Detective Kang Tae Joo is removed
from all investigations, effective today.
Procedure followed.
[Seo Ji Won]
Sun Young, why are you here?
How's Ji Won?
Still unconscious?
I heard
she got hurt
trying to catch the suspect with you.
Seriously,
it's always about that darn suspect.
Why are you only here now?
Where were you back then?
Were you chasing the suspect again?
Come out for a second.
Kang Sun Young, first,
explain what happened to you.
Why were you in the car with him?
And why did he do that to you?
Shouldn't you
ask if I'm okay first?
What's your relationship with that punk?
A student got into a car accident.
So I went to the hospital with him,
and he offered to give me a ride home,
so I just got in.
Then
how does he know about our mother?
You think I told him?
He suddenly started saying weird things,
so I asked to get out, but he got angry.
And then, the accident happened.
Did that guy do anything to you?
No, nothing like that happened.
Jeez, that woman really is something.
Even in death, she's dragging her kids down.
Don't talk about her like that.
Mom did her best for us.
Best?
You call that the best?
That woman left you when you were sick
and went off with another man.
- You don't know what you're talking about!
- Tae Joo, stop!
Sun Young, just hang in there
a little longer.
Sorry.
He told me to apply for a transfer.
He kept threatening me with my son,
so I had no choice.
Yeah, I see.
It was
about seven years ago?
Everyone from the office
went on a company outing.
Back then,
Mr. Cha, who didn't even have kids,
got along so well with my son.
He treated him like his own nephew.
But
he'd even torture my son mercilessly.
Is that punk even human?
Jeez,
I've been talking too much about myself.
You must have
a lot on your mind too, Detective Kang.
No, it's all right.
Isn't it ironic?
We're the ones who drove out Cha Si Young,
and now we are in trouble.
It's probably just a coincidence.
Do you really think so?
Cha Si Young
is a horrible man.
He'll use any means to get what he wants.
Try not to go up against him if you can.
Otherwise,
the one who'll get hurt
is you, Detective Kang.
Don't worry about me.
I don't care
about means or methods, either.
[Modako]
Welcome!
It's an honor to have someone
as distinguished as you here.
This way, please.
Yes, this way.
Here.
If I get caught, I'm dead.
Let's call your debt to me even with this.
Which one of those two?
Both of those punks.
Please visit us often.
[Modako Club VIP Pass]
Bring another glass here.
Hey!
Alright, you guys talk.
You're such a decent man.
So you must've been shocked.
So, what about that punk?
We can throw him in jail, right?
Of course, that's nothing.
But I heard that woman filed
a complaint against me. How do we...
That's why I'm asking.
Why did you hit a woman?
I'm sorry. I just lost it in anger
before I knew it.
Then there's no other way.
You'll have to admit
you were having an affair.
What? An affair?
Your mistress, Kang Sun Young
has been demanding you get a divorce,
but you refused to do it.
So during an argument,
things escalated into an accident.
Now, holding a grudge,
she's claiming you assaulted her.
But my wife's going to kill me.
Sir, you really don't understand women.
She won't kill you.
Jeez, your back always acts up like this.
What should we do?
When you get old,
everything just starts breaking down.
First you fooled around
with a married man, now what?
You tried to replace me, his lawful wife?
How can you even call yourself a teacher?
What are you talking about? Let go!
Don't you dare deny it!
You're the daughter of a bar hostess.
No wonder you act the same.
What else would you have learned?
She's the daughter of a bar hostess?
Sun Young!
Oh my, Sun Young!
What's all this about?
What are you doing?
What? Why?
Can't I do this much to the mistress
who slept with my husband?
W-What?
She's a bar hostess' daughter.
No...
Mother, it's not true.
It's not true, Mother.
It's really not true.
Mother?
Oh dear, Mother!
You've got such a fine daughter-in-law.
Oh my, isn't she impressive?
Mother, it's not true.
Mother, I swear it's not true.
Break up with Ki Beom.
Mother...
They say a woman's fate
takes after her mother's.
I shouldn't just brush it off.
Mother, what she said earlier isn't true.
Please believe me.
Your mother was like that too.
Men flocked to her even when she did nothing.
She didn't live like that from the beginning.
After your father passed away,
she had to raise you somehow,
so that's how it ended up.
I'm afraid
you might even take after her
in bringing misfortune to your husband.
That's what scares me the most.
Sun Young.
Please let Ki Beom go.
I'm begging you, okay?
[Kangseng Bookstore]
[Muwon Photo Studio]
Sun Young would look beautiful
in a wedding dress too.
Sun Young will stay
at a relative's place for a while.
Nothing's wrong, I hope.
Sir, this way.
Oh, you're totally wasted.
How come you can hold your liquor so well?
Of course, I can.
Hey, wait, wait.
Stop right there.
Hey, wait. I'm paying today!
Alright.
Right here.
Darn it. Alright.
Here.
[Modako Club VIP Pass]
Thank you!
Here.
Thank you, sir!
You're really generous!
Hey, what's your boss doing?
The guests are leaving.
Hey, why the boss?
Oh, it's fine, man.
I'm close with the owner here.
Oh, really?
Go call him over!
- Go call him right away!
- Yes, sir.
Mr. Park!
Oh my, Mr. Jeon!
Is everything alright here?
Good, good.
Thanks to you, Mr. Park,
I had a great time again today!
I'm leaving!
- Bye, sir!
- Goodbye, sir.
I'll be back tomorrow too.
See you again.
Come again, sir!
Is that punk out of his mind?
That nephew of the county governor
is basically living here for free booze.
Anyway, rich people are always the worst.
How long do we have to keep babying him?
Cleaning up after him is one thing,
but this is too much.
Cleaning up what?
I mean...
I'm the boss here,
and that punk acting out
in front of everyone...
It's embarrassing even
for my employees to see.
Darn it.
Why does the booze taste like this?
Are you still watering it down?
No way!
Since I got suspended back then,
I've never done that again.
With all the customers
you've introduced to me,
do you really think I'd disgrace you?
- Really?
- Of course.
Does it not suit your taste?
Hold on. I'll bring you something else.
Si Young, what about this?
The most expensive bottle we've got...
You little...
What the hell is this?
Are you bugging me?
How dare you!
It wasn't me.
It's a misunderstanding. I swear!
Not you?
Get lost.
Yes, sir.
Si Young,
why would I...
Believe me, it really wasn't me!
Prove it.
Fine, I'll prove it. I'll prove it!
Oh, my head.
Gosh.
- Ji Won.
- Yeah.
Are you feeling a little clearer?
What's wrong with my head?
More importantly,
did they catch the suspect?
Is that what really matters right now?
Did they catch him or not?
Not yet.
Darn it!
Seriously? That's what you're asking
after a narrow escape?
The camera!
Did you find my camera?
What camera?
You didn't find it?
Un Hui, is this even the right place?
I checked with Mr. Park,
and he said it was here.
Then why isn't the camera here?
It's not like it can sink into the ground.
Maybe the suspect took it?
Think about it.
Since it had captured him, do you think
he would've just left it behind?
Darn it, we can't lose that.
That would have been a scoop.
[Modako]
Huh? Where did it go?
Where is it?
Jeez.
What are you doing?
Looking for this?
Got you, you rat!
So?
What?
Who?
Got it.
This is interesting.
Very interesting.
[The suspect's features]
Do you remember anything else
about the suspect's features?
Is it okay to just let him do this?
Prosecutor Cha will go crazy if he finds out.
Leave him be.
[Body type, any weapons used]
He's trying so hard to catch the suspect.
I think I already told you
everything that day.
I didn't see his face.
I told you everything I could remember
about his height, build, and voice.
Sorry for calling you in again.
[The suspect's...]
Anything else coming to mind?
No.
Honestly, I don't even
want to think about it.
Yes, I completely understand.
[The suspect's last words]
Then, just a few more questions.
Ms. Kim Mi Yeon, when the suspect left you,
what did he say before he left?
Couldn't he just ask me directly?
It's just that our situation
is a bit complicated.
I'm sorry.
He said if he caught that woman,
he'd let me go.
But would a man who killed five people
really let me live?
Five?
What do you mean, five?
He said he killed five people.
What exactly did the suspect say?
Well...
See that woman?
Once I catch her, I'll let you go.
How about it?
Will you cooperate?
Don't try anything stupid.
I've killed five women.
Killing one more
is nothing.
Hey, what the...
He said five?
Maybe that punk got it wrong?
He wouldn't be mistaken
about something like that.
Then, if there's one more victim,
why hasn't the body been found yet?
- A missing person!
- Hey, rookie!
- Yes.
Go get the missing persons list, now.
- Yes, sir.
- Hurry up!
Yes!
[Investigation Division]
I checked all recent missing persons cases.
These three are the only ones that match.
[Missing Person Report]
This victim's build is larger
than the suspect's.
He wouldn't have attacked recklessly.
He might've mistaken her for a man too.
Then it's one of these two.
Tae Joo,
who do you think it is?
What exactly is going on here?
Sir, you're here.
I clearly told you to exclude Detective Kang
from all investigations.
- Are you taking my words lightly?
- There's been
another serial murder case.
Couldn't think of a better excuse,
so you came up with that?
Why?
Did a body turn up somewhere?
The suspect said it himself.
He claimed he's committed five murders.
It could be
a lie or an exaggeration.
Now you're seriously going to
let the suspect to play you?
But we still have to look into it!
We're the police!
And what if you really end up getting played?
Then
I'll take responsibility.
Of course, you'll take responsibility.
Apologize to Jeon Kyeong Ho
and reach a settlement.
Then I'll let you back in.
Assault is prosecuted upon complaint,
so no complaint, no charges.
I think I'm being pretty generous.
Yeah, Detective Kang, just apologize.
Sir, just...
Tae Joo.
Even if it's unfair, what can we do?
Let's catch the killer first.
So?
You're going to apologize, right?
No.
Detective Kang.
Jeez, you always take
the hard way for no reason.
Let me make a proposal this time.
If you let me handle the search,
I'll resign regardless of the outcome.
I'll submit to an investigation too.
About the search operation,
as you said, Prosecutor,
if nothing turns up, the police
and prosecution will look like fools again.
If nothing comes up,
just pin it all on the guy
who's quitting anyway.
If I'm a card you're throwing away,
make full use of me.
So be it.
Let's wrap it up that way, Mr. Cha.
[Muwon District Prosecutors' Office,
Kangseng Branch]
[Missing Person Report]
[Potential Crime Scene
in the Choi In Sook Case]
It's Choi In Sook.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
If it's Choi In Sook,
that's the third murder.
Based on both the date
of the disappearance and the location,
it fits the suspect's pattern more.
I'm sure of it.
Choi In Sook.
Hello?
Is anyone here?
Anyone home?
Who is it?
Is that you, In Sook?
That darn girl, so despicable.
Leaving her sick mother and running off?
How could you call that human?
She'll be punished by heaven!
I must've been out of my darn mind,
giving birth to a girl like that
and even celebrating it.
Did your daughter say anything when she left?
She said she was going
into town to buy me clothes.
She could talk a good game.
What does someone
who stays home all day need clothes for?
Isn't that just an excuse to run away?
That nonsense again!
Why would I leave home?
I know you're praying for me to die
as soon as possible.
I know it all!
It's getting cold soon.
You'll get sick if you don't bundle up.
I'll just buy some clothes
and come right back, okay?
Darn it, come home or don't, I don't care.
Since I'm buying,
I might as well pick a nice one.
That darn girl.
Do you really think your daughter ran away?
That must be why she still hasn't come back.
But why are you looking for her now?
Are you afraid
she died some sudden, violent death?
No way! I don't know about anything else,
but she was supposed to live a long life.
A fortune-telling monk said so.
If she was coming back from the market,
she'd get off there and take this road.
From the bus stop
to Choi In Sook's house is roughly
500 meters.
So that means we have to
search this whole area, right?
We'll need at least two squads.
If something really turns up,
what happens then?
A search operation?
[Muwon District Prosecutors' Office]
What are you doing right now?
Why are you teaming up with him
instead of getting rid of him?
It's a pretty credible tip.
And if nothing turns up,
someone needs to take responsibility.
It won't be too late to remove him then.
So you take the credit
and dump the blame on someone else?
By the way,
you and Kang Tae Joo were classmates, right?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Being classmates
doesn't mean the law bends for him, right?
Isn't it nice to be outside after so long?
The wheelchair is overkill.
I told you I can walk.
Didn't you hear the doctor?
You might feel dizzy after a while.
What if you fall while walking?
Jeez.
How did we both end up
in the hospital like this?
Jeon Kyeong Ho, or Jeon whatever...
Just wait till I'm discharged.
I'll deal with him!
Still, I like being here with you.
It's nice taking walks together like this.
What's so good about it?
Look, we're the only patients
out here by ourselves.
What can we do? Neither of us has a guardian.
What do you mean? You've got your brother.
I guess
he's ashamed of me.
He doesn't even visit.
Didn't you hear?
Your brother beat Jeon Kyeong Ho up badly.
[Police officer arrested]
Still, he's going through a rough time
[for assaulting an active teacher]
because of it.
But
he's not going to
get in serious trouble over this, is he?
I didn't want to tell you
because I knew you'd worry.
But I figured you should know.
Your brother really cares about you
so much.
Where did you wander off to?
You're a patient.
What brings you to me first
instead of Ji Won?
How's Ji Won?
If you're curious, go see her yourself.
You know you're getting
discharged tomorrow, right?
I'll be here on time.
You're leaving already?
Why? Got something to say?
Tae Joo, you know...
See you tomorrow.
Who are you?
Hey, don't you recognize me?
Seo Ji...
Wait, you guys said she was fine, but why...
You!
Are you really the Kang Tae Joo I knew?
How could you lose the suspect!
And why are you resigning?
Well, even if I did sleep a little,
what is all this?
"Slept a little"?
Wow, Seo Ji Won, awesome! You're back.
There might still be a way.
What way?
Well,
I'll let you know when I'm certain.
I'm going to help you catch the suspect,
so just wait.
I'm going to take a break for now.
- Then what about the suspect?
- Am I the only cop?
They'll catch him.
You're not Kang Tae Joo, are you?
Well, I'm just a little tired.
Maybe because I'm getting old.
You should stop doing dangerous stuff too.
You really... You almost died this time!
Why?
You won't get hit in the head
all the time if I'm not around, right?
Why?
What?
Knock some sense into me sometimes!
Keep me on my toes.
You're the only one who can do that.
[Seo Ji Won]
Who's there!
Jeez!
You punk!
You startled me!
I almost died!
Then why did you sneak in like a thief?
I thought you might be sleeping.
What is it at this hour?
Did you find the camera?
- No.
- Still not?
Anyway, this came to the newsroom.
It seemed urgent.
[For Reporter Seo Ji Won, deliver by today
From Tae Joo's friend]
"Deliver by today, from Tae Joo's friend."
What's this? It's not even an arrest.
Whether a body is found or not,
today will probably be
the last time we see each other.
Are you satisfied now?
Things turned out the way you wanted.
- The way I wanted?
- You don't have to see my face anymore.
Any last words?
Make sure to catch that punk.
I heard you're quite a capable prosecutor.
I don't care if you get promoted
or become famous because of this case.
Just catch that punk
before he kills more people.
You haven't seen today's paper yet, have you?
Read it.
There.
[Controversy over fairness due to
close friendship with the prosecutor]
"Controversy over fairness
due to close friendship
with the prosecutor."
What kind of nonsense is this?
So this is how we become friends?
My friend!
Now that things have come to this,
we really need to close your assault case.
It's them!
Making a big show of it?
That way, rumors will spread
that we cut ties.
Why didn't you indict Sergeant Kang Tae Joo?
- Did your friendship play a part?
- Watch your expression when you get out.
Act like my close friend.
Just let me finish the search operation.
Why should I?
I don't see any reason to cut you some slack.
I want to find her daughter.
For Ms. Choi In Sook's mother.
Huh?
Isn't that Governor Jeon Tae Geun?
Yes. Go take a picture!
What's going on?
Governor, please say a few words.
Please say a few words.
How do you feel?
Could you please say something?
How is your condition?
As someone holding public office,
I stayed silent until now
about my own family's matter,
- fearing it might look like outside pressure.
- What a show he's putting on.
But I can't stand this anymore.
Look at my nephew here!
He can't even move around properly
on his own.
Right there!
It's all because he was assaulted
by that police officer!
And yet, how is it that a cop
who assaulted an innocent citizen
faces no punishment whatsoever?
It's unfair!
I need a full eight weeks to recover.
My students are looking for me
at school, but I can't go to them.
Is this how the police behave?
Is this acceptable?
I said I'd report in for questioning
after today's search is done!
Why are you doing that?
Are you the only cop in Korea?
What are you doing? Why aren't you
arresting that violent cop right now?
Yes!
What is that?
Kyeong Ho, are you really
on an eight-week recovery?
Wait, is it even okay for you
to drink like this?
Eight weeks? What nonsense!
Getting the medical report isn't hard at all.
I spent some money
to screw that detective over!
You should've just done your usual nonsense.
Why mess with a teacher?
Mess with her? I didn't even touch her.
She caught on first and came at me.
Who does she think she is?
Hey, is she that pretty?
She looks
even prettier than Miss Korea.
No, no!
- Hey! Turn that off now!
- He looks fine to me.
Turn that off!
What? Is he actually injured?
It's a frame-up! This is fabricated!
What exactly is fabricated?
Let's get out of here quickly!
Governor, please say a few words!
Did you know about your nephew's crime?
No, absolutely not!
Have you ever pressured the investigation?
A hostess' daughter
acting all high and mighty...
- That punk!
- Tae Joo!
Hey!
Kang Tae Joo, you punk!
Are you going to make the same mistake twice?
You said you'd find Ms. Choi In Sook.
He looks perfectly fine.
He's perfectly fine. Please say a word.
Mr. Jeon Kyeong Ho, please go now.
Wait!
Uncle, Uncle!
We should go together...
- So, what are we photographing?
- We'll begin the search operation.
The search scene here.
Do you really think we'll find anything here?
Unfortunately, yes.
Keep distance from the person
next to you and move slowly!
- Yes, sir!
Don't just pass by the reeds, leaves,
or branches in the thicket.
Examine them thoroughly! Got it?
- Yes, sir!
Keep your distance! Move slowly!
You're Prosecutor Cha Si Young, right?
I'm Seo Ji Won, a reporter
from Kangseng Daily.
You were impressive today.
I received a tape from an anonymous tipster,
but I have no idea who sent it.
Was it you who called
Jeon Kyeong Ho and Governor Jeon?
That was nothing.
Kim, did you wash the car properly?
Yes, I cleaned it thoroughly.
Did you know Sergeant Kang Tae Joo
was deployed on the operation today?
It seemed like a fairly important operation.
If he makes a contribution,
he might avoid disciplinary action.
Whoever that tipster was,
they probably expected
that you would blow it wide open, Ms. Seo.
I didn't know you were classmates
with Detective Kang.
You must have been quite close, huh?
I had the chance to get close,
but I missed it.
I heard you're close with Detective Kang.
How did you become friends?
Well, we grew up in the same neighborhood
since we were kids.
Since you were kids?
Am I already too late?
I found something.
Where?
Over here! This way!
Preserve the scene.
And call the forensics team.
[Choi In Sook]
You finally came back, my girl.
You must've suffered.
How wronged you must
have felt all this time...
I didn't know I was running late.
And I just kept scolding you for being late.
I was wrong,
my baby.
Don't go anywhere anymore.
Stay with me.
Mom.
Have you been well?
I missed you.
[Kangseng Daily]
I'm back.
What is it?
Ms. Seo found the film
with the Kangseng serial killer on it.
- What?
- It's being developed now.
Isn't that the biggest scoop?
But I don't think
the photo will come out alright.
Don't jinx it. Shut up!
[Film in development
When light is on, no entry]
Oh, it came out. It came out.
It came out?
Thanks for the meal!
Eat up. It's an extra-large special,
on the house today.
What's gotten into you? You're usually
strict about paying even with friends.
You must've had a really hard time
because of Sun Young.
Now that Sun Young's cleared her name
and the scandal's all gone...
What are you talking about?
You really didn't know anything?
It was even on the front page
that Tae Joo beat that guy up.
It's probably that guy.
The one who took Sun Young in a Grandeur.
Ki Beom...
Why didn't you tell me?
Even if no one else knows, I should've known.
I'm your groom, and you're my bride!
- Ki Beom...
- Where is that punk now?
Let's break up.
What?
You just got here,
and you're already leaving?
Yes, I'm leaving.
Take care. I won't walk you out.
No need for that.
I'll just leave after causing trouble, sir.
You really worked hard.
You've been through a lot.
[Stepping away for a moment]
My art tube...
- Oh my!
- Uh, you scared me!
You startled me!
What are you doing?
I left something behind.
What about you, sir?
What did you leave behind?
My art tube.
My drawings are in it.
So why are you here?
I'm friends with the owner.
Huh? With Andy Lau?
He's my friend's younger brother.
Oh, okay.
Your tone is a bit off.
Don't you have a killer to catch?
When are you ever going to
catch him at this rate?
Why does everyone bring up the killer
whenever they see me?
Well...
I'm not a cop anymore. I quit.
Then what about the killer?
The other police officers will...
You just focus on your studies.
Go home early, and...
If you see anything like a scarecrow
at night, just run, okay?
Why?
Because it might not actually be a scarecrow.
Remember what I said.
Why aren't you answering?
Well...
Can't you not quit being a cop?
I want you to catch him yourself, sir.
Oh, this is just, well...
Jeez.
If only grown-ups' business
were as simple as flipping pancakes...
What's this?
It's a bribe.
When you eat it,
just think it over twice more, okay?
Bye!
Giving a bribe to a guy who got fired?
What a waste.
Stop staring at it, okay?
Do you think staring
will bring back your focus?
Jeez, I thought we finally
got a real scoop this time.
Let's run it as is.
As is?
I can't even make out the eyes,
nose, or mouth.
You never know. Someone might recognize him.
No way.
At least one person will!
The suspect himself.
Even if it doesn't identify him,
it can still pressure the suspect.
"You've been caught on camera."
Let's break up.
Ki Beom!
Ki Beom, are you okay?
Stop it.
What's wrong with you today?
Hey.
If you're tired, go home first.
I'll handle it.
No, we have a lot to tidy up.
Go home first.
We're almost at closing time anyway.
- I'll do it.
- Jeez, just listen to me.
Excuse me.
Is this yours?
Yes, thank you.
It's late. Do you think
you can go by yourself?
I'm fine. It's just a quick bus ride.
Goodbye.
She should've gone home earlier.
It's really dangerous these days.
Huh? It's raining.
What? It's a scarecrow.
If you see anything
like a scarecrow at night, just run.
Because it might not actually be a scarecrow.
Yes, hello?
Sir.
Well, a body...
It's another murder.
Why are you telling me this?
Did you forget I quit? I'm hanging up.
The dead girl
is Min Ji.
Who?
Kang Tae Joo!
- Hey, you...
- Why are you here?
Hey!
Kang Tae Joo!
Sir.
- Hey, stop him! Keep him away!
- Block him, you punks!
- Keep him away! Block him!
- Sir.
- Kang Tae Joo!
- Hey, stop him!
Hey, you punk!
Hey, you!
What are you doing here?
Kang Tae Joo.
[Kim Min Ji]
We said we'd handle it.
What are you doing here? Go! We'll handle it.
You really need to leave.
So why did you...
Hey, your nose is bleeding.
What's going on with you?
Kang Tae Joo!
Hey!
Take him away, now.
Kang Tae Joo!
Someone get him out of here!
Hey, bring a stretcher.
A life's mission?
How did you end up getting into that,
your life's mission?
It might have started
that day, I guess.
This time, I'll be the one asking.
Was it you who ruined my mission,
Mr. Lee Yong Woo?
Mr. Lee Yong Woo.
Oh, come on.
Repeating the same thing isn't fun.
Alright.
Since it's something I did anyway,
I'll lay it all out.
Are you saying you'll confess?
It's going to be a pretty long story.
You've got enough time, right?
Of course.
Where should we start?
But
please tell me your story too.
It's no fun if I'm the only one talking.
You tell yours,
and I'll tell mine.
That way,
we can complete our story.
"Our story"?
Yes.
Ours.
I've got to catch that punk.
Let's catch him together.
[National Saemaeul Leaders Convention]
So that's why you came back?
Unbelievable, Seo Ji Won.
We didn't even see a strand of his hair.
Does that make any sense?
You don't even know
what kind of woman she is, do you?
- You're being fooled too.
- I said shut up!
Jeon Kyeong Ho again? Seriously?
Thinking back now, it was all bait.
Kang Sun Young!
Who's there?