Dylan is really not
coming back to join us.
Thame from MARS.
He’s never left you behind.
All he did was to make your song
reach Miss Pemika.
It even proves to me that…
Idols aren’t fake like those with egos
Hey. Po, how is it going?
I’ve noticed it a few times already.
You have a crush on him, don’t you?
What do I have to do to make us close?
Keep talking, I guess,
to learn more about each other.
You’re really not good
at crossing the road?
How do you cross the road
in front of Oner then?
I need to watch
the traffic lights carefully
and cross when there are
many people around.
How about you?
Are you good at crossing the road?
I can cross,
but since becoming an idol,
I’ve always had Mick
and the security team with me.
I never get to go anywhere on my own.
Being an idol seems nice.
You always have people
to take care of you.
But you don’t have anyone like I do,
so you need to be careful.
Even if you're crossing with others,
make sure not to stay on the edge.
And if I get the chance,
I'll be there to walk right with you.
What?
You just smiled at me
while you were crossing the road.
That’s because I didn’t think it was you.
Who did you think it was?
Thame?
Come on.
You’re always thinking about him, huh?
Did you already forget
he’s not allowed to come to the company?
Also, he doesn’t like men.
Do you think
you know your friend well enough?
If he doesn’t feel anything,
why would he stay on the phone
with me all night?
All night?
Yeah.
How many nights?
Yesterday was the first one.
One night?
I don’t want to brag,
but when we were trainees,
we stayed on the phone
until morning almost every day.
If you’re using these talks as a measure,
I’d probably already be in a relationship
with him ages ago.
You’re his friend,
but I’m…
His coworker.
I bet he feels nothing special about you.
What makes you say that?
Let’s say it again.
What makes you think he feels that way?
Well,
last night when we talked,
it seemed he wanted to know
and understand me,
learning what I like or dislike,
what my family background’s like,
and how I came to work.
And how is that different
from a job interview?
It’s different, of course.
Before that,
I accidentally told him first that
I wanted to understand him
beyond just work.
Wow, you’re being pretty forward, huh?
It wasn’t intentional.
THAME
Let’s find out who understands him better.
Hey. Don’t.
Annyeong.
Damn it. Jun?
Why is it you talking?
Wow.
You recognize my voice.
What a sweet moment.
I’m not calling you.
I’m calling Po.
I want to ask him
to take care of Nano’s matter.
He told Dylan he went to practice dancing
at the studio outside,
but he went to check
and couldn’t find him.
He didn’t pick up the calls either,
but he posted an IG story of him
at the company’s practice room.
Dylan got tricked, huh?
Serves him damn right!
I’m going to tease him.
I’m near the practice room.
I’ll go check for you where Nano is.
What are you doing there?
Thame, I have a question.
If someone says
they want to understand you beyond work,
do you think they feel something for you?
They just want to be friends.
Why did you ask such a nonsense question?
Okay, okay.
That’s all I wanted to know.
Bye-bye.
See?
Thame has no clue.
All he thinks about is work.
You need to stop letting your mind wander.
Po didn’t pick up your call either?
No, but Jun picked up instead.
He’s with him now.
He said he’d look for Nano for us.
-Perfect timing, huh?
-I was thinking the same thing.
Why such perfect timing?
There’s no practice session.
Why the hell did he go there?
I think… he probably went there
to discuss work or meet someone.
To meet who?!
I don’t know.
I’m sitting with you here.
Why are you upset with me, huh?
Well, I can't go to the company,
so it's inconvenient to do anything.
Huh?
Someone like you
wanting to go to the company?
You’re acting strange, dude.
By the way, last night,
who were you talking
to on the phone all sweetly?
I saw you talking from before I left
until I came back in the morning,
and you were still talking.
Are you in the talking stage with someone?
Talking stage? Nonsense.
-I just talked to…
-Nano pulled a fast one on me.
He must know for sure
that I’m back with you guys.
Well, you were stalking his IG story.
I was curious.
He told the company he was going back
to study, so I wanted to know
what he’s studying and where.
Look at all his IG posts.
I don’t understand even a single one.
NANOWONGMARS LET’S GO FISHING TOGETHER
MY FIRST SCUBA DIVING EXPERIENCE
I’M SUPER EXCITED
THANK YOU, UNCLES AND AUNTIES
FOR TEACHING ME TAI CHI TODAY
I HAD SO MUCH FUN
I’LL JOIN YOU AGAIN NEXT TIME
MORNING TAI CHI SESSION
LET’S LEARN HORSEBACK RIDING, HEHE
Or could it be a subtle hint
that he won't be returning
to the group’s house?
I don’t think so.
He’ll come back, trust me.
Or else, who watered that orange tree?
He bought it.
Anyway, we need
to bring him back and talk.
I’ll call Po,
asking about Nano’s schedule.
THAME
Nano isn’t in the practice room.
It’s you again?!
Po left his phone with me.
I just had him do a little work for me.
What did you ask him to do?
I saw Nano's schedule was empty,
so I had Po fill it up for him.
And this is the concept
we’ve come up with, Miss Gam.
It’s something like
bringing idols together
to compete in a brain teaser game.
Well, I've done something
like this before,
so I don't want that repeat content.
Oh, please excuse me.
I left my stuff here.
Oh, I’ve figured it out now.
How about doing something funny
or a role play?
I think that doesn’t fit my product much.
Well,
I’ve heard your discussion.
How about we try this?
Pepper, Dylan, are you ready for today?
Drink and let’s go camping!
It’s going to be fun.
Jun, why are you bringing so much stuff?
Do you have two necks?
I happen to be a generous person.
I’ve prepared one for others.
Here you are.
Thame, say hi.
Is he still not awake?
Or does he not like you yet?
By the way, did he call you last night?
He did, but…
So, Jun planned the camping trip?
Yes.
It’s solely his idea.
I’m just saying what he briefed me.
We ended up pushing the project through.
Jun is good at it, isn’t he?
Nano doesn’t have any schedule,
while you’re still under punishment,
but he finally came up with a plan
to bring you all together.
That’s so amazing.
Who else could do it like that?
Hey.
I’m sleepy.
I’ll hang up.
Eh?
That sounds exactly like him.
He only called to ask about work.
Or maybe…
Thame doesn't like it
when I keep talking about you?
I bet this is the reason.
And now I’m standing close to you.
What?
Whoa.
Are you already thinking
that he's jealous of me and you?
You’re being like this again.
I already asked him,
and now you’re still imagining things.
Come on.
Hey, Nano is here.
Hey?
Are my eyes playing tricks on me?
Have you been showing up early these days?
I'm just someone
who has discipline, you know.
How about you, little bro?
Where have you been?
We haven’t met these days.
Hello, Sphere.
Hello. This is Nano from MARS.
I’ve heard we’re going on a trip today.
Come with us.
Hey, hello.
It’s been a while. How have you guys been?
Come sit here.
Where are you going?
I need to concentrate.
Who picked the location?
It’s damn far.
It's hot, not chilling at all.
What's not chilling?
I think it’s pretty chilling here.
You’re the only one chilling.
Why complain, huh?
Hurry up. Help me unload
the stuff from the car.
Did anyone tell Po
to keep an eye on Thame well?
If something’s up,
let me know as soon as possible.
I’ll be the one reporting it
to Miss Pemika.
You two aren’t allowed to say anything.
-Got it.
-Yeah.
Where are the MARS members now?
Have they arrived?
Or did they get lost?
Here they are.
They haven’t finished setting up?
It’s done.
We're about to start filming.
Let’s go.
Per, please open
the show as scripted, okay?
-Got it.
-I’ll help them down there.
The first mission Brainy
assigned MARS to do
is "Drink and set up the tent"!
Hey! Is that all the energy
you’ve got, huh?
When are you helping me here?
How about you squat for me instead?
Stop messing around and get over here.
I’m not messing around, okay?
How are we supposed to do this?
When did I look like
I was messing around, huh?
I don’t know.
What we agreed on initially
was a chill glamping trip,
focusing on the vibe, wasn’t it?
Well, Miss Gam asked for a change.
She said glamping
doesn’t require much skill
and doesn’t fit her product’s concept.
That’s why she switched
to serious camping.
She wants the boys
to show what they've got.
Showing it now, aren’t they?
Can we make it up?
Since the tent looks this deflated,
I feel bad
for the client’s chicken essence.
We can’t, bro.
We don’t even know
how to set it up ourselves.
Don’t look at me.
Why are you looking at me?
They hired you, not me.
Thame, let me see the manual.
Dylan, let me give it a try.
Come take a look.
What is it like?
Now, move.
Let’s drink and let the fun continue!
Cut.
You can read Chinese characters?
I can’t.
I’ve just started learning
the beginner level,
but I've set up this kind of tent before,
so I kind of know what to do by feel.
Hey.
Hey, don’t do it like that.
We must press the safety lock first.
Be careful.
Look at us messing around for so long.
Here we go.
Come.
You want to do this, right?
Wow.
-The next game is outdoors again?
-Come on.
Is this what he told
the company he would learn?
That’s why he doesn’t have any schedule.
He must have really made up his mind
not to be an idol anymore.
Just to not be an idol,
does he really have
to learn so many things?
Is there a way
I can talk to Nano alone for a moment?
You know how to handle him?
I’ll have to give it a try.
-Then, I’ll…
-I’ll tell Mick you need more interviews.
Why did you interrupt Thame like that?
So, what were you about to say?
You already said all that.
The next mission is called
"Drink and Fight"!
Here’s the rule.
Whoever gets pushed
out of the line first is eliminated.
If any member gets eliminated,
you can go do more interviews with him.
Stick with the same interview.
We’re just changing the background.
Actually, I’ve had this idea in mind
but didn’t share it with anyone.
But if anyone asks,
tell them it’s my idea.
Yes, Mick.
You’re the best.
This is what you have to do.
The four of you must make Nano
the first one eliminated.
-Start!
-Go!
Ouch!
The first member eliminated is Jun.
The plan went a bit off track,
but it’s good
since I now have time to brief you.
What’s good about this?
Now I’m stuck with you again.
Did you see Thame’s look just now?
He didn’t seem okay with this.
Wow.
Do you still think he’s jealous?
Well, if he isn’t,
why would he look at me that way?
You’ve taken it too far for me to handle.
I think we need time.
Anyway, let’s focus on Nano for now.
What are you planning
to talk to him about?
Hello, Thame.
Don’t worry about us at all.
I believe someone talented like you,
no matter where you are,
will be successful.
I promise, with my little finger,
that I’ll grab a ticket to cheer for you
at your concert in Korea!
See you there!
Keep fighting, bro.
Okay, cut.
Let me continue
the interview a little more.
I’m curious to know each member’s plan
after the group activities end.
What about yours, Nano?
Mine?
I’m thinking of shifting focus
to something else.
I want to try
something completely different.
For example?
It’s hard to answer now.
I’m interested in many things.
You know, my plans include
cooking, going on a trip,
and learning a language.
Forest planting sounds nice,
and diving is also interesting to me.
All of those things
you uploaded on your IG, right?
Eh?
You stalked my IG, too?
Well,
your IG reminds me of a friend of mine,
who went through a time in life
where changes were happening.
That’s why he tried
so many different things.
I bet your friend
was looking for something new.
It’s because he feared.
So,
these were what you did
before working at Oner?
Yeah.
Nano’s IG reminds me of myself
during that time.
I was both heartbroken
and unemployed.
I couldn’t rely on myself.
I was totally lost.
But the strongest feeling was fear.
Nano?
He fears working as a group again?
The person who always shines
bright on stage?
What was your friend’s fear?
He feared disappointment.
My friend once devoted himself
to something,
thinking it would define…
his life forever.
But when it didn’t go as planned,
he thought he must try different things
for himself
so that he wouldn’t have
to rely on others.
So, how did it end?
He realized
he probably feared too much.
It’s okay to feel disappointed,
but we also need to be able to start over.
In the same way?
Perhaps
it’s better this time.
But it’s said
the same book,
no matter how many times you read it,
will always end the same way.
We can’t change the ending.
Thame…
is tearing the last page
and rewriting the whole page with you.
The reason everyone was trying
to make this schedule happen here
is not for anything else,
but just to talk to you.
They really want to write a new ending.
Rewriting, and then what?
One day, it might still end
the same way anyway.
And if that day arrives,
this main dancer
who has to rely on the group
will end up with no future ahead.
Mick! Mick! We’re in trouble now.
Thame and Jun have been in the forest
for a while and still haven’t come out.
I don’t know if they got lost
or if they’re fighting again.
Gosh. We’re screwed.
Why didn’t you help
keep an eye on them, huh?
If something happens,
who must take responsibility?
It’s me. Which direction did they head?
-That way.
-Okay.
Everyone, stop.
Go look for Thame now.
That way. Go now. Hurry up.
Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up.
-That way.
Thame!
CAFE
CAMPSITE
POOL
OUTDOOR ACTIVITIES AREA
RESTROOM
He told me to come and hear you guys out.
But I think we can’t change anything.
I don’t want to rely on you all anymore.
After it ends,
someone in my position
won’t make it through anyway.
Do you think we'll make it through, huh?
You know what?
I play in a movie,
but as a supporting character.
As for me, I’ll probably end up
writing underground songs.
I wouldn’t get to sing anymore.
Others will probably remember me as an MC.
And what’s wrong about us
relying on one another?
Look at him.
He’s this old but just got employed.
Do you think we all could make it through?
But what Jun said is right.
How old are you now?
It’s totally fine to fail sometimes
and rely on others sometimes.
Falling once
doesn’t mean you have to die with it.
But the person who will make it through
is someone like Thame, right?
What makes you say I’ll make it through?
I couldn't even keep the group together.
How can I make it through?
That's how it is.
Since we're all crappy people,
let's get back up
and move forward together.
And if we fall again,
no matter how many times,
we'll just carry each other
along like this.
And if we really fall again,
I think you'll make it out
better than the rest of us.
You even have more skills
than Dylan, Thame,
Pepper, and me.
What’s wrong about
being a main dancer, huh?
Lisa is also the main dancer of the group.
Come on. Lisa can rap, too.
Hey, I can teach you how to rap.
What the heck?
I don’t want to trouble you.
You can even ask Thame
to teach you singing.
Just tell us, okay?
If you kept silent and ran away like this,
how would anyone know
what you really wanted?
Do we look that smart, huh?
Come on.
Are you calling me back to join the group
or just to scold me?
We want you back
and also want to clear things up.
So, what’s your answer?
Try.
Just a love song
That you need to listen to
Just lyrics that are nothing new
But you and I know the meaning
Between the lines
You have to sing this song
with full projection.
Don't hold back your voice.
You need to sing strong,
push your voice out,
and add more power to it.
What do you mean by power?
Are you asking him
to do push-ups or something?
Can you explain it in a way
that is easier to understand, Dylan?
You’d better use your brain, buddy.
-Whoa.
-Dylan, you’re damn stupid.
Hey, stop.
If your high notes aren't strong,
you need to use your breath to help.
Try it this way.
Just a love song
That you need to listen to
Just lyrics that are nothing new
But you and I know the meaning
Between the lines
Just a love song
That you need to listen to
Just lyrics that are nothing new
But you and I know the meaning
Between the lines
There are no perfect sweet words
Just listen with your heart to find
The answer I’ve been searching for
Love is nothing else but you
Here you are.
See? If you had given it to the him
from the start,
we wouldn't have had
to struggle going to camp.
But camping was your idea, wasn’t it?
And it did work, right?
But it wasn’t comfortable for me.
If you had been a little smarter,
it would have been
more comfortable for me.
If you’re that smart, why didn’t
you come up with the idea yourself?
Also, if you were that smart,
you wouldn’t have been tricked
by that maknae from the start.
Hey.
Stop fighting already.
I’m back.
Anyway,
thank you.
I want to tell you that all this time,
whenever a problem arose,
I knew you all handled it
without letting me know about it.
But I’ve grown up now,
and we’re the same team.
What I want to say is,
from now, when there is a problem,
share it with me.
Nano, if you can teach
this kind of mindset to Jun,
that will be super amazing, bro.
That sounds like you can help, dude.
Hey. I told you to stop fighting.
Don’t you know that
just stopping us from fighting like this
already helps a lot?
By the way, Jun,
thank that person for me.
Po?
Sure.
I’ll call and thank him.
Wow.
You picked up so fast.
Why did you call?
Nano wants to thank you.
Well, Thame,
do you have anything to say to Po?
No.
I’m sleepy already.
I’m leaving.
IS IT CLEAR ENOUGH
HE ISN’T INTERESTED IN YOU?
You can remember Po’s number?
How could you know
it’s his number?
I was just guessing,
and I was right.
So, the person you talked to
the whole night was Po, right?
Yeah.
We talked about work.
Nobody would talk about work all night,
not to mention
you acting jealous of Jun and him.
Jealous?
You didn’t realize you were jealous?
If I am to be jealous,
doesn't that mean
I must have feelings for him first?
Are you saying
you don’t have feelings for him?
Well,
I guess so.
Really?
So, what you're doing right now
is really bad
because you're giving him false hope.
What?
Think about it.
You talked on the phone with him
all night.
You remember his number.
You even acted jealous
when he was close to Jun.
He’s probably imagining things too far,
thinking that you have feelings
for him already.
You're really such a badass if you don't.
So, I’m treating him badly?
Before thinking
that you’re treating him badly,
answer me first
if you have feelings for him or not.
I just want to make him feel
he’s important to me.
Because?
I don’t know.
You’ve never had a crush on anyone before.
That’s why you don’t know.
Do you want to know
if what you’re feeling now
means you like him?
If I like him,
I’m not hurting him, right?
You’re not.
But if you don’t like him,
then you’re seriously hurting
his feelings.
Tell me what I have to do
to find out if I like him or not.
Just do what I’m about to tell you.
Thank you.
Are you here to help me cross the road?
Well,
that’s not the reason.
So, why did you come?
If you want to know
if you like him or not,
you have to walk closer to him.
Is something up?
Can you…
stay still for a while?
Then, try touching him.
After you touch him,
if you hear
your heart beat faster than usual,
that’s…
what’s called love.
I think the way to prove to the company
that we can continue as MARS is our song.
When you said
it’ll be the five of them together,
-did that include Pepper?
-Yes.
If that’s the case,
it wouldn’t count as every member.
MARS doesn’t need to have five members.
With four members,
MARS can be perfectly complete.
You see now how serious it is, right?
That’s why I told you,
between Thame and you,
it can never be possible.