Switch off the cameras.
I said switch off the cameras.
Thank you, Brother.
As the minister of coal and mines..
..I assure you that
our international..
..diamond trading center..
..is going to be the
center for the whole world.
Get up.
Move. Freeze.
Nobody moves.
Khokha.
Look..
Lara, get the car.
Hey, bossy.
You aren't doing the right thing.
You won't be able to escape.
If you say anything else..
..then you won't survive, Minister.
Well done.
But you were firing blindly.
What if one of the bullets had hit me?
You would've died if
Marcos wanted to kill you.
If I wanted to kill you..
then you wouldn't have survived.
Hey, my camera.
No photography allowed
at the minister's place.
You won't forsake your
passion for direction.
Stop it.
DC. - Sorry, boss.
Since I was struck by lightening..
..the current is still inside.
But I forget.
Sorry for that.
What next? - Look, Marcos.
Till the news of the heist
doesn't die down play cool.
You'll get your share
after I make the deal.
"The beautiful ambience."
"The scenic valleys."
"Where have we wandered to?"
What a place.
What fresh air.
Wonder how people live..
..all their lives in the
hustle and bustle of the city?
Yes, Raj. There's so much peace here.
No tension or problem.
I have a suggestion.
Let's buy a grape orchard.
We'll drink and serve others as well.
Save me, save me.
Their child is stuck in
my luggage boot. Get him out.
But how did he get
stuck in your luggage boot?
I'll tell you that later,
first save me.
Okay, we're coming. - What?
We aren't here to do social work.
Look..
..he's a child after all.
Whether it's human or a gorilla.
Keep a smile on your face.
They should think that
we're here to save their child.
Come quickly.
Hello.
Look there. They're smiling.
They're here to save him.
We're here to help.
Thank you. You saved my life.
We didn't save you..
but that gorilla's child.
Aren't you ashamed?
You steal baby animals.
No, no, I didn't steal the baby.
There were bananas
in the luggage boot..
..and that's why the baby climbed in.
And the boot closed shut.
And just like you two,
they thought that I..
Are you two tourists?
Is there a hotel,
motel or a place to stay nearby?
There's nothing around here.
But my village is closeby.
You can spend the night at my house.
I am late.
That's good. Savitri, see that
they have proper breakfast, okay.
I'm leaving. I am in a hurry.
Bye, darling.
Careful. Careful.
Sister-in-law,
you can speak good Hindi.
Living with him, the entire
village and I have learnt Hindi..
..but we couldn't learn English yet.
Oh, meet my children.
This is Varun, he's taken after him.
This is Rosy, she's taken after me.
And he's Jackson.
Who has Jackson taken after?
Madam. Tea.
Thanks.
You two continue with your breakfast.
The function has started.
Please excuse me.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you've done me a favour..
..by depositing your
hard-earned money in this bank..
..and putting your faith
in me and I thank everyone for that.
Pack the luggage. And I'll get a taxi.
Your hard-earned money
is locked in this bank..
..and I am the key.
Save me, save me. - Come on.
What are you staring at? Run. Quickly.
What have you done
You robbed the bank. - Yes.
No one will come forward, get that.
You had decided that
we won't do anything wrong.
We were going to change, isn't it?
That's only if the
world lets us change.
The security guard
left the money unattended..
..and was drinking Pepsi.
What could I do?
Sharpen your.. knives and blades!
I have a gun. - Please don't kill me.
Move fast or else I'll kill you.
Raj, quickly.
Bye-bye. I've made it outside.
Catch them. - Running won't help..
Catch them.
Thief.
Come on, Dhanno. Move.
Yash, you got me trapped
in a big mess today.
Faster.
How long do you want
to conduct sting operations..
..for petty amounts, petty thief.
I am better off as a petty thief.
Petty thieves get minor sentences,
get that.
I'm locked up for 15
days and then released.
When you get locked up..
..you won't come out for 15 years.
That's why I never got
into a partnership with you?
What are you doing?
Have you gone crazy? - This is
the only way to stop them, you thief.
You idiots. Robbing your own money?
"There's something
different about you."
"Your company's different."
"There's a different
kind of passion in you."
"You've knocked me off my senses."
"There's something
different about your eyes."
"Your effect is completely different."
"Your qualities are different."
"You're like a complete new package."
"We've hit the jackpot."
"We're loaded with money."
"Luck has supported us."
"And the babes are impressed."
"We've hit the jackpot."
"We're loaded with money."
"Luck has supported us."
"And the babes are impressed."
"Everything is fine now."
"Now we're living in style."
"Everyone's walking behind us now."
"We walk in front."
"It's time to have fun now."
"There's just happiness around."
"Live it up. It wasn't easy."
"These moments are very special."
"Your style is different."
"You've got a different
kind of mesmerizing effect."
"Your radiance is different."
"That has come straight
from the heart."
"We've hit the jackpot."
"We're loaded with money."
"Luck has supported us."
"And the babes are impressed."
"O darling, fall in love with me."
"O dear, accept my proposal."
"On the tune of this money."
"Dance with me."
"Create an ambience for us."
"Make my heart beat
as hard as the drums."
"Lord, I am thankful to you."
"Now you do justice."
"We're your devotees after all."
"Forgive us if we're at fault."
"Your condition is different."
"You have a different gait."
"You have a unique smile."
"Anyone who sees you
says the same thing."
"We've hit the jackpot."
"We're loaded with money."
"Luck has supported us."
"And the babes are impressed."
We thrashed him black and blue..
..even then he didn't say anything.
He didn't utter a word. - Kill him.
Scoundrels. Rascals.
You think I ruined the village.
You. What did you tell the police?
Those thieves are my friends.
I called them from the city.
They're my friends!
And you?
What were you saying?
That because I couldn't
rob every house in the village..
..I opened a bank and robbed everyone.
Zandu Lal, I was only doing my duty.
Doing your duty.
Give me the gun.
Give me the gun. - Here. - Here.
That one is empty.
I have only two options left now.
Either I murder a few
of you and get locked up again.
Or else I catch those
two scoundrels at Durban..
..and bring them back here. - Durban?
Yes, they're from Durban.
I found a train ticket for Durban..
..in the bag,
which they had left at my house.
Those two fled, so he'll flee too.
Everything I own is right here.
My wife and children.
My home. Everyone.
Where else will I go
if I don't come back here?
Tell me what should I do?
- Go to Durban.
Go to Durban.
Sir, did you see anything?
That's it.
Get ready for action.
- I am ready, sir.
But, sir, backup hasn't arrived yet.
We can't wait for backup..
..or else diamond thief Marcos
will escape from our clutches.
Carefully.
Sir.
Idiot.
Nobody moves.
Super-cop Arjun Singh. - Oh God.
Out. Out you girls!
International criminal Marcos.
You made a big mistake
by coming to Durban.
Because I am a part
of the police force here.
Everybody, hands up.
I normally don't
engage in an encounter..
..if the criminal gives up easily.
I suggest that you
throw down your weapons.
Or else I'll turn this
sea red with your blood.
Open the door.
You're a lucky man, Arjun Singh.
You're fated to die by my hands.
Papa. Papa. - Grandpa.
Is he fine? - He survived.
Yes, ma'am.
The doctor has taken 12 bullets..
..out of the 14 that he was hit by.
- 12 bullets.
And the two others?
- His life could've been endangered..
..if they had tried to take them out.
So.. - Both of them
are in the stomach.
But no problem, no problem.
Why, Grandpa?
Are they chocolate toffees..
..that will melt away in the stomach?
- Tuktuk.
No, dear, they won't melt.
But when those bullets
travel in his stomach..
..he will get tickled. - Tickled?
Yes, tickled. And because of that..
..he won't be able
to control his laughter..
..irrespective of how tense he is.
- Oh, God.
- Commissioner, I want to talk to you.
Even during the operation,
in a state of unconsciousness..
..Arjun was saying,
"My wife shouldn't find out.."
"..or else they'll shoot me."
Actually my daughter
Kajal is suffering..
..from a split personality disorder.
But there must be
a big reason behind that.
The reason is inside, Doctor.
That fool Arjun.
She thought he's a hero.
But after their marriage..
..she found out that he's no hero,
but a big failure.
That poor girl's
dreams were shattered.
She kept her frustration in her heart.
And because of that
she developed this ailment.
And now the condition is, Doctor..
..that Kajal has fits at
least once a day for ten minutes.
And when she has the fits..
..she wants to kill Arjun. - Oh no.
Oh yes.
I have to attend an important meeting.
But my staff is right here.
Excuse me, sir. Time for juice.
Orange.
No one in my family
has ever had orange juice.
We only have pomegranate juice.
- Right.
No problem, sir.
Mummy.
You want pomegranate juice?
Has anyone in your family
ever seen a pomegranate?
You're laughing.
Am I joking?
I am not laughing, Kajal.
I mean Kamini.
I am feeling..
ticklish in the stomach.
I see.
I'll take care of your tickle.
Or else, because of the
bullets in your stomach..
..you'll keep laughing
in front of my Kajal..
..and that poor girl will keep crying.
Bullets? In my stomach.
How could you survive after
being hit by so many bullets?
If you had died..
..then at least Kajal would've
been free from your clutches.
Why did you go to catch
Marcos alone? Tell me.
You're a police officer,
but you got beaten up by criminals.
Weren't you ashamed?
I say.. I say, Kajal.
Kajal, let's forget the past.
I am dead. - Mummy. - Save me.
Doctor. - Boss.
But you were bedridden.
O my God!
Sir barely survived.
"No problem."
My wife left me.
I'm not scared of dying.
I feel like jumping
out of this window.
Save me.
But you wanted to die.
I have small children.
I can't give them a mother's love..
..but I can get them a new mother.
Save me.
- Don't move. Someone save him.
Boss. Doctor.
- Dad. - Look at him, what he's doing.
How did this..
What are you doing here?
Actually,
Sister-in-law, there was a storm..
..but luckily sir survived again.
And what are you doing with this?
Who brought this? Throw it away.
Who is it?
Oh, Lord.
Someone threw a wreath on
me as soon as I entered this city.
Seems like the entire
city knows those rascals.
Come in.
Stand at the back.
Sir.
Yash. - Get well soon, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Congratulations, you survived.
- Thank you.
I don't want your flowers.
Sir, you can accept his
flowers but not mine? - Shut up.
Cheater, thief, blackmailer.
You live with such a great man.
Do some social work. Do something big.
Be like him.
- I am better off the way I am.
One day you'll die by my hands.
Yash, ask him to get out..
of my sight.
I said go. - Leave.
Something happens every time..
I see him.
Control yourself, sir.
If you move,
your stitches will open up, sir.
Control, sir. Control, sir. Control.
Hi, Raj.
Naughty boy.
Hi, darling.
How are you?
Who's he? - Rascal.
Congratulations.
Hi. - Hi.
Raj, you.. here?
You didn't send this
month's installment.
I was slightly busy due
to my brother's engagement.
That's why.. - I thought.. you forgot.
You do remember your promise,
don't you, darling?
Of course, you'll be my next actress.
No. - Congrats! - Thank you.
Why are you showing it again?
I'll.. send it tomorrow.
I get bored after
10 minutes in a party.
Meet me right now.
Sanjana. Sanjana.
Where are you? - Sanjana. Sanjana.
Where are you?
Hi. - Hi. What's wrong?
All your friends are searching
for you and you're hiding here.
The girl who's getting
engaged is my best friend.
I am not her enemy
that I'll go sit there.
Enemy? I didn't understand?
Oh, God.
If I go and sit there..
..then won't that boy
choose me over my friend.
Your friend is quite
beautiful as well.
I saw her. - Tell me something.
What would you choose between
a television and plasma? - Plasma.
And between an Indica and Ferrari.
- Ferrari.
That is the difference.
She's the television and I am plasma.
She's Indica and I am Ferrari.
I see.
So you think you're the
most beautiful.. - "I think."
What do you mean?
Just a minute
Take a close look at me.
You're beautiful,
but not as much as you think.
I have a shack at Sunset beach.
You can find me there
everyday. - What?
You don't find me that beautiful..
..so you won't come there either.
We'll see.
I think that girl's half crazy.
- Oh no, she's completely insane.
But she's made me crazy as well.
Who's creating a
commotion at midnight?
Seems like a new tenant.
He's not visible in the dark.
Hello, my friend?
What's this commotion?
- I am chopping wood.
Is this the time to chop wood?
- It's cold now..
..so should I chop
wood in the morning?
During the day,
I was shivering with cold.
What if I freeze to death at night?
Will you take me to the crematorium?
Won't you think about the neighbors?
The neighbors didn't think about me.
My heater broke down.
Did anyone lend me another one?
These misers didn't even
give me a piece of wood.
You give it. And I will
stop chopping wood. You give it.
The heater in our house
is working perfectly.
There's no wood in our house.
There must be a chair, sofa, table..
dining table at home.
Anything at all. Give me that.
I'll manage with that. Give it.
See. When I asked for your
furniture you couldn't say a thing.
Hey, should I come down?
No. We don't call strangers
home at this hour. Go.
I don't like this man.
He can cause us trouble in the future.
Should I teach him a lesson?
- Forget it.
He's a frustrated man.
He must have some problem as well.
Tell me something.
Is that girl really beautiful?
She is.
But I made a mistake.
I didn't praise her.
- You did the right thing.
The more negative you behave..
..she'll be more impressed.
One more thing.
She should think that..
..that several girls
are crazy over you.
I knew it.
What is this?
What is this? - My heart.
Can't you girls think of anything..
..other than love and heart?
Explain to your friends.
What does he think of himself?
There's something about him..
..that's why 150 girls
are crazy about him.
Excuse me. - Thank God.
We won't have to give
this month's installment.
Oh God, now you don't say
that you're in love with me.
Please. - Me, with you?
No way. - God is great.
At least I found one girl..
..who thinks about
other things than love.
What's bad about her?
- What's good about her?
She thinks she's beautiful.
Beauty should be.. - Like me.
No. You have shortcomings
as well. - Like?
Look, your face is fine at the top..
..but the problem starts
as we come down, isn't it?
The nose could be sharper.
Actually, you know beauty
isn't about the face alone.
No, no, it's just about the face.
Look at your face.
You look so handsome. - I know.
I am very handsome. - Bye. - Bye.
Hello. - Hello, hello, hello.
Look.. I am not responsible
for whatever happened.
You are responsible.
Your entire face has been blackened.
- No, no, no.
My friend did it. - Friend.
Those two scoundrels
met me as friends as well..
..and dishonored me in
front of the entire village.
And that's why, whenever
I see someone with a black face..
..I see myself.
See. See.
No, no, no.
I will clean it, okay. - No.
It's my face. I like it black.
What's your problem?
- I do have a problem.
Ever since I've been dishonored,
I hate black faces.
You hate black. - I hate black.
He hates black.
What's wrong with you?
What the.. - He hates black.
No, no, no.. - You hate black.
No, I.. - Obama is the president
of America and you still hate us?
Look.. I said.. black face.
Not the full body.
He hates black. He hates black.
So bad.
Excuse me, why is there
a crowd gathered around here?
Some Afro-American
people beat up an Indian.
This used to happen in Australia.
It has started here as well.
Great.
Seems like he's been badly beaten up.
Get up, Brother. Get up.
You recognized me?
Who won't recognize an angel?
You're the only one who
stepped forth to help me.
Can't you see?
My sight's distorted.
Those scoundrels beat me up so badly.
How many fingers?
First take off your socks.
Why are you joking with me?
- That's good.
Come. Let's take you to the hospital,
Zandu Lal.
Just a minute.
How do you know my name?
Your news was in the newspapers.
You robbed a bank in the village,
isn't it? - No.
- It's been published here as well.
- What's going on?
Why is there a crowd?
What's happening?
Clear! Clear!
Come on, move.
- Yash. You here? - Sir.
How's your social work?
- Doing fine, sir.
And your friend.
That cheater, thief, blackmailer.
What is this, Yash?
You're such a decent man.
Why do you keep the
company of that blackmailer?
Leave him.
- Sir, can you leave your dog?
No, no, no way.
So. He's human after all.
I've raised him.
I'm trying to reform him,
sir, and I'll succeed.
Hey, you can reform the world later..
..first take care of my condition.
Yes, come on. - Sir, I..
No, I am going that way.
I'll drop him there.
Okay, bye. - Okay, sir.
Thank you.
Yash, where were you?
You know Zandu Lal is in the city.
You met him as well.
- What do you mean? You too.
This bank heist will ruin our lives.
Damn this neighbor..
Why are you disposing
your skirt in our house?
Skirt? You're mistaking
my loincloth for a skirt.
I was keeping it out to dry.
There was a gush of wind..
..and it flew away. - Hey..
Dry your clothes inside.
If you have a problem
with my wet clothes..
..then I'll send them to your home.
Dry them, iron them and
send it back on a hangar.
Do you think we're washer-men?
What should we do with him?
Tear it. - Tear it?
Tear it.
No, no.
That was my honeymoon loincloth.
Scoundrels.
This city has troubled me a lot.
Oh, God.
It hit him. - He's gone today.
I won't spare him.
Why are you hiding inside now?
Come out. - I am not hiding.
I am searching for my gun.
I came here to murder two people.
If I have to kill four,
there's no problem.
Come back, Raj. He's hiding.
I am sparing you for
the sake of my friend.
Who are you trying to scare?
Come on, I'll deal
with both of you. Come on.
He's coming. He will do what he said.
Come down, we're here.
Deal with us.
Can't you find the gun?
- I've found my gun but..
Today is Tuesday.
And I don't commit
murders on a Tuesday.
You're fortunate.
You survived.
Let's go. Come on.
Firstly,
Zandu is in the city and now him.
Why are you worried?
It's a big city. How can he find us?
He'll wander around
for a few days and leave.
He isn't hovering around us, come on.
Why did you all come here?
- We had to.
You don't come meet
us or attend our calls.
I have so many things on my plate.
I don't even get time to breathe.
But you've got time to play.
Who are you talking to?
Mind your language.
- Don't shout at Marcos.
Marcos, you've been
working with us for years.
Why are you so impatient today?
Those diamonds are worth millions.
It can change anyone's intentions.
And it's been so long
since I gave you the diamonds.
Marcos, it's a big deal.
It's bound to take time. - Two days.
I give you only two days.
The third day.. will be your last.
This man can be a problem for you.
And you know I don't like problems.
Richard,
I need your casino at any cost.
Marcos, the Riveir is the most
expensive casino in all of Vegas.
You'll get your money in two days.
Two days.
Go, go. - Move, come on.
Boss, they are minister's men. Run.
Come on. Come on. Come on, fast.
- Come on. Come on, fast.
Seems like the movie has started, sir.
Listen to the sound quality, Naidu.
It seems like someone's
shooting outside.
Someone is really shooting.
But we don't have backup again, sir.
We don't need it.
Come on. Move fast. Naidu.
Sir, sir, sir, sir.
Naidu. Naidu.
Superman. Naidu.
Sir, bullets are being
fired from both sides, sir.
If I get hit I will die, sir.
Please cover me, sir.
If I cover you, who will cover me?
Sir, you're used to taking bullets.
There are already two bullets inside.
It won't make a difference
if you're hit by a few more, sir.
Come on, move. Move. Move. Move.
Help! Help!
Help!
Marcos.
Thank you. - Sir!
Sir.
Sir, any amount of
praise is less for you.
It seems like a lion is
holding its prey in its claws.
Yash, Arjun caught Marcos.
Strange.
Even I couldn't understand that.
Yes, sir. I am coming tomorrow.
And I am completely assured..
..that you'll take
care of me for good.
Thank you. Thank you.
"I won't leave you today.."
Excuse me, there's a power failure..
..and I can't see
anything in the dark.
My house is closeby.
Will you take me there?
I have an important work tomorrow.
I need to leave early.
Come. - Thank you.
By the way, what's the job..
..that's making you jump
with joy even before it's finished?
Two people are going to die tomorrow.
Two people are going to die. - Yes.
And you're celebrating.
- Why shouldn't I?
They were both rascals.
They came to my village
and robbed my bank.
It's him. It's him. - What?
I mean.. Uncle, how did you find out..
..that those two rascals
live in this city?
Those fools..
left their bag in my house.
You left the bag there? - Yes.
And tomorrow those
two will be in my clutches.
How is that?
- Their photographs were in the bag.
There were photographs
in the bag? - No
No, he's right. There weren't
any photographs in the bag.
I remember their faces clearly.
I've captured it in my eyes,
like a wounded snake does.
I thought of getting their
sketches made by an artist.
But Mr. Arjun advised me that..
- Who Mr. Arjun?
Police inspector Mr. Arjun.
He's a famous inspector.
He said, "Don't worry, don't worry."
"The police records
have the photographs.."
"..of all the criminals of the city."
Come home and I'll show it to you.
It must surely have my photograph.
Feels like I've come to my home.
That's the one.
You live in that house?
And that house which you see..
That's where those
two scoundrels live.
Come out!
You dare call my loincloth a skirt!
Tomorrow I am going
to see the inspector..
..and turn your pants
into a skirt. Yes.
Once I get hold of
those two scoundrels..
..then I'll deal with these two.
Thank you. Thank you.
Good night.
When he finds out we'll
have nowhere to run.
Madam, where should I
throw this bouquet? - Throw it?
Keep it here.
What's wrong, Naidu?
- My photo wasn't published.
Of course it will be published.
You do something brave as well.
What did sir do?
We fell on Marcos together.
Fell on him, what do you mean?
Marcos was lying unconscious.
Sir just kept his feet on
him and got his photos clicked.
I was there as well.
But he pushed me away.
Look.
That half-a-head you see is mine.
..did something brave..
Mr. Zandu Lal, you came to the
right place. Your job will be done.
Thank you.
"No problem."
Oh, God. - What happened?
As soon as I thought
of those two scoundrels..
..their images flashed before my eyes.
It seemed as if they
just walked past this way.
Which way? - This way. Behind you.
What's the point of stealing here?
That's how the inspector will
be degraded in front of Zandu Lal.
He's been rewarded handsomely
for capturing Marcos. - Yes.
The money is in this safe.
I admit it wasn't just difficult,
but impossible to catch Marcos.
The government has rewarded
me for my bravery..
Hello, Sister-in-law. Hello.
You're fortunate to have a husband
like him. - It was my duty, sir.
He isn't just your
husband but God. Look.
He's a brave man. A brave man. Look.
Sister-in-law. - Why you..
What's this?
From which angle does he look brave?
Brave. - No. No.
Run. Run. Hide.
We are done for.
Hide quickly, hide.
Not there. - Inside. Quickly.
Help! Help!
Open the door.
There's place here.
- Only for one, come on. - Okay.
"No problem."
What's going on outside?
Sister-in-law has been
graced by the 'Devi' (Goddess).
Which one?
Sridevi. - The Goddess of death.
Papa, quiet.
Bullets are speaking.
Seems like she's in this room.
Throw him out. - Who? Who?
You.
Help! Help!
"No problem."
How much more will you deceive me?
Kajal made sweet porridge and you..
Eat the porridge.
- It's hot. It's hot.
Eat it hot. - Eat it, Papa.
Eat it, Papa.
Otherwise we'll have to have it.
Eat it.
Eat some more.
Why are you eating like this?
And so hot. - She's fine now.
I'll feed you properly.
Ma'am.
There's been a robbery.
- What? Robbery?
Papa, there's been a robbery.
The reward for catching
Marcos is gone.
Inform the police.
- Police? - Yes, police.
You're a police inspector
and I am the commissioner.
We'll be defamed.
Brother, you need more help.
At least keep a dog that
barks on seeing the thieves..
..and not when they leave.
And keep some bodyguards too..
..who can protect you from your wife.
And stop publishing fake
photographs in the newspapers.
People get happy pointlessly.
Brave man.
You're not even half the man.
You aren't worthy of
being in the post office.
Whenever Kajal turns into
Kamini I have to face slander.
If I didn't love Kajal..
..I would've strangled her to death.
What's wrong? Why are you laughing?
Ms. Universe's photo
has been published.
Look.
They make just anyone.. Ms. Universe.
Somebody help!
These girls are committing suicide.
Come on, hurry up!
Oh, my God.
O God! Stop! Somebody stop them.
Somebody help!
I want to die.
Leave me. - Come out, come out.
No, I don't want to live.
- Why do you want to die?
Leave me. - Come out.
Shut up!
Why are all you girls
committing mass suicide?
Because of him.
All of us love him so much.
And today we found out
that he loves some Sanjana.
Sanjana? - Yes.
He says she's the most
beautiful girl in the world.
Look at me. What's missing in me?
I am Ms. Durban.
How did you become?
What?
I mean how did you get fooled?
What's so special about him?
- Take a closer look.
He's got everything.
My heart starts pounding
in his presence.
But if he loves Sanjana
then why hasn't he told her yet?
He will tell her. Do you
know about his ego, his arrogance?
He'd rather die than say 'I love you'.
Sanjana will have to say it.
Come on, round them up. - Come on.
Break it up, come on break it up.
Come on, take them inside.
Sir, I am not one of them.
I come from a decent home. - I see.
Where is your home?
'If this scoundrel
finds out the truth..'
'..then I'll have to spend
the entire night in prison.'
You're from a decent
family and you don't go home.
Tell me, would you prefer
the lock-up or my home?
Sir? - Don't worry,
my wife's visiting her parents.
Don't stare,
Naidu, you know I am a decent man.
But.. my girlfriend before Kajal..
..looked.. just like her.
Come, baby. Come.
Your girlfriend was manly.
Careful,
the wig might come off. - What?
I mean.. I might go out of breath.
Oh my.. that's the grace which..
wives lack.
Come.
My dear..
You have a beautiful
wife and a cute child.
Why do you men always do this?
Men are dogs. - Yes.
But I am helpless.
I haven't received my
wife's love for years. - What?
One day we were making love..
..and she had a fit.
Split personality.
I didn't realize
when she broke my head..
..when blood starting oozing out.
After that day, I couldn't muster
up the courage to go up to my wife.
Oh my.
You're really very sad.
Come on, come on. Come.
We'll see what happens.
What do you mean by
'we'll see what happens'?
I have AIDS.
AIDS.
Where are you going?
To switch off the lights?
- No, Sister.
To get a taxi for you?
Yes, yes, yes.
Surprise.
How did you come back home?
And Tuktuk? - What could I do?
I was getting bored without you.
But that Tuktuk..
She insisted on staying
with her grandpa.
So I left her there.
Anyway, I'll freshen up.
Don't go inside. - Why?
There's someone inside. - Who?
Sister. I mean she's my sister.
Sister? What do you mean?
Hey!
He's your sister?
I am his friend, Sister-in-law.
Actually he doesn't have a sister.
Once I tied him the
sacred thread of 'Rakhi'.
Since then he's been
calling me his sister.
Thanks for the clothes, Arjun.
Mine got slightly spoiled.
So nice to meet you.
I am leaving. - Nice meeting you.
I am your father, get that.
Okay. - Okay.
Bye. - Bye.
Hi, Raj. - Hi... - Hi.
Aren't you attending the wedding?
- Whose wedding?
Sanjana's.
Come on, we're getting late.
- Let's go, let's go.
Congrats, Sanjana. - Thank you.
Hi. - Hi.
- Sorry, for this. - It's okay.
You didn't invite me to your wedding.
It all happened so suddenly.
I forgot to invite so many friends.
Who is the lucky one?
He's your choice. Must be handsome.
No, he's okay.
You can consider it as a compromise.
Compromise? - Of course.
There's no one made for me.
But he has one quality.
He doesn't have an ego or arrogance.
All the time he just keeps saying,
"I love you, Sanjana."
Just because he says 'I
love you' you agreed to marry him?
No, he does. - Even I..
Yes, you were saying something.
It's too late.
We aren't married yet.
It can be cancelled as well.
What? - You don't know me.
I am very crazy.
And if I find someone better,
who loves me more then why not.
Sanjana, I..I also really love you.
Really. - Yes, I love you very much.
But how did you suddenly..
- Not suddenly.
Remember when we met the first time.
"Television, plasma. Indica, Ferrari."
That's when it happened.
I swear that I love you.
He said, "I love you."
Let me get married now.
She's getting married.
I asked her to get two gowns stitched.
I have to make someone say I love you.
Come on.
She really is crazy.
Papa, Raj is here.
Welcome, welcome, welcome. Come in.
Did you have to fall for the
commissioner's daughter? - Commissioner?
You petty thief, have you ever..
..seen anyone other than
the constable or inspector?
I am Yash. Raj's elder brother.
Yash Raj. - No, no, no.
We don't have any
connection with them.
We're Ambani's. - Ambani's.
No, no, we don't have any
connection with them either.
They're Indians and we're foreigners.
NRI's. - Oh, I see.
Sit down, sit down.
Papa, Raj was saying..
..that he'll buy Reliance
as soon as we get married.
Sit down, sir.
Hello, sir. - Hello!
"No problem."
You?
Ram Lal, you didn't
come see me this month.
I haven't received my salary yet.
You know my servant.
Actually my younger
brother does social work.
He has sympathy for poor people.
Like servants, maids, cooks, driver.
He's the support system of the poor.
He takes away their money.
To make a fixed deposit.
I can't believe it.
Do you have poison?
Will cyanide do? - It will do fine.
Let's mix it in Raj's
milkshake and give it to him.
Grandpa.
Sister and brother-in-law
are here as well.
"No Problem. No Problem."
Yash. Arjun.
Only God can save you now.
Where did he go?
My brother is very religious.
When he sees a temple..
Yash, you? - Sir.
You know him.
Kajal, he's a big social
worker of the city.
Greetings. - You were saying
that your brother is a social worker.
He too, sir.
He's a smaller one,
and I am slightly bigger.
Save me from this rascal today, God.
Yash, you never told me
that you have a younger brother.
You never asked me, sir.
Sir. - I swear on Sanjana,
I will stop everything from today.
Stealing, blackmailing..
You're getting the most
beautiful girl in the world..
..what else are you asking God for?
You! Scoundrel, rascal, how dare you!
'Oh my.. that's the grace which..
wives lack.'
I have the entire clip.
You carry out raids
and take cheap woman home.
Sanjana! - Quiet!
If you say anything
else I will beat you.
You never come to see your friend.
And he's here to ask for
my sister-in-law's hand in marriage.
And without telling me.
Kajal, did you recognize him?
- I know.
Of course she'll recognize me.
- How are you, Sister-in-law?
Hi. My God.
That's surprising.
Everyone knows each other.
I know him too.
There's another one coming for you.
This is special for Raj.
Raj, this is for you especially.
You forgot, didn't you, Ram Lal?
It's Sunday today.
It's my day of fasting.
'Scoundrel, curse you.'
Sit down, sit down. Please sit down.
'If this scoundrel becomes
a part of this family..'
'..he'll ruin everyone.'
The commissioner doesn't
see anyone without an appointment.
Okay, will you do me a favor?
Will you deliver these
two photographs to him?
These two are inside. - Yes.
And sir's younger daughter
is getting married to him.
So, is this final?
- No problem from my side.
Just Kajal and Arjun..
What do you say, Arjun?
I..I was thinking, Father..
Thank God, it didn't break.
Whatever is inside is safe. Safe.
You were thinking about something.
- What's there to think?
We often lose good boys if we think.
Like you.
That's means this alliance
has been finalized.
Let's have sweets.
Have sweets. - These are fritters.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Have sweets. Have sweets.
No Problem, No Problem,
What?
What are you staring at?
What did you think?
You will run away from the
village and come to the city..
..and I won't find you two.
You.. - Me. I am..
Uncle. Uncle. - Uncle.
Uncle, we love you. - Nephew. Nephew.
What did you think?
Uncle must be dead.
You two came here to
talk about your alliance.
You didn't even tell me.
- We made a mistake, uncle
Mistake, mistake. - It hurts.
Uncle, aren't you the one..
..whose bank was robbed
by two scoundrels? - Yes, yes.
Did you find them? - I found them.
The money? - I'll get that as well.
It's fine if they give it peacefully.
Otherwise, I've got the
police department with me.
We'll hang them upside
down and beat them.
Heard that. Heard that.
Uncle, let's not talk about this.
Meet your daughter-in-law.
Hello, Uncle. - Bless you, dear.
When have you scheduled
the engagement for?
Tomorrow is Sanjana's birthday.
With your permission tomorrow..
Fine, fine, fine. I accept.
You exist. You exist.
I had lost faith in You.
But He's there. - Yes, He's there..
Sometimes human beings
go crazy with happiness.
Also with sorrow.
Even I did.
First tell me.. where is my money?
We spent it.
You spent it.
All of it?
Actually,
Uncle, we robbed only one bank.
If we had robbed two or four banks..
..we would've spent that as well.
We're big spenders .
How will he get engaged?
Uncle, don't drag
my engagement into this.
You're already in this
and so is your engagement.
Raj, there's just one
way to stop his laughter.
No. No, I won't steal.
He won't steal..
Where are you going?
Stay here and talk to me.
Yash, I just swore on Sanjana inside..
..that I won't do anything
wrong again after today.
After today. - Yes.
This day won't end
until 12 o'clock midnight.
We'll finish the job by 11 o'clock.
Listen.
I have a foolproof plan..
..of stealing at the minister's house.
Uncle. - Yes.
You go home and we'll get the money.
Home?
You don't know my home.
I don't know your home.
Uncle.. - Don't try to fool me.
Go fool someone else.
Until I get my money..
..I am going to tail
you two like your shadow.
Understand.
Think that I am your boss now.
And you'll do as I say. Get that?
Okay, boss. - Okay.
See that.
Criminal Marcos commits
suicide in jail. Funny.
For the last time I'm asking you,
where are the diamonds?
Or else this will be
tomorrow's breaking news.
How's that?
You'll be finished.
Funny.
Don't to go, Don't to go.
Take us out now. Quick.
Stop them! He's Marcos!
You said there are just two dogs.
Where did the third one come from?
The third one must be new. Come on.
We climbed up a 40-feet
wall and the gate is open.
Look. Is that the guard?
He's sleeping. - If he's sleeping,
go wake him up. Go.
Your saviours are dead.
Marcos.
Please.
The minister has a bank
right here in his house.
Yash, I suggest that
you take only what we need.
Here, go and count it.
- We won't count.
Did you count while robbing the bank?
I am the manager,
I know this was the amount. Take it.
Where are the diamonds?
Upstairs, in the safe.
Give it.
Give it. - Look, boss.
You'll have to take
the evening flight..
..to your village,
instead of the morning train. - Why?
Tomorrow's my engagement.
What will people say?
"Where is uncle?"
Then I'll have to attend
your wedding as well.
There's time for the wedding.
We'll say that uncle is dead.
Seems like someone's coming.
- If someone's coming then let's run.
Come on. - Bring him.
Marcos.
Marcos, there's been
a robbery. - What?
Marcos, there's been a robbery.
Someone took my money
along with the diamonds?
I know you'll make excuses.
I've committed mass
bloodshed for these diamonds.
And now you say, "Marcos,
my belongings have been stolen.."
"..along with the diamonds."
Do we.. look like idiots?
I want my diamonds.
I want my diamonds. - Marcos.
I want it!
Stop him. - I want it!
Marcos, stop.
What are you doing? - I want it.
He'll die. - I want it.
If he dies, we won't get the diamonds.
We won't get the diamonds.
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry, old man.
Sorry. DC. Give him a jolt.
Come here, Minister. - No.
Get up.
Boss, he's dead.
He's dead. Boss..
Boss, you told me so.
I told you to give him a jolt..
..I could've killed him too, fool.
Boss. Boss.
You can't die.
We're ruined.
It was a mistake, boss.
Why are you crying like that?
Was he your father? - No.
Did he have to die today?
Police officials have a personal
life as well. - Definitely, sir.
Sanjana is getting engaged.
There's so much to do and..
he's lying here.
Tell me,
did you find the murder weapon..
The wire they used to electrocute him?
No, sir. The murderer
didn't leave behind any clue.
Naidu. Criminals first
leave evidence behind..
..and then commit the crime.
You only need the eyes to see it.
Sir.
Sir. Sir.
What, sir?
Did you think that I fell? - Yes.
I intentionally went inside.
To take this.
Whoever opened this safe..
..his picture must be in this.
Get it developed and
meet me there directly.
Yes, sir.
"Ladies and gentlemen. Boys and girls,
please get on to the dance floor."
"Are you ready to dance?"
"Shake your hips and move your body."
"DJ, you rock the house."
"It's hard to control
when you start dancing."
"The drummer beats
the drum just for you."
"Your grace is famous
all the way till Canada."
"You twist better than Shakira."
"We don't care about a damn thing."
"Let your hips shake,
keep on dancing."
"Keep dancing more."
"Please, take me to the dance floor."
"Come on, dance."
"Don't control yourself
in this moment of happiness."
"Drink country or English."
"Pour me some from
your intoxicating eyes."
"Two hearts have united."
"All the rituals have been completed."
"Just dance the way you like."
"Move your feet and shake the ground."
"You twist better than Shakira."
"I'll dance, even you dance."
"The whole world is dancing,
seeing me dance."
"Like I do, even you can do."
"Let those hips swing."
"Your earrings glitter,
your face glows."
"The moon praises your beauty."
"Your beauty has stolen
my peace and my sleep."
"You're the only one for me."
"Your eyes have ravaged my heart."
"You twist better than Shakira."
"Come on, dance."
Naidu.
Sir.
"Come on, dance."
"Dance, shake your hips."
"Dance, come on."
Yash, why are the
police coming towards us?
You're going to be the
commissioner's son-in-law.
So the police are bound
to congratulate you.
Come on, dance.
"Dance, shake your hips."
"Dance, come on."
What's this joke, Mr. Arjun?
What have we done?
Minister Sanyal's murder.
Murder? - What? - Murder?
Mr. Arjun,
we didn't commit any murder.
We only went there to steal.
What nonsense are you speaking?
They're accusing us of murder..
..that's why I am
telling them the truth.
Shut up. Shut up, please.
He's gone crazy with happiness. - Yes.
Mr. Arjun,
you know what a decent man I am.
Decent? This is your decency.
Take these glasses off.
Let me see your real face.
Boss.
Uncle? So you're their boss.
No, I am neither their
uncle nor their boss.
I am total loss, sir.
My wife, children, and the
entire village is waiting for me.
And it's time for my flight as well.
Sir, please let me go.
I haven't done anything.
Look, sir. Take a look yourself.
We only committed
a robbery and not murder.
Mr. Arjun, you've known me for years.
I am a petty thief,
I blackmail people. Remember.
Remember, sir.
Tell that to the court and not here.
Take them away. - Yes, sir.
Sister, look what
brother-in-law has done.
You knew that..
he was a thief, a blackmailer..
..but still you..
- Papa, I say let's forget the past.
And think that I took the
right action at the right time..
..and saved Sanjana's life.
You ruined it as well, rascal.
Wait! Take me along.
Take me along.
Until yesterday I
had only robbed a bank.
And today I've also
committed a murder.
A minister's murder.
Boss, you're confessing
in front of the police.
Did you commit the murder?
- I didn't rob the bank either.
But I've been accused of it.
Scoundrels.
I'm stuck in this because of you.
You two got me stuck in this.
It's your bank which he
robbed and I got stuck in it.
I was getting engaged,
but instead I got arrested.
You're putting the entire blame on me.
You wanted that crazy girl.
You wanted the money.
And I am stuck in all this,
trying to save you two.
I know that we three are stuck.
But I don't understand..
..who's responsible for it after all?
Why did it stop?
There's a shooting going on.
- Here, have sweets. Here.
That rascal blackmailer
has been arrested.
And his friend.
The decent one who wore spectacles.
He turned out to be a bigger conman.
Murderer. They'll be hanged. Hanged.
Brother, have sweets.
Here. Don't be shy. Have it.
You're distributing sweets.
He'll ruin your life
before getting hanged.
No, no, please.
I've thought of a scene for your film.
Come and meet us
at the police station.
What's wrong, sir?
Why are you so angry?
Those three ruined me.
The entire family is
asking me weird questions.
What answers should I give them?
Bring them to the torture room.
- Yes, sir.
Is there a shooting. - Yes, sir.
Actually,
sir, the director of this film..
..was looking for
an honest police officer.
And I said our sir would
be absolutely perfect for this role.
Would you like to work in films?
Of course I would.
- Do you have the passion?
Who doesn't? - Can you act?
It's the hero's role, sir.
What does he have to do after all?
Explain to him the
scene that I told you.
Is the lighting ready, Bhaskar?
Sir, there are three
inmates locked up here..
..and they've been
charged with murder.
But you know they're innocent.
You let those three flee from here.
It's a nice scene. - Nice, isn't it?
But who are these
three innocent inmates?
It's them, sir.
Them. Thief, blackmailer, murderer.
They're innocent.
They.. they wouldn't be
innocent even in their childhood.
But they are in the film.
In films what happens
doesn't happen actually..
..and what doesn't
happen is what happens.
They're culprits,
but in your view they're innocent.
You hate them but you
also have to love them.
This is a test of your acting.
Can you do it?
No, he can't do it. - No way.
He'll fail.
- He'll fail. - He'll fail.
Call Salman. - Music.
"Mr. Cool. He's the dude."
"We're cool. We're dudes."
"We've got a carefree mood."
"We're known for
all the wrong reasons."
"We're nice, we're honest."
"We're one in a million."
"Stealing isn't our business."
"Why have you caught us?"
"Did we ask anyone.. for rent?"
"We've been framed."
"We've been arrested
just by accident."
"But believe us..
believe us we're innocent."
"Take a good look at us,
we're innocent."
"But believe us..
believe us we're innocent."
"We're honest, we're innocent."
"We never did anything wrong."
"We never swindled anyone."
"You're heroes and
don't look like villains."
"Listen carefully..
there's no case against you here."
"Why did you beat us?"
"Why did you thrash us?
Why did you hurt us?"
"Your truncheons"
"But believe us..
believe us we're innocent."
"Take a good look at us,
we're innocent."
"He's go the moves."
"He's so cool."
"We like that."
"He's go the moves."
"He's so cool."
"We like that. - Come on, now!"
"Hey, release us
from these handcuffs."
"Speak respectfully with the jailor."
"Sir, you're the pride of India here."
"Hey buddy, I am your only hope here."
"You're our support.
You're our only kin."
"Don't be arrogant."
"We'll lose our homes.
Your guns will torment us forever."
"I know now.. I know you're innocent."
"Now I know for sure
that you're innocent."
"I know now.. I know you're innocent."
"Now this is my order
that you're innocent."
Mr. Director, say cut.
Sir, the director
fled with the artists.
Yes, sir. - Ran away?
Thank you, Mr. OP.
Thank you very much.
You've done us a favor.
I'll give you back all your tapes.
First give me back my family.
- What family?
Yes. Your men kidnapped
them in order to save you.
Who? - Our men?
Welcome. - Marcos.
Hi, babies. - Hello, boys.
Khokha.
Once.. in a blue moon.
Your family will reach home safely.
You go.
Poor babies.
Good shot.
Where are the diamonds? - Diamonds.
What's this new problem
of the diamonds? - Which diamonds?
The same diamonds you stole
from the minister's safe..
..before we could get them.
Sir, there's a confusion.
We committed the theft.
But we didn't steal any diamonds.
The minister said that
the diamonds were in the safe.
And these scoundrels
say there were no diamonds.
Can I say something, Mr.
Marcos? - Yes.
You're their boss, speak.
There's no driver of the bus.
You can all ask questions,
but let someone drive. Please.
The diamonds were worth millions..
..and we stole them
with great difficulty.
And you got it very easily.
So naturally you won't tell us easily.
That's true.
If the diamonds are worth
millions then no one will say it.
Marcos, the bus is heading
towards the ravines.
Marcos.
Dumbo. - Yes, boss. - Dumbo.
I'll tell you, quickly. - Yes.
Dumbo. Stop it.
Darling. Where are you?
She's getting a completely
different type of a fit today.
This is the third attack.
And what about the attack on me?
The criminals ran away
and you didn't even realize.
I realized. I realized.
I could've caught them as well.
But the director didn't say cut.
What could I have done? Ruin the shot.
What was the need to be a hero?
Kajal, I say let's forget the past.
Run. Run.
No. I am your daddy. Arjun's there.
No. No.
Kamini..
Father-in-law, you are here?
She's here.
Father-in-law, run.. Run.
Outside, in the water. Under water.
Jump.
Arjun.
Do something? - Why?
You've defamed me in
the entire police department..
..by fixing that murderer's
alliance with my daughter.
I say let's forget the past, Papa.
Forget it, now.
Arjun. - Arjun's dead.
I never waited for
the train at the station.
But today I am waiting for
the train lying on the tracks.
My wife. My children.
He's here.
Our savior is here.
Come on. Come.
Come.
Excuse me, what are you doing?
I am dying. Don't you see?
I am committing suicide.
What fate!
Our savior is committing
suicide himself.
Brother, you can go ahead and die.
But first save us. - Why you..
Do You see?
Is this world worth living in?
People like these..
Why should I stay alive?
Everyone wants to live.
But no one's asking the
dying person why he wants to die.
We were going to ask after
you'd have saved us, sir.
No, no, we'll ask first.
Brother, why are you trying to die?
My entire family was killed
by a bomb in Afghanistan.
Lord. - Parents, wife, young children.
They hurled a bomb and..
I have their photograph. - No, no.
We believe you. We believe you.
But.. we didn't kill them.
But you didn't save them either.
Then why do you want to stay alive?
And what will you do by staying alive?
Even if you survive today..
..tomorrow you'll
be killed by a bullet.
Or blown up by a bomb day after.
So it's better that
you die peacefully today.
Right, right.
- That's correct. - It's a nice deal.
Goodbye. - What now?
If it's a slow train,
we'll be minced slowly.
And if it's a fast train..
then we'll become mincemeat.
Come on. Come on.
No, no!
No. - Come on.
Release us. - Release us.
He wants to die. - No!
Which track are you running it on?
I haven't done anything.. - Stop the..
You saved me again.
You know if I come up there,
I'll ask many questions.
What the hell are you doing?
That's fate.
Who wants to die and who's dying.
Reverse. Reverse. Reverse.
Stop the train.
Diamonds.
You doubt me? - Who else?
You took the money out of the safe.
I gave the bag to boss.
Right in front of you.
Don't raise your hand on me.
Thieves.
Do you think I'm like you two?
I am an honest man.
I swear on you,
I don't have the diamonds.
And I swear on my wife and children.
Then where are the diamonds?
Marcos doesn't have them.
You guys have them.
If I don't have them,
then where have the diamonds gone?
Can I.. say something? - Say it.
Please don't get angry. - Say it.
We swore, so you swear too.
Boss, I don't have
any relation with you..
..but you're a nice man.
And he's..
he's always been close to me.
My friend, my brother, my life.
I swear on you two,
I don't have the diamonds.
"You're a villain and not a hero."
"Arjun, you're a pain in the neck."
Arjun, you've made the case worse.
What is this?
Earlier she'd have only
one fit in a day for 10 minutes.
And now she gets
three-four fits a day..
..which lasts two-three hours.
You broke her sister's engagement.
Tarnished her father's honor.
Got your daughter
dropped out of school.
Let's forget the past, Doctor.
Now tell me how will she get better?
She won't get better now.
It's impossible for
her to get better now.
No, no, Doctor.
At least get her back
to her earlier condition.
Where she had one fit in
a day for 10 minutes. - Yes, Doctor.
We're used to it now.
Give her shock treatment.
Do something she
doesn't expect at all.
Give her happiness. Happiness.
You broke her sister's engagement,
didn't you?
Now you get her sister married.
But with whom? - With any cat or dog.
I mean with anyone.
Anyone. The D.I.
G's son is not too bad. Rahul.
He also likes Sanjana.
But will Sanjana agree? - Papa.
People who're betrayed
in love commit murders..
..suicide,
so marriage is not difficult.
We'll convince her.
You just prepare for the wedding.
Arjun.
No.
I won't let this happen.
- And I won't let you go.
Look, Yash has gone out to get food.
Let him come back,
then we can think of something.
I don't have time to think. Let me go.
I won't let you go.
The police are there.
They'll kill you.
What will I do without Sanjana?
I won't let her marry anyone else
as long as I am alive. - Raj! Raj!
He's gone out to get food,
wonder when he'll return.
And he's gone to get
shot and won't return again.
Raj. Raj.
No, no, don't cry.
You're looking so nice.
The makeup will get spoilt.
That's why I am crying inside.
Forget that deceiver.
In spite of whoever he
was he was still my first love.
I see him all the time.
Oh, God. - What happened?
Even now I can imagine
him walking up to me.
Yeah, right.
You're not imagining, it's him.
How dare he!
Mr. D.I.G. He's the boy.
You're getting married.
How else should I punish you?
I accept any punishment
but not this one.
Come with me or else..
- Or else? - Or else what will you do?
Or else what, son?
- Why are you silent? Say it.
What will you do?
I will shoot.
You will shoot. Shoot
How could you think
that I'd shoot at you?
Raj. You can't do that.
You know how crazy I am.
Don't worry. Don't worry.
I don't keep my gun
loaded because of someone.
Hey, boys, arrest him.
Great.
Papa, what happened?
- Not here, but there.
But my revolver is never empty.
If anyone tries to move,
I will kill the groom first.
And then the guests one by one.
I think you don't
know what you are doing.
We've done so many things
without telling anyone.
I didn't become a
boss by doing nothing.
What is this bag?
It was lying upstairs
so I picked it up.
I'll have to give
daughter-in-law some gift.
I have another plan.
Do you? - Yes. - Try it.
You've taken the D.I. G's son hostage.
- D.I. G?
Do you know what
can be the consequences?
You told me that they're
getting Sanjana married..
..to some laundryman's son.
- Yes.
Mr. D.I. G's surname is
'Dhobi' (Laundryman).
No Problem,
What else will you make me do,
scoundrels?
Father, I've switched off the lights.
They can't see us now.
Catch them. Catch them.
Sorry. - Hey! Relax.
Situation under control.
Calm down, relax.
Daddy, where is Sanjana?
Where is Sanjana?
- Where have they gone?
I think they fled.
No Problem, No Problem,
No Problem,
Petrol. Petrol.
Not on the face. Not on the face.
Pour it anywhere but the face.
- Not on the face.
Not on the face.
There's still time.
Look. Here's the minister's
murder recording. Look.
Take the evidence of your
innocence and give us the diamonds.
How many times do I tell
you we don't have the diamonds?
But I have an idea.
Give us this tape so that
we can prove ourselves innocent.
And then we can search
for the diamonds together.
We're dealing with scoundrels.
They won't listen like this.
Hey. - Dumbo, massage him properly.
Why me?
You get a lot of ideas.
The petrol will go to your
brain and burn all your ideas.
What are you staring at?
Look, this isn't drenched.
Pour it here.
We'll be fine, boss.
Until we have the diamonds.
But we don't have the diamonds. - Yes.
Till they think that we have
the diamonds they can't kill us.
Right. Right. We won't kill you.
We will only set you ablaze.
We'll set you ablaze
and she'll douse it.
again and she'll douse it.
Boss, I've got a suggestion.
Why doesn't she set
us ablaze and you douse us?
She'll set us ablaze
again and you douse us.
What difference will that make?
You won't get burnt?
Of course I will.
But it won't have that
smouldering sensation.
What does it mean? What does it mean?
Is it necessary for
everything to have a meaning?
But what does it mean?
- Just a minute.
It won't have that
smouldering sensation.
It won't have..
Boss. - What are you repeating for?
Set him ablaze. I'll do it.
Douse this fire! - Water.
What are you doing?
Douse this fire! Water.
What the hell! - I am burning!
I'll help you. God, I am also on fire.
Pour water.
God, I am also on fire.
I can't turn it on.
I am on fire.
Help! Help!
Come on.
Come after me.
Scoundrels, we won't spare you.
Hello, the one wearing the coat.
Hey, man with the cap.
Our boss is a don.
Come on. - Keep swimming.
Come on, swim.
Boss, we're safe.
Why are you crying if we are safe?
There's a hole in the boat.
Hey you, do you want to die?
What should I stay alive for, madam?
Couldn't you tell us that
there's a hole in the boat?
We could've gone to another boat.
He's crazy, plug the hole.
Plug the hole. - Yes, I am crazy.
My entire family was killed in Iraq,
where were you?
But what's our fault?
The entire world knows
whose mistake it is.
But you're clinging on to him.
Did you ask him why he's
killing people? Now you all die.
Scoundrel, we won't die yet.
Why you.. - Fool,
what's that heading towards us?
Sign on these papers.
What? What should I do?
Sign on these papers, son.
You didn't have to
make papers, Father.
Could we achieve anything
by shouting till date?
And also, my health is not well.
What was the need to
prepare the documents, father?
Anyway, after you I
am going to own everything.
The house, property.. Right, Kajal?
These isn't my will.
I am talking about
your divorce with Kajal.
How could you say something
I can never even imagine?
If you're the commissioner
then I am an inspector. Senior.
And nobody in this world
can make me sign against my will.
Sign it!
You don't keep a loaded gun..
..and consider yourself
to be a big hunter.
Kajal. - You can't even
hit one bird with two stones..
..and you try to hit
two birds with one stone.
Grandpa. Mummy is getting
a new kind of fit. - Yes, dear.
Sign it. - Kajal, Kajal.
What Kajal?
That criminal abducted
Kajal's sister..
..and you just watched. - I.. I.. I..
Sign it. - I'll do it.. I'll do it.
Mistake. It's burnt my mistake.
Arjun! No Problem,
Kamini. Kamini.
I say let's forget the past.
Past. Past.
You like covering up the past,
don't you?
No. No. - Here.
Grandpa, please save my father.
- Let him die.
He's a pain in the neck. - Grandpa.
Yash. These innocent people
got involved unnecessarily.
She's innocent.
Isn't he innocent as well?
He hasn't harmed anyone.
He just took us home once..
..and then lost his house and family.
Just think about his family's
condition without him.
Raj, let's make a promise.
If he's killed in an encounter..
..then we'll raise
his children. - Done.
And what about the wife?
- She'll get married again.
She's smart. - Quiet, you scoundrels.
Quiet. - What happened, Uncle?
- Did you hear?
They're saying that they'll
kill me in an encounter..
..and get my wife remarried
and will take care of my children.
Rascals. I curse you.
You think I'll die
and you two will survive?
Is it?
Who was it?
- Billa. Murderer. - Billa.
They're still after us.
There's someone upstairs. Come on.
What will we do? - What are
we going to do? - Wait, let me think.
Hey, you..
Who's there?
- Should I throw a hand grenade?
No, no. We've laid mines. - Mines.
Whoever steps on it will get blown up.
Sofia, careful.
Oh, God. This scud
missile is really amazing.
Should I blow up
that tank and test it?
No, We've sold one diamond
and bought these arms to kill Marcos.
You did the right thing.
Otherwise Marcos
wouldn't have spared us.
He's a dangerous man.
What dangerous?
He's a big balloon.
He lays us on the tracks
and the train comes after him.
He pours petrol on
us and gets burnt himself.
That's because of his four foolish
accomplices. - We are insulted.
And the fifth one? - She's a queen.
I've seen love in
her eyes for me. - Yes.
On the yacht, she was
making gestures at me secretly.
Then she's sister-in-law. - No.
Come on, pick up the weapons.
Be careful with the bazooka.
And listen don't forget
that we've laid the mines.
Boss, they left.
But how will we get out?
Marcos.
Run. - Follow them, come on. Move it.
Wow, lovely.
Let's go inside. Inside.
All arrangements done. - Yes, sir.
Why is there such a big reward on me?
Because you're the boss. - Boss.
This.. is a police station, Raj.
This.. is a police station, come on.
Greetings. - Wow!
What a lucky police station this is?
The opening's tomorrow..
..and the criminals
have arrived today.
Where are the rest? - Right here.
They ran away.
But I didn't run. But I didn't run.
You're tired as well.
Yes, I am tired. But I didn't run.
I didn't run.
And why should I run, sir?
When I haven't done anything
then why should I run?
I am innocent, sir.
We'll find out how innocent you are..
..as soon as we reach
the headquarters.
How is that, sir?
We've got a machine, a lie detector.
And it can detect lies and the truth.
You have such a machine? - Yes.
Sir, why didn't you say that earlier?
Sir, I kept running and running.
Sir, take me to that
machine right now. Come, sir.
This machine isn't working.
It's stating wrong as
right and right as wrong.
Repair it quickly.
Or else some honest man
will get beaten up by our boss.
Sir.
So, this is the machine.
- Sit down.
Sir, this..
- No disturbance during interrogation.
But, sir, this.. - Shut up.
Or else I'll make you sit here.
- Sit down, sit down.
Sir is getting disturbed. Sit down.
Hello, hello.
What is your name? - Zandu Lal.
Wrong. Wrong. Wrong.
Who is the boss?
- Boss, I.. - Right, right, right.
Good. And how long have
you been running this gang?
Gang?
I run a bank.
Wrong. Wrong.
Are you a man or a woman?
I..
I am a woman.
- Right. Right. Right.
I had my doubt.
But your machine is working properly.
You're being tested
and not the machine.
How many women are you having
an affair with other than your wife?
Other than my wife..
Other than my wife I
have an affair with all women.
Right. Right.
That means sorrow in the
house and merriment outside.
What is this, sir? - Sugarcane.
Silent assassin. - Silent assassin.
It leaves no mark behind
but causes a lot of pain.
If you..
Hello. Hello, Kajal darling.
What?
Tuktuk is missing.
It's been two hours.
She's nowhere to be found.
Kajal.. Kajal, don't worry.
Why are you laughing?
- An underworld boss..
..who murdered the minister..
..robbed a bank,
you think you can beat him up..
..on grounds of right and wrong.
And your children
can roam around freely.
What do you mean?
I mean.. my children
have kidnapped your child.
Right.
Look, boss.
I say let's forget the past. - I see.
I just say that.
Don't harm my child, please.
Your child will be absolutely safe.
You've released me
and also given me a car.
I will call my gang members..
..and inform them to
take your child back home.
This boss is just..
- Why did you disconnect it.
He'll be safe in the police station.
I told them.
- But, sir, you didn't say anything.
I am the boss, I talk in codes.
"I love my heart.."
Hello, Kajal.
Don't worry, Kajal.
Tuktuk will come home soon.
What? She's at home.
She's at home. - Really? - Yes, Naidu.
Kaja, I..
Zandu Lal.
You fooled me?
Hey, I'll not spare him!
Move aside.
Papa. Papa, are you fine?
Why are you yelling at me?
You should look where you're going.
You should look where
you were going, sir.
It's your mistake. Yes, sir.
Let's forget the past,
call the ambulance, Naidu.
Ambulance.
Raj. Raj. Raj.
Sanjana.
Boss.
Tell me something.
Is your incoming free in your mobile?
Yes. - It is, isn't it?
Then why did you disconnect my call?
I would've been charged for the call.
Why did you disconnect my call?
- Uncle, don't hit Raj..
Quiet. I will slap you. Quiet.
Scoundrels. - Boss.
- You handed the diamond to me..
Don't hit us, boss.
You didn't think
what would happen to me.
"No problem."
What is this?
- It's a diamond. Diamond.
I can see that, fool.
But what are you doing with it?
I had them.
Didn't I tell you the other day?
That's how we brought
the fake weapons.
And what about when you swore on us?
Are you two dead?
Boss, please release me. I
want to say something as well, please.
Release him. - Release me, please.
Hey!
Boss, the sugarcane. - No.
Boss, no. - Boss, me too.
How many pieces should
I break one sugarcane into?
Daughter-in-law, you can't hit me.
I am your brother-in-law.
- You're her brother-in-law.
What if she had suffered
burns the other day? - Answer him.
We've got the diamonds.
We could've gotten
plastic surgery done.
What if your father-in-law
had lost his arms and legs..
..because of the train?
Boss, we have the diamonds.
We could've gotten new ones.
How many more diamonds do you have?
That's all that I have. - He's lying.
He's a liar. - Boss.
Let's take his clothes
off and search him.
No, no, no,
not in front of daughter-in-law.
Daughter-in-law, turn around.
Turn around.
Let's take his clothes off.
- Boss. Boss.
I will strip him. - No, boss.
Raj, what are you doing!
Raj, leave me.
With these diamonds I
can open up hundreds of banks.
I can bribe the judge,
police and the minister.
A few diamonds will be enough.
Only one diamond will be enough, Boss.
I've done all the calculations.
Come here, let me explain to you.
Come here.
Boss, it's not more valuable than
my love and your wife and children.
You want to go back to your village,
don't you? - Yes.
Fine, then let's give them to Marcos..
..and take the evidence of
our innocence. - Of course, of course.
It's better to bribe everyone, boss.
Otherwise he'll take the diamonds..
..kill everyone and won't
even handover the evidence.
Be quiet. - Shut up. - Keep
your mouth shut. - Listen to me, boss
Boss. Boss.
Listen to me. Be quiet. - Be quiet.
Yash was right.
We can't trust Marcos.
Then what should we do?
We can't approach the police.
They'll shoot us at sight.
We can get the police's help.
There's one way.
Do you want anything else, dear?
Mother never buys me balloons.
Uncle will buy it for you.
Why uncle? - Buy a little extra.
As a child,
you would argue with daddy..
..to fulfil every small wish of mine.
And today when it's
the question of my life..
..can't you convince daddy?
Here's your candy.
- And here's your balloon.
If we can impress the child..
..the mother will be
automatically impressed.
Sister Sanjana. Sister Sanjana.
Tuktuk.
Save me! - What did you do?
ou asked me to buy extra balloons.
But so many that the child flew away!
Mummy, save me. - God.
Someone save me.
"No problem."
Mummy. Mummy, save.
Give me.. - Mummy.
You're trying to kill my child.
I am saving her, I'm not killing her.
- Okay. - Blue.
Yellow.
Red. Red.
Your aim is good.
- I just realized that.
Mummy. Mummy.
Thank God.
You know how scared mother was.
Who gave you the balloons?
She was playing with us?
Tell me,
dear, who gave you the balloons?
I think the child can't
speak because of the shock. - Yes.
I think it's not right
to question her right now.
Thank you, Raj.
If it hadn't been for you..
..then I wonder where my
child would've been flying today.
You two saved my child that's
why I'm ready to forget the past.
But who knocked daddy down?
Some enemy.
We haven't found that car driver yet.
But your brother-in-law and the
police are still searching for them.
You know,
Sanju, they tried to kill him..
Isn't it enough that he survived?
He's more shocked than hurt,
that's all.
Daddy wants to say something.
But he can't speak.
Then let him write it.
He isn't dying that we'll
make him write his will.
Sister, why is he pointing
towards brother-in-law?
He's asking me to help these two.
Oh, he'll help us.
Sister, give him a strong
dose of 500 cc and let him rest.
Yes, sir.
Daddy. Daddy, please cooperate.
Daddy, take the injection.
Now here's my plan.
There's a transmitter in this pen.
This time I will kill
three birds with one stone.
You won't have to give the diamonds.
I will get the evidence
of your innocence from Marcos..
..and then arrest him
Mike testing. One, two, three.
Inspector, are you ready?
Yes. Yes.
Don't worry. Don't worry, boys.
'Operation three birds' is ready.
Calm down. Calm down.
Welcome, babies.
Just you two?
Where is the third one? The tall one?
I am asking because he's dangerous.
Something could be fishy.
No, no, this isn't any plan.
- Diamonds.
Evidence.
Yes, the evidence.
We need evidence to prove
that you murdered the minister.
Come on, let's go.
Come on. Everybody down.
Sir, sir. The dog's going that way.
Am I the officer or is the dog?
Sir, you are. - Then follow me.
That's fine.
Thank you very much.
Wait.
Where are the rest of the diamonds?
Rest of them? What? - Diamonds.
That's all. - They're not.
This is just half. - Cut.
We're trapped.
Don't worry, don't worry, I am coming.
We're almost there.
Hello, hello.
There's a microphone.
Sir, there's no one here, sir.
Naidu, look they're so stupid.
They went inside the wrong building.
We're in the wrong building, sir.
We should've followed
the dog and not you.
O God! Where have
you brought us, Sanju?
Is this a place to meet someone?
I should've never listened to..
Daughter-in-law, you?
- To hell with daughter-in-law.
It's all your fault.
Raj and uncle haven't returned
after meeting Marcos yet.
Arjun hasn't returned either.
- I see, Arjun went along as well.
If it didn't concern you, Sanju..
..then I wouldn't have sent
him on this dangerous mission.
Don't worry,
they'll be absolutely fine, okay.
Why haven't they called yet?
Hello. - You rascal,
scoundrel, cheater.
It's them. - Speaker. Speaker.
You're bound to get
stuck if you take only half.
Couldn't you tell us
that we're taking only half?
You gagged my mouth.
You didn't let me speak.
- Tell me something..
..where did you hide
the rest of the diamonds?
Daughter-in-law and
sister are right here.
Let it stay hidden.
Just do as I say.
Bring the diamonds here or
else they won't spare me and boss.
Did they kill Arjun?
He got us into this.
He sent us ahead and he
went inside the other building.
He hasn't got here.
He must be hiding
somewhere out of shame.
The coward. Sister! - What?
Sister! - What happened?
Please stay fine. - I am fine.
Stay fine. Stay fine.
Hello. - Yes, go ahead.
Hello, Yash.
What's wrong with your voice, boss?
Not boss, consider that
it's your father speaking.
I am in trouble, son.
These people thrashed
your father badly.
For the first time
someone called me son.
Is it okay if I call you papa?
Do you speak from your heart, son?
- No, Papa.
I am speaking from my
mouth but I really mean it.
I suggest you bring
the diamonds quickly.
Your papa has to go back
to his village, isn't it?
Come on.
- I am coming right away, Papa.
Right away.
Papa.
Idiot! What are you doing?
What did I do? - What did you do?
You dropped so many
things on my head..
..and now you're asking what you did.
You banged up my head. - Shut up!
It's a chain and not a thread.
It's a chain.
Tell me where the key is.
With Sofia. - What? - With Sofia.
Sofia?
Hey! Hey! - What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
Cutting the chain!
It can be cut with the axe.
Are you doing it for
the first time? - Yes.
Son, get some practice first.
Hit it, hit it.
Let it be, son.
It's better to remain tied up.
Your father won't
look nice without hands.
Papa, let me practice some more.
No, son.
Marcos!
See what happened to her? Come on.
Where are you going?
- Where are you going?
I am coming back, Papa.
I'll just get the key and come back.
And papa?
- He's going to get the key.
Something's wrong.
Where is Sofia?
Where is Sophie?
Boss, that tall guy took Sophie.
He took her away?
But he came to free his papa.
Instead he took the girl away.
See, he deceived us
as well and not just you.
Press it.
What are you staring at me for?
Keep pressing it till
they don't give us the address.
Keep pressing it.
Hello. - Do you want
the girl or the diamonds?
Hey. I thought you came here
to return the rest of the diamonds..
..and free your friends.
I didn't come there
to give the diamonds..
..but to take the
rest of the diamonds.
That's why I abducted your girl.
Where is Sophie? - What did you say?
It won't make any difference
to you even if I kill Sophia.
You just need the diamonds.
What are you saying..
- Marcos, you rascal.
You want to kill me.
- Cool down, baby. - I will kill you.
I will kill you.
- Take care of her. Sophie....
Sophie, come down.
Did you hear?
Come with my men and the
diamonds to the 'Dhaba' (Inn).
The deal will be made there.
If you try to act smart..
..then I'll grind your
diamonds into powder.
And you can make bread from it.
Without the vegetables.
Yes, boss.
Gather everyone.
But, boss, it can be dangerous..
..to go to the place
where he has called us.
I know that.
But today there's a 'Baisaki'
festival at the 'Dhaba'..
..and there'll be many Sardars.
We'll go there dressed
as a Sardar as well..
..so that they don't recognize us.
Sardar? How can I,
sister and Sophie dress like a Sardar?
You can do any getup you want.
I'll dress up like a Sardar.
But your getup should be such that..
..Marcos doesn't recognize you.
Father. Father,
give me one last chance.
This time I will kill
five birds with one stone.
Marcos has four accomplices.
Don't be tense.
The idea that I have
today cannot fail.
We'll go there dressed as Sardars.
No Problem,
"Standing tall with
a broad chest-chest."
"Everyone says they're best-best."
"Standing tall with
a broad chest-chest."
"Everyone says they're best-best."
"Standing tall with
a broad chest-chest."
"Everyone says they're best-best."
"The Jatt's look so majestic."
"Punjabi, the merry Punjabi's."
"Their hearts are filled with love,
they're the best."
"They're a merry bunch,
only scared of God."
"Don't ever try to test them."
"Everyone says they're best-best."
"The Jatt's look so majestic."
"Punjabi, the merry Punjabi's."
"Shake your waist,
look into my eyes, dear."
"I am fair and you are by my side.
Our hearts will connect today."
"Shake your waist,
look into my eyes, dear."
"I am fair and you are by my side.
Our hearts will connect today."
"They're always in
a happy mood all the time."
"Hit the dance floor. And enjoy."
"From right to the left."
"Everyone says they're best-best."
"The Jatt's look so majestic."
"Punjabi, the merry Punjabi's."
"Standing tall with
a broad chest-chest."
"Everyone says they're best-best."
"The Jatt's look so majestic."
"Punjabi, the merry Punjabi's."
Standing tall with
a broad chest-chest.
Everyone says they're best-best.
Boss. It's him. He's the one from the
railway tracks. - What is he doing here?
Punjabi, the merry Punjabi's.
What is he doing here?
Brother-in-law, who is he?
- The angel of death.
Death always hovers around him.
Give me a last glass
of 'Lassi' (Buttermilk).
Brother-in-law,
he's asking for his last 'Lassi'.
Raja, get him some
'Lassi-wassi' with extra butter.
Hey, rascal.
I only ordered for
'Lassi' what is 'wassi'?
'Mutton-shatton', 'Murga-surga',
'Chai-shai', Parathe-sharathe'.
You always mention two
things but feed only one.
Scoundrel, stop talking nonsense.
Or else I swear I will kill you.
What do you say?
Let's kill him? - Yes, let's kill him.
How can you kill me?
Death couldn't kill me himself.
But this time I've made
foolproof arrangements.
I will surely die,
but all of you will die with me.
Death is very closeby. - Closeby?
What are you looking around for?
It's coming from above.
I have unscrewed all
the bolts of the ceiling.
Go. Go to heaven. Help us.
Hold it tight. Or else we'll die.
You all warded off death again.
But, you won't be able
to do it for long. - Quiet.
You always try to die wherever we are.
How will I go to my village now?
Papa. - If I die..
Don't say that, Papa.
Your son is still alive.
Son. Why you..
I don't mean anything.
Did you come to save your
papa or to abduct the girl?
If I hadn't done that..
..then Marcos would've
killed our entire family.
What family? - You're my papa.
He isn't my friend
but my younger brother.
Your brother is dead.
For the sake of the diamonds..
..you told them to kill us.
Keep your diamonds with you.
No, Raj. Brother-in-law
didn't say that. - She is right.
Marcos wanted to kill me
for the diamonds. - No. Sophie.
That scoundrel was
instigating you against me..
..that's why I instigated
his men against him.
Half the diamonds that are
there with them are worth millions.
But not more precious than you.
They've got diamonds worth millions.
Dying cancelled.
Come on, give the diamonds.
Hey, I'll kill you
if you touch the diamonds.
You'll kill me if your hands are free.
Come on. - Hey.
Boss, don't let him
check your back-pocket.
Hey, shut up!
- Thank you. One minute. - Hey!
Money is an evil thing.
Look, if you come ahead..
I'll kick you.
You will go ten feet down. Got it?
You'll kick me away but
this ceiling will fall on you.
Thank you.
Why you..
Brother, don't let him go.
Don't worry.
We won't spare him.
Hold it. I'm coming.
- I'll hold it. You go.
Hold on.
Dad. - Save me.
Save me. Save me.
Beat him.
What are you staring at?
Help us up or else we'll die.
If we come there we'll die too.
Are Sardars afraid of dying?
He's absolutely right.
'Jo Bole So Nihaal' (What you utter,
shall be fulfilled).
'Sat Sri Akaal' (Eternal is the Lord).
'Jo Bole So Nihaal' (What you utter,
shall be fulfilled).
'Sat Sri Akaal' (Eternal is the Lord).
Father, why are you hanging here?
Stay quiet. Don't take a hasty
decision. Think with a cool head.
Hey, idiot, catch me.
Relax. Relax or I'll hit you.
What sort of a boss we have got?
Don't move.
You too.
Give me the diamonds, come on.
Papa. We've got the diamonds.
Hey, you fool.
Give it to me.
Throw it. Throw it.
Throw it.
I've got them.
Marcos. I've heard that
there's a reward on your head.
Boss, don't tell him.
"No problem."
Son. - Papa, run.
Shoot them.
Marcous.
Why you..
It's the same one.
- It's the same one.
Thank you.
No problem.
Catch it.
Raj.
Give it here.
Pick it up.
"No problem."
Uncle.
Old man.
Give me. Give me.
Tuktuk. - Tuktuk.
You fool.
Come on.
'Lassi' is just 'lassi' after all.
And 'wassi' is our love.
You make fun of us.
I know, I know.
You're all very honest.
I was only instigating
all of you so that you kill me.
But why do you want to die?
What should I stay alive for?
My family was crushed
under a tanker in Rajapatti.
I had their photo.
- Just a minute. Just a minute.
You said that your
family was in Afghanistan.
Yes, but he said Iraq to us.
Where is your family?
Your family, my family..
Doesn't humanity have any family?
No matter who dies in
any corner of the world..
..but it's humanity
that's murdered after all.
That's right. - That's why I am dying.
But I can live.
If I get these diamonds.
But what will you
do with the diamonds?
I'll give it to America..
..and tell them to maintain
peace all over the world.
You are right. - He should
get the diamonds. - That's right.
But, brother, where are the diamonds?
He has one bag.
Catch him. Catch him.
No.
"No problem."
Diamonds.
The fishes are
swallowing the diamonds.
Boss. - Diamonds.
Boss. - Diamonds. - Boss.
Where are you all going?
The tank will explode.
The fishes swallowed the
diamonds and went into the ocean.
All the diamonds are gone.
Boss, our diamonds are gone.
The fish have the diamonds now.
Boss, don't cry.
We've lost the diamonds and the girl.
No one knows till date where
Sophiya went after this incident.
Marcos and his friends got punished.
440 years prison term.
Zandulal came back to his
village and opened a new bank again.
There was also a child
in his house. Chinese.
Super-cop Arjun Singh
was sent to Port Ridge..
..for police training again.
Yash and Raj started fishing business.
They were sure that they
would catch a few fishes..
..which had swallowed their diamonds.
Sound. - Rolling. - Action.
"No Problem. No Problem."
"Everybody say no problem."
"We're filled with love. No Problem."
"We live carefree. No Problem."
"We win by losing. No Problem."
I lost my heart and won yours.
No problem.
"We're filled with love. No Problem."
"We live carefree. No Problem."
"We win by losing. No Problem."
I lost my heart and won yours.
No problem.
"Everybody come on let's see."
"Don't worry about anything."
"Don't waste this fervour."
"Let's have some romance."
"Let's dance, let's dance.
Fill me in your arms."
"Let's enjoy life."
"No Problem."
"Everybody say no problem."
"We'll get out of here.
Whenever we get the opportunity."
"We're like the breeze of air.
You'll never catch us."
"Come to me, come in my arms."
"We'll start a new story.
We'll never separate."
"Everybody come on let's see."
"Don't worry about anything."
"Don't waste this fervour."
"Let's have some romance."
"Let's dance, let's dance.
Fill me in your arms."
"Let's enjoy life."
"No Problem. No Problem."
"Everybody say no problem."