Previously on
Seducing Drake Palma.
We’ve only known each other
for a week.
But in that one week,
I’ve seen you cry twice.
Can I be the one instead?
I promise I won’t make you cry.
Do you know Drake Palma?
He’s my cousin.
No way?!
Our dads are brothers.
We’re both Palmas,
and both handsome.
It runs in the blood.
I think this is where we end.
Are you breaking up with me?
Please, let me go.
Breaking up is a mutual decision.
And I don’t wanna break up with you.
We fight...
then apologize.
Then I give in again.
Four down, one to go.
Just one more, and you’ll
get a feel of my joke.
I’ll just head home,
there’s an emergency.
I’ll take you home.
You don’t deserve to
be treated this way, Alys.
No one should make you cry.
[In French] Only you
I love you, Drake Palma!
Alys!
Alys, honey...
Alys, are you okay?
I’m okay.
Aunt Liana, I missed you!
What brings you here, Aunt?
I just landed from Singapore and
I want to give you your presents.
What? Aunt, thank you!
You’re welcome.
By the way, is your Mom here?
I think she’s meeting with a client,
and Dad’s still at the office.
Good. You know I
can’t handle your Mom.
I don’t understand why
she and Mom can’t get along.
They’re both kind and pretty.
Their jobs are even related,
since Mom is a designer
and Aunt’s an
event coordinator.
It’s so weird.
Aunt, do you want some snacks?
Yes, perfect—I’m starving!
Let’s go, then!
You know what, Aunt, I’m
really glad you’re here.
At least, I have someone to talk to.
And I won’t cry alone anymore.
I didn’t live for 17 years
just to cry all the time.
So…
So, what?
Tell me the story.
Because your Daddy said
you already have a boyfriend.
You want to talk about him?
Dad is such a gossip!
Ugh, it’s so annoying!
But no, Aunt—
Tripp is not my boyfriend!
He and Drake are cousins.
Do you expect me to jump
from one cousin to another?
No way.
What did you say?
It’s nothing, Aunt. Don’t mind me.
Anyway, your Dad said,
Tripp is nice.
Oh no, Aunt!
Tripp is far from nice.
He’s so mean.
He’s always teasing me!
Tell me more about him.
Fine, okay.
So, Tripp and I first met
during Freshman Walk.
Actually, I had a boyfriend that time,
so I treated him coldly.
He asked me to be his partner.
- How about us instead?
- Huh?
I have a boyfriend.
I didn’t know it was
a buddy system.
Since I didn’t have
a choice, I went for it.
But he was so annoying, because—
What’s your name again?
Tripp Marco.
Remember it.
Hello, Tripp!
I hope we become friends.
- Friends?
- Mmm.
We’ll see.
I was surprised that he
suddenly got grumpy.
He walked out on me,
and I was thinking,
What’s his problem?
As if it’s my fault.
So, I ran after him.
Hey, Tripp!
Are you giving up?
It’s because...
Why are you being so grumpy?
We just met, and you’re already
snapping at me?
Then, we were okay,
we became friends.
But one time,
I really appreciated him.
Because honestly, Aunt, I
was being bullied in school.
One time, some girls threw coffee on me.
I didn’t even know them.
And he was there.
They ganged up on me.
Alys…
He lent me his jacket, then
came with me to buy clothes.
But you know what’s so annoying?
I told him I’d ride his motorcycle
on one condition.
He had to go slow.
Are you ready?
Let’s go.
Tripp!
Don’t speed up!
Tripp! Stop!
I wanted to strangle him!
My soul was left
on the street.
And then...
He texted me when he saw me
crying because of Drake.
I can only tolerate you
crying five times, Alys.
That’s your third already.
When you reach five,
I’ll make my joke real.
He said, “Four down, one to go”
What does that joke mean?
Honestly, I don’t know.
Does he mean he wants
to be my boyfriend?
What a joke. He’s annoying.
You know what, for once,
I agree with your Dad.
Tripp seems nice.
So why don’t you just
dump that jerk boyfriend?
- Drake?!
- Ssshhh!
I thought we were leaving?
Hold my hand.
Huh?
You said I lack affection, right?
Hold my hand. Let’s go.
Wait.
Looks like you got upset
by what I said.
No.
I can’t, Aunt.
I don’t know.
No matter how badly Drake
treats me,
it never crossed my
mind to leave him.
Do you love him?
He’s a part of me.
I love him despite his flaws.
Isn’t loving someone means
loving them completely and unconditionally?
Seriously? It’s become my default
that whenever I cry, I look for tripp.
Maybe he’ll suddenly show up
and send me some random text.
Aww, our baby is now a lady.
Alys, I’m so proud of you.
By the way...
What do you
want for your birthday?
Oh, my gosh!
My birthday’s coming up soon.
My debut is next week.
Yes, so what do you want?
Aunt Liana, do you think you
could convince Dad to get me a condo?
- Condo?
- Mm-hmm!
Why? You don’t want to
live with your Mom?
Oh, because she’s strict, right?
No, it’s not that, Aunt.
I really love my mom,
it’s just that…
I just want to live next to Drake.
Come on, Aunt!
Do you think I’m
being too clingy?
Is it a dumb decision?
I don’t know, it’s just that…
Drake and I have been together so
long, and we’ve been through so much.
Really fun and happy ones.
Of course, I won’t just give up!
I’m already here—why
would I back out now?
So, now I understand
why you want a condo.
So, I will tell your Dad
and convince him for you.
Yay! Thank you so much, Aunt!
Okay, I’ll send
you the address.
I think I’ve kept quiet long enough.
It’s time for me to be territorial, too.
The Cove Tower?
Yes!
This is a nice condo.
Yes, I hope Dad or Daddy or anyone
agrees, I just really want a condo!
I will try, okay, for
your birthday.
- I’ll try to convince him.
- Thank you so much, Aunt!
Thank you!
Thank you, Aunt.
I really missed you!
I love you, kiddo.
I love you, too, Aunt.
So, where’s Drake?
He’s at his condo.
Tell him to come by tomorrow.
He’s your escort, right?
Oh, okay.
Maybe Sheen could
be my partner instead?
I’m sure Drake won’t even agree.
But I’ll try calling him later.
I don’t want to talk to him in
person—it’s nerve-wracking.
Oh, by the way, Dane is
coming home next week.
For real?!
Sorry, I was just shocked.
Really?!
Yeah!
Since next week is your debut,
your birthday, it’s going to be very fun.
Dane has to be here
to spend a week with us.
Felice is going to be happy.
You know those two, they were
lovebirds before he went to the States.
Yeah, Felice will come too.
You know what, I think your debut is
gonna be very beautiful, my baby!
I hope so, Mom.
- I’m sure it’s gonna be beautiful.
- Oh, yeah!
It’s because of you, Mom!
What now?
Should I call him?
What if he says no?
Do I apologize for what I said?
But why would I apologize?
Gosh!
I’ll take my chances.
Okay.
Drake, please, pick up.
Hello?
Uhm, why are you calling?
I take back saying sorry.
Hello? And why do you
have Drake’s phone?
What do you even care?
Why are you calling?
Please give him the phone.
Please.
He’s asleep!
I’m not going to wake
him up for you! Duh!
What are you doing
in Drake’s condo?
Please tell me
you’re just studying.
Take a guess.
Shai—!
You’re such a leech!
Just a little more
patience, Alys.
Don’t give up yet.
I want you to only give up,
when you can say
you’ve given it your all.
You’ve done absolutely everything.
So don’t you dare say...
don’t you dare say I left you.
Today is a brand new day.
I’m going to class again.
But Lord...
please, I hope I won’t
see anyone today.
I hope there won’t be no problems,
no issues, nothing!
Lord please, I just
want to study in peace.
And I hope I won’t
run into Tripp.
I still keep thinking
about what he said.
It’s really confusing.
Are you avoiding me?
Tripp!
I said are you avoiding me?
Good.
Because when you brought me
into your life,
I never planned on leaving.
- You and your cheesy lines!
- Ouch!
Hey, where are you going?
Uhm...to my class.
I’ll take you.
No need.
Go ahead, just go.
Fine, I’ll go first.
Hey!
I’m easy to talk to.
You’re so sensitive!
Come on, let’s go.
Okay, fine.
Let’s go.
Take me.
Why is Tripp looking
more handsome?
Damn!
Let’s go, I’ll take you.
Let’s go, you’re so persistent.
You’re playing hard to get.
Whatever you say.
You’re sitting pretty there.
- You’re going to get scolded later.
- Classmate!
Hey, I’m early today!
Yes, I have a new life now.
Hi!
I hope there’s
nothing to do today.
What are you doing here?
Don’t you have a class?
Free cut.
Thought I’d sit in here.
Okay, it’s up to you.
Uhm...
Tripp?
Yes?
- Can I ask you something?
- Mmm?
You said you’ll always
be on my side, right?
You won’t ever fool me, right?
I think I’m starting to
have trust issues with guys.
Zy...
I won’t play you, promise.
My cousin fooled you,
so why would I?
Do you know Shaira?
Shaira?
Yes.
But we don’t talk anymore.
Why?
Nothing.
How close is she with Drake?
Close?
I have no idea.
Because when Drake
and I were in second year,
he suddenly got quieter,
and Shaira turned snobbish.
But she used to be nice,
the only problem was when
Drake kind of had a girlfriend,
Shaira turned mean.
Why are you asking?
Oh, so it was because
of Aunt Katrina.
If it weren’t for her, Drake and Shaira
would probably be together now!
Am I really the one
butting in?
Nothing.
Okay class, take your seats
and please get your assignments.
Alright, I’ll go ahead.
- Bye!
- Bye.
So, where are we really going?
I just want to check
out this art bar nearby.
Good thing it’s my vacant
time. You always suddenly–
Tripp, son! Oh—
- Dad?
- I’ve been looking for you!
Who is this with you?
- Oh, I’m Alys—
- My girlfriend.
- What, girlfriend?
- Oh!
So, you’re my son’s girlfriend?
I’m his Dad.
- Nice to meet you!
- You can call me Uncle Tristan.
Okay.
You look really pretty, dear.
Oh, thank you!
Wait, I’ll introduce you to
Tripp’s cousin.
Let me just call Drake, okay.
Drake, come here!
Oh, sh–!
By the way, this is–
Drake!
Drake, let go of me!
Drake, can you please
let go, you’re hurting me!
Sorry.
Sorry?
“Sorry” again?
Why are you with him?
Stupid question.
Of course, you’re together.
Wow.
Are you accusing me
of cheating on you?
Why, aren’t you?
Wow!
Should I faint right now?
Me?!
You’re accusing me
of cheating?
Huh?!
Are you out of your
goddamned mind?!
No! You—are you
out of your mind?!
No, I’m not!
Then, why were
you with my cousin?
Well, why were you with Shaira?
There.
I asked!
Just to be fair, right?
I was busy.
Busy?
Busy with what?
Were you so busy that you
didn’t think of me for five minutes?
Alys...
Trust me on this one, okay?
Trust?
It’s so hard to trust you, Drake.
Because every time I do,
I’m the one who gets hurt.
I’m the one crying alone.
I’m the one who gets tired.
Even if I don’t want to
be paranoid, it’s so hard.
What can I do if there’s a Shaira who’s
willing to snatch you away anytime?
Since when did
you get so stubborn?
Since last week.
We’ve been apart for so long, so
much has changed in me, Drake.
Why? Did you miss me?
In those three weeks we weren’t
together, did I ever cross your mind?
Even just once?
Let’s go home.
Huh? What?
Seriously, after everything I
said, “let’s go home” is all you’ve got?
Wow, you’re really something!
My gosh! One kiss and
all my anger disappears!
So unfair!
I should be mad right now!
What’s going on?
Family reunion.
What?
- Your entire clan is inside?
- Mmm.
What?!
Your whole clan’s inside,
having a reunion, and look at me—
I’m in my CA uniform
with a strawberry stain?!
I’m not going in.
Stubborn.
Dad’s expecting you.
I don’t want to! I look so ugly!
My cousins are ugly
too—you’ll blend in.
Wow, thanks for that.
Fine, get out, I’ll change clothes.
I can stay.
Huh?
Hey, get out!
Okay.
Don’t you dare look, okay?
I’ll try.
My beautiful girlfriend.
Let’s go.
Hi!
Thank you so much.
Hi, Drake!
The baby will
definitely love that.
Uncle Steve!
The one in the
shower will be different!
I missed you!
Thanks!
- Hi, Aunt Katrina!
- Hi, Alys!
Drake!
Where’s Aya?
We have so much food!
Oh gosh, Uncle, Aya?
I don’t know where she is.
Wait, I’ll just entertain
some other guests, okay?
Okay, thank you!
See you later.
We’re still at war.
I just let that moment slide.
After this,
I won’t talk to you again until you tell
me why you were with that octopus Shaira!
Alys, let me introduce
you to my relatives.
My cousins—Lucas and
Teodoro—they’re Palmas, too.
- Hello, Uncle!
- This is Alys.
Hello, Uncle!
Tristan! Tristan!
Hey! What’s up?
Ugh, this guy!
Is he trying to kill me
with stress and nervousness?
This is Drake’s girlfriend.
She is Alys.
- Oh, hello.
- Girlfriend?
Yes.
Hi!
Wait, I’ll come to you.
Oh…uhm…
I dumped her.
She was boring.
Then she and Drake
ended up together.
Cool, right?
Are you serious?
So, we’re good?
We’re good, right, Alys?
We’re good.
- Let’s go.
- What? I don’t know with you!
You’re so annoying!
Are you crazy—
Am I a playgirl?
I was just joking!
What joke?
If it was just a joke,
you should’ve told your dad.
He might think
I’m some dirty girl.
Ouch! Ouch!
Hey, that hurts!
You’re so annoying!
Well, you practically
called me a dirty guy, too!
Your drama won’t work
on me anymore, got it?
You’re so irritating!
Take back what
you said to your dad.
No way!
Tripp, come on!
I said no.
Please, Tripp!
Just this once, let me
ask this favor from you!
I said no!
Tripp is so weird.
He’s so good at teasing, but
sometimes, he looks so sad.
Sometimes when I pity him,
I just want to hug him.
Hey.
Hey!
Fine, yes!
But that’s the last time, okay?
Don’t do it again.
You’re too nice, you know that?
I know!
Sometimes, try being grumpy.
You’re way too lovable.
Ouch!
Do that again and
you’ll be in trouble.
That’s the problem with you.
You don’t take what I say seriously.
That’s going to be a problem,
you’ll see.
I don’t want to entertain him.
He talks too much,
all pick-up lines.
That’s why I keep smacking him.
People think he’s my boyfriend
number two because we’re close.
As if I have a choice!
Just tell me a story.
What do you want?
A happy one? A sad one?
Or maybe a funny one
so we can just laugh it off?
Anything.
He said he’s serious!
He said it’s “symbolism”!
What kind of art is that?!
Only he would think
of something like that!
You know what, Tripp, you’re like someone
I’d bring home and put in a pet cage!
You’re like a parrot, you
never run out of things to say!
Um, Tripp…
Why are you always sad?
Huh? Am I sad?
It’s weird, but even when you smile,
I can see and tell that you’re sad.
Hey, I’m your friend, right?
Share something with me.
Sorry if I get weird sometimes.
It’s just that…
my Mom got married again.
I thought she and dad
would get back together,
but they didn’t.
Family problems are tough.
I undertand your weirdness.
Alys…
Mmm?
Oh, sorry.
I couldn’t help it.
Okay, I’ll go ahead.
What was that?
What just happened?
Did he leave already?
Well, he better be.
He’s so annoying,
I should punch him.
Where have you been?
You’ve been gone for so long.
Uhm…just getting some air.
Getting some air?
For that long?
Gosh, I feel guilty.
Why do I feel like
I’m the bad one and not Drake?
Ugh, this is all Tripp’s fault!
Drake and I need to fix this
before it gets worse.
I’ll do my best to make
this relationship last.
What are you thinking?
Uh...
Nothing.
I just missed you.
So, what’s keeping you busy now?
Is it Shaira that made you
forget I still exist?
School works – the usual.
Drake.
Mmm?
Can you please not
make me cry again?
I’m scared Tripp might take
his joke seriously.
Promises are meant
to be broken.
So I’ll just try, okay?
Drake...
can you be my
escort for my debut?
What’s that?
I just thought...
it’s different if my boyfriend
will be my escort at my debut.
Of course, I want my debut
to be a night to remember.
So...
yes or yes?
I’ll say yes if you
promise me one thing.
Stop talking to Tripp.
Huh?
I said stop talking to Tripp.
What? Why?
How can I avoid him when
he’s the one I’m always with?
You know we can’t
always be together, right?
I know that.
Drake, why don’t
we make a truce?
Mmm, I’m listening.
Okay.
I won’t talk to Tripp anymore,
but you have to promise me
you won’t talk to Shaira either.
Why are you so
jealous of Shaira?
Isn’t it obvious?
Because you’re always with her!
Sshh!
Alys, what else do I need to do?
To make you believe when
I say it’s only you.
Hmm?
Shaira is just a friend.
I know.
She needs me.
But I need you, too.
I’m glad you do.
Because, Alys,
I need you so much.
And that it hurts.
I know I’m not vocal
about my feelings.
And I’m sorry.
Please don’t go away.
After my dad replaced my late
mom with Katrina,
I was deeply hurt.
I told myself love is dispensable.
I was afraid to love.
Until I met you.
You annoyed the hell out of me.
Honestly, I didn’t like you then.
But slowly, you entered my heart.
And you stayed there.
My love for you felt different.
I was surprised.
I got scared because I
didn’t know how I fell for you.
I feel like I’m drowning in
everything that’s happening.
I know I irritate you.
But, Alys...
This is who I really am.
This is how I am.
I can’t change that.
You’re always in my heart,
Alys Zyril Palma.
So, please trust me.
And don’t leave me.
I can’t promise to
be the ideal boyfriend,
because if I make that promise,
I’ll end up breaking that promise
over and over again.
I know that, Drake.
All I want is for you to
be more open with me.
I’m not a mind-reader, Drake.
It’s hard for me to read you.
We keep misunderstanding
each other because I don’t get you.
I just wish you’d trust me more.
I wish you’d trust me enough
for you to tell me everything—
everything you think,
everything you feel.
Sounds fair.
Do you promise to be
more open this time?
I promise I’ll try.
Stop crying.
How about you?
How’s school?
It’s fun.
But it’s way more fun
when you’re with me, of course.
You know what…
Mmm?
…so many girls are
picking on me at school,
because they know you and
they know you’re my boyfriend.
Why didn’t you tell me?
It’s fine with me.
No problem at all.
Well, it’s not fine with me.
Wow, protective, huh?
That’s new.
Shut up, Alys, I’m trying
to be a good boyfriend.
So, stop mocking me.
“Shut up, Alys, I’m trying
to be a good boyfriend.”
I said shut up!
Stop mocking me!
That’s music to my
ears—say it again!
Hello?
[In French] Only you.
What did he say?
Well, whatever it
was, I’m still giddy!
Good night, Drakey baby!
Alys…
Mmm?
Should I be worried?
I won’t let Tripp steal you, Alys.
Not a chance.
Where have you been?
You’ve been gone for so long.
Uhm, just getting some air.
Getting some air? For that long?
Why are you lying, Alys?
Am I losing you to Tripp?
Why are you hurting me?
On the next episode of
Seducing Drake Palma.
Dane, you’re here!
What happened to you?
You are ugly,
but you’re getting even uglier.
Are you really my sister?
Good thing I’ve got my
super cute brother here.
Stop!
I need to avoid Tripp
so things will be
peaceful with Drake.
You’re really avoiding me,
aren’t you?
What should I do?
Should I greet him, or just
walk past like I didn’t see him?
What to do?
Drake!
Oh no!
Oh no, this can’t be happening!
It’s my birthday today!