It's done.
Master,
we got her.
Good.
Do you know what this is called?
This is karma coming due.
My dear third brother
could be cruel enough
to ruin his own brother's future.
Then don't blame me
for making him taste the torment
of losing his beloved.
But Master,
that man Xie said
he couldn't get out.
He had no choice
but to hide in the capital for now.
What?
This...
What... what else did he say?
He said...
losing his beloved
is agony beyond bearing.
Third Uncle's beloved...
Everyone in the manor is still there.
Could it be Gu Jinzhao?
For the next two days,
do nothing else.
Keep an eye on Fourth Uncle.
No.
He won't show himself.
Watch that Chen Zhong.
See what he does next.
Yah!
Mr. Jiang sent word.
They found traces of the villains.
They seemingly headed for the capital.
You just
lock them in there?
With people coming and going,
what if someone finds out?
You don't understand.
The darkest place is under the lamp.
Don't worry.
Tomorrow morning,
the trafficker will come inspect the goods.
Once they're in his hands,
there are plenty of ways
to erase her trail.
Chen Yi.
Take my card
to the City Garrison.
Tell them I'll be there shortly.
And...
Fetch my seal from home.
Hurry.
Yes.
Sir.
Are you going to...
Seal up the city.
Since she's in the city,
lock the capital down for me.
Shut the gates and search.
I'll take both.
Forty taels of silver.
Not a coin more.
Follow him.
What are you doing?
Let us go!
Brother.
Give me some water.
So much nonsense.
Then don't eat.
Sir, sir.
This is truly awful.
I can't swallow it.
How about this?
Take this thing
off my wrist.
Take this to a pawnshop.
It'll fetch at least a hundred taels.
Look. What is this?
You've done well.
Of course.
Hold it.
Seize this woman
for me.
You...
What are you doing? You...
This pink pearl
was brought back from the Western Sea.
In the capital, there's only this one.
It was given by our Old Madam
as part of the dowry
for my young lady.
Speak up.
How did it get into your hands?
I...
I don't know.
Nanny.
This is the gentleman.
Stand down.
I hear
you want one with fine looks,
one who can read and write,
and from a good family too.
Goods like that
do exist.
But
they won't come cheap.
Name your price.
Two hundred taels, then.
Why is there only one hundred fifty?
This jade pendant of mine
is worth fifty taels at least.
But
you must let me see the girl first.
Then I'll give it to you.
You want to inspect the goods?
Fine.
Then come with me.
She's inside.
Go on.
By now,
she has been drugged.
When you take her away later,
the road will be easier.
The drug will do her no harm.
Step aside.
[Third Uncle's voice.]
Don't run.
Don't move.
It's all right now.
- Yanyun
- It's all right.
You scared me to death.
It's all right.
It's all right. It's over.
Are you okay?
Yanyun.
Jinzhao. Jinzhao.
Stop!
Don't pull me.
Get away.
Then perish!
Perish!
Young master.
She saw our faces.
I know.
Young master.
Don't be afraid.
Yunting killed him.
Don't be afraid, young master.
Gu Jinzhao was abducted by thugs?
Yes.
In his panic, Lord Chen
called the Five City Garrison.
All city gates were locked.
They claimed they were hunting bandits
and searched house by house.
In the end, she was found
in a house in the south city.
So this is the man you chose, Gu Jinzhao.
You.
Take a few men.
Take my warrant with you
to the City Garrison.
Bring back the thugs
who kidnapped Gu Jinzhao.
Tell them this case
falls to the Xuanfeng Guard.
Yes.
Bring out the prisoners
caught yesterday.
Yes.
My lord.
You needn't follow.
Why is she not back yet?
Hupo.
Go check at the gate.
Yes.
Mother.
Shall we go back
and wait inside?
Tell me,
Jinzhao is far too willful.
When a bride returns home,
who doesn't go to her father's family?
But she...
She insisted on her mother's family.
Look now.
Trouble came, didn't it?
Mother, calm yourself.
Jinzhao
was indeed a little willful.
But
she didn't know
she would be abducted.
At least she was saved.
Wasn't she?
But still,
she was missing all day and night.
Who knows what happened?
And she is a Grand Secretary's wife, no less.
From now on,
the gossip won't be light.
That's exactly what I fear.
If tongues wag about her,
Yanyun will be dragged into it too.
Honestly.
My lord.
How is it?
All of them were caught.
I took a shortcut
back to report to you.
My lord,
before Mr. Chen traces this to us,
we should run.
If we don't leave now,
it'll be too late.
It's over.
It's all over now.
They're here.
They're here. They're here.
My lord.
Third Madam is back.
Should we go too?
You go.
My lord.
I need to go out.
Go out? Where?
Chen Zhong just sent word.
The Southern Office
will add two million salt permits next month.
I must go at once.
Chen Zhong, prepare the carriage.
Yes, Master.
Wait.
Need it be so urgent?
Can't you leave tomorrow morning?
What do you know?
Mother.
This...
You should put me down.
I can walk myself.
Mother.
Jinzhao was frightened just now
and sprained her ankle.
I'll take her back.
Go back, then.
Yunting.
Young master.
Do you think
I look like a joke?
Who does such a thing?
How shameless.
Mother.
Yanyun
is clearly doing it on purpose.
On purpose?
This is at home.
Does he need so many schemes?
Honestly.
A good man has been led astray.
About what happened today,
no one is to mention it again.
Yes.
If anyone
dares wag their tongue
and I hear of it,
no trial needed.
Beat them dead where they stand.
Yes, yes.
It's getting late.
All of you may leave.
Will you sit?
I'll take off your shoes.
How is it?
You were wronged today.
This time you were abducted.
People will inevitably gossip.
By carrying you in like this,
if any blind fools still dare,
then don't blame me
Let no one say I gave no warning.
Sir.
I'll be back soon.
Miss.
Let me help you bathe.
Let Nanny Zhao do it.
Go back and rest.
If anything feels wrong,
tell me.
I'm fine.
It's nothing.
Listen to Miss.
Go back and rest.
I'm here.
It's all right, Nanny Zhao.
We'll do it together.
I have urgent matters to handle.
Let them wash you properly
and get some real sleep.
Don't wait for me.
I'll be right back, all right?
I'll be right back.
Take good care of Madam.
Yes.
I warned you.
Yet again and again, you went too far.
This time, you even
laid hands on your sister-in-law.
Because I hate you.
Why?
Just because I killed Fifth Brother?
But I barely know nothing then.
I was just a child.
I'm your blood brother.
You could have taught me.
Why did you ruin my future?
I also studied ten hard years.
Now I can only manage petty affairs.
Do you know how much I hate you?
So you know
you killed Fifth Brother.
You brought it on yourself.
I brought it on myself?
Chen Yanyun, I brought it on myself?
No.
You were jealous of me.
You were jealous
that Mother loved only me since childhood.
So you ruined my whole life.
I won't let you live well either.
I'll make you taste my pain.
Pain worse than death.
I knew it
when I saw the way you looked at that woman.
I knew
that woman is your weak spot.
I wanted something to happen to her.
I wanted to abduct her.
I wanted to sell her to a brothel.
I wanted her trampled by the whole world.
With all your crimes,
exile to the far frontier would be fitting.
Go to Shaanxi. Find Second Brother.
I have written to him
about all you have done.
He will deal with you.
Your children and wife are innocent.
The family will look after them.
Chen Yanyun!
Go sleep in the study.
Are you angry with me?
Yes, I am.
Leave at once.
I don't want to see you.
Don't talk to me.
I'm going to bed.
I won't go.
If I leave,
I'm afraid you won't let me back in.
You are a Grand Secretary.
And you're afraid of that?
Yes.
A grand Secretary fears nothing.
Except this.
Where did you learn such words?
Wenyuan Pavilion?
I learned quite a lot.
All right, all right.
I said I'm sorry, okay?
Just now,
I sent Fourth Brother to Shaanxi.
He likely won't return.
Why?
The kidnappers who took you
were bought by him.
To get revenge on me.
He put in quite some effort.
Why would he do that?
It's a long story.
Do you still remember
that I had
a late fifth brother?
At six, he fell into water by accident.
But many years later,
I learned
he had not fallen by accident.
Fourth Brother pushed him in.
So
I cut off his imperial exam path
and barred him from the exams.
But by then,
he had passed the provincial exam.
So he hated me to the bone.
If
I had known earlier
that he would turn his revenge on you,
I would have...
Would have what?
I would have been far harsher.
But if he suddenly disappeared,
and Mother learns of it,
won't it be hard to explain?
At home, just say
Fourth Brother has gone
to Shaanxi for business.
Rest well
these next few days.
No need to pay respects to Mother.
I'll tell her
you are unwell.
You're making decisions for me again.
Linxia House is about to reopen.
I was thinking
I should go take a look tomorrow.
I know
you worry that Mother and Sister-in-law
will question me endlessly.
But I have nothing to hide.
Rather than avoiding some things,
it's better
to face them openly.
All right.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll go with you
to greet Mother.
I'll tell her beforehand.
Otherwise,
she may not let you out again.
You mustn't go.
That would make it seem
I borrowed your power
to force her to agree.
When the time comes,
even if she agrees on the surface,
she'll still blame me in her heart.
I have my own way.
All right, all right.
As my lady commands.
It is late.
So now,
shall we sleep?
Come.
Fourth Brother too...
He left just like that.
What business is it?
The roads are so far,
yet he took no one with him.
I said I would go care for him,
but my lord refused.
He said this time
he must go toward Yulin Pass too.
It would be too hard.
Yanwen
must have learned from Yanyun.
He has learned to cherish his wife.
Yanyun
cherishes his rather too much.
Third Madam is here.
Greetings, Mother.
Sit.
Have you recovered?
Thank you for your concern, Mother.
I am well now.
Where is Yanyun?
He went early this morning
to Wenyuan Pavilion.
So he has returned to Wenyuan Pavilion
to handle affairs?
Yes.
Then
that is good.
Yanyun
has regained his post as Grand Secretary.
As a Grand Secretary's wife,
inside and outside the household,
you should conduct yourself properly.
Yes.
By the way, Mother.
Linxia House under my name
is preparing to reopen.
So I asked the cooks
to make some
new styles of pastries.
Early this morning,
I had them prepared and sent here.
I hope Mother
and Second Sister-in-law
will let everyone try something fresh.
How very thoughtful, Jinzhao.
Linxia House pastries
must be fine, of course.
Only,
for us, they would have been enough.
You may not know,
she never takes sweets.
Second Sister-in-law is right.
My grandmother
reminded me long ago.
She said Mother has diabetes
and cannot eat sweets.
So these pastries
were specially remade.
A separate portion was made for Mother,
and no sugar was added.
Only licorice and dates
were used for flavor.
I also asked Mother's
usual physician
to examine them.
He said these pastries could be eaten.
Only then did I send them over.
It is kind of your grandmother to remember.
Since such care was taken,
I must try them.
Not bad.
As long as Mother likes them.
I also have a presumptuous request.
My shop Linxia House
is still short of staff.
I heard Mother's maiden family
is a great clan.
If Mother could recommend a few people,
you would be helping me greatly.
So that's it.
Mother, please rest assured.
Whoever Mother recommends
shall be treated fairly
in wages.
Very well.
Tomorrow I'll write home.
Jinzhao is no simple woman.
Ask if they have someone
- She knows Mother
- to spare
- favors her maiden kin,
- for your business.
yet turns even that
into a means to please Mother.
She
was abducted.
- Such a flagrant mistake
- Since
you have business to attend to,
will be pardoned like this?
your daily morning and evening greetings
can be waived too.
Yes.
Since Jinzhao's Linxia House
will only receive female guests,
I suppose from now on,
the Grand Secretaries' wives
will be regular guests there.
The ladies of Wenyuan Pavilion
hold a tea gathering
on the seventh of every month.
Now that Jinzhao
is also a Grand Secretary's wife,
the day after tomorrow is the seventh.
Then, Jinzhao,
have you already received an invitation?
I have never heard of this tea gathering.
It's normal not to receive one.
After all, you are still young.
Those ladies are older than you,
and are born to noble houses.
Naturally,
you have little to talk about with them.
Yes.
Old Madam.
Third Madam.
The household of Chancellor Wang
just sent an invitation.
They invite Third Madam
to tea the day after tomorrow.
I understand.
How is your injury?
I'm all right now.
Have they caught
the mastermind?
Mr. Chen is still checking.
I haven't asked much.
You were truly lucky this time.
Had Third Uncle been any later,
you might already
have met with harm.
I truly never expected
you would choose to marry him.
Was it because of his rank and power?
But in my heart,
you should not be that kind of person.
I don't know what you mean.
I have to go.
I'll leave first.
You are that unwilling
to speak with me?
How could you say that?
I am only in a hurry to go out.
By the way,
since I have married Mr. Chen,
you should call me Aunt Chen.
You...
Forgive me.
I stepped on it by accident.
Forget it.
I don't want it.
Young master.
Let's go back.
Tomorrow,
take this earring
to the silver shop.
Have them make an identical pair.
Send it to Gu Jinzhao.
Young master,
you must not do this.
We have already
made too many mistakes.
If I tell you to go, then go.
For her,
I've already gone so far...
Why can she still act
as if nothing happened?
So there really is such a tea gathering.
What?
You want to go?
You don't want me to?
Of course not.
I'm afraid the Wangs
will plot against you.
Is it connected
to last time's roadblock?
Yes.
What a man is
this Wang Xuanfan?
Last time, in the disaster grain case,
he deliberately
threw dirty water on you
and had you jailed.
Why is he here again?
Since last time,
I told my teacher
that if we want land equalization across the realm,
we must start with ourselves.
Grand Secretaries
must take the lead in auditing their own households
and clear their own taxes.
Only then can they
to audit lower officials.
When lower officials
have cleared their own households,
then audit the gentry and wealthy households.
So my teacher required
officials of the third rank and above
to examine themselves and return what was owed.
Wang Xuanfan is
a famed Daming landowner.
In one go, he disgorged
tens of thousands of taels.
No wonder.
Take his livelihood, you kill his parents.
No wonder he hates you.
So
he devised a method
to incite the scholars to make trouble for me.
No matter what the result,
he wanted to pin the charge
of unfair land equalization
on my head.
A stain is what Grand Secretaries fear most.
Once a stain like this
is seized upon,
I very well might
be sent home under disgrace.
So that is it.
The invitation has reached Chen Manor.
Mrs. Chen said
she will come.
Which Chen Manor?
Chen Yanyun's.
The tea gathering is the day after tomorrow.
I sent for that Gu Jinzhao.
Why invite her?
Have you nothing better to do?
She is also a Grand Secretary's wife.
Shouldn't she be invited to the tea gathering?
Did someone
make you angry somewhere?
You're taking it out on me.
Where else could I be angered?
Isn't this all because of
your rotten idea?
Fine, fine, fine. All of you,
all leave.
You had me stir up those scholars
to block Chen Yanyun's carriage
and cry, 'Unfair reform!'
And what happened?
Now I've dragged myself
right into it.
Chen Yanyun knows.
Even if he does, no need to fear.
Those scholars
were not wrong to begin with.
This land equalization is unfair.
You know nothing of this!
Do you know what slogan
those scholars are shouting now?
Audit the imperial estates.
Count His Majesty's private property.
I told them
to shout that land equalization is unfair.
I never told them
to audit His Majesty's land!
Then Fu Hailian scolded you?
What else?
Before Chen Yanyun,
he gave me a thorough dressing-down.
And you, of all people,
still invited Gu Jinzhao.
Aren't you ashamed?
What do I have to be ashamed of?
You're the one who's ashamed, all right?
Since this time
you suffered at Chen Yanyun's hands,
all the more I must invite Gu Jinzhao.
No.
You want to go that badly?
You saw through me.
I'm afraid they'll plot against you.
I'm not so easy to bully.
True.
I'm even more afraid
you'll clash with them.
What?
Are you afraid you can't protect me?
Trying to provoke me?
I am a Grand Secretary.
Though my seniority is shallow,
protecting you is more than enough.
Then that's settled.
I want to attend the tea gathering
not for my own amusement,
but because
it is the Grand Secretaries' wives' tea gathering.
If I don't go,
am I not cutting myself off from that circle?
That would embarrass you too.
I know.
These Grand Secretaries' wives
are all senior to me.
Even Mrs. Shen
comes from a noble family
with deep learning.
Don't worry.
I won't offend them.
All right.
Then I'll ask around for you
about these ladies:
what their temperaments are
and what they like.
Where would you ask?
They are all noble ladies of the capital.
If people find out,
they'll mock you behind your back.
I have my own ways.
Mrs. Chen, this way please.
Mrs. Fu.
Mrs. Wang.
Mrs. Yao.
Mrs. He.
Greetings, ladies.
Greetings, Mrs. Chen.
Please sit.
Miss Qingpu.
Please come this way to rest.
Look at this new bride.
Her pearls and jade are so plain,
yet she looks so fresh and pretty.
Her skin is so dewy.
Youth is such a fine thing.
Mrs. He, you flatter me.
I dare not accept it.
If we speak of beauty,
all of you ladies
are far more elegant and peerless.
I merely
was born a little later.
By the way,
today
is my first time at this tea gathering.
I prepared gifts
for all of you ladies.
Please, no gifts.
This is a tea gathering,
not some place outside
to curry favor and do business.
The husbands of those seated here
are either Grand Secretaries
or important court ministers.
We ourselves
also bear imperial titles.
If we start exchanging gifts,
once word spreads,
at best, we invite ridicule;
at worst, we give people a handle against us.
When Mrs. Fu set this rule,
I thought she worried too much.
I didn't expect
someone would truly bring gifts.
I was rash.
This is my first tea gathering.
I thought courtesy could not offend.
I did not know
such customs applied.
The fault is mine.
When Mrs. Wang's invitation arrived,
I set about preparing gifts.
I ought to have
sought Mrs. Wang's guidance first.
Since the invitation came from you,
a word of guidance was surely in order.
Yes.
It was my oversight.
Is everyone here?
Yes.
The garden is ready.
Let's all go together.
It's nothing serious.
Don't worry.
I hear
the post of Left Vice Minister of Rites is vacant.
Court nominations were held twice,
yet no choice was made.
In my view,
Lord Zeng Ruoyu
is steady in character
and a renowned great scholar.
He fits the post perfectly.
Mrs. Yao,
what do you think?
My husband
has praised Lord Zeng several times too.
This round of nominations
will most likely favor Lord Zeng.
Good.
My husband said
Wenyuan Pavilion needs Pavilion Secretaries.
I remember you have a nephew
who is a Jinshi from Jingning 35.
Perhaps put his name forward.
Then on behalf of my nephew,
I thank you, Madam.
Mrs. Shen.
You seem
a little distracted today.
Madam.
You know
my husband's temper.
It comes fast and goes fast.
When you return, tell Keqian
he need not worry too much.
He only loses his temper like that
with those he trusts.
I understand.
Thank you, Madam.
Let me go! Let me go!
Let me go, all of you! Let me go!
I'm a court official! Let me go!
Have you no law in your eyes? Let go!
Is there no justice left?
Let me go!
Reporting to the Commander,
At the West City inn,
I seized An Deyu and his wife.
One official seal was found.
Please inspect it, sir.
An imperial warrant?
The Three Judicial Offices are still reviewing it.
How could His Majesty issue such an edict?
Ye Xian.
Investigating Censor of the Censorate.
An Deyu.
You sold offices, neglected duty, and corrupted the law.
By imperial command,
take him to the Imperial Prison.
Lies!
You are slandering me!
My lord.