(Watch on www.kisskh.club Support Admin)
If someone cried in your place,
how would you feel?
Who, P’? Daotok?
Kram’s coming back to Thailand.
It wasn’t easy clearing my schedule to go to California.
You’re not gonna ditch me, right?
In return for helping you, I have one condition.
What condition?
- Help me block my ex.
- Huh?
Help me keep my ex away.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Keep him from messing with you.
Mm.
Shit, why?
Is he really that persistent?
Fine.
What do you even call this?
A guard dog.
Yeah.
You’re right.
Because if you two get back together,
I’m the one who’ll look like a fool.
North said the same—he doesn’t want to be the fool either.
Oh.
So he’s making me the dog instead.
That bastard North really loves me, huh?
Alright, give me more details.
His name’s Kram.
A guy?
What do you mean he’s coming back?
He went to study in the U.S. He’s graduating now.
Why not just get back together and end it?
Let’s get back.
Hey, hey—
What’s your damn problem?
Dao’s new boyfriend?
No.
Then who are you?
Why are you cursing at me?
It’s my job.
What?
Stay the hell away from him.
Oh, Dao sent you to block me?
Yeah.
You should pretend to be his new boyfriend.
No.
And I don’t want to be. Just stay out of his life.
I’m not free enough to sit here and curse you out, asshole.
You’re the laziest guard dog ever.
Why would Dao even pick you?
Yeah, seriously. There are millions of other people.
I can’t even complain—I still need him.
What are you to Dao?
None of your damn business.
If you stop messing with him, that’s the end of it. Go find someone else.
There are tons of people better than this kid. Trust me.
Don’t be so hung up.
What kind of person are you?
I’m out, asshole.
Wait. Talk to me first.
How’s Dao? Is he doing okay?
You idiot.
P’Cream.
Hm?
If you keep missing someone,
does that mean you love them?
Not always.
My boyfriend killed me here.
In this tub.
I still think about him every day.
If you only miss the good memories,
then maybe it’s love.
But if you miss the pain he caused,
then it’s not love. It’s resentment.
What are you doing here?
I’ve got an exam in this building too.
I saw you sitting here, so I waited.
So when are you going to California?
Next week. Waiting for him to finish his exams first.
I’m done with mine already.
Damn, so you’re on break already?
I’ve still got a bunch left.
But you’ll get to travel with your boyfriend soon, right?
Yeah.
I’m finally gonna live my life to the fullest.
Hey, you Daotok.
So,
you—
ever think about opening your heart?
No.
You asked me about this again.
I told you,
I’m not interested in that.
Everyone’s worried about you.
They want someone to take care of you.
And don’t say you can take care of yourself,
because you’re in the hospital once a month.
It’s fine if you don’t open your heart.
But you know, right?
that not everyone’s an asshole like your ex.
Go.
Go where?
Your life’s getting way too comfortable.
Seriously.
Hey.
Every day you don’t have to earn a single dime,
you just eat.
You’re getting fat.
My friend’s talking to a dog now.
Let's go.
Or you’ll complain you can’t read in time again.
What’s your problem?
Dao’s not replying to my texts.
I’m blocking you too.
If you block me, you can’t curse at me.
Thit.
Damn it.
Then just come along.
Yeah, yeah.
Shit, seriously.
How’s Dao doing?
Normal.
All 32 organs.
None missing.
Why’d he send you to block me?
Does he hate me that much?
If you were smarter, you wouldn’t be asking me.
Thit, do you have a wife or something?
I’ve seen you texting for a while now.
Wife my ass.
I’m doing guard-dog duty right now.
For the kid next door’s ex.
Dao?
Yeah.
I can’t not do it, damn it.
I really want him back.
I regret it now.
I want another chance.
Damn, you’re seriously hopeless.
Do I look like your therapist?
Shit.
Go see my personal consultant.
Guaranteed eye-opening.
Hello.
Arthit recommended me.
We already had this one.
Let’s get something else.
Oh, Dao. What are you doing here?
I waited for him in front of his building.
Took him to eat, then brought him here.
I just came to buy coffee, then I’m heading back.
- Hey.
Why rush off?
I have to get back to John.
He must be lonely by now.
You’ve got tons of ghosts in your room.
He’s probably playing with your cat.
- North.
- Yes?
That’s not the same at all.
Besides, everyone came with your partner.
Why should I stay?
This place has so many good menu items.
Let’s order.
You order first.
I’ll take this one.
Oh, P’Thit. Hi, P’.
How’d you get here?
By car.
Good that you’re here.
Let's talk.
Now?
Yeah.
About that guard-dog thing you asked me to do—
I texted and cursed him out.
Kind of randomly.
He said he wanted some advice.
So I dumped him on Fah.
Had Fah talk to him instead.
Maybe talking to Fah will knock some sense into him.
Mm.
He said
he truly feels guilty and wants to apologize to you.
He realized he shouldn’t come back into your life.
Fah, continue.
- Huh?
- Go on.
He told me he treated you badly before, right?
I don’t know the details,
but it must’ve been serious.
He said he’s reflecting on himself now.
But if possible,
he’d like to try again.
I think it’s up to you, Dao.
Whether you want to face him one more time.
Because even he isn’t sure
if he’s chasing you out of love
or just guilt.
Thank you, P’Fah.
Sure.
If I can help, I’d be more than happy to.
Because actually,
Phoon also
care a lot about you too.
Thanks, Maew.
The day I'm going to talk to him,
can you come with me?
Why?
Otherwise, You won’t be able to help at all.
I’m just asking you to block him away.
But you still need P’Tonfah to speak for you?
Fine.
You can go back to studying.
I can head back on my own.
Hey.
Do you think I’m a nice guy, so I’m taking you home?
I just don’t feel like studying.
So I’m using you as an excuse.
Otherwise, Fah wouldn’t let me off the hook.
You can drive, right?
Drive for me. I’m sleepy.
What are you listening to?
Want to change it?
No need.
It’s just kinda surprising.
Didn’t think anyone still listened to this.
Where are we now?
We’re lost.
Huh?
What the hell?
Shit, just make a U-turn up ahead.
Hey!
Why the hell are you driving so damn slow?
Dude, you’re going 40.
Since I was born, I’ve never driven 40 before.
Switch with me. I’ll drive.
No.
Is it true med students don’t get any sleep?
Not really.
At least I get three hours.
Three hours? Are you insane?
I’d rather die, seriously.
Exams are over.
I’ll catch up on sleep.
No way, you idiot!
Ow!
Did I just blink or what the hell was that?
Sorry.
I forgot to return it.
Why are you up so early?
I haven’t slept yet.
Alright, I’m off.
Hey.
Wait.
Are you gonna tell Kram yourself, or should I talk to him?
Talk to him for me.
Yeah.
Are you serious?
Dao wants to talk to me?
Yeah.
If you’re coming, come quick.
I’ve got unfinished business with him during the break.
Your ex-husband’s coming back.
Why are you here?
Well?
I’m here to do my job.
Are you still playing guard dog?
Get out.
I asked him to come.
You.
If you’ve got something to say, say it. I’m going to bed.
Dao.
How have you been?
I’m good.
And you?
Not so great.
Dao.
I…
I’m sorry.
For everything.
For what?
Huh?
What are you apologizing for?
Say it.
When I first pursued you,
it was because
I made a bet with my friends.
We said
you’re very private
and probably hard to win over.
Whoever succeeded first
would get the money.
How much?
5,000.
5,000 baht.
Couldn’t you earn it yourself?
Is there anything else I should know?
But when we were together,
my feelings for you were real.
Then why did you cheat on me?
Dao.
Say it all.
Is there anything else I should know?
Well…
When I…
was dating you,
I…
was seeing someone else.
I lied to you and took your money to gamble on football.
I secretly sold your photos.
I slept with your friend.
I lied to you countless times.
Even though you were so good to me.
I’m sorry, Dao.
- Let’s start over.
- You’ve got some nerve, asshole.
Wait—do you even realize how fucked up you are?
You’re seriously messed up.
You know I’m a terrible person already, right?
But you’re on a whole different level of fucked up.
You’re absolutely disgusting.
You bastard.
I get it.
Why rub it in?
Next time, pick a better husband.
Do you remember when you first courted me?
You picked me up and dropped me off every day.
When it rained, you gave me your shirt.
In the mornings, you bought me grilled pork.
In the evenings, you took me to tutoring.
When I finished class,
you waited to take me home.
I decided to love you
because no one had ever done that for me before.
I liked you.
I liked your kindness.
But all this time,
you never really loved me, did you?
No, I did love you, Dao.
- But back then, it was—
- Don’t call that love.
It’s disgusting.
Oops.
Did you come back because you felt guilty?
Should I forgive someone who feels remorse?
I’m not that kind-hearted.
Try using your brain for once.
Dao—
So disappear from my life.
I don’t even have an “it’s okay” for you.
Not even that.
-Wait, Dao.
-That’s enough, man.
If that were me, I’d be crushed already.
Where have you been?
You’ve got Khun John with you now.
Michael doesn’t need an imaginary friend anymore.
So why show up now?
To congratulate you.
Michael,
you’ve finally unlocked what was in your heart.
From now on, you can stop thinking about him.
I guess so.
You can be happy now.
Honestly,
I was prepared.
I knew I’d get completely chewed out.
Especially after seeing his face like that.
It just confirmed
that he doesn’t love me anymore.
I really…
don’t deserve forgiveness.
I’ll just have to live with the guilt.
Why do I have to sit here listening to your bullshit?
I’ve got no one here, you know.
And I have to fly back soon.
Alright, fine.
Go on, say it.
When he cursed me out,
do you think he felt better?
Probably a bit.
Otherwise he’d keep going.
If that’s true, that’s good.
At least he got to vent some of his anger at me.
Let me ask you something.
How’s Dao doing here?
How would I know?
Aren’t you close?
Close for what?
I thought you liked Dao, so you helped him and all that.
What the hell?
We just had some kind of agreement, that’s all.
I…
I’m the bastard who made Dao lose faith in love.
I need to pee.
I can’t hold it.
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
Damn it, that’s my car!
There’s a car right next to it—why mine?!
You idiot!
-Hey, sorry, Thit! Sorry, sorry!
-You asshole!
-Sorry, Thit!
Shit!
I’ve taken care of it.
What’s up?
I’m heading out.
Flight’s this afternoon, asshole.
I need to drop Khajornsak off at Maew first.
Huh?
Khajornsak is the cat.
Then… what about Maew?
P’Tonfah’s boyfriend.
Huh?
I’m leaving the cat with P’Tonfah’s boyfriend.
Oh.
Yeah.
Give me a sec.
Ten minutes.
Hey.
Yeah?
Dao.
Thanks, man.
For coming to help.
Mm.
It’s nothing.
What’s this guy’s name?
Khajornsak.
Or you can call him Khun John for short.
What kind of cat is named Khajornsak?
Shit.
North said you keep a snake too?
Yeah.
Are you scared?
I’ll go play with it sometime.
Mm.
And who are you leaving it with?
Direk.
He’s old already. Might as well stay home and babysit his grandkid.
What did your dad say?
Direk?
He didn’t say anything.
I think Direk has come to terms with it.
I’m the only one
who still can’t accept it.
If you’re still around,
come visit our son sometimes.
He misses you so much, you know.
Is it good?
Hello, Khun John.
So cute.
Be good, okay? No being naughty, Khun John.
Please take care of him.
Hey.
Yeah?
Take good care of him.
Me?
Yeah, you.
You asked him to help you.
So you better take good care of him, got it?
Hey.
He went all the way across the world to help you.
Has he ever complained
or shown any sign of being upset?
Never.
Phoon once told me
that talking to spirits like that
drains his life energy.
So
just take good care of him.
That shouldn’t be too much for you.
Yeah, yeah, I know, Fah.
Stop nagging.
Look at how you act.
- Have a safe trip, man.
- Safe travels.
Please take care of Khun John.
Mm.
Don’t worry.
Dao, take good care of yourself too.
Eat your meals on time.
Have a safe flight.
Yeah.
Nong Dao.
Have a safe trip.
Thank you.
We should go now.
Going with Arthit, just the two of them.
I'm starting to worry about Dao.
No need to worry.
Even he look quiet
but he’s a fighter.
Dao is
really strong.
Just like Phoon now.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
It’s just a sneeze.
Don’t get sick while you’re with me.
Or Fah’s gonna chew me out again.
He’ll say I didn’t take care of you.
Hey.
Do you have another one?
Do you have another pair of earphones?
I forgot to bring mine.
Hey.
Nope.
Then—
- Can I borrow one side?
- No.
You’re so heartless.
Your playlist’s really good.
Share it with me.
Mm.
I’ll share it.
Which one do you want?
All of them.
What are you drawing?
A scene from a novel.
That’s really nice.
You can hire me.
You’re good at selling yourself.
A little.
Emma, do you like to painting?
I do.
How about you, Dylan? What do you like?
I like music.
Then when you grow up, you will be an amazing musician.
No.
When I grow up, I’m going to be a doctor.
Why so?
So I can treat you.
Mom.
I’m home.
Your house is so tidy.
Direk always has someone clean it.
Even if we only come once a year.
You and your dad?
Mm.
We come back around Christmas.
There’s a guest room at my place.
You can sleep there.
Let’s go inside.
Hey, hey.
You don’t eat the skin?
No.
Seriously?
Why?
I don’t like it.
It’s hard.
It pokes my gums.
No way.
You’re disrespecting fried chicken.
They worked so hard to make it crispy. You can’t do that. That ruins the whole system.
No, no—give it here. I’ll eat it.
Here.
The meat.
Give it to me.
It feels so nice here.
My mom liked this spot.
I can tell.
She liked drawing too.
Really?
Mm.
You said you take drawing commissions, right?
Then I’m hiring you.
To do what?
Finish the drawings my mom left unfinished.
These ones.
She drew them when she was very sick.
But she passed away before she could finish them.
She’d probably like this spot.
It feels
warm.
Is my mom still here?
I’m not sure.
It feels like when we were at your dad’s house.
But right now,
I don’t see her.
Is it really okay for me to finish these?
I think if someone finishes them,
adds beautiful colors,
my mom would be happy.
Okay.
Hey.
Hmm?
In case...
Just in case.
If my mom were really still here,
is there a way for me to see her?
Like how Meen can see Do?
Do you think
humans and ghosts can really live together?
Technically, they shouldn’t.
Then why can Do and Meen stay together?
Because Do still has unfinished business.
And Meen is still holding on.
Time to stop dreaming.
I used up all the courage I had to make this decision.
I love you, Meen.
So much.
But.
I have to go.
Do.
Where are you, Do?
Grandma once told me that the world of the living and the world of the dead can intersect.
But in the end, we learn that love means letting go.
Letting the dead rest in peace.
And letting the living move on with their lives.
Yeah? What’s up?
Go on.
Direk.
What if I don’t find her?
I’m just...
I really pushed it, Direk.
I came all this way.
There’s nothing you can do. You know that.
And going that far—
wasn’t it so you could be sure and finally let go?
Have you really let go, Direk?
Yeah.
How did you do it?
Because I have you.
That’s unexpectedly touching.
Hey, I was about to get emotional and you ruined it.
Go on.
Let me get so moved I cry, okay?
You’re such a pain. I’m not talking anymore.
If you can mess with me like this,
that means you’re doing better, right?
A little.
That’s good.
Alright then.
I’ve gotta get back to work. Gotta earn money to feed the buffalo.
Yeah, I’ll call you later.
That’s it.
Oh.
I was about to come up and see you.
Got carried away with the drawing.
But it’s not finished yet.
No rush.
Take your time.
This chair—
my mom died right there.
Can I sit?
Yeah.
What’s wrong?
This place—
is where she passed away.
Emma.
Wake up.
Mom, please wake up.
Mom.
Please wake up.
Direk.
Dad.
It was Christmas, right?
Your mom—
she was very happy.
She wasn’t in any pain at all.
She must have made peace with her death.
But she probably regretted—
that she wouldn’t get to watch you grow up anymore.
She wasn’t in pain at all.
It’s just that—
she’s not here anymore.
She’s at peace now.
There’s still love left here.
I can feel it.
There’s no pain or sadness at all.
But she’s not here anymore.
Not here—
or anywhere.
She’s gone.
Hey, do you have a crush on someone?
Are you crazy? I don’t like anyone.
Hey—
Idiot. That’s suspicious as hell.
Can you help me out? P’Arthit lost his keycard.