KING THE LAND
Wild geese live for over 100 years
and never abandon their partner
once they are mated.
They are a symbol of eternal love.
ONE HOUR AGO
What do you think? Don't I look great?
Sure, you do.
But less than the man of the hour.
Let's see.
There it is.
Looks great.
- I'll take this.
- This?
Yes, this one.
That obviously looks very humble.
It suits you perfectly.
You have no idea.
The Korean people were known
as the white-clad folks.
So for our biggest celebrations,
the most honored person
would put on a white garment
and carry out the most important job.
Of course, that'll be me today.
I'm the most noble and honored man here!
Yes, I know that.
So put that on and do your thing.
I'll put this on and do my thing.
Give me those clothes.
I can't put you up
for something as important as this.
You can't handle it.
The clothes are mine,
and that job is mine too.
Hand it to me. That's an order!
I'm the most noble and honored.
Sa-rang.
The bride and groom
will share their wedding drinks.
Bride and groom,
hold up your cups respectfully
and have your drinks.
What?
Hey!
You're here.
Why are you there?
You wanted to switch. You gave the order.
You said this was important!
How dare you deceive me?
There's nothing more important
than sweeping the yards
to make the place clean
for our guests on this special day.
- You!
- What?
- You, come here!
- No, you come.
I'm coming!
- Okay.
- Hey!
Get back here. Stop!
What are you going to do?
Sa-rang, you're beautiful.
- You.
- Hey.
- Get back here.
- You can come back later.
How dare you deceive me?
Hey!
You!
EPISODE 8
Why did you agree to something
you didn't want to do?
I'm here on behalf of the hotel.
I couldn't allow any damage to it
because of my personal wants.
It wasn't easy to get this contract.
I still didn't like it.
- What do you mean?
- You and him doing that.
I didn't want to see it.
Wait, are you jealous?
Why would I be?
Only losers
with zero confidence get jealous.
Which means
that's far from something I would do.
- Then why?
- Just because.
I didn't like seeing you with another man.
That's called jealousy.
It wasn't.
Do you know what he's like?
He's probably dated well over 100 women.
- He's probably married too.
- Wow.
Two, three… no, four times.
Wow, really?
You can't be with other guys,
but especially not him.
Never. Not at all.
Okay.
Then let's say it wasn't jealousy.
But something like jealousy.
It wasn't.
I wasn't jealous.
Yes, that's what I said.
Anyway,
you acted very wisely today.
I was worried
everything was going to fall through.
I'm here on behalf of the hotel.
I may be a jerk who only does as I please,
but work is still work.
Since when?
From now on.
Why?
I want to protect something.
I'll protect it at all costs.
And to do that,
I'll build up my power.
Are you going to work out?
No, I already look great.
- Oh my.
- Why should I?
Where do you find such confidence?
I was
only sharing facts.
I truly apologize for not realizing that.
Why are you staring at me like that?
Because I love it.
What?
Love.
I'm saying I love everything.
Well, the weather
and the wind.
The weather.
Yes, the weather is wonderful today.
What great weather.
Hey!
How dare you ruin my sacred wedding?
You made a fool out of my love!
Love?
Love, my foot.
You said you've dated
over 100 women until now.
And you were married twice.
Or was it thrice?
It's not a crime to be popular.
Though someone as unpopular as you
would never know.
I'm popular enough.
I just chose not to date people.
A woman-chaser like you
can't even comprehend how popular I am.
You're quite proud for a penniless pauper.
- How much do you have?
- A whole lot.
Excuse me.
If you two are going to fight,
I'm going home.
We aren't fighting, Sa-rang.
We aren't. We're just warning each other.
I'm warning you.
You're banned from being
within a 100 m radius of Ms. Cheon.
Got it? Go.
Did you forget about the contract?
I'm the one who gives orders.
Get rid of him!
What? Get rid of me?
- Yes, you.
- You think that's possible?
You… Oh.
- Get rid of me?
- Yes.
Go quickly.
You can't get rid of me!
Let go! Wait, you're really doing this.
Man, I'm walking on air.
Finally.
It's the two of us.
Yes.
Let's take a walk, Sa-rang.
All right.
Isn't it tough
to wait on guests for a living?
Of course it's tough.
It's not always easy
to serve every guest with a smile.
I'll give you a hotel.
Pardon?
I have lots.
You can choose whichever one you like.
Then you won't have to live
such a tough life.
It's all right, really.
It may be tough, but I still love my job.
It'll be even better if you own a hotel.
What I want to do
isn't business management.
I want to provide a happy day
for every guest we have.
It's a special thing
to present happiness to someone.
And it's not something just anyone can do.
You're such a wonderful woman.
I knew it.
I have a good eye for people.
I must have a party!
Party time!
Sure.
Go inside.
I had a wonderful day thanks to you.
Sa-rang, see you tomorrow.
Yes, Your Highness.
Don't you think that smile was too big?
It's finally over.
Great work today, Mr. Gu.
Great work.
Put these on.
I'm all right.
You dragged those around all day
without a break.
Don't you feel bad for your feet?
Show some kindness and let them rest.
You're acting like
you did something wrong.
What if someone sees me?
No one will, so calm down.
What are you doing?
You can sleep here tonight.
Sleep here?
Great work escorting that headache
and working overtime
on behalf of our hotel.
He may be our VIP guest,
but you're our VVIP employee.
You deserve to stay here tonight.
Don't turn it down.
I won't. Thank you.
You must be hungry.
Order some room service.
Eat whatever you want
and rest up.
This is an employee benefit.
Okay.
Good night.
Mr. Gu.
I told you to order room service,
but you choose instant noodles?
The best late-night snack
is instant noodles.
You don't know, do you?
What do you take me for?
Of course I do.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
In that case,
I choose this.
To think we came all the way
to the Han River for raw instant noodles.
You really don't know a thing.
If you're at the Han River,
you've got to have this one.
Read this. "The original cup noodles."
Is it that good?
I think
I simply must
get that machine in my room.
Come on.
Then it wouldn't taste like this.
It only tastes this good
when you throw in this soft river breeze
and that dazzling night view.
That's key.
At times, I come here
for instant noodles and beer after work.
It tastes like heaven.
Hey.
You kept this awesome attraction
all to yourself?
You're more selfish than I thought.
Do you have to criticize me that much
over some instant noodles?
"Some instant noodles"?
These are the best instant noodles
I've ever had.
They're so good.
I'm glad.
In that case…
I rarely share this secret with others.
The time is now.
One dumpling.
- On top.
- Yes.
Isn't it good?
This place makes great dumplings.
I never got to enjoy such treats in life.
I lived in vain.
Anyway.
Is there a good timing for beer too?
- Of course there is.
- When is it?
- Now!
- Now?
- Now! Hurry.
- Now.
- I was right, wasn't I?
Nice timing.
- You're home.
- Dad!
What's going on?
- Did you come early to play with me?
- I'm…
too tired to play.
- Go play with Mom.
- I knew it.
You would never play with me.
Cho-rong, why don't you show him
the new dance you learned today?
I'm the best dancer in my class.
Later. I'm tired.
Where's dinner? I'm hungry.
Should the three of us eat out?
Or should we order something?
I want short ribs or fried chicken.
- Should we?
- I'm sick of eating out.
Let's just eat whatever we have.
Honey, can you take out the trash?
Honey?
- Dad.
- Yes?
Where's your shame?
If Mom cooked for you,
shouldn't you at least take the trash out?
But I ate her food enthusiastically.
Do you know how hard that is?
It must be one tough job.
When I grow up,
I'll never marry a lazy bum like you.
What?
You used to say I was the coolest.
I didn't know any better
because I was too young.
What?
That was ages ago.
You're all grown up. All grown.
First floor. Going down.
Doors closing.
Did you sleep well?
Yes, thanks to you.
How do you want your breakfast?
What time is it?
Eight o'clock.
My shift begins at 3:00 p.m. today,
so may I sleep a little more?
I'm sorry.
I thought your shift began earlier.
All right. Go to sleep.
Okay. Thank you.
Yes?
I pushed your checkout time to 3 p.m.
- Thank you.
- Okay. See you later.
- Sleep tight.
- Okay.
What are you doing?
Oh no.
What do we do?
- Hide.
- What?
Hide.
What do you want?
I heard you checked in yesterday,
so I came by to see
if you found anything uncomfortable.
This unannounced visit is uncomfortable.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to take extra good care of you.
My checkout's at 3 p.m.
I asked to make sure I'm undisturbed
because I wanted to get a good rest.
Did you miss the memo?
I'm sorry.
But if you need anything
or find anything uncomfortable--
I don't need anything. Goodbye.
He's so cool.
That curt manner is his charm.
Hello, you've reached Manager Kim Su-mi.
His Highness is looking for me?
Yes, okay.
Oh my! What's happening?
Where are you?
You can come out now.
Is she gone?
It's not like you did anything wrong.
I didn't want to give the wrong idea.
Your behavior right now
will give people the wrong idea.
I said this was your employee benefit.
You just made me look odd too.
I'm completely awake now.
- I must go.
- You don't have to.
I told them not to disturb me.
No, I'm fine, really.
I had a good rest thanks to your kindness.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
I forgot.
You're not the type that just listens.
Nobody will come,
so don't mind them and sleep some more.
Okay?
- Good afternoon.
- Not for me.
This isn't even the first time.
Are you teasing me?
Were you my mortal enemy
in a previous life?
Why do I have to run such petty errands?
Why?
What's this?
Your Highness, this is a dress that meets
the dress code for tonight's party.
Make sure you attend the party in this.
Says who?
The prince!
Your prince!
This is from His Highness.
It's the outfit for tonight's party.
You must wear it.
He can be annoying in so many ways.
But he sent you a present as a friend.
You must be happy.
He's not a friend.
Stop it. I know you're glad.
Then allow me to open it.
See that?
Good grief.
He didn't have to…
That little…
Sa-rang.
I knew I had a good eye.
I knew it'd look good on you.
It's awkward to be in something like this.
I wanted you to see
the kind of outfit that suits you best.
I knew you'd look great
in an elegant garment like this.
I see.
Thank you.
Let us begin the party.
What are you doing?
And your outfit?
I'm volunteering.
All my butlers are dressed like that.
Relax and sit, Sa-rang.
Well,
how can I relax and sit
when I feel uncomfortable?
It's all right, ma'am.
Please relax and take a seat.
Allow me to serve the wine.
Shouldn't you tell us about it?
I prepared this extremely overpriced wine
befitting of your position, Your Highness.
Drink up
and help boost our sales numbers.
Does this hotel serve wine with that face?
What? Are you telling me
to drink this and die?
Take it however you like.
You can either drink it and die,
or die and drink it.
Let me prepare your food.
What's going on? Why is he serving us?
I put him up to it. For us.
But why?
You deserve only the best service.
Someone like the hotel's head manager
seemed to qualify,
so I got him.
Thank you very much,
but I'm still a staff member
of this hotel.
Look at yourself right now.
What suits you
isn't a uniform, but a dress.
Not a hotel, but my royal family.
Marry me.
Sorry?
This is an official proposal.
Will you marry me?
Wait, what are you…
Sa-rang,
my love.
No!
- Never.
- What are you doing?
Flat out no.
I object to this proposal.
Who do you think you are?
Me? I have the right to say this.
Because I'm…
Ms. Cheon is one of my employees,
and I'm her employer
who has a responsibility to protect her.
Not only that, you're a player,
and I can buy this too!
Anyway, no.
I won't play along with this joke anymore.
I'm off.
Let's go.
Give me the ring.
What?
You're accepting this?
It's a present for me.
Give it to me.
I've never seen such a pretty ring before.
Thank you for regarding me favorably.
I'll keep your kindness in my heart
and cherish it for a long time.
Wait, are you turning me down?
I'll just accept the thought.
It was a huge honor to serve
a gentleman like you, Your Highness.
I'll remember you for a very long time
as the most fabulous guest I've ever met.
Please visit us again
as our best guest in history.
We'll always serve you
joyfully and wholeheartedly.
This was the first time
I wasn't hurt after a rejection.
I was wrong.
You're unlike what I thought.
You're much more special and fabulous.
Your Highness, you're the one
who's special and fabulous.
Okay.
I'll back off this time.
Next time, I'll come back with a ring
that's much prettier and more expensive.
Don't turn me down then.
May we eat? I'm hungry.
With Mr. Gu, of course.
No, he's here as a server.
I don't want to dine with him.
But it's your last day.
Let's all enjoy supper.
Well, if that's what you want.
- Take a seat.
- Forget it. I don't want to eat.
Mr. Gu.
Hermès.
If you want it that badly,
then I'll join.
Sit down.
Serve before you sit.
Thank you.
- Do it for me too.
- You've got hands.
You're really annoying.
He has many girlfriends.
This is a present from me.
Why isn't it just us two?
I'll be back soon.
Don't start dating someone else
before I return,
Sa-rang.
You're always welcome here.
Hey, you should go. You're running late.
I had fun thanks to you.
This is your tip.
You're pretty stingy for a prince.
What is this?
Give me a blank check.
This is generous
considering your performance.
Be prepared as a guide next time.
Good grief.
Don't ever return.
I'm shutting the hotel down.
I'll return before then.
Don't miss me too much.
See you again, my friend.
What are you doing?
Come on. I don't need friends.
Me neither.
That makes you and I the same.
I'll be back.
My brother, Won.
Don't come back.
You two really are friends,
having fun until the last moment.
Friends? Hardly.
I hate guys like him.
May I ask you something?
Why did you do that?
You would never accept
an order to serve food.
And you dressed like a butler too.
Because I promised to show
a great performance
as a representative of this hotel
until the very last moment.
So? Did I do okay?
I hope I was worth training.
Yes.
You did a splendid job.
Anyway.
Why did you take a while
to answer him yesterday?
He proposed with sincerity,
so it wasn't good manners
to turn him down easily.
You shouldn't allow such punks leeway.
There's no need
to show him manners either.
Wait.
Did you consider
accepting his proposal even for a moment?
It's a secret.
There are no secrets between us.
Of course there are secrets between us.
You're about to make me really sad.
Will you be like this?
You really won't tell me?
It's a secret.
I mean…
Please excuse me.
Where are you going? I'm not done.
It's the busiest time of the day,
so I should go.
Please excuse me.
- It's a secret.
- What?
Where's the Grand Ballroom?
Please come this way.
A secret?
We're landing soon.
It's dangerous, so I'll wrap up.
No, I got it.
You can get ready for landing.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Dear passengers,
we are now arriving
at Incheon International Airport.
Please remain seated
until the aircraft makes a full stop
and the seatbelt sign turns off.
Thank you for flying with King Air.
Our flight crew
will always serve you
in safety and comfort.
My gosh!
Pyeong-hwa, what's going on?
I know we've never met, but may I come in?
Sure, come on in.
One second.
What happened?
I think she sprained her back.
Could you put ice on her?
After about 15 minutes,
you can put a pain relief patch on her.
Okay.
Don't worry. I'll take care of her.
Yes, thank you.
I'll introduce myself properly next time.
Okay.
I'll come by tomorrow.
Don't do anything today
and go right to bed, okay?
Okay. Thank you.
Good night.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Take care.
He's so attractive!
- Who's that? The guy from that time?
- My back!
My back.
I'll put a pain relief patch on you.
Goodness, you're such a fool.
It could've been much worse.
A promotion isn't worth getting hurt over.
It's not that I'm dying to get promoted.
It's my desperate struggle to survive.
If you struggle a few more times,
you'll go broke buying these patches.
Do you want to be a purser that badly?
It's not that I want to.
I really have to be one now.
But I don't think
it'll happen in this life.
What if this is your last life?
Don't just give up.
You even hurt your back working hard,
so keep it up until the end.
No matter how hard I try,
I can't even do half as much as others.
What do the others do?
Nobody works as hard as you.
A FEW HOURS AGO
I thought you wanted to become L1.
I guess you aren't desperate.
I'll work harder.
That's your problem.
Everyone works hard.
It's because you only take
standard procedures.
Other teams
carry the duty-free books around,
selling and even delivering
the items themselves.
They'll get in trouble if they're caught.
The company will go berserk.
Do you really think they don't know?
Pyeong-hwa.
There's no free lunch in this world.
Only those who are passionate enough
to put up with such danger
get promoted.
Don't be scared.
I'm just sharing an example.
To triumph in this fierce competition,
you need to show enough passion
to match what the others are doing.
Sa-rang.
Yes?
Are you free tomorrow evening?
SAMSAM SPA, HOT KILN SAUNA
Why do I get freckles only on my face,
not my feet?
They're never in the sun.
There's skin on the feet too.
But why would your soles get freckles?
They'd need to see the sun.
It's a shame we get freckles on our face.
Oh my.
You can get duty-free items
without going on a trip?
Yes, I'll personally deliver
items of your choosing.
Try a little harder.
Oh my, a door-to-door service?
That is quite amazing!
Oh my.
Is this that miraculous cream
that flattens out
every single wrinkle on you?
You're right.
You can give it a try.
Let's see.
My gosh.
My eye wrinkles are disappearing.
I feel ten years younger already.
Yes, your wrinkles
really disappeared in an instant.
Is this really only 59,900 won?
Is this not too cheap?
What's that?
Let me test it too.
Me too. Let me give it a try.
- Me first.
- Okay.
One second. Let me put it on you.
I was here first.
This is a limited edition
for in-flight duty-free services,
and a special promotion began
just this month.
I saw this a few times
at department stores,
but it was too tiny and expensive
for me to buy it.
This is my chance.
How many can I get? I'll take them all.
You can't take everything.
Don't be like that, young lady.
I can buy two of them.
No, I'll take them all.
How much can I get? Like 50?
You have made a very wonderful decision.
- You look so much younger.
- Really?
Yes, your wrinkles are gone.
- Already?
- Yes!
Mr. Gu, did you visit HR?
Why?
You couldn't find
an old personnel record, right?
He matched up every single file
with the hard copies since your visit
but found nothing and came to me crying.
He's begging you for the name.
Never mind.
Who is it? Who are you looking for?
It's fine.
Isn't it in our online database?
It was all digitized.
It wasn't on the server.
That's why I went for a hard copy.
Then the person
probably wasn't important here.
What?
If an employee's records
weren't kept in the files or the server,
it means they weren't important.
In a word,
a nobody.
What do you mean?
Those who are powerful
or important end up getting recorded.
I mean, some go down in history.
But for the rest of us,
it doesn't matter
if we disappear without a trace,
so their records get deleted.
I'm telling you for your sake.
Don't end up like your mom.
See?
Nobody remembers her.
Both you and me.
That's life for a loser.
No one in this world is a nobody.
Come on in.
I expected the prince to be fussy,
but he was rather friendly and polite.
He also promised me he'd have
all of his guests stay here from now on.
I knew you'd make this happen.
Thank you.
Invite Prince Samir
to our 100th anniversary.
Yes, Father.
I'd like to take charge
of the 100th-anniversary event.
What?
Do you know how important this is?
We only invite the very elite
among our VIP guests.
You can't handle that yet.
Know your stuff before you speak.
It's King Hotel's biggest event,
so it must be held at King the Land.
You must've had a tough time
managing everything alone.
You can leave it to me now.
Yes, you finally came to your senses.
Okay, you can take charge.
Father.
Won can't handle this yet.
Seeing how well he handled Prince Samir,
I think we can rely on him.
Hwa-ran, have faith in him
and let him try this.
You can do it, right?
- Yes.
- Great.
- Let's eat.
- Okay.
Let's eat.
Are you really starting something with me?
You said I'd have to
fight you for life here.
It's inevitable, so I'll try my best.
Do you think someone like you
has a chance against me?
I told you before
that someone like you
shouldn't own the company.
Since when did you care so much
about the company?
It's because you went too far.
If you placed an employee in danger
over some ginseng,
you should've at least sent help.
Or you could give the staff
the incentives they deserve
for bringing up sales.
What are you trying to do?
The employees are supposed to
earn their paychecks.
Why should we give them incentives
simply for doing their job?
- That sounds like you.
- Don't be snarky.
What are you betting in this fight?
I've put in everything.
I'm putting up my fight
with everything on the line.
I didn't want to fight.
But you keep getting me involved.
I keep seeing employees suffering
from unfair treatment.
I'm complicit if I stay put.
I'm going to try and protect the people
that you deem
as nobodies.
Who do you even think you are?
At the very least, I have a conscience.
So I'm better than you.
Let's have a good fight.
You know what?
Those who fight for others…
stand no chance against someone
who fights for themselves.
Good luck.
What's this?
Why are you there?
Let go of me. Let go.
Cheon Sa-rang.
No.
Let go of him.
Let me go!
No!
Hello, sir.
That's what you call being a nuisance.
It was a special request
from the head manager.
It may seem like a simple favor to you,
but for us,
it's an order that must be obeyed.
I'm sorry.
Did I keep you here late?
No, sir.
Even if it hadn't been you,
it's only natural for us to serve
every single guest with utmost care.
Please come by whenever you like.
I'll leave on time in the future.
Goodbye.
Tap on it and let it seep in.
That's nice.
Try it.
Hello?
May I see you?
Right now?
I'm busy right now.
- I'll see you next time.
- I'll go to you.
- You're going to come here?
- Yes.
I have something to say too.
- Is this important?
- Yes.
This isn't a place
to say something important.
I'll see you next time.
No, I have to see you now.
Where are you?
SAMSAM SPA, HOT KILN SAUNA
You found me all right.
- Hey.
- And you're in sauna attire too.
Why is everyone lounging around?
It's a sauna.
- Show me your arm.
- I know that.
So why is everyone lying here
instead of at their homes?
That's what people do here.
You have to wear it like this
not to lose it.
What did you have to say?
Do I have to say it here?
I told you.
That's why I wanted to see you later.
- Let's go outside.
- No.
My friends are here.
- Your friends?
- Oh my, Mr. No!
- What brings you here?
- Hey.
You should go.
It'll be a pain if you stay.
Hurry and go.
I wanted you as my wingman,
but you were an awful actor.
I'm doing so well.
Everything is sold out thanks to me.
Hey, I'm the one who did everything.
You need to act naturally to draw a crowd.
Mr. No, try one.
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Anyway,
wasn't I a good actor?
You were totally awful. So rigid.
You need to do better to draw people.
Try to be more natural.
Exactly. I said your role is important.
I won't help if you give me a hard time.
Let's go.
Did you skip dinner?
Is it your first time trying these?
I can't believe
you've never had these before.
Try this too. Here.
Thank you.
By the way, what's with these?
They don't seem like regular eggs.
- Let's go.
- Aren't they good?
They were roasted on a stone plate.
Go on. You can have these.
Goodness, thank you.
Hey, wait.
Are you here to eat eggs or to see me?
How could I leave before finishing these
when she kindly gave them to me?
This is quite delicious.
Wait.
How about Mr. No instead of Sa-rang?
Me?
The more the merrier, right?
- I say yes.
- Why won't you ask me?
Come on, we're all family.
Give her a hand.
Just be a wingman.
A wingman? For what?
He's not good at it.
It's not a big deal.
All you have to do
is memorize a few lines.
Wait, you can get duty-free items at home
without traveling abroad?
Yes, and you get an extra 10% off too.
Wait, an extra 10% off
of the duty-free prices?
Yes.
On top of that, just for today,
if you purchase red ginseng extract,
you get one for free.
Then I'll take four ginseng extract sets
and three multivitamins.
And one eye cream for you, babe.
Get your stuff while they're on sale.
You won't find another chance like this.
Wait, red ginseng is half off?
Which brand?
Let me see it too.
It's this one.
Right now, it's buy one, get one free.
I see. Duty-free items.
Is anything else on sale?
Everything.
Cosmetics, liquor, accessories,
health supplements, everything.
Take your time
and let me know whatever you need.
- This one's good.
- It's cheaper than duty-free?
Of course.
I bought this from her last time,
and it was half the price
you see at department stores.
You can't travel abroad every single day,
so I think this is a great chance.
This is wonderful.
- My gosh.
- You want three? You won't even finish it.
- Just get two.
- These are half off.
- Two, two, two, so six packs.
- So cheap.
- Right?
- This is great!
You should probably get one each.
This is the cheapest one.
You wanted to get this.
- Yes, this is it.
- Really?
- Cheers!
You'll be able to reach the top
after a few more rounds.
Thank you.
I'll never forget your help.
Thank you, Mr. No.
Well, I'm good at everything.
You were really good.
You'll make a living
no matter where you go.
Anyway, do you have to go this far?
This is illegal.
It's not illegal.
It's not, right?
It's not illegal, right?
It is.
It is?
Only I didn't know?
I'm sorry.
I thought you knew.
This is really wrong.
Why are you taking it so far?
Don't be so harsh on her.
She must've been pressured into doing it.
And she's paying
for that extra discount too.
Why would you even spend your own money?
What if you get caught?
Because I have to.
Let's stop now.
Wrongdoing isn't for everyone.
People like us can't sleep in peace
after we do something wrong.
This darned conscience.
Why do we stay honest
when nobody gives us the credit?
Who cares if no one does?
We can give it to each other.
We all know that
Pyeong-hwa is a great worker.
Yes, our little bear is the best.
Stop it.
Who cares if it's just you two?
I'll give you the credit too.
What good is that, Mr. No?
But still, I'll give it to you.
I'll remember that the company
made you take things this far.
I won't forget it.
Thank you for saying that.
The ones who should know that
are those up high and not you, Mr. No.
You'll see a better day. I know it.
Let's make a toast for that day.
Sounds great. Cheers!
- Cheers!
It was wonderful to see you
try so hard today.
You were the best one.
Mr. No?
Do you want to play?
Mr. No.
You like Sa-rang, right?
Do you even need to ask?
It's so obvious.
No.
What? Really?
Then we'll lose you
and go with the Arab prince.
Why are you bringing him up right now?
He's a total player
with the worst personality.
He called Sa-rang last night.
He offered to fly us out to Dubai
on a private jet this summer.
That prince's generosity
is out of this world.
We're in for a treat thanks to Sa-rang.
He called?
Wait.
I clearly remember you two saying
I pass as Sa-rang's boyfriend.
You both said you'd take my side.
Me?
Yes.
To be exact, it was both of you,
including Pyeong-hwa.
Me too?
Yes, I clearly remember your approval.
My gosh. Is betrayal your specialty?
This isn't betrayal.
We're just being smart.
Dubai is calling us!
Hey, we're all one big family.
Let's not do this.
But you said you didn't like her.
So I think we're done here.
Wait.
Let us
chat some more
until we use up all these coins.
Please sit.
Tell her.
Tell her what?
How you feel.
"I like you. Go out with me."
How is that so difficult?
Do I have to say it in words?
It's the heart that counts.
She won't know if you don't say it.
If you keep beating around the bush,
you'll end up losing her.
Just ask her out.
Nice!
Isn't a cold treat nice
after sitting in the hot sauna?
Yes.
I get why people come here.
Thank you for today.
We're all one big family,
so we should help each other out.
You've changed a lot.
You used to be so scathing,
but you even make jokes now.
Are you free next weekend?
Why do you ask?
I want to talk about us.
About us?
Yes, about us.
Let's talk about us.
Okay.
WONSIKDANG
Welcome.
What's all this?
Are you Ms. Cheon Sa-rang?
- Yes.
- May I take your coat?
Thank you.
This way, please.
Our restaurant only serves
the chef's special.
Is that all right?
Yes, please serve me your best.
So who's the chef?
I'm today's chef,
Gu Won.
I see. Do you also cook?
It'd be faster if you asked
for the things I couldn't do.
I remember that
you couldn't even peel an onion.
Please forget that ancient history.
I received special training
from the best chef,
so please be rest assured.
You're quite passionate.
I will let go of my worries.
I'm solely in charge
of cooking and serving tonight.
So I ask
for your generous understanding
even if you face a bit of delay.
Sure, I'm okay with that.
Please take your time
and bring me delicious dishes.
We must have a drink on a night like this.
I made this sangria myself.
You made this yourself?
Yes.
Let me try it.
This is really good.
The appetizer.
How could I eat something this cute?
Then you can just stare at it.
No, I must try it.
Thank you.
- This is so good.
- Of course.
So you really can cook.
The problem is that
I'm good at everything.
Look forward to the next dish.
Okay.
Pasta.
Let me try this.
This is really good.
You should try it too.
Here.
- Pretty good.
- It's not just good.
It's really delicious.
Chef Gu.
This is excellent.
Thank you for noticing.
You made it all worthwhile.
Anyway, what's the occasion?
It's a very important day.
What is it?
A day to treat my VIP, Ms. Cheon.
It finally hit me when Samir was here.
I found out what it felt like
to humor and serve all kinds of jerks.
Then I realized you must've made
a lot of effort to be the best talent,
so I wanted to treat you with my best.
I knew it.
I felt like I was warmly welcomed
as soon as I entered.
I'm glad you felt that way.
So sincerity always works.
Thank you.
It's an honor to enjoy
such wonderful dishes.
Also,
I'd like to have
a serious conversation with you.
What's it about?
That's to come after dinner.
I'll tell you then.
The best part is yet to come,
so give me a minute.
What is it?
Do you want to know?
- May I have another glass?
- One second.
- I'll bring it over after this.
- I can get it.
You're kind of cool today.
I'm always cool.
Now.
This is the highlight of the meal.
Are you all right? Are you hurt?
No.
What will you do with all these?
As long as you aren't hurt,
it's all right.
Do I have…
permission?
KING THE LAND
- Are you upset?
- As if.
Don't be upset.
- That's not--
- Forget it.
You have feelings for Sa-rang, don't you?
You don't pass as Sa-rang's partner.
Be careful!
Sa-rang!
Mr. Gu!
I heard you finally declared war
against Ms. Gu.
I will take charge of the hotel.
Are you okay?
No.
I'll leave in a bit.
It's because I want to see you.
Mr. Gu!
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon