ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
A bracelet with my initials on it.
What does that mean?
What does a bracelet mean as a gift?
"BRACELET" SOUNDS LIKE "CHERISHED LOVE"
IT'S A GIFT FOR LOVERS
Love?
BEFORE GIVING THE BRACELET, LEARN OF THE RECIPIENT'S PREFERENCES
"From an elder,
it means forever caring."
Okay, I get it.
Here.
You're home.
Have you packed your things?
I haven't started packing.
Are you still not done packing?
I'll do it later.
Were you waiting for me to come home to pack for you?
No.
By the way, Mom and Dad.
Jiaxu will pick me up tomorrow morning
to go to the airport together.
We're on the same flight,
so we'll return to Yihe together.
What a coincidence.
Now you can sleep in tomorrow morning.
Okay, that works out.
-Then… -Our car is on restricted use tomorrow.
Yes, that's true.
Well, remember to call regularly
when you get back.
No, video call us when you arrive.
I know.
Video call, okay?
Good night. Good girl.
-Good night. -I'll miss you.
-Go and rest. -Okay.
-I'm sleepy. -Okay. Your dad drank a lot.
-Bye. -Okay, bye.
Sleep early, okay?
Bye.
NANWU TO YIHE, 9:50 TO 12:45
TICKET SUCCESSFULLY CANCELED
CONFIRM
NANWU TO YIHE, 08:20 TO 10:10
CONFIRM PAYMENT
PAYMENT FAILED
NANWU TO YIHE, NO MATCHING RESULTS FOUND
PURCHASE PLANE TICKETS
PROGRAMMERS OF THE DREAM GAMES
Guys, sorry to disturb you.
I have an important meeting
to attend in Yihe tomorrow.
I must take this flight back.
Can you guys
please click on this link to help me get a ticket?
Thank you.
SHARE WITH FRIENDS TO BOOK FASTER AS A VIP
NANWU TO YIHE, 8:20 TO 11:15
Good morning.
Jiaxu, did you not sleep well last night?
I had some work to deal with yesterday.
Your breakfast.
Thank you.
Where's the thing I gave you?
Do you not like it?
Let's go.
Jiaxu, did you not have breakfast?
No.
Have this then.
Thank you.
Will juice alone fill you up?
Yes.
Open your mouth.
Take this and eat it.
Wait.
Thank you.
We still have time before boarding.
Let's sit here and rest for a while.
Here.
Duan Jiaxu?
It's Yuan Lang. From high school!
-Yuan Lang. -Yes!
-It has been a while. -Yes, it has been.
Sit down.
How many years has it been now?
We had a class reunion recently.
Why didn't you come?
I was too busy with work at that time,
so I couldn't go.
I heard from Jiang Ying
that you're excelling at work and very busy.
You're earning quite a bit, right?
It's okay.
Is this your girlfriend?
No, my mistake.
I heard
that you and Jiang Ying are together.
Jiang Ying and I?
Who told you that?
Are you not?
I don't remember who told me.
I was mistaken.
Sorry about that.
I speak without thinking.
I was just spouting nonsense.
It's time for me to board.
I'll get going first.
See you. Come to the next reunion, okay?
See you.
So…
Who is Jiang Ying?
It's the woman we ran into during dinner
on New Year's Eve.
It's not that kind of relationship.
You also saw how she treated me.
How could I have anything to do with her?
Besides,
didn't I promise you before?
If I get a girlfriend,
I'll introduce her to you first.
But I remember there was another woman before.
I came to Yihe
when I was in high school.
You came to the airport
with her.
Did you think she was my girlfriend?
No.
I'm just
asking.
BOARDING PASS
So
he never forgot what he promised me back then.
He didn't lie to me.
I misunderstood him back then.
CHAPTER 14, CONNECTION
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL ANTICIPATION
Bye.
When did you arrive?
Just ten minutes earlier than you.
So what are you doing?
Did he see you back here?
So which identity did he use to see you back?
I'm not sure.
You're not sure? Why do you say that?
Did something happen?
He told me
he hasn't dated for the past few years.
Did he volunteer that information?
I guess so.
Then what else are you unsure about?
Weiwei,
do you remember what I told you before?
His way of speaking and personality
is sort of…
But I do think
that he has been a bit strange lately.
Strange?
He's even stranger than before.
I just feel that…
He makes me feel
that he might have feelings…
I might be overthinking it
or I am being too sensitive.
Do you think
-that he also likes you? -No.
Well, not really.
Then what is it?
Maybe just a tiny bit.
Gosh, you're such a coward.
How can you be afraid to even say it?
What is so bad about you?
I just think
that it's impossible between us.
I've always had this feeling
precisely because I like him.
So even when he does something normal,
I misinterpreted his intentions.
Sangsang.
It's not a recent development.
I'm familiar with this feeling.
Considering our relationship,
a change wouldn't be easy.
Sangsang, tell me.
What exactly are you worried about?
If he were a stranger
or someone who hadn't watched me grow up,
I would definitely pursue him
if I liked him this much.
Even if it means being ghosted
or being rejected,
I wouldn't be afraid.
But because this person watched me grow up,
could he really have such feelings for me?
How is he someone who watched you grow up?
At most,
he's a big brother that you met when you were a child.
I'll tell you what I think.
So you listen, okay?
I'm looking at this from an observer's perspective.
Now, both of you
are adults, right?
Even if he is four or five years older than you,
so what?
In today's society,
even an eight-year gap isn't strange,
let alone a five-year gap.
Besides,
none of us thinks it's strange.
Only you do.
What are you so conflicted about?
So what do you think I should do?
First of all,
stop thinking about the fact
that he's older than you.
Just interact with him
naturally.
Do you understand?
Interact naturally.
And secondly…
If he doesn't make a move, I don't.
But if he does, I strike first.
Got it?
Think about it carefully.
I need to unpack my things.
If he doesn't make a move, I don't.
But if he does,
I strike first.
How did you meet him?
We met while we hung out.
Where?
A bar.
When you were drunk, you told me
that you met him at a KTV.
Yes.
We met at a KTV.
It looks like there is no such person.
Could itreally be me?
Hello, Shenlan.
Call Qian Fei.
QIAN FEI
Hey, what's up?
I'm busy right now. What is it?
You're pretty smart.
The guy that the girl said she likes
is most likely me.
Right? I was right!
I knew it was you.
I knew it the moment you described him.
Since you're so clever, let me ask you.
How did you win your wife's heart?
Well, it's my charming personality.
Why? Are you going to chase her?
Just go ahead. She likes you, doesn't she?
Just directly confess to her.
No, I have to pursue her.
Mainly, my girl
has always felt
that I couldn't possibly like her.
So I have to be straightforward with her
to make her happier.
Your girl?
How is she your girl now?
Does she know
that you already know she likes you?
She doesn't know yet.
So I have to pretend that I don't know either.
I have to save her face.
As expected of you.
When do you plan to tell her?
Just tell me
how you won over your wife.
I'm busy right now, man.
Stop bothering me. Let's talk later, okay?
Don't forget.
Okay, bye.
DUAN JIAXU
The woman
that you saw at the airport before…
JIAXU
Sangsang!
Keep it down.
He is making his move!
What?
He is making his move.
Should I make mine too?
Yes.
-Now? What do I do? -Yes, now.
Answer the call first.
Answer it now.
-I should head out. -No, do it here. Right here.
Hurry, or else, he will hang up.
Hello?
What took you so long to answer?
Are you busy?
No.
What's going on?
I'll tell you later.
What day will you be free?
Why? What is it?
Nothing.
I just want to take you out to a meal.
A meal?
He's asking her out.
Can I?
Sure.
I still owe you a meal anyway.
What do you mean?
Are you saying
that you will take this meal I'll treat you to
as the one you owed me last time?
You'll get quite a good deal.
So when are you free?
Saturday. Wait, no.
How about Friday?
I have to go to the library to study
with my classmates this Saturday.
Okay.
Then
I'll send you the time
and the name of the restaurant.
Okay.
That's all then.
Bye.
What's going on?
Don't exclude the two of us.
Sang Zhi's crush
is asking her out!
-Really? -Crush?
Do you mean the one
whom you've had a secret crush on,
works at a game studio,
is very handsome,
and you threw up on?
Well, you don't have to mention
that I threw up on him.
Okay.
So he asked you out for a meal.
-That's great. -It's working out, Sangsang.
Your secret crush is about to turn real!
What do you mean?
It's not like we're strangers.
What about you and Jiang Ming?
You two--
Me and him?
We're just ordinary friends.
I already made it clear to him.
Sangsang sure is charming.
He suddenly asked you out.
Is he going to confess to you?
Confess?
That's not likely.
We're just having a meal, I think.
Why not?
-I'm sure-- -Wait a minute.
Since he has made his move,
it's definitely more than just a meal.
You have to be fully prepared.
-She's right. -Got it?
Do something about your hair and outfit.
MARCH 14TH, WEDNESDAY
HE NEVER FORGOT WHAT HE PROMISED ME BACK THEN
I'M THE ONE WHO MISUNDERSTOOD HIM
We did a couple of runs with the QA engineer.
The overall process of the Celestial Progression System
is already functional.
The response capacity of the NPCs
looks even more real than before.
However, the AI's generalization ability
is still not very strong.
Dawang, do you have any ideas?
Although we don't have beta testing yet,
considering the level of completeness,
I still have confidence in the Celestial Progression System.
What?
I'm just stating my opinion honestly, okay?
Besides,
there's still room for improvement.
We just need to add more language data
and expand our language database,
so that players can feel
that every character in our game world truly exists.
All right.
Then we'll expand our learning library
based on the players' profiles
and their discussion points.
Let's work hard
to make the AI more realistic and convincing.
Next month,
we'll invite players for a demo test.
We're just a few months away from launch.
Everyone, keep up the good work.
Thank you, guys. I'll get going too.
Thank you, Dawang. Bye.
Jiaxu
sure is a talented guy.
He looks especially handsome today.
What?
You look cool today, Jiaxu.
Work seriously.
He's here.
He's already here.
Are you ready to go?
I'll be right down.
Sangsang, it's your first date.
It's not a date.
It's just a meal.
-Right. -Sure, it's a meal.
You look pretty.
If I go,
will you guys feel lonely?
Not at all. Just go.
That's pretty.
Bye.
-Bye. -Bye.
-Be careful. -Have a fun date.
It feels like marrying off my daughter.
What's wrong?
You look pretty today.
Later, we'll go to the restaurant
we went to last time.
I'll also introduce someone to you.
Is someone else joining us?
You'll find out later.
Let's go.
Didn't I promise you before?
If I get a girlfriend,
I'll introduce her to you first.
If he has a girlfriend,
I shouldn't sit in the front passenger seat.
Do you take me for a chauffeur?
Buckle up.
He seems to be in a good mood today.
Is he really taking me to meet his girlfriend?
Over there.
Let me make the introductions.
This is Siyun,
the producer of A Dream of Jianghu and my superior.
This is Sang Zhi.
-Nice to meet you. -Nice to meet you.
Come and take a seat.
Sit.
I went with him
to the airport to pick you up before.
Do you still remember me?
Yes, I do.
I always hear Xiaoduan talk about you.
I heard you're studying at Yihe University.
Yes.
The last time I saw you,
you were still in high school.
Now you're so beautiful.
You must be hungry. Here.
Order what you want to eat.
Go ahead.
Siyun, have you ordered what you want?
Yes, I've ordered some.
See what you like to eat.
Jiaxu.
What do you want to eat?
Why don't you and Siyun order first?
I'm going to the restroom.
Okay.
Let's order these for now.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Last time,
I didn't have a chance to properly greet you
when I met you at the airport.
I'm sorry to have troubled you
at the airport at that time.
It was no trouble.
I really shouldn't have tagged along.
But I didn't think much of it.
I just wanted to help.
Xiaoduan had a mild fever that day.
I wanted to have my husband drive him,
but he had to meet a client at the last minute,
so I drove Jiaxu.
He wasn't feeling well that day,
so I got out of the car with him to find you.
Later, he even said
he was afraid you might feel uncomfortable
with a stranger around,
so he asked me to leave first.
That's why I left
without telling you.
No, it's okay.
At first, I thought
you were his relative's child
because he was very angry that day.
When you were crying in the restroom,
he was still talking about it.
The restroom is over there.
Go now.
We'll have a nice lunch later.
It's all right.
I remember
when I first met her.
She was wrestling with her brother
and could cry on a dime.
Her biggest worry in the past
was probably getting into trouble at school.
But just now,
when I saw her holding back tears,
my heart broke for her.
That's how young girls are.
They'll grow up eventually.
Don't be too worried.
So
that was what they were talking about.
I actually thought they were…
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Xiaoduan
is a great guy.
He's young and promising.
He's also good-looking.
The most important thing is that
since I've known him,
he has been single
and hasn't been involved in any messy relationship.
To be honest,
I'm really curious
what kind of woman he will end up with.
Here, have some more water.
Thank you.
What are you guys doing here?
We were going to have a team meal today.
This restaurant came up with good reviews,
so I brought everyone here.
Jiaxu, who is this?
-Who is she? -Who is she?
Introduce her to us.
A friend.
A friend?
-What kind of friend? -Tell us.
He said friend,
not sister.
In the past, he always called me his sister
or a relative's child.
Xiaoduan, make the introduction.
Come on.
My friend's name is Sang Zhi.
She's studying at a university here.
This is Li Xun,
our company's middleware consultant
and Siyun's husband.
I'm Li Xun.
Hello, Li Xun.
Hi, I'm Jia Yang,
Jiaxu's junior.
-Hello. -Hi, you can call me Xiaobai.
Hello, I'm Zhang Sen.
I'm also Jiaxu's junior.
Hello, I'm Xiaobo.
-Hello. -Hi, I'm Xiaomi.
-Hello. -Hi.
Nice to meet you.
I thought you were here to eat. Go on.
Wait. Why don't we eat together?
It's a company gathering.
Since you're his friend, join us.
Excuse me.
-Can we join the tables? -Come and help out.
Let's join the tables.
I'll help you.
Menu, please.
How about we eat elsewhere?
Can we?
Li Xun, Siyun, we have plans.
Enjoy. We'll leave first.
Are you not joining us?
You guys can go ahead.
Bye, Siyun. Bye, Li Xun.
-Are you leaving? -Why aren't you joining us?
-Jiaxu, why are you leaving? -Why did he leave?
What do you want to eat?
I'll make a reservation.
I'm not hungry yet.
Jiaxu.
Let's not come to this restaurant again.
I feel that we're not meant to eat here.
They just wanted to join in the fun.
They meant no harm.
I know.
I meant this restaurant.
All right.
Let's find somewhere else to eat.
Jiaxu.
Did you ask Siyun to explain it to me?
Did she tell you?
Yes, she told me.
Jiaxu.
Didn't you tell me
at the airport at the time?
I believed you.
Is that so?
I know
girls your age
always like to believe in some strange sixth sense.
And I don't want you to misunderstand.
Or else…
It will be troublesome later.
So where are we going later?
Well,
if you don't want to eat,
why don't we watch a movie?
The theatrical version of an anime came out recently.
I happen to know a theater nearby.
It should be ahead.
We still have 15 minutes.
We can take our time.
Jiaxu, can I order a drink?
Sure. What do you want?
-I'll have white peach oolong tea. -Welcome.
I want 30% sugar.
White peach oolong with 30% sugar.
Large and make it hot.
YU XIN
-How are things? -Anything else?
No, thank you.
Just one cup?
Yes. How much is it?
Scan the code here.
One hot white peach oolong with 30% sugar.
It's done.
I might
be back late.
-She's coming back late. -Late? What time exactly?
What's the situation?
Let's ask her.
Then
does that mean it's a success?
-Don't come back. -Seriously?
Something is up!
Was I right? Did he confess?
No.
We're going to watch a movie.
Is it the theatrical version of the anime?
-Didn't we agree to watch it together? -Who are you texting?
My roommates.
Hi, your white peach oolong is ready.
Is it for drinking now or takeaway?
-Now. -Drinking now.
Here.
-Thank you. -Thank you.
-Have a good day. -Can you throw this for me?
Sure.
Don't you want a drink?
I'll buy a bottle of water
at the theater later.
What's so funny?
As expected of you.
What about me?
Nothing much. It's just very healthy.
Healthy?
What's wrong?
Why is it milk tea?
Milk tea?
It really is milk tea.
Did they get the cups mixed up?
Don't tell me you're allergic to milk tea.
I'm allergic to milk.
But it's okay. I only took a small sip.
Do you feel any discomfort?
No.
Wait here for me.
I'll get you another drink.
Are you really okay?
I bought you tea.
Okay. Thank you.
What happened to your face?
A rash is breaking out.
Don't touch it with your hand.
I'll take you to the hospital.
No, I'll just buy some medicine.
Listen to me.
-Let's go. -Wait.
What about the movie?
We'll watch it next time.
Why did it have to be today?
-Thank you. -We couldn't even watch the movie.
How frustrating.
Here. Take the medicine.
It should make you feel better.
The doctor said to take two pills.
Siyun.
What a coincidence.
How so?
I happened to see a cake on my way in,
so I bought it for you.
What do you want?
Siyun.
Are you free this Friday?
I want to buy you a meal
and ask you for a favor.
What kind of favor?
Well, do you remember
the girl that you went with me to pick up
at the airport before?
Your relative's kid.
She might have misunderstood
that you're my girlfriend.
I want you to help me explain it to her.
Sure, no problem.
I'll find an opportunity
to talk to her over the meal.
By the way,
can you also tell her
that I haven't had a girlfriend for years?
Do I have to mention that too?
Okay.
Is there anything else?
That's all.
Can I leave after the meal?
Okay.
I won't be the third wheel.
-I'll get back to work. -Go on.
Thank you, Siyun.
One more thing.
What else do you want me to tell her?
When you say that I haven't been dating,
can you make it sound natural?
-It's just-- -Okay.
I don't need you to teach me.
Duan Jiaxu.
Why are you acting like an inexperienced young boy?