(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Aurora borealis is the light created
when Earth,
forever unable to reach the Sun,
draws in minute traces of solar plasma
through the power of its magnetic field.
Perhaps this brilliant, mesmerizing light
is nothing but a sad, momentary delusion.
The Earth is yearning to touch the Sun.
It believes that even a collision
with those tiny particles
means they have made a connection.
That night,
for the first time,
I desperately hoped my delusion
would become a reality.
But the Earth cannot touch the Sun,
and auroras do not appear
in the sky over Seoul.
Joo Ho-jin,
let's go back inside.
Or how about we stay
until the lights fade away.
No, let's not.
I really don't wanna see them disappear.
We saw them together, like I promised.
Isn't that enough?
It's almost gone.
Why are you still here?
I told you to get lost.
Are you scared because I threatened
to kill you earlier?
Uh, well, it was scary,
but I'm out here waiting
because I'm not sure what to be scared of.
Look, all you need to do
is act like you don't know anything.
Oh.
But I'm not a good liar.
The wedding is off,
and I don't want anyone to find out.
Ah. People will though.
Is there a problem here?
Huh? You started
this whole mess, Shin Ji-sun.
You're not scared of me at all.
You're just mocking me, aren't you?
I have great reflexes
since I used to be an athlete.
This phone still works.
Mm, you're getting a call.
You should take it.
It really was a mistake.
Did he cheat on you?
Seems like he's begging you
to take him back, but don't do it.
An affair is irredeemable.
It's a point of no return.
Hmm. Is that so?
If someone's cheating,
that's crossing a line, right?
Jin-suk.
I can't tie the knot with you.
I've been cheating.
So don't ever call me again.
We are done now.
You're the one?
You cheated?
I'm going to, here on out.
Cheat.
You can't get it open?
Old hotels in Europe are like this too.
The doors get stuck easily.
You… just kind of pull it. It'll work.
You must be tired.
The shoot was super long today.
Oh no, I'm getting puffy 'cause I'm tired.
I can see this shoot
was particularly tough.
Yep.
I was freezing,
and I didn't know what to say
because the aurora borealis
didn't show up.
So I started a fire and made some
roasted potatoes and some marshmallows.
It turned out pretty good, actually.
I still have a food baby
from all these potatoes.
Why didn't you split them with Hiro?
Was he acting up again?
It's not that.
Hiro's pretty careful about his diet
because he gains weight easily.
Nanami said that I shouldn't bring it up.
I see.
And she also explained why he's like that.
It's 'cause he's been allergic
to all sorts of things.
On top of suffering from dry eyes.
Also, I noticed his hands were cold
when I held them.
I thought it was just me.
You were holding hands?
Why won't this open?
So I'm gonna look out for him from now on.
Come on!
That's why I ate all the marshmallows
by myself and didn't share.
He seemed to be grateful
and gave me a smile.
He's called "Prince Charming."
Makes sense to call him that, I think,
'cause he has a cute smile, you know?
Ah, why won't this door open?
- Huh, it's really not opening?
- Ah, no, I got it.
Oh, and when he grins, he's got dimples.
Where?
It's right about here.
Would that be considered a dimple?
Dimples should be more visible than that.
Why won't this open?
Did someone break this door?
Oh, it worked!
Thank goodness!
I banged my head. Ouch.
Get some rest.
Thank you.
Oh.
Hiro says he likes japchae,
with plenty of mushrooms.
Could you teach me how to make that dish?
I don't know how.
- I thought you knew how to make it?
- I never made that dish before.
YouTube might have a recipe for it.
Yeah, look it up. Uh…
You should go in and get some rest
'cause you ate too…
too many marshmallows by yourself
and your face is puffy.
Who are you gonna cheat with, then?
Hmm,
could be any guy over 21. Anyone will do
as long as he's single, right?
For real? Anybody will do?
It's not like I wanna be
with someone I have feelings for.
Well, if you're not looking
for a man to start over with,
why do you wanna cheat so badly?
Once I really cheat,
I can return to Jin-suk.
It's a fine line.
It's gonna be over for good that way.
Hey, you know,
you shouldn't be doing this to yourself.
It's not my problem,
but still, this is messed up.
Is it? Should I ask someone out
that I already know?
That would be more dignified?
Ask somebody you know?
Wait a minute.
You don't mean Ho-jin by that, do you?
Do you?
Your mind can be a little lost right now,
but you're not that crazy, right?
He's not the right man for this.
He doesn't fit my criteria.
Your criteria?
'Cause I won't do it
with someone I could eventually like.
Or even love.
Or anyone I once had feelings for either.
I used to
like Joo Ho-jin.
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
Why aren't they opening the gate?
In-su, you talked to them earlier.
Were you able to figure it out?
I'm telling you, they said
we don't have a valid permit.
We're running out of time.
What should we do?
Ho-jin's on the line,
so let's figure out what's going on.
The Ministry of Tourism thought
we were supposed to shoot tomorrow.
- What?
- Oh shit!
Man, Producer Kim has done it again!
That idiot. This is great.
They said the head office is over there.
We should ask the people that work there.
We need to get this before the park opens
and people arrive. Should we ask them?
Yeah. Joo Ho-jin,
can you show her where it is?
Yeah.
Can you let the cast know?
- Yes, sir.
- Let's go.
Hey, can you please tell the cast
we've been delayed
for at least 30 minutes?
Sure. Got it.
Great.
I used to like Joo Ho-jin.
They're complicated.
What's happening over there?
She was a dying zombie
yesterday. I guess she's been revived.
Taking photos again?
You like photo?
Don't walk around by yourself.
There are bears in Canadian forests.
Bear.
Uh, word for…
F…
A panda! A panda!
Bear! Grr!
- What's that?
- Uh…
Chomp! It'll bite you like…
Oh, bear? A bear?
Yeah! Bear. Yeah, you get it!
Bear, dangerous.
That was nothing like a bear.
Plus, you're more dangerous than a bear.
You're a zombie.
Oh.
Why are your hands so red?
You sure get cold easily.
Aren't you freezing?
- What are you doing?
- Hand warmers are crucial.
You want mine?
Take 'em. They're warm.
I have a bunch of them on me.
I'll be okay.
I brought this.
Uh…
Sugar-free!
No sugar. No fat. No fat.
Candy.
- Ame?
- Yes, ame.
Oh, it's called "ame"
in Japanese, right?
We may not speak the same language,
but things that are sweet and keep us warm
are totally universal, right?
Nanami said that you glowed
when you were with me.
Since we're alone, I can check for sure.
Even without words,
one can sense these things.
Uh…
Wait, wait.
You wanna tell me something?
Talk to me through this.
Glowing.
Sparkles.
Sparkles? Sparkling?
What is?
So this is what was glowing.
Hmm?
What about my earrings? What?
Man, that was close!
Imagine if I'd asked her if she likes me.
What would've happened?
So there really are bears around here.
Chomp! It'll bite you like…
- One, two, three!
- Let's get a picture.
- Cheese!
- Come on one, two, three.
Ah, awesome!
My daughter's gonna be so happy.
- Thank you.
Oh, this feels good.
I have seen your movie, like, three times.
- My dad is a huge fan of yours too.
- Best day ever!
One, two, three.
Hi.
Oh, we're saved. Man, seriously! Phew.
- Let's get it done, then.
- Mu-hee!
Thank you so much.
- Do Ra-mi is the best!
- Thank you.
Oh. Mu-hee, stay here.
They'll pick you up.
Everyone's gonna drive through here.
- Let's go, Ho-jin.
- Yeah.
Can you… stay here?
You… you promised
to teach me Japanese earlier.
Ho-jin, don't leave yet, please.
Just stay here, all right?
Guys, I'll stay if that's okay.
- Mm.
- Okay, then. Hmm.
Ah!
Now you want me
to teach you some Japanese.
No, you said that…
Uh, you're scared of her,
so I'm here to protect you.
Thanks for your concern, but I…
I'm not uncomfortable
in this situation anymore.
I'm not some… ridiculous little boy
who's chasing a girl who doesn't love him.
So it's not that bad?
I thought you had trouble sleeping
and spent your nights awake, worrying.
Hey, wait.
- Is the sun blinding you?
- It is.
I'll shield you.
Careful.
- We'll walk this way.
- Okay.
I really like Canadians.
They're so warm and friendly.
Is it because they live in such a nice,
quiet place with lots of fresh air?
It only seems that way
because the park isn't open yet.
Usually, it's crowded and loud.
Have you already been here before, Ho-jin?
Yes, when I was a kid.
I used to live in the US with my family.
You head that way,
there's a small waterfall.
Oh! A waterfall?
It's not far. About a 20-minute walk?
- Do you wanna see it?
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Oh.
- Be careful.
What is it?
Sorry, I can't find it.
Maybe I went the wrong way.
You have no sense of direction.
How would you remember
a path you took as a kid?
If we keep going, we'll miss the shoot.
Let's go back.
Where are you going? Just follow me.
But… we came from over there.
Or is this it?
So majestic.
Is the waterfall over there?
Right by the mountain?
Uh, yeah.
I think so, I guess.
How about over there?
Where?
Oh, right by the mountain. That's it!
There! That's the waterfall!
I don't see it.
Just pretend you can see it.
Yeah, sure I can see it.
Look, all this water is coming
from the waterfall.
Wow, a waterfall!
If you insist any kind of falling water
constitutes a waterfall,
that would mean
that tap water is a waterfall too.
Yeah. That makes this a waterfall.
No one in the world
would call this a waterfall.
So that means
it's just a waterfall
for you and me, Ho-jin.
Fine, then. It's our waterfall.
Ah!
Wow!
Waterfall water feels so nice and cool.
Do Ra-mi made me do it.
She… she forced me.
I said be careful.
Do Ra-mi?
Thanks for all your hard work, everyone!
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah! Woo-hoo!
- Yeah!
- Oh, you're a natural at this!
You're good.
But here. You gotta do this. And then…
Smack!
Carefree like nothing happened.
Oh no.
Like this. Yeah, that's it.
Got it? Got it?
They don't even speak the same language.
Look at that.
Nigiru? What does that mean?
Hey, over here!
In this desperate moment of crisis,
I'd like to present to you
these powerful warriors of our production
coming to avenge us!
Welcome! Whoo!
Okay, let's resume the match!
Let's crush them!
- Yeah!
You did it!
How'd you manage that?
Joo Ho-jin!
You can do it!
Push that one away, and the game's over.
If ours stops in the middle, we win.
Carefully now.
- Mm.
- Go!
- Come on!
- Let's win this thing!
Yeah!
It's all right. It's all right.
Good job. It's okay.
Ah!
Good job, everybody! It was a close one!
Joo Ho-jin! Joo Ho-jin!
Joo Ho-jin!
Really?
Everyone!
Hiro-san says to commemorate
the crew's victory,
he's covering our drinks tonight!
Woo-hoo!
Hiro! Hiro! Hiro!
Hiro! Hiro! Hiro! Hiro!
Arigato!
You said he hated losing,
but he seems to be having a good time.
but you don't seem too mad about losing.
It was so much fun
that I didn't mind losing.
He said he had a lot of fun.
Me too.
See you again in Italy.
Mm. Goodbye.
Thank you for your hard work.
- After you.
- Thank you.
You didn't like Ms. Cha Mu-hee at first,
but while filming,
you seem to have changed your mind.
No.
I hate that zombie even more now.
Thanks to her, I've become a joke.
- Get out of here already.
- Joo Ho-jin!
- For God's sake.
Jeez.
Um, could I…
could I maybe ask you for another favor?
Joo Ho-jin, are you
looking to get married?
We've got a show planned.
A dating variety show,
and I think you… you're a great fit.
I, uh, would love to have you on it.
I really can't help you with that.
Oh, oh.
So it's a no, then.
Well, Shin Ji-sun spoke to me about it,
and she said you'd definitely say no.
You have someone
you've liked for a bit, right?
It's what she told me. Is that right?
Is, uh, that a "no"?
Oh! Oh my.
I should get that. It's ringing.
Excuse me.
Ah, I shouldn't have asked him.
Maybe you're just imagining
things. Or you dreamt it.
Hello?
Can I have your attention, please?
Uh, thanks to everyone who worked hard
during the shoot despite the cold weather.
Uh, I'll be leaving
before the rest of you,
um, since I have another gig in Seoul.
I'll see you again in Italy.
Thank you again!
You going back to the hotel?
Our call time isn't till 8:00 a.m.,
so you can stay out longer.
No, that's okay.
Okay. Wait right here. I'll get the car.
Why did the TV turn on?
Surprise. It's me.
You look pretty shocked.
You've been talking about me
with that guy.
Whatever. Get lost!
You're being shy.
You got to kiss him thanks to me.
Follow me.
I got something fun to show you.
Joo Ho-jin!
Now.
I'm gonna start by asking a few questions
Cha Mu-hee needs answered.
So Mu-hee is leaving tomorrow,
but you haven't messaged her?
It seems like you don't even care
if she's here or not.
Why… are you acting
as if that hot kiss never happened?
Just pretending you don't even care?
Ah, you said you'll never ask her out,
even if somebody threatened you,
is that right?
Are you going to keep that promise?
Shin Ji-sun stole your heart?
Oh, please stop.
Stop asking him stuff like that!
Come on, say it.
Does Cha Mu-hee
mean anything
to you
at all?
You better answer me, Ho-jin.
Don't make me wait too long.
You already know the answer.
Why are you acting like this?
Cha Mu-hee is a girl
who'll never be loved.
That was decided long ago.
Did you not get enough sleep last night?
No, I didn't. I'll sleep on the plane.
Here.
Can you see the Northern Lights in Korea?
No way. That would be insane.
Yeah, that'd be insane.
Cha Mu-hee, I'll drive you to the airport.
Get in.
Yeah.
The birds are flying
I heard it in the sky
Something they want to imply…
Mu-hee!
Where are you going?
Oh, man. What's going on?
Stuck in my throat
Round and round
I wanna speak out
But no one's there
Echoes of my voice
Answer alone
Round and round, my life just goes on
And now you blow a kiss
From the palm of your hand…
It's Cory Lane.
A Canadian singer.
A well-known singer-songwriter.
Oh, he's pretty famous, isn't he?
I feel like I've heard this song.
Don't know how to waltz…
Aren't you tired?
You must've been up late
drinking and stuff.
Not so much, actually.
I went back to the hotel.
I figured you had gone to bed early, so…
Oh.
I see. Right.
So don't let your heart run away…
I, um…
I slept very little.
I mean, I felt so restless.
How could you pressure me like that?
Then leave me hanging there
like nothing happened.
Is this about the gun?
Can't get you off my mind…
Uh, no, that's…
Yeah.
I mean,
it was as if you'd shot me in the heart.
How could you
shoot me like that and leave?
You know I'm terrible with directions,
and you just left me there.
I felt so helpless.
Yeah, sorry.
I did mention Do Ra-mi
was the one who did it.
I felt so bad, so I basically left
'cause I didn't know what to do.
I'm aware you're spontaneous
and you prefer
to sort things out afterwards
by pretending that… nothing happened.
I figured I'll drive you back,
so you don't fool me.
Just like you did before.
You didn't seem
to care about it at all though.
I couldn't sleep at all either.
Please don't go, Mu-hee.
I, uh… I'm trying to figure this all out.
I'm… the type of person
who needs time to figure things out
before making an important decision.
Which is why I'm willing to do
something I swore I'd never do.
I'm gonna talk to Ji-sun.
I don't want to be
a person who's playing people.
You know…
I've been losing sleep myself since then.
I won't pretend everything's all right
and just go on like…
nothing happened, you know?
You should take a nap
until we get to the airport.
I don't want to.
This Cory Lane is a good singer, isn't he?
Farewell to loneliness
Are you on a later flight as well, Ho-jin?
Do you have any plans?
Want to go sightseeing?
Yeong-a is buying lunch
for the whole curling team later.
Ah, you're the king of curling.
Then what are you doing after lunch?
I haven't decided.
Oh!
I'll call you
once I figure everything out.
Oh, you might already be
on the flight then.
Okay. I guess, let me call you later
when you land, okay?
Okay.
Don't forget to call.
So don't let your heart run away…
Farewell to loneliness…
The weather is great.
This song is perfect!
Can't get you off my mind
Your lovely, tender smile
Keeps running through my mind
How would you know
If I could be the one?
So please come closer
We're dancing on the clouds
Don't know how to
Waltz
Hey you.
Mu-hee, what are you doing?
I'm listening to music.
The song that was playing
in Joo Ho-jin's car.
It's by a singer he likes, so we decided
that it's gonna be our song.
Mu-hee, this isn't about the song.
Yong-u.
Don't worry. Please relax a little.
She's not getting married.
She spoke to her fiancé and called it off.
I was able to eavesdrop on the phone call
when she told him it's over.
Oh, really?
Joo Ho-jin has no idea.
He's about to find out.
I'm going to talk to Ji-sun.
It's hard to move on when the person
you like becomes single all of a sudden.
You think he likes you that much,
and this won't matter at all?
Do you?
Oh, then I was worried for no reason.
If he said he likes you that much,
there's nothing to worry about.
He won't change his mind.
I better go.
Honestly, I'm way too petrified to ask.
I have to go see him
before he talks to her.
Wait up!
Oh my God.
I think this could be our song
from now on. It's so gorgeous.
You'll think about me
whenever you hear it.
And I'll think about you.
There you are.
Are you here to buy records?
- Yeah.
- Mm.
I wanted to buy a new book.
Uh, do you have any recommendations
I can read on the plane?
Ji-sun.
I was wondering if you've got time
to talk in private.
I've been wanting to… talk to you.
Hmm. I know.
I need to talk to you too.
Let's do it.
- That looks good.
- I'm buying today.
- Soup for everyone.
- Oh!
No lobster. Keep it simple.
Come on, Ms. Cho.
- How about some steak?
- No way, get noodles instead.
There aren't any noodles on here though.
Oh. Mu-hee, I didn't know you were here.
Did you miss your flight?
Ho-jin was supposed to have lunch here?
- Where is he?
- Oh.
He didn't come with us.
He stopped at the bookstore instead.
You didn't know
I called off the wedding, Ho-jin?
So Jin-suk didn't call you?
I thought you were just
acting like you didn't know.
He hasn't called me. It's kind of weird.
He used to call me
whenever you guys were arguing.
But I thought, well,
perhaps the argument was so serious
that he didn't wanna tell me.
Jin-suk would bug you a lot
when we had problems we couldn't resolve.
I think I've relied on you a lot myself.
But you won't have to
smooth things over any longer.
I think it's better for you
to pretend you just don't know.
Is that what you wanted to discuss?
- Let's go have lunch now.
- Ji-sun.
Hmm?
What a beautiful movie.
I just love a happy ending.
But…
But what? You're just
a side character who got in the way?
Oh, or maybe a villain, right?
And the waterfall?
What about the song
we listened to in his car?
I mean, those moments
were a part of the story,
but that's not how it ends.
So maybe you should just move on.
You look pathetic otherwise.
If you get in between them,
this prearranged plot is gonna play
in your head over and over again.
Does this make you feel sad,
rejected, hurt?
I would just pretend
that nothing happened.
Just like when you were a child.
You're good at that.
Yeah. Do what you did back then.
Pretend you haven't seen it.
You don't know it's not true.
Run away!
- Oh my God! I'm so sorry.
- I'm okay. I'm okay.
- Are you okay?
- I said I'm okay.
Do you need something?
What's wrong?
Mu-hee is here.
Uh… Ho-jin!
I'm going crazy.
Cha Mu-hee!
What's going on?
Why aren't you on your way to Seoul?
I'll catch a later flight.
- You don't have to worry about me.
- Where's Yong-u?
He's waiting at the airport. I better go.
No, wait a sec, please.
Let's wipe this off, then we'll talk.
Shin Ji-sun isn't getting married.
You know that.
You talked to her.
Yes, I know.
Well, that's great.
What?
From now on, it'll be much easier for you.
No more running away and avoiding her.
I hope you can make it work now.
You missed your flight just to say that?
I'll head to the airport now.
You should just go back inside.
She's waiting.
You say whatever pops up in your mind
when you're frustrated.
Look, Mu-hee,
tell me what you really mean,
and don't run away.
Yeah. Do what you did back then.
Pretend you haven't seen it.
You don't know it's not true.
Run away!
Do you…
not like me at all, is that it?
That's it.
That's all I needed to tell you.
It hurt my pride,
so I figured I'll try harder.
I wanted to make you
fall for me just once.
But the wedding's off,
and her presence makes this ridiculous.
I missed the flight because I rushed over,
hoping to see you before she could.
Ho-jin…
were you upset I was leaving at all?
Were you?
I guess…
…I am too late.
Remember how Do Ra-mi manipulates me
like an online troll.
She keeps laughing at me.
And she says you'll never like me.
It's just not gonna happen.
That's why…
I'll try to deal with the fact
that I can't be with you, and move on.
It's too painful.
I can't do this to myself.
I'll just get my heart broken.
I don't know how to come back from that.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
I made you feel like a fool
the whole time. Forgive me.
I'm over it now.
You don't have to feel
sorry for me any longer.
I have cleared the air with Ji-sun.
I'm accepting it now.
Have you been able to figure things out?
I don't feel comfortable sharing that
considering our situation.
You've been so open about your feelings.
Crying, laughing, and everything.
I found that baffling, yet fascinating.
I was very worried about you,
but I tried to be open as well.
I tried to take care of you, Mu-hee,
but now I'm realizing
your emotions have been controlling me.
We should stop right here, Mu-hee.
It's like
when we met, and we were standing
at the crosswalk near the tracks.
You were standing
on the other side of the tracks…
and I ended up
telling you to go after her.
Goodbye.
So farewell, Joo Ho-jin.
Don't make it seem like
it didn't matter to you.
I've been wronged.
I was about to cross the street…
'cause I wanted to be with you.
So Do Ra-mi was wrong, and you were right?
I hope that's the case.
'Cause I'll still root for you.
Keep in mind
I'm never gonna leave your life
Ever long…
You'll be okay…
So stay close…
I was losing my mind.
I changed our booking to a flight
with a layover in Japan. We gotta hurry.
Mu-hee.
I…
I messed it all up.
Did he do it again?
Wow.
How dare he.
Who does he think he is?
So stay close…
So babe, I promise I won't ever leave
I didn't try to smooth things over
between you and Jin-suk
because you asked me to.
As long as your relationship
was still working,
I always felt safe
in my own world that I created.
But someone has entered my life
and turned it upside down all of a sudden.
I tried pushing her away,
out of fear that
my whole world would fall apart.
But she showed me the bright side of life.
Forever I'll never leave
I won't ever leave
Are you okay?
You haven't budged since earlier.
Are you unwell?
TWO WEEKS LATER, SOUTH KOREA
As you asked,
I didn't let the production team know
you came to South Korea.
As for Ms. Cha Mu-hee,
she'll be attending a concert
sponsored by an advertiser.
I know you didn't ask me to,
but I thought
I'd check her schedule just in case.
A concert?
She went to a concert
without a care in the world?
After what she did to me?
That woman. Is she an actress?
Huh?
I believe she is.
Ah, Mr. Kim,
I don't know if you've heard of her.
Do Ra-mi. It's…
Cha Mu-hee?
Ah, that's her name.
Oh, you know her?
- Sure, I do. Cha Mu-hee.
- Oh, really?
Oh.
This concert
will be interesting.
Good evening.
"Good evening."
"I am Roberto Vancini,
the Ambassador of Italy to South Korea."
"Thank you for attending this concert
that commemorates the 140th anniversary
of South Korean-Italian
diplomatic relations,
hosted by the Italian Embassy."
"I hope tonight's
musical journey will take you to Italy,
and I hope it will be a delightful
and memorable experience."
"Thank you very much."
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?