(Uilhan Brewery)
(1. Malting, 2. Malt milling, 3. Mash tun, 4. Hopping)
(Kim Se Jeong)
(Highly passionate, highly sensitive)
(Lee Jong Won)
(Shin Do Hyun)
(Baek Sung Chul)
(Uilhan Brewery)
(Naro Beer)
(Brewing Love)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Scenes with child actors and animals were filmed...)
(under production guidelines along with experts.)
This is my feeling. This feeling is mine.
My gosh.
- What's wrong? - It's nothing.
- Are you okay, Mr. Yoon? - Don't come near me.
- Wait. No! - I told you not to come near me.
Oh my goodness. Watch yourself.
Goodness, look at all these mosquitoes.
Hey, you're right.
Goodness.
You should head inside first.
Right, you should come inside soon as well.
No way.
Whatever.
Just go to sleep.
Hello, sir. I should've been the one to call you.
Sure. I'll come see you soon.
Of course, sir. Take care.
- Goodness. - Hey, good morning.
Well, I...
Who were you on the phone with that had you so polite?
Someone who helped me immensely when in need.
A few years back,
I once rescued his child.
Ever since then, he's been helping me...
in every way possible which I'm grateful for.
Hold on. How many people have you saved?
Who keeps count?
Then, is the person you rescued doing well?
I heard about an opportunity to study abroad,
but he hasn't mentioned his child ever since.
I can't even remember the face.
It'll take a while until the others get here.
- How about some coffee... - Hey, there. Good morning.
It's good to see you.
- Hello. - You're here.
Ms. Beautiful Bang, did you sleep well?
- Good morning. - Hey, there.
He's a snorer.
I see everyone's punctual.
(Jisang Liquor)
- Have a safe trip back. - Have a safe trip back.
- Bye. - Good job.
Wait.
There's dust.
- Really? - Yes.
- Thanks for that. - Right.
- We'll get going, then. - Sure.
Hold on. Do you have your phone?
Yes, right here. Do you all have yours?
You have your phones, right? Off we go.
Wait. Do you have your wallet too?
- Wallet. - Mine's in my purse.
We have everything, so shut the door already.
- Right. - Good.
- Watch your hands. - Sure.
Hold on. Your seat belt.
Got it. Done.
Right.
(Jisang Liquor)
She has left.
(Episode 6)
Shouldn't the boss be back by now?
Is he going to stay there all day?
The void one leaves behind is always this big.
With the oddball of a boss gone,
there's zero excitement.
Why are you asking for someone who isn't here?
Focus on those who are actually in your vicinity.
Catch.
No wonder I can't be bothered to work today.
What a poor working environment.
I didn't realize it until now,
but the boss' face kept me energized.
- Exactly. - Hey.
You're nowhere near handsome,
so work harder.
Why you... Don't you have mirrors at home?
You're one to talk when you're a newlywed.
- As if... - There's a difference.
Unbelievable. Does a man's good looks put food on the table?
If you like Mr. Yoon that much, why not keep him to yourselves?
Don't be ridiculous.
Our relationship is strictly business.
Hold on. Isn't that Mr. Yoon?
- What? - I think that's him.
Wait. Wifey!
Wifey, wait.
Goodness.
What? The people here...
have no respect for their village chief.
What's this?
Hey, over here.
The ladder's shaking. Someone hold it for me.
Darn. How can I get down from here?
- Mr. Yoon! - Boss!
Boss. What's going on?
We saw him go in.
- Mr. Yoon? - Boss!
Hey.
You should've told us that you were back.
Where have you been?
I told you I had a workshop to attend.
- I thought you had left for good. - Same here.
You must've had a great time with those from a major company.
Have you already forgotten about us?
- Exactly. - It was only an overnight trip.
One might think I was gone for 14 months.
Nothing happened, right?
Did something happen? A lot of things.
- It's a disaster. - Yes, it's a disaster.
- Exactly. - That's right.
What?
(Red Liquor, Liquor Street 5th Avenue)
(Jinjin Beer)
What's with all the business cards from wholesalers?
Those who had Naro Beer at the festival...
must've spread the word about how great it is.
We hit the jackpot.
My gosh. We've got so many business cards.
Could this be the beginning of us being a major company?
But...
I don't know if we can push out enough beer.
Don't be ridiculous.
We should push it all out.
We should even if we can't.
I'll self-medicate to meet the demands.
We should work day and night.
One shouldn't pass up on an opportunity like this.
It's an opportunity.
I guess you're right. Things might be tight,
but Jisang Liquor agreed not to compromise my schedule.
By coordinating the schedule, we'll be able to meet the demands.
- Nice. - All right.
But that means you'll be a lot busier.
- Don't you worry. - Don't you worry.
But will that major company let you have it your way?
If they tell you to work with their schedule,
that'll hurt the production here.
That will be a major crisis.
Hold on. The village chief...
has a point.
Don't be ridiculous.
Chae Yong Ju would never.
Don't you know what she's like?
She's right.
You have a tendency to put a damper on things.
What's your problem?
I was thinking of the worst-case scenario.
That being said,
- we should call Chae Yong Ju and... - That...
won't ever happen.
I trust her.
- Good. - Exactly.
(Brewing Love)
Is this actually true?
Isn't it obvious?
The article was released by Baekmok Liquor.
It was to make a fool out of us.
In My Name? That's Yoon Min Ju's beer.
Why is his name in the article?
The information must've leaked from our end,
and they're announcing a beef of a similar concept.
That's how Baekmok operates.
They play games by using the media.
What was being done while Baekmok was preparing to strike?
Marketing Team?
It's a good thing...
I'm always checking in on our competition.
If the chairman had seen this news article...
This leaves us with one option.
Our beer must hit the market first.
I heard a task force was put together...
to develop a new beer.
That's right, sir. My team's Ms. Chae has been...
- Ms. Chae, you answer me. - Go ahead.
Is it true it'll take six months to develop this new beer?
Yes, six months is the minimum...
- Make it three. - Sorry?
You get three months.
How was the first meeting?
Will the task force run well?
Ms. Chae has put everything on the line.
She even put together a workshop.
What's her deadline for the new beer?
- Six months, sir. - That long?
Ms. Chae isn't fooling around on this project.
What if this only puts the Marketing Team in the lead?
Report back to me on everything that goes on.
Our team must take credit for the new beer.
You know why I gave you this job.
That's too tight of a schedule.
He'll have to spend all of his time...
on the new beer to meet that deadline...
- which will hurt his business... - Can't you do it?
We'll do it. Why would you say otherwise?
Don't you know Ms. Chae? She'll make it happen.
She'll persuade Mr. Yoon and have him focus on our beer.
Right.
Wait.
How can we move up the deadline by three months...
just because we're afraid of Baekmok?
There's more reason...
to make a proper beer that'll guarantee us a win.
Getting the job done despite the obstacles...
proves one's worth.
This hurts the trust we built with Mr. Yoon.
If we move up the deadline by three months,
he won't have time to brew his own beer.
Chae Yong Ju, why would you care about his situation?
What can he do when he signed the contract?
- Sir. - Tell him to focus on our beer!
As if his own beer is of any importance.
His sales are next to nothing.
Don't play down his business like that.
Chae Yong Ju, it isn't like you to say...
something can't be done.
I know, but this is something I don't want to do.
Hold on. Was that sign always there?
I saw someone do it and thought I'd try it.
What about the reserve forces?
Here, mister. Have two.
Nice.
Unbelievable.
I can't believe one's too busy to even eat.
The deadline for our new beer went from 6 months to 3.
- What? - What?
Completing a 6-month project in 3...
will kill us.
I already have three jobs, so that isn't possible.
Who is it? Who ordered this?
Maybe it's my fault.
Focus.
Here, you must...
Only look at me
Hold on. Does CEO Yoon know?
Our hard work paid off.
We'll be busier from here on out, so I'll call Chan Hwi.
Put him on speaker.
It's been a while since we heard his voice.
- Toast. - That's right.
Hey, boss. Did you hear the news?
Jisang Liquor moved up the deadline.
What do we do?
This will affect the brewing of Naro Beer.
What did you decide? Will you shut it down for a while?
Shut it down? What do you mean by that?
See? What did I tell you?
I told you we couldn't trust Chae Yong Ju.
Unbelievable. I knew it!
What do we do, boss?
This is bad.
What on earth is happening?
Is what you said true?
No way.
Didn't you know?
Didn't Chae Yong Ju call you?
Let me call Ms. Chae.
Do it.
(CEO Yoon Min Ju)
She's not picking up.
What do we even know about her anyway?
We know nothing.
Do what you're told.
If you launch the new beer in three months,
the Busan office will be normalized that much sooner.
That's what you want the most.
I'll only say what I can promise you.
I will never do wrong by this place...
or your beer.
You do know, don't you?
Whether I'm being sincere or not.
So, I hope you see me...
as who I am.
Darn.
Yong Ju.
I heard the news.
If all goes well,
we might get to go back to Busan in three months.
Our family will be thrilled to hear this.
I know.
(Hwi's Toast)
Chae Yong Ju. Yong Ju, wait.
I think I made a huge mistake.
I told Mr. Yoon.
- Tell him what? - About the deadline being moved up.
I thought he already knew!
(CEO Yoon Min Ju, 5 missed calls)
Are you kidding me?
(CEO Yoon Min Ju)
(Branch Manager Nam of the Busan office)
Hello? Hey, Yong Ju.
I heard you were in Busan yesterday.
That's right, sir.
I was there for work and couldn't go to see you.
The boys told me how delighted they were to see you.
They may not say it out loud,
but you can imagine how they're screaming on the inside.
But they were thrilled to see you and said they would hang on tight.
I saw newfound energy in them.
Yong Ju, thank you.
We'll see each other again soon.
Sure. I'll be in touch.
We're going to do our best to hang in there.
So come back to us.
If all goes well,
we might get to go back to Busan in three months.
Our family will be thrilled to hear this.
If you launch the new beer in three months,
the Busan office will be normalized that much sooner.
That's what you want the most.
What I want the most?
How many times did I tell you?
There's a reason I was against her from the start.
She's going to ruin the business we have here.
- Those... - My gosh.
who get in the way of our beer,
I...
I won't let them get away with it.
To be honest, our lives depend on this.
Don't you agree?
Don't be like that.
We should hear her side of the story first.
That's right. She did a lot for us including helping us...
- at the beer festival. - Exactly.
She has a point.
Of course.
I don't feel at ease saying this about her.
It makes me uncomfortable too.
However, I'm furious with her...
and will take her by the collar if I see her face.
What can I do when I'm upset with her?
Is it just me?
That's true. You have a point as well.
Of course, it's upsetting.
I'll take her by the collar...
and teach her a lesson.
(Uilhan Brewery)
Oh, no. This is the worst timing for her.
I'm really sorry.
I take it back.
The promise I made you.
I don't think I can keep it. I'm sorry.
Is there anything else you have to say?
No.
Okay, then...
can you go now?
I have no right to feel hurt.
Boss.
Was someone here?
No.
We'll go home now.
My limbs ache. I can't do any more.
Good job, everyone.
So that you don't feel any pressure,
I'll find another solution.
We have a clear solution.
Dump Jisang Liquor.
Scrap the deal.
You must be upset at Chae Yong Ju too. Yes or no?
You can all go now. Clock off.
You're such a softie. It won't do you any good.
You should get angry about things like this...
and cut out everyone involved.
Yes. You're too nice.
See you. Good job.
- Bye. - See you.
- Darn you. - Yes.
He needs advice like that.
- Not from you. - He'll be upset.
(Uilhan Brewery)
I can't meet the demands at this speed.
Why wouldn't I be angry?
Of course, I'm angry.
But...
how could I show it?
I know just how much it took her...
to talk to me.
Is there anything else you have to say?
No.
How horrible she felt...
as she drove over to see me.
I could feel it.
You're still up?
You're going to drink?
You never drink at home...
because you say it's like bringing work home.
I just felt like it today.
Why would you feel like it?
You didn't drink at home...
even when your branch was about to get shut down.
Can I have just one drink?
Were you always...
so tense and alert even when you got drunk?
But then who could I blame?
It's my fault.
Granny.
I never...
had any doubts about my work.
I did everything I was told.
I never wondered why it had to be done.
On top of that, this time,
the livelihood of my Busan family is at stake.
Why would I hesitate?
Whatever it may be,
I have to do it.
I must make it happen.
But today...
Darn it.
Today...
I didn't want to do it.
I really didn't want to do it.
I made a promise to him...
and I didn't want to break it so easily.
- Did you just say, "him?" - Yes, "him."
He's not usually like that.
He never did that before,
but today, he took my wrist and pushed me away.
This is the first time you talked about someone else to me.
You should be friends.
I'd love us to be friends.
But...
It's done for.
Who is it?
Who is giving my Yong Ju such a hard time?
Give me a name. I'll break the person's back.
Who?
Hang on.
How did he know the launch date?
I never told him.
The only people who knew about the six-month deadline...
were the six TF Team members.
But the CEO knew about it already.
He gave the exact time frame of six to three months.
What is this?
You have no idea how evil their team is.
This is them inserting spies onto the enemy team.
There's a spy on our team.
(Jisang Liquor)
The new product will be out in three months,
so I came up with a new plan, budget, and strategy.
Can you check the budget for me?
You did this already?
By when will you be done?
Let me go over it and see how much revising it needs.
Okay.
Good morning.
Office.
(New Product Development Plan by Jisang Liquor and Uilhan Brewery)
Get in here and...
Ms. Chae, why are you...
Hello.
You seem to have many questions for the TF Team,
so I came by myself.
I'll sit down.
Ms. Bang, take a seat.
Shouldn't I be in the know about product development?
I should get updates.
Yes, of course. I should've reported to you.
I feel terrible...
that you had to go behind my back.
What? How dare you talk back at me like...
You should...
take on someone in your own league.
Don't use my people.
Ms. Bang works for me now.
As of this moment, you won't get a single update...
on what the TF Team's doing.
If you insist on being informed, come directly to me.
I'll kindly answer your questions.
You just made a big mistake.
I'll make up for that mistake...
with a successful product launch.
You're so darn confident.
I am. What could go wrong?
So many of you are so interested.
I promise I'll live up to your expectations.
Wish me luck.
Excuse me, then.
You're not coming, Ms. Bang?
We don't have enough hours in the day to work on our product.
Right.
Excuse me.
What the...
That lunatic...
Stay back after work. That's an order.
I will.
(Jisang Liquor)
Let's walk.
I fed all the information on our team...
to the director.
- I feel... - I hope you feel bad.
But the guys who made you do that should feel even worse.
So ditch the guilt and apologies.
We now have to make up for what happened.
You mean Mr. Yoon, right?
I feel bad that we broke the promise,
but the head office made a decision.
- We can apologize... - Exactly.
Anyone can go against their word...
and apologize and say they had no choice.
It's just one promise.
But I don't want to break it.
I hate it even more to end it this way.
To me, a promise...
is how I get close to someone.
Being on time.
Not going against my word.
Sticking to the basics...
is how I show my respect.
"I want you to like me,"
"and I want us to get close."
To me, it's a proposal of sorts.
I'd like us to become people who could make...
and keep many more promises in the future.
You're saying that while eating a popsicle?
Don't seniors say such things over a drink?
I didn't want to bare my heart while drunk.
Go home and rest up.
We should start damage control tomorrow.
Bye.
She calls this damage control?
- Oh, my gosh. - I feel drowsy.
I'm sleepy.
We must've been...
blinded by greed.
We didn't think before we took such a big order.
The boss will be packing it all on his own.
I should go and help, but...
Chief. You're the youngest here.
What are you doing lounging with us?
What?
Other than Jjuan over there, we're all the same age.
What are you saying?
I was born in May and you in December, kid.
I was born in March.
Darn it.
Hey, wake up, November-born baby.
I'm awake. I'm up.
You're not awake.
I am, darn you. I'm awake.
I'm up.
We can go back after just one more hour.
- Yes. - Yes.
I feel like how you feel.
I'm sorry, Boss.
Mr. Yoon!
- You're here already? - Yes.
You don't have enough today again?
Everyone's clamouring for more beer.
I'm doing my best, but I'm short on labour.
Where is everyone?
They're recovering after a stressful few days.
Oh, dear...
Then you shouldn't have taken the order.
I'm caught in the middle now.
Sorry. I'll work as fast as I can...
I don't care about what you do. I need the beer.
By when can I have it?
By tomorrow.
- What? - You'll have it by tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Can you do that?
- Yes. - Good.
I'll come back tomorrow, then.
You're a pretty and handsome bunch.
- Do your thing. - Bye.
What are you doing here?
I said I couldn't keep my promise,
but I never said I'd cause you trouble.
I heard you couldn't keep up with the demand.
We're about to make you much busier.
Of course, I should be responsible.
- What should we do first? - I get how...
you convinced Chan Hwi,
but how did you convince the others?
(To TF Team that's one team)
(Team Dinner Rejection Coupon)
It didn't take any convincing. They came willingly.
Because we're one team.
Laugh.
We're one team.
Did you get home safely last night?
I was worried you'd be driving at night.
Would someone that worried...
send someone else away...
in such a cold and unfriendly manner?
Were you...
very upset?
No. Why would I be?
I'm so used to getting sent away, I don't feel a thing.
(Amour and Marriage. Here's your date's photo.)
He doesn't have a good look.
Why would you read my texts?
Whatever.
Hey. Check to make sure they're tight properly.
(To tie up securely.)
Your dialect. What does that even mean?
How dare you shout at a senior?
I shouted? What's that word?
Who will swap with me?
We have a language barrier.
Don't you know what it means to tighten...
I can't hear you from over there.
(Uilhan Brewery)
Two, four, six, eight...
Wait...
(Bar Code Labels, In My Name Bottle Caps)
Why does it have to be up there?
(Bar Code Labels)
Goodness.
Be careful.
I can totally...
reach it, you know?
- I'll do it. - No, I'll...
- This... - Well...
Why are you getting nervous?
You see...
No, I'm not.
Hey...
Is that so?
All right, that was all the help I needed.
You may go home now.
What about you, Yong Ju? I won't go if you're not.
No, please leave. You've done more than enough today.
Keep your mouth closed. I'll take responsibility until the end.
You should all go home.
This is an order, not a request.
If so, I will go home first.
Keep up the good work.
He's right. Those who need to stay can stay. The rest, let's go home.
- Bye. - Bye.
Ms. Beautiful Bang. This is our chance to run away.
I'll stay behind and help with the rest.
Rao.
Take Mr. Kang with you.
Why? Are you really fine without me?
We've got enough people. Thanks for your help!
Go home.
- Bye. - Bye.
Boss!
Are you working without any fuel?
Unless you wish to die a day earlier, come over at once.
- Okay. Let's go, everyone. - Come on.
Why did you come? I called so you'd take a rest.
It might do us good physically, but not mentally.
We needed to feed you guys.
Gosh, how did you know I like soybean broth noodles?
Really?
I heard Chae Yong Ju brought over some talented manpower.
As expected from Yong Ju.
Honestly, I was starving. You ladies are the best!
- Is that so? - You're such a sweetheart.
Good grief, is someone coming after you or something?
You've got teeth. Why aren't you using them to chew?
They're right. Take your time eating.
- Eating fast has become a habit. - Goodness.
- We normally devour in one minute. - Yes.
Goodness, I love how you two dig in.
- What do you need? - Give me some more.
The eggs.
I love it.
I'll take four.
- Good grief, have one each. - Here's one handful.
- Thank you. - Chew it, all right?
Swallowing it whole is dangerous.
- Can I get two portions of noodles? - Noodles...
- What a greedy girl. - Unbelievable.
- You have to chew it, okay? - I love her.
Should I give you a bucketful?
Give me an egg.
- An egg? - Yes, an egg.
(All Memos, Bang Ah Reum's 2023 CEO Project Proposal)
(Bang Ah Reum's 2021 CEO Project Proposal)
(Bang Ah Reum's 2020 CEO Project Proposal)
(Bang Ah Reum's 2018 CEO Project Proposal)
I picked some...
I pulled some out on my way.
Well, you seemed depressed the whole day today.
You didn't eat dinner, either.
Do you know the feeling of being stripped naked?
It's like...
your lousiest side you never wanted others to know...
has been exposed.
- Hey. - Yes?
Do you mind checking this?
My goodness.
Whenever I get such a feeling,
I look at the highly praised presentations I made...
as a new recruit.
I can't believe we have such a thorough worker!
The compliments I received.
- The attention they gave me. - A few pages is enough to know.
- Ah Reum. - The me who did not hesitate.
- You're extraordinary. - I think about it constantly.
Right? I adore her.
With that, I forget about the lousy me of the day.
Nice.
Ah Reum. Is this how I do it?
Ah Reum. Please confirm this.
- Ah Reum. Isn't this a typo? - One second.
Ah Reum. Should I revise it like this?
- Ah Reum. - Please, Ah Reum.
- Ah Reum. - Ah Reum.
The more I get promoted, the scarier it is to get things wrong.
I become hesitant about everything.
(Sent E-mails)
I check the e-mails I have sent over and over again.
I always worry about whether I made a mistake.
(New Product Development Presentation)
Even that small responsibility is too much for me.
But what wears me out the most is...
hiding it from others.
That's why I glammed myself up like a shield...
to look perfect on the outside.
It worked quite well, you know?
But that girl appeared.
- Hi. - Hi.
Ah Reum. Isn't that a limited edition?
- Goodness. - Seriously, you have everything.
I feel a great sense of deprivation.
- Good morning. - Good morning.
Ms. Chae. Isn't Ms. Bang's bag gorgeous?
Getting your hands on it is almost impossible.
Yes, it's pretty.
Congratulations.
She's so indifferent about it.
But doesn't that make Ms. Chae cooler?
- You're right. She's cool. - Right?
- We're leaving first. - Bye.
The girl who effortlessly exposes the perfect image...
I've tried hard to create.
She's on another level.
Because belittling an opponent is just too easy a way out.
I simply wanted to be of help.
But the guys who made you do that should feel even worse.
You should personally take responsibility.
Don't you get paid the big bucks because you're supposed...
to take responsibility for your team's mistakes?
Ms. Bang works for me now.
I hate being compared.
But truthfully, I compare myself to others the most.
Because I can't accept the fact that I'm jealous,
I hate myself.
Aren't I...
a total mess?
The beer purity order?
Do you know what that is?
Was it "Reinheitsgebol?"
What do I comfort her with?
Tell me again. I'll do as you tell me to.
What was the purity order again?
Reinheits... What?
Who comforts others as they are told?
Do it from your heart.
Fine.
Reinheitsgebot.
Yes, that.
Beer can only be made with...
water, malt, yeast, and hop.
That order restricts using the four ingredients.
That was why Mr. Yoon did a lot of thinking.
"What is my purity order?"
Sensitive, anxious, delicate, emotional,
or something like that.
Anyway, that is...
how he created this one.
In My Name.
What do you think? Is it a mess?
It's good enough.
I agree with you.
To me,
you're good enough.
Ms. Beautiful...
Bang.
And...
you're...
truly pretty.
I always wondered how you get up to the second floor.
I can't seem to find a way over there...
It's this way.
Okay.
What?
For real?
I see.
Goodness.
My gosh.
So this is what it looks like. Oh, goodness.
Did you take all of these yourself?
Of course.
Gosh, you're a great photographer.
How many cameras do you have?
Goodness.
Yes, this place! And that one.
The ladies freaked out because of these.
I did, too, you know?
Oh, right.
There's Photo. You did an amazing job decorating the place.
What's that room over there?
May I have a look inside?
Yes.
Oh, my.
Hold on.
It's a photo of me.
Is this what you wanted to show me?
Yes.
It was my first photo.
Your first photo? Even though there are tons in here?
Of a person.
I see. It came out really well.
What's this, Mr. Yoon? Taking a photo of me...
and showing me places not even Photo has access to.
Why are you being so nice to me?
Right?
You managed to come inside a place nobody can.
Isn't your heart beating a little fast?
What nonsense are you spouting?
I am a former Special Task Force agent.
I always maintain...
my calmness.
Really?
Yes.
I can have this photo, right?
No.
It's mine.
Come on. Stop being cheap. It's just one photo.
My face is on it. This... Why...
Why am I nervous like he's a stranger? What's wrong with me?
I'm sorry.
I don't hold back when I'm certain about something.
I certainly like...
this one.
I'm talking about the photo.
Oh, the photo?
Right.
I see.
Goodness gracious.
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you for inviting me.
Shall we get to work? Let's work.
The photo...
Gosh, nice.
Good luck!
- Bye. - I'm off.
- Bye. - Bye.
- Goodness. - Great work, everyone.
Good job.
Now then, I've got to say goodbye here.
Customers won't stop asking if I'm going to sell toasts today.
I'll get going, too.
- Thank you for today. - You've done well.
Be careful on your way.
I'll get in touch, okay?
Why?
Come on. Stop being so cold.
But that's charming.
- You should get going. - Go ahead.
- I'll be leaving then. - Bye.
Bye.
I should get going too. I've got plans in Busan.
Really? I'm also going to Busan.
The pink teddy bear brother wants me to come over.
That guy? Is he doing well?
Yes, he is.
Well then...
Right.
Thank you for everything.
I see.
I'll get going now. Bye.
- Min Ju! - Min Ho! How have you been?
You grew taller in the meantime.
What brings you here?
Min Ho. You pestered Min Ju to come, didn't you?
I did.
A family needs to see each other often.
I'm guessing Dad's not home.
He went to pick up a guest we're having today.
A guest...
I should've contacted you before coming home.
Don't you also know that guest?
I heard she was the one who saved you six years ago.
Hey!
Don't pass out. Hold on.
Hey.
Who did you say it was?
Does Dad know who that person is?
Didn't you know that your dad was always in touch with that person?
I had no idea.
Good grief. This is all because of the lack of communication.
Well...
Neither of us brought up what had happened back then.
I'm also seeing the guest for the first time.
The guest has never been invited to our house before.
So that person is on their way here, right?
Come in.
- Hi. - Let's head inside.
Hi.
Hey.
It's okay now.
Everything is okay now.
Why are you here, Mr. Yoon?
What...
(Brewing Love)
Why did you do it?
Why did you wreck the town?
Stop caring about me.
I told you I had a lot of secrets.
I might want to know those secrets.
If you want me to wait until you're ready to talk, I'll wait.
Don't avoid me.
I won't avoid you, either.
I don't regret my decision back then.
Don't avoid me.
Don't disappear from me, okay?
I will never leave you, Ms. Chae.