[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 15]
Serving chopsticks.
Get another pair.
Don't bump into it when turning this.
Over here.
Hurry up.
Put one here,
and put one here.
Don't bump into it when turning this.
[February 5 Wednesday 14:45]
Chef Jia took more than
half the kitchen staff with him.
I need staff.
How many do you need?
I want 3 sous chefs,
and a dessert chef.
I can't give you 3.
I'll give you 1 first.
I'll transfer the rest to you
from other departments.
Okay.
Mr. Ji, Mr. Xue.
What is it?
I just went to Manager Chen of purchasing
to have him sign
the guests' dietary restriction list.
I happened to see him
lock the door and leave,
so I came to ask what is going on.
Got it.
As for people from other departments,
I want Xu Miyu.
You can arrange the rest as you see fit.
Ms. Xu,
our kitchen is understaffed right now.
Are you willing
to stay and help Chef Li?
I am.
Great.
And me.
I can help too.
You?
I can cook.
I made the 8 cold dishes and 8 hot dishes
for our family's New Year's Eve dinner.
Then Chef Li,
you decide this.
Where is the sous chef?
Here.
Come here.
I am Guo Luda.
Okay, Mr. Guo.
Today you are responsible
for reading the orders
and serving the food.
The banquet hall and the Chinese
restaurant must be separated.
You can't make any mistakes.
Okay, no problem.
Okay.
It's 3:10 now.
Let's begin.
Come on, hurry up.
Find someone to open the office.
Okay.
Darn it.
Chen ran off with Jia Shikun.
I never thought about
getting anything
from them in the first place.
But now they've made things look so ugly.
[Staff Personal Health Standard]
The troubles facing the Chinese restaurant
may be worse than I imagined.
Prepare some flour and minced meat for me.
Okay. How much meat?
1.5 kg?
2.5?
2.5 kg.
Then slice some sweet potatoes,
along with perilla leaves and eggplant.
Make all the slices a bit thick.
Hurry up.
Okay.
We're still short-handed.
Find some more people for me.
All washed?
Do you know how to peel tomatoes?
Peel them?
Okay, I'll do it.
I'd better do it.
Didn't she say we're short-handed?
Let me do it.
Why don't you try this?
Okay.
Just score a cross at the top.
Then put it in boiling water.
Then the skin will split open.
Try it.
Okay.
It didn't burn you, did it?
I'm fine.
You have to slide the tomatoes
down the side of the pot.
Don't just drop them in from the top.
Otherwise, the splashing water
will burn you.
Let me try again.
Here it comes.
Careful, it's hot.
Looks and smells great.
How does it taste?
It's time.
Guys, it's 5:00.
Hurry up.
Dinner in the banquet hall
starts promptly at 6:30.
Let's hurry up, guys! Come on!
You'd better go help Mr. Ji.
Mr. Ji.
I'll take over.
You go greet the guests.
Okay, I'll leave the rest to you.
Give it to me.
I put your suit
in the kitchen office.
I was afraid it might get dirty here.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming all this way.
Not at all.
You can go over there first.
Please, right this way.
Kenny.
Marcos.
We meet again.
Yes.
Let me make an introduction.
This is the Commercial Director
of Puqi Group.
Mr. Cheng.
Mr. Cheng, this is
Mr. Ji Feng, General Manager
of Purong Hotel.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too, Mr. Cheng.
We have your table ready.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
We've prepared an appetizer for you.
[All staff of Purong Hotel]
I believe it's a dish
you're very familiar with.
[warmly welcome Mr. Marcos]
Thank you.
[We will serve you sincerely]
Okay.
This is a Spanish cold soup.
Enjoy your meal, everyone.
I'm serious.
This tastes exactly
the same
as what I had in Cordoba.
Really?
You should try it.
That's something.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Not bad.
Next up are the Shanghai dishes.
Come on.
Please enjoy.
This is exactly like
the kind I had as a kid,
deep-fried dough sticks
made from sourdough.
Your hands would be
covered in oil after eating.
It smelt so great.
It's a pity that nowadays,
you can't find
breakfast shops like this anymore.
I see.
That's a pity.
Then we hope you
can come to our hotel
for breakfast more often, Mr. Cheng.
It's a deal.
Mr. Cheng,
is it convenient for me
to add you on WeChat?
No problem.
Come, add her on WeChat.
What do you think?
It's fried quite well.
Just right.
[All staff of Purong Hotel]
What do you think?
[warmly welcome Mr. Marcos]
You can scan my code.
It smells really great.
[We will serve you sincerely]
The taste of childhood.
Right?
Okay, got it.
Are you satisfied with the dishes?
Isn't it greasy?
If you feel it's too greasy,
some soy milk will help.
Enjoy your meal.
It can relieve the greasiness.
Eight-Treasure Duck.
It's done.
[Purong Hotel Chinese Restaurant; Dine-In;
Eight-Treasure Duck]
Poached Shrimp, one, two, three.
Seven plates of Poached Shrimp.
No, eight...
Eight plates.
How many plates exactly?
Don't worry about it.
Start cooking first.
We'll plate whatever we get.
The guest would like to cancel
the Tofu with Crab Roe.
Tofu with Crab Roe...
This has garlic.
The guest wants it remade.
So noisy.
My head’s about to explode.
Put it there first.
And Stir-Fried Shrimp with Rice Wine.
-Is it done?
-Yes. Yes.
Waiter,
when will the dishes
for our table be served?
We've been waiting
for nearly half an hour.
The kitchen is preparing.
It will be served right away.
Please wait a moment.
Hurry up.
Waitor,
we've finished our cold dishes.
When will you serve us the hot dishes?
Right away.
I'll go urge them now.
Hurry up.
Mr. Guo, you go inside and help.
Leave this to me.
Okay.
Get me a fresh one.
Here.
Six portions of Braised Wheat Gluten.
Okay.
Okay, go.
Careful.
Is the Tempura ready?
A bunch of idiots.
Hurry up, bro!
Mr. Ji.
Sorry, Mr. Ji.
I was in such a hurry,
I didn't recognize you.
-It’s okay.
-Sorry.
Mr. Ji,
the large private room
in the Chinese restaurant
just ordered 18 portions
of Hainanese Chicken Rice at once.
The staff were too quick.
They've already served all the chicken rice
meant for the banquet hall.
We might come up short here.
Chef Li, are there any other options?
We can use the cooked rice
to make soy sauce fried rice.
But it's too hard.
It's not suitable for the final dish.
How about making noodles?
I'm afraid it's too late to make it now.
What kind of noodles do you want to make?
The guests have been eating
seafood and red meat all night.
A bowl of plain noodles now
would be refreshing
and cut through the grease.
It's good, but it lacks a gimmick.
We can make plain noodles in chicken soup.
Chicken soup with mature hen
from Southern Anhui.
Since it's to cleanse the palate,
it can't be too rich.
How about Fish Bone Soup
with Bamboo Leaves?
I can make it.
You'll make it.
Okay.
Chef Li, please keep
an eye on things here.
I'll go outside and take a look.
Okay.
Let's go.
Mr. Ji.
Try some.
I don't need this much.
I'll just have a bite.
I haven't tasted it properly yet.
Let me have another bite.
Mr. Ji,
this whole bowl is for you.
You've been too busy to eat all night.
Have some noodles to line your stomach.
Okay, thank you.
Who came up with this terrible idea
to change the menu at the last minute?
What's going on?
Xu Miyu,
why is it you again?
The Hainanese Chicken Rice
is the favorite staple food
of Shenjiang Industrial's boss.
I'm telling you,
this is a business banquet,
not a local feast in your hometown.
Change it back immediately.
Why can any kind of person
boss around in my kitchen now?
Who let this person in?
Kick her out!
Qiaoqi.
Director Lu,
the Hainanese Chicken Rice
was added temporarily at 5:00 p.m.
Why is it no longer available?
It's because the guests in the large
private room of the Chinese restaurant
are business owners from Guangdong's
new energy manufacturing sector.
What do you expect our kitchen to do?
As for this bowl of
plain noodles
in Fish Bone Soup with Bamboo Leaves,
you won't find it
at a typical hometown feast.
The bamboo leaves are from
Mount Emei in Sichuan.
The fish bones come from
Pengze crucian carp in Jiangxi.
And these noodles
are fresh handmade noodles.
Now you know how to
introduce it to the guests, right?
What are these nonsense words
you cobbled together?
Are you trying to bluff me?
I don't care what ingredients you use.
If this noodle dish fails,
will you take responsibility?
I will.
Mr. Ji.
Mr. Ji, I'm sorry.
I was just too anxious.
Director Lu, do me a favor.
Should I take these noodles up?
Put them on the cart.
How could we let you serve the dishes?
Not bad. Pretty good.
Glad you like it.
Pretty good.
Marcos, let me introduce you.
This is the executive chef
in charge of tonight's dinner,
Chef Li Qiaoqi.
Marcos.
Mr. Cheng.
-Hello, Chef Li.
-Hello.
Hello. I didn't expect you to be so young.
Chef, let me tell you,
I am really satisfied
with tonight's dinner.
Mr. Cheng even said
he must see for himself
such an amazing chef like you.
Also,
I want to
express my gratitude to you in person.
Thank you for your hard work.
The praise from Mr. Marcos and Mr. Cheng
is our honor.
Actually, in Purong,
there are many chefs like me.
Thank you all.
Thank you for your hard work.
This lady...
My butler?
Hello, Mr. Marcos.
Actually,
your butler is also
a very excellent chef.
Today's plain noodles are made by her.
I really finished that bowl
of plain noodles.
What a surprise, Ms. Xu.
I didn't expect you
to be such a good cook.
Well,
can I
order the plain noodles now
for my breakfast tomorrow?
My pleasure.
Then I want to order a bowl too.
I will come here specifically tomorrow
to have this for breakfast.
No problem.
Let's add each other on WeChat.
Well,
I think the food here
tastes really good.
The most important thing is the broth.
It's hard to make.
That broth is really delicious.
They are back.
Awesome.
Good job, everyone.
You did great.
We finally got through
this without a hitch.
Even though Chef Jia
disappeared without a word,
our Chinese restaurant won't disappear.
Chef Li Qiaoqi,
starting tomorrow,
you will be the acting
head chef of the Chinese restaurant.
Any objections?
Feel free to raise them
and we can discuss them together.
No objections.
Since there are no objections,
please follow
the new head chef
and work together
to keep our Chinese restaurant running.
Okay?
Okay!
Good. Thanks for your hard work.
Wrap up your work,
and go rest early.
Okay.
Thanks.
I didn't expect this at all.
You are the best.
You must be exhausted today too.
I'm fine.
Thanks for your help.
I have something else to do.
I'll get going.
Qiaoqi.
I made this.
Try it.
Eunuch Xue, are you
bribing the new head chef?
How am I like a eunuch?
What kind of nickname is that?
You're biting the hand that feeds you.
Eat it while it's hot.
Thank you.
I'll get back to work then.
Eunuch Xue? How do I look like a eunuch?
What?
The Chinese restaurant found
a new head chef so quickly?
She was promoted from the original
sous-chefs of the Chinese restaurant.
She was set to become head chef
after tonight's banquet.
Didn't Jia Shikun tell me
that everyone in the Chinese restaurant
except him is useless
and can't accomplish anything?
Then...
What's wrong with Ji Feng?
Is he just grasping at straws?
Or is it that
Jia Shikun is completely lying to me?
That won't do. I have to go take a look.
Isn't this Mr. Duan Jr.?
What brings you down to our kitchen?
So, where's your new head chef?
Why are you looking for me?
It's you?
Can't it be me?
You're on Ji Feng's side?
Whoever promotes me,
I'm on their side.
What do you want?
How much does Ji Feng pay you?
I'll double it.
Come to Kuanli,
and you can still be the head chef.
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
I just learned for the first time
that your head chefs
at Kuanli come in bulk.
You think I'm lying?
If I'm not mistaken,
Jia Shikun was also lured to Kuanli
by your words.
Mr. Duan Jr., I might lack backbone,
but you don't have
to treat me like a fool.
Don't be ungrateful.
Sorry,
I really plan
to stay in Purong's kitchen.
What can you do about it?
[F&B Department, Li Qiaoqi]
Li Qiaoqi, right?
Let's see
how big a storm you can stir up.
Let's wait and see.
Take care. I won't see you out.
Mr. Yang, may I walk you
through tomorrow's schedule?
Our hotel has prepared...
Wait a minute.
Hello?
Ms. Xu, give me the room card.
-What? What happened to my grandpa?
-I’ll go open the door.
Mr. Yang, are you alright?
My grandpa fell into a coma yesterday.
He woke up today
and couldn't remember anyone.
I want to rest early tonight.
I understand. I'll arrange it.
Thank you, Ms. Xu.
Mr. Yang, the room is ready for you.
I haven't finished what I was saying.
Mr. Yang is tired.
He wants to rest.
I have important matters
to discuss with him.
What do you know?
You can talk to him about it tomorrow.
Whatever it is,
we'll talk tomorrow.
Okay.
I won't disturb you.
Good night.
Good night, Mr. Yang.
Thank you.
[Purong Hotel Staff Apartment]
[Marcos's grandfather attended
the youth architectural design program]
[at Huiwen Yingzao in Shanghai, China.]
[Marcos's grandfather attended
the youth architectural design program]
[at Huiwen Yingzao in Shanghai, China.]
You've worked hard, honey,
especially being pregnant.
Did the contract signing go smoothly?
Not yet,
but soon.
The boss had a great meal tonight.
He said he was going
to eat somewhere else,
but guess what?
He ended up listening to me.
The five-table banquet
has been moved to our Purong Hotel.
You are amazing, baby.
But that Xu Miyu,
showing off everywhere
and going against me in everything.
She's so annoying.
Who are you talking about?
Who else could it be?
Your ex-wife.
If it weren't for her,
I would have signed the contract today.
She was the one who stopped me,
insisting that the boss needed to rest.
Why is she like this?
I think she must
hate me.
She's trying everything
to exact personal revenge.
I can't be bothered to deal with her.
Anyway, I'll go see the boss
first thing tomorrow morning,
to press my advantage
and make sure to get this contract signed.
Otherwise,
all my hard work over the past 2 days
will be in vain.
Right.
You can definitely
get the contract signed.
I have faith in you.
Go to sleep.
I have to work early tomorrow morning.
What's wrong with me like this now?
I make my own money to support myself.
Is it any more shameful
than being your full-time nanny?
Hello, Director Lu.
Mr. Yang's flight has been rescheduled.
We are arranging a car
to take him to the airport now.
Ms. Lu.
Thank you for your warm hospitality.
Mr. Yang.
Regarding the cooperation agreement
we discussed at the last banquet,
have you made a decision yet?
I have an emergency
and need to leave China now.
Let's discuss our cooperation later.
Thank you for your understanding.
Of course, I understand.
I wonder if you could
reach a letter of intent with us first.
Even a verbal agreement would do.
It would show
your recognition of our services.
Purong Hotel has a great reputation.
There's no need to rush.
Besides, long-term cooperation
is not a trifling matter.
I think we should sit down
and talk this through sometime.
When exactly is that?
That depends on you.
If your hotel
can maintain excellent service as always,
then when I'll visit
and whether we cooperate
is just a matter of time.
Yes.
Ms. Lu, are you coming
to the airport with us?
I won't be going.
I have a meeting later,
so I'll leave it to you
to see him off, Ms. Xu.
Have a safe trip, Mr. Yang.
Welcome back to Purong Hotel.
Thank you.
-Please.
-Thank you.
Mr. Marcos,
your flight is delayed.
How long is the delay?
Four hours.
Four ho...
See if there are
any other places you want to go.
Whatever.
Can I arrange it then?
Let's go to East Changzhi Road first.
This is the Huiwen Architectural Design
and Research Institute.
Its predecessor
was Huiwen Yingzao, built in 1942.
At that time, in addition to
producing a large number
of exquisite architectural designs,
a large group of outstanding
foreign design masters also came here.
They set up
a youth architectural design program here,
cultivating a group of
rare and excellent
architectural design talents for China.
This story
is a fine example,
both in terms of cultural exchange
between China and the world
and in the field of architectural design.
These are some photographs
from Huiwen Yingzao,
including a few group photos
from that time.
Ms. Xu,
the one on the far left of the second row
is my grandfather.
If only he were here too.
Do you want to call your grandfather then?
Will he still remember me?
How will you know if you don't try?
Mr. Yang Siyuan, you have a phone call.
Grandpa.
You have the wrong number, child.
I am in China.
In Shanghai, China.
I'm looking at
your pictures when you were young.
At Huiwen Yingzao, see?
This is Wang.
Li.
This is our monitor.
You still remember them?
More than remember,
I miss them to death.
Huiwen Yingzao.
Shanghai, China.
The place where I once studied.
Yes.
Grandpa.
Grandpa, then...
Then I am...
You...
Aren't you my Marcos?
Come here quickly.
I miss you.
I miss you very much too.
My flight arrives tomorrow,
then I will go see you immediately.
Come over quickly.
I'll wait for you.
See you tomorrow.
I'll hang up now.
Time flies,
but beautiful memories last forever.
Let me take a picture
of you with your grandpa's photo.
Can you?
Come.
One, two, three.
Thank you.
Ms. Xu.
Can I have a hug?
Of course.
Thank you.
You know what?
You...
You know what, I...
You are the most considerate
hotel attendant
I have ever met traveling the world.
You make me feel
especially secure.
It feels very much like coming home.
Thank you for saying that.
Then,
you are welcome to visit
Purong Hotel often in the future.
Coming often is a must.
And I will let all my staff
come and
enjoy the service here.
We will definitely
serve you wholeheartedly.
Okay.
It should be about time.
Let me take you to the airport.
Great, let's go.
This way, please.
[Unread]
[Loading]
[From: CBO Marcos Yang]
It's done.
What's done?
Marcos wants to sign
a long-term contract with us.
This is all so sudden.
I heard gossip from the front desk
that he's very hard to deal with.
He seems pleasant on the outside,
but is as solid as a rock on the inside.
I thought we had no chance.
Secretary Wu,
notify the management to hold a meeting
in an hour,
after Director Lu
comes back from the airport.
Okay.
You're here.
Talk to you later.
Okay.
Our hosting of Liberty Group this time
was very successful.
They have verbally promised
a long-term contract with us.
All processes are moving forward.
The sales department has made
such a great contribution this time.
We should thank
Mr. Qian for his strong support.
You are too kind, Mr. Ji.
This time, our sales department
is honored
to fight side by side
with Mr. Ji.
This time, Director Lu
has secured such an important client
for our hotel.
It demonstrated our strength externally
and boosted our morale internally.
Although Director Lu
just got transferred here,
her performance has been outstanding.
After discussing with Mr. Qian,
I announce
that Lu Zhenzhen
is promoted to VIP Account Manager.
Ms. Lu, you'll take the lead
on the follow-up with Liberty Group.
Yes.
[Changzhi Road]
Sir, I'll get off here.
Next is
the HSKP Department.
Well,
Mr. Ji,
our HSKP Department's
performance this time
indeed fell short of
the standard of a five-star hotel.
As the leader in charge,
first of all,
I need to make a self-criticism.
It's my fault for
choosing the wrong person.
The executive floor forewoman Xu Miyu
neglected her duty
while receiving VIP guests.
It almost
caused a major accident,
bringing irreversible losses
to the hotel.
She is...
Xu Miyu.
So you still know how to show up.
You made mistakes at work
and are late for the meeting.
What are you trying to do?
Do you still respect me as your leader?
Do you even care about
the hotel's work discipline?
Do you think just
because you're a forewoman
you can completely disregard us
managers?
No, Mr. Feng.
I was taking a guest to the airport,
and the traffic was
a bit heavy on the way back.
-I'm sorry.
-Look.
Still making excuses.
You blame the traffic
for being late to the meeting.
You forgot the VIP's allergies,
and you blamed others for not telling you.
If all of us were like you,
shirking responsibility
whenever there's a problem,
how would any work get done?
Ms. Xu.
The executive floor
will be ruined by you sooner or later.
Mr. Ji.
I'm sorry.
Our HSKP Department
made such a huge mistake
in this important VIP reception.
I take full responsibility.
I didn't discipline this subordinate well,
and I can't shirk the blame.
Please punish me.
Mr. Feng,
don't be in a hurry to ask for punishment.
Let me finish first.
During the HSKP Department's
VIP reception,
there were some mistakes at first.
But fortunately,
the forewoman and staff
on the executive floor
later
observed carefully,
found the problems in time,
and quickly adjusted themselves
to improve the service quality.
In the end, with high-quality service,
they cooperated with
the F&B and sales departments
and successfully completed
this reception task.
Their performance was commendable.
But as for
the cause of the series of accidents
in the HSKP Department,
investigation shows that
they were caused by a handover accident
during the transfer of documents.
Mr. Feng,
do you have anything to explain?
Well,
well...
As for
the shampoo reselling by our staff
and the linen scandal,
our investigation shows
that you were behind both, Mr. Feng—
stealing from the hotel
and lining your own pockets.
The evidence is conclusive.
In addition, the GM's Office
has recently evaluated the abilities
of all department leaders.
Mr. Feng failed to meet the standards.
Based on the above points
and the hotel management regulations,
I hereby announce
that Mr. Feng is dismissed.
You can't fire me.
Mr. Ji,
Mr. Feng is the head
of HSKP Department after all.
You made the decision
to fire him all by yourself?
Isn't that a bit too hasty?
Exactly.
At the very least, you should
discuss it with Mr. Wei first.
So what you're saying is,
the hotel's general manager
can't make personnel
decisions independently?