[thunder rumbling]
You're working for SherKhan?
SherKhan is working for him,
don't you get it?
I don't work for nobody. I work for us.
Fuck that!
So having me beaten up was
all for us too? Why do you keep lying?
Look at this bullshit!
When are you gonna cut the crap, huh?
Who's Milord? I don't get it.
He's the boss.
He's Fatso's boss.
He had me beaten up, that's who he is.
The biggest dealer in Fort-de-France.
You dealing crack, Kylian?
What are you dealing?
Never crack.
I promise I'd never touch that shit.
Okay.
I know this might be tough to understand,
but it's for our own wellbeing.
All of us.
Crack isn't gonna
keep a roof over our heads.
You dealing? What, weed?
Which block? Fuck's sake, Kylian, explain!
I'm not on the streets.
I dealt a bit of pot
to get enough cash to buy coke.
No one knows who I am.
Trust me, it's safer that way.
I sell the coke where
it earns me the most, in France.
I mean, I will be soon.
I just closed a huge deal.
I got merchandise coming in overseas.
We're talking millions.
Completely insane, this guy.
[phone vibrating]
- [Marvin] We gotta do something.
- [Annabelle] See a therapist?
FATSO - Everything was stolen,
there's nothing left.
[Marvin] I guess it's to be expected
with Mama's death.
He's not coping. We didn't see it.
WE'RE CHANGING HIDEOUTS.
I'LL CALL YOU AFTER.
[Marvin] He's losing it.
It's true, he's Milord.
Milord was Dylan. It connects.
So this son of a bitch swiped
Dylan's username to sell goddamn poison?
That is disgusting.
How long have you been doing this?
Answer her, Milord, or whatever!
Two years, maybe.
Nah, he's being played for sure.
Marv, there's an apartment
full of their shit. It's a huge operation.
Two years.
We were always together in school.
- Had to keep it a secret.
- Stop talking!
Aren't you all fed up, though?
Living in this shack, counting pennies?
Not being able to afford a damn gas stove?
Having to hide the babies
'cause we're too poor for custody?
Who do you think got the damn stove?
How do you think we got the stand back?
It's the best solution to use Milord.
Yeah, it might be hard, but that's life.
You say a shack?
You wouldn't have dared
talk like that in front of Mama.
- Take your things, get out of here.
- Marv--
I said take your shit
and find somewhere else to stay,
'cause you can't stay here.
Better to keep it secret.
It was to keep you out of the mix.
[sucks teeth] Don't give me that bull like
you're a gangster! Life isn't a movie!
You had better knock this shit off.
I mean it. It's pathetic.
Get out.
[bittersweet music playing softly]
Hey! Give me that ring!
Mama thought you were pure, you bastard.
You realize that?
Give it back, now.
No.
[bittersweet music continues playing]
[phone vibrating]
KIKI
I'm sorry
[rap beat playing faintly on headphones]
I DON'T HAVE
THE STRENGTH ANYMORE
[Ambre] Hard to believe, huh?
XHESUS
I miss you already
The weather's nice, I'm thinking of you…
What are you doing?
Why aren't you answering?
Is there a problem?
Why's this guy being a dick?
[sucks teeth]
Fuck this. Shit.
[sighs]
I appreciate it.
It will just be for tonight.
Don't worry, my mom knows.
You get in a fight with your brothers?
It'll blow over. I'm sure it will.
Won't be that simple, I'm afraid.
It will! That's family.
[sighs heavily]
You don't know my family.
Want to drink something?
If you are.
["No Pain No Gain"
by Shaka Zulu & Lylyo playing]
FATSO
Where have you moved to?
Enter.
- [door closes]
- [song stops playing]
I just want to talk with you.
We've just lost our mother.
You know that, I imagine.
I'm worried about Kylian.
He's my responsibility.
He's grieving. He needs structure.
And what he's doing with you here…
this shit is the exact opposite
of what he actually needs right now.
Anyway, all this to say,
you're gonna have to do this without him.
I'm serious, he's done.
- Look, I'm not sure exactly what he said--
- That's not the issue!
I know all about your thing.
And I will not let him
be involved any longer.
All I'm asking is let him be.
Marvin… our business don't work like that.
- [Ludo] Mmm.
- [Marvin] Alexy?
This is happening, you guys hear me?
Look, you're all adults. You know
you can work with anybody you want.
And, anyway, I'm gonna
be on that kid like white on rice.
So there's nothing you can do.
You might want to be careful.
Kylian is 16!
He thinks he's some kinda boss.
He's gonna fall flat on his ass.
He won't go to prison.
But you?
You're all over 18.
You realize that?
Do your business without Kylian.
- [door opens]
- You just gonna let him go like that?
- [door closes]
- It's disrespectful, man.
Crazy.
We'll handle it.
[darkly expectant music playing]
[alarm ringing]
- [ringing continues]
- [Lily grunts]
[ringing stops]
[expectant music continues]
[Lily] My uncle's here.
And?
Why does he have to show up at 7:00 a.m.?
He always come this early?
Yeah.
My mother works with him…
for him at city hall.
It's fine.
'Kay.
Are you coming with me to Claire's party?
It's a costume party.
- Got anything white?
- No.
Okay.
I'll just bring you one.
Can dress up as Tony Montana.
I'll be Michelle Pfeiffer.
[laughs]
[woman] Seriously?
You were here yesterday.
[man] Sorry. Yes, but the contractor's
being a pain in the ass.
Really.
Hi.
- Morning.
- [woman] You sleep okay?
[Lily] Yeah, fine.
Same, thanks.
If you can be ready in ten minutes,
I'll drop you off.
[Lily] Okay.
[sighs]
Alex Croquet.
I know. Kylian Lafleur.
I know you too.
Lily has spoken of you.
Your mother just passed.
Tough life.
Go tell your mother I'm heading out.
Lafleur.
Can't say Lily hit the jackpot, huh?
[sighs]
Just how many are in your family?
A lot.
So you've lost count too.
So, to summarize,
you're kicked out
and you're mooching off the Juliards.
What's your plan?
Don't tell me the others
will be showing up here as well.
[sighs]
It's not sustainable.
What?
Your plan.
Your kind's all bloodsuckers.
I see 'em every day.
Not your fault,
you were just brought up that way.
It won't be here, Kylian.
Not my family.
Find yourself another Lily, champ.
Get out of here.
Go steal yourself a bike.
Get your ass out.
[darkly intriguing music playing]
[darkly intriguing music continues]
[faucet running in background]
Oh, hello, Kylian.
- Doing well, Mrs. Torville?
- Oh, yes.
Doing well.
Uh, where's Alexy?
He didn't tell me anything.
Just asked me to come by
to clean the place up a little.
He leave any message for me?
No, I'm afraid not.
Thanks.
[sighs heavily]
[line ringing]
[line disconnects]
Mrs. Torville,
may I please borrow your phone?
- Mine is out of battery.
- Here.
Thank you.
[line ringing]
- [Fatso] Yes, Grandma?
- Where are you?
- Forget it.
- You for real?
Very.
Listen up, meet me on the field tomorrow.
You better be there.
You alone?
So what now?
- Where's that tool you borrowed?
- Yo, I promise I don't have it.
- I need it.
- What for?
- You don't have it?
- No.
King threw it away.
Hang on.
What are you doing?
[scoffs] What do you
want me to do with that?
[laughs] Man, I got you! It's real!
That way, I can have it on me
without anyone knowing.
Thanks, my man.
Go pay respects to Mama's grave.
Do I have to?
Yes.
Will you tell Milord?
- What?
- Will you tell Milord I helped out?
Yeah, I'll tell him.
- [man 1] Yo, pour me another shot.
- [man 2] You're gonna drain the bottle.
[indistinct chatter
continues in background]
Thought I asked you to watch the bar.
Well, I'm watching someone else
while you're here.
- You in love or what?
- [sucks teeth] I'm pissed off at this man.
He better be ready if I see him.
And you in love with SherKhan or what?
Why are you eyeballing him?
Remember that bastard
returned our cash to SherKhan?
You forget all the risks
you took for that money?
Of course I haven't forgotten.
Well, we're getting it back.
It's ours.
Just gotta find out where it's hidden.
Follow the next guy.
- [Annabelle] Yeah, okay.
- [suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues]
[men chatting indistinctly]
[engine sputters and dies]
[horn honks]
[engine sputtering]
[suspenseful music continues]
Hello.
[women] Hello.
I thought I saw
your ugly-ass face, Lafleur.
- What you want?
- The fuck you care?
- You following me?
- You think you're a star, is that it?
Doing my nails.
I'll wait outside.
If you want.
Okay, what do you want?
Cheapest.
Basic manicure, five euros.
Perfect!
[sucks teeth]
Your little buddies'll love this.
See ya, homo.
I don't care. Go on.
["Madame" by X-Man playing]
That's not bad.
I like guys
who take pride in their appearance.
Well, what do you want from me now?
It's a shame what happened the other day.
Didn't get to know each other.
Nicely put.
What do you want?
Just a little spying.
On who?
SherKhan's crew. They know me.
SherKhan again?
- You're obsessed!
- I'll give you five grand.
Plus 50% of what you make.
- What?
- We're partners, aren't we?
50/50.
[SherKhan] Yo, Lafleur!
So, what, not fleeing for the hills?
You lose that lame little scooter?
I like men who clean up nice,
but not little bitches.
Your guy works for free.
He sold my shit in France
without taking commission.
Let's do it again.
[woman] Jérôme!
You gonna be a King?
Yo, if you're looking for a real G,
call up your boy, SherKhan.
[woman] Jérôme!
Come on.
Your mom is calling.
[woman] Let's go, Jérôme!
You want to know me?
[suspenseful music playing]
I like your guys. Punctual.
Where are you hiding it?
In your ass.
Original.
The point of using groceries
is not to hide them.
Keeping up appearances, that's all.
When the tide is low,
you'll all see little crabs and shrimps
hide under the sand.
They typically come out at night to eat.
Almost always at night.
Okay, does anyone
have any questions about this?
- [kids] No!
- [teacher] Hmm.
- Are you hungry?
- [kids] Yes!
All right, let's go.
[indistinct chatter and laughter]
Excuse me? So sorry,
but I can't stay any longer.
- I was only free until noon.
- Oh, yes, yes, no problem.
I appreciate you helping us out.
Thanks.
Thaïs!
- I'm going.
- See ya!
- [kids laughing]
- [indistinct chatter]
[unsettling music playing]
Nolan?
- Who's that man?
- Uncle Jocelyn.
Uncle Jocelyn?
Hey, Jocelyn!
Jocelyn! Yo!
[dramatic music building slowly]
What the hell is he doing here?
[dramatic music playing]
- What you doin' here?
- Mind your own shit, Milord!
Get out!
You're fucking me over.
You're out here rambling
about how the streets will save us.
All your bullshit.
And you blow it all up, man.
What for?
- Mad you're not the man of the house?
- [chuckles]
While you're making ten kilos,
I'm making over 80.
I buy all my shit.
I don't steal it.
Put it on your CV, if you want a job.
My team dropped me 'cause of you.
I'm in real fucking deep shit now
thanks to you.
I want you to talk to them with me.
- Yeah? For what?
- Tell them that you're an idiot.
And that you're never
gonna cause problems again.
[laughing]
Man, I gotta hand it to you.
You got real nerve, man.
No one can hold a candle to you.
Respect, man.
That's a fact.
Ah…
So why haven't I busted your teeth? Hmm?
I guess I'm too kind.
Should've done it a long time ago.
Should've yanked one out every time
you said something I didn't like.
You'd be eating mashed potatoes.
So get out of here.
Yo!
[yelling] You son of a bitch
piece of shit!
What did you do with Dad?
He's sending Jocelyn to monitor the kids?
- [Kylian] Stop!
- What the fuck did you do?
You dealing with Dad? Goddamn bastard!
- [Kylian] Stop it!
- We agreed to not get them involved, yeah?
That'd we'd keep them out!
You really are a bunch of assholes.
You, Dad, and yeah, bro, you too!
I swear to you,
next time he gets anywhere close to them,
I'll goddamn destroy you!
[Kingsley whistles]
You're just winning hearts left and right.
Mmm-mmm.
Come here.
Did Milord tell you?
Yeah. He wants to test you.
That's dope!
What are we doing here?
Scaring someone.
Who?
[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct chatter continues]
- Oh, that's Uncle Jocelyn!
- Shh!
[man] Damn straight we are.
[Jocelyn] I gotta take a piss.
[man] Watch out.
[urinating]
[gasps]
Man, don't you ever come near the family.
Got it?
You ever get within
a single block of the kids,
- I swear no one will ever find your body.
- [groans]
- Understood? Don't come near the family.
- [dull thud]
- [groaning]
- [Léo grunts]
- [blows landing]
- [Jocelyn groaning]
Enough.
[Jocelyn coughs]
And tell Dad the deal's the same.
Five percent. That's it.
We don't give in to threats.
- [grunting]
- Ahh!
I said enough!
- [coughing]
- [Kylian] Let's go.
Did I do well?
Give me the gun.
- [woman] Yes, we've made a note.
- [door chimes]
[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct chatter continues]
Put this on twice a day.
After, use it as a mask on your face
and keep it damp.
- Then you rinse it off and apply ointment.
- [grunts]
You got a real good heart.
Hope they pay you well at this hospital.
It's fine.
Not afraid they'll return?
Who?
The guys who did this.
[sucks teeth]
[grunts] Bunch of losers.
They can't scare me.
[Cassandra] Then who?
Just drop it.
You know who my cousin is?
You know SherKhan?
When I'm out of here…
What?
It won't be a "welcome home" party,
that's for damn sure.
So don't make me better too fast.
[chuckling]
You know, I do spells too, if you like.
- Yeah? You can for real?
- [darkly introspective music playing]
Like… would he know it's from me?
But it won't be anything too extreme?
Doesn't have to be.
Okay.
- Don't spells need hair and shit?
- I just need a sense of his habits.
Learn about him more.
I need to get a visual idea
of where he goes.
Well, he's got his bar in Trénelle.
And he visits his mother.
He often hangs out at the Marina du Marin,
that asshole.
That's where his dope is shipped from.
[Kingsley] Hold up.
SherKhan is using Croquet's boat?
No.
Yep.
Man, amazing.
You made him talk! How'd you do it?
I'm a professional.
[Thaïs] One euro each.
[woman] All right.
[Kingsley] Thaïs, Mathis, Nolan!
Let's go home.
We haven't finished!
Seems to me that pretty soon
they won't have to work the stand.
Damn straight, darling!
Our life is about to change!
[pensive music playing]
[pensive music continues]
[bag crinkling]
Eighty kilos on the way.
One million euros.
- I know.
- So what are you doing, then?
Couldn't be sure
your other phones were safe.
King took them.
Don't feed me bullshit. Not one message.
You cut me out completely.
What's happening?
Your brother came to see us.
Marvin.
We can't deal with this bullshit.
Your brother turns up, stirring up shit.
The other making trouble? Not cool.
[Peace] You gotta rein them in.
They don't respect you,
so they don't respect any of us.
This shit's fucked.
I won't lie to you.
I don't know what to tell my new buyers.
- Meaning?
- Guys from Grenoble.
They're solid.
They pick their coworkers carefully.
We don't know if you're with us or not.
That'll piss them off.
What are you planning on telling 'em?
If they ask me, I don't know, man.
Marvin, what'd he tell you?
[sighs] To do it without you.
[laughs]
You're gonna go ahead without me?
With everything going on,
not sure if we're gonna do any of it.
- This shit is messy.
- I got it.
No, you don't.
What's that? Must've misheard you.
[menacingly] You don't got shit.
[exhales]
[darkly intriguing music playing]
We got two choices.
Either we go to war…
or we get fuckin' rich.
[Pearl] And how
are you gonna deal with him?
Can you send me a recent resume?
Mmm-hmm.
What about your time gardening
at the Balata?
I was only there two months.
[woman] So what? Put it.
You gotta work on your cover letter, too.
[Marvin sighs]
I'm tired.
I know.
SOS GARDENING
THE FIRST UBER FOR GARDENING
It's been a shitstorm ever since Mama.
We've got nothing to bind us.
She held us together.
No way we're gonna make it.
No, none of that's true.
We're gonna grow distant
or kill each other.
This, it's all just a rough patch.
I know you guys.
You're strong.
You'll all be okay.
You handled Kylian just as you should.
Did what you had to do.
That took some big balls.
Like… a lot?
More than two?
[both laughing]
[loud knocking on door]
- Expecting someone?
- Mmm-mmm.
Let us in.
What are you doing with Kylian?
Why the fuck you here?
Why the fuck are any of you here?
Seems we got an issue with you.
I've been told
you were stirring up some shit.
Came to see for myself.
You're talking to me?
[scoffs]
Get the fuck out.
Had no business talkin' to Fatso.
It's fine. We're moving, anyway.
But let's make a few things clear.
Don't ever come back.
Forget about them.
Keep out of my shit. Shut your mouth.
You got it?
- [sucks teeth] Get the fuck out my home!
- [pan sizzling]
[Marvin] Hmm.
Uh-uh.
Have a bite, man. Sit down.
You're gonna piss them off, you know.
You're out of your minds.
Yup.
That's why we need a guarantee.
- Marvin.
- Hang on.
"Hang on"? What are you doing, Kylian?
What's happening?
This is just family business.
- Let us deal with it, yeah?
- What? You're in my house!
- [Marvin] Chloé, please stop. Enough.
- Hell no, I won't stop.
Stuffing your face with my food?
I don't give a fuck.
Kylian…
keep up this act all you want,
but not with me.
Could have a sleepover here too.
Want to piss me off that badly?
In my house?
Do you know what it means
to show up at a safehouse?
Means you're a dead man walking.
Means we'll rearrange your face
till your little girlfriend
can't recognize you anymore.
Brother or not, changes nothing.
Don't pull that shit ever again, Marvin.
Understand me? There are rules
and they go beyond you and I.
So you better swear to me
that you won't be a problem.
Swear.
Say it, Marvin. Who cares?
[sighs] Okay.
Do you swear that there'll
never be any more problems?
I swear. Now beat it.
[gentle music playing]
Thank you.
[gentle music continues]
- [rap beat playing on headphones]
- [rapping indistinctly]
[woman] Ambre? Ambre!
[shouting] Ambre! Clean this now.
[rap beat continues playing]
[in French] ♪ Workin' hard, money's tight
No matter how hard we try ♪
♪ They're waiting for your decline
Show's over 'cause we ain't got a dime ♪
♪ Don't give a fuck what you think
I won't waste my time ♪
♪ Been feelin' dead inside
Since she passed ♪
♪ Got my heart feeling tight ♪
♪ Sandmen, slumlords
I'm wipin' them out just the same ♪
♪ Fuck this shitty life
These rhymes are my escape ♪
♪ I want to succeed
I want to work hard and touch the sky ♪
♪ Sandmen, slumlords
I'm wipin' them out just the same… ♪
- [rap continues in background]
- [man in English] Hey!
[partygoer] Hey! Whoo!
[Ambre rapping continues in background]
[rap beat fading]
Why'd you bring me here?
Got no place to go.
Not welcome at the house anymore.
Wasn't my decision.
Sure.
Never mind.
I'm better off among the dead
than among the living.
[Annabelle] What's that?
[Kylian] It's my shipment.
- How much?
- Taping me?
Are you serious? Come on!
[chuckles] I'm kidding.
Why did you ask me here?
I'll tell you.
But first, I gotta ask you something.
If Marvin and King find out I'm with you,
I'm a dead woman.
Last time, how much did you make?
Four hundred.
How many kilos?
Twenty.
We got eighty.
I got guys in Grenoble who are buying,
but I might have an issue with them.
Why's that?
One of my guys set it all up,
but now I got some problems.
He's not trustworthy.
- The guy you worked with--
- Xhésus.
Xhésus.
You want his digits.
Yeah.
You're still gonna
need someone over there to receive it.
Fatso will be there.
Let me do it.
What? No.
No Xhésus, then.
- All right, I'm off.
- Hang on.
What?
Belle?
- Why is she here?
- Xhésus is her contact.
- What?
- So she's going with you.
Hell no. You better be joking.
You brought this on yourself, man.
You, Peace, K2R,
you forced me to go after my brother.
So this is revenge?
I make changes accordingly.
So we were wrong about your brother?
Should've ignored him?
No, of course not, but all you had to do
was tell me that my brother talked to you.
I would've dealt with him on my own.
You were testing me. Okay.
Let's put everyone to the test,
back to square one.
Everybody's a blank slate,
and right now, Annabelle is going, period.
Do what needs to be done. Don't fuck up.
[introspective rap music playing]
[rap music continues]
[Ambre rapping on phone]
- [Ambre rapping]
- [introspective rap music continues]
- [rap music continues]
- [fire crackling]
Everyone out!
There's smoke, let's go!
Move, go, go!
Let's go, hurry up.
Léo! Where's Léo? Where is he?
It's okay, he's at soccer. Let's go.
Go, run, run! You sure?
[Cassandra] Yes.
Léo! Léo, are you there?
[muffled] God damn it!
[rap music continues]
["No time" by J-One playing]