EPISODE 14
Thank you.
The floor's slippery. Careful.
It's fine. You don't have to.
I told you not to move!
What are you doing?
It's fine.
The doctors were just worried.
I don't need all that.
The smart doctors know what they're doing.
Listen to them.
Don't do anything
on your own from now on, okay?
You don't listen.
Are you hungry?
What are you doing?
Let's just stay like this.
When I thought it was the end,
I regretted it so much.
I was given another chance
but wasn't honest again.
You won't die.
I'm sorry I didn't believe you.
No, I'm sorry.
Yu-ra isn't an easy opponent.
Even after I saw
her unimaginable true colors,
it took over three years
to end it with her.
Someone being beyond your imagination...
I know what you mean.
When you spend a long time with someone,
it's hard to see that person properly.
You try not to believe it.
You only realize it after you see the end.
Your ex-fiancée is trying to kill me,
and Min-hwan and Su-min get paid if I die.
They joined forces.
Ms. Yang's husband's having an affair.
I think my fate moved to Ms. Yang.
It's not over with their marriage.
There's something more.
I have to find that out.
To protect Ms. Yang.
Just stay by my side.
RECENT DESTINATIONS
Wait for me.
Stop it!
CAFE FORBIDDEN LOVE
DRIVE-IN THEATER
CAFE LOVE AFFAIR
HOTEL LONELY
The police think
a drunk driver caused the accident.
They'll never catch her.
We put someone
on Yu-ra, Min-hwan, and Su-min.
But we haven't caught anything yet.
We put people on them after the accident,
so there's no lead.
If you knew in advance,
you should've discussed it with me first.
I wasn't sure that you were on my side.
I'm sorry, Seok-jun.
Don't. I'm not that angry.
The only way is
to find Jeong Man-sik and Bae Hui-suk.
They must be heading for Incheon.
And Oh Yu-ra must be looking for them.
I'm sure.
It's a matter of who's faster.
By the way, how long
do you have to wear the sling?
Until Ji-won tells me to stop wearing it.
Honestly, I can take it off now.
But she promised to take care of me
while I had it on.
Ji-hyuk.
Do you remember anything more
from the accident?
Not really.
I went to the memorial hall to see you.
The car broke down there.
Is that all?
Maybe not,
but I can't think of anything right now.
-Ji-won?
-Yeah?
-Eggs.
-Okay.
What else?
I should go. I'll see you tomorrow.
Thanks for today.
What's wrong?
Ji-won.
Does it hurt again?
I'm sorry.
It's the only thing I could think of.
I can't believe you.
Can you...
stay the night?
Good night.
I'll get the light.
Mr. Yu, what are you doing?
I understand what you mean,
so I'll just hold you.
It still hurts. I swear.
Always be by my side.
No matter what you do,
do it by my side.
That's all I need.
Are you up? I was going to wake you.
Do you want strawberries? It's so good.
It's the yummiest I've had...
What? Did you have a nightmare?
Wait. Does your arm not hurt?
Is it okay now?
It hurts.
No, you were just...
Wow. You know how to lie now.
It's true.
What did you dream about?
It's a secret.
I know we're both assistant managers,
but I'm acting manager,
so I have to say this.
You take a day off too often,
as if you're part of the owner's family.
I had some issues at home.
You did? Is there anyone here
who doesn't have a home?
Is there anyone here
who doesn't have issues at home?
Darn it. Why did the personnel decision
have to be made now?
That jerk is just so lucky.
There's so much work
piling up around us...
Unbelievable.
Shall I help?
-Ms. Yang!
Is it okay to work now?
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, I'm okay.
What?
What are you doing?
Why couldn't I reach you?
Kang Ji-won came to work
as if nothing happened.
What the hell is going on?
Ji-hyuk's been discharged.
That must be why.
I told you to act like nothing happened.
What do you think she'll do?
It's easy to pull her hair and yell
if you want to fight.
Be patient
if you don't want to live like a bum.
Will you come to the gym later?
You'll feel better
after we talk while working out.
This brat is so rude.
I shouldn't get involved
with such low-standard people,
but nothing gets done
if I don't do it myself.
We found Man-sik and Hui-suk.
They were scared, so they tried to hide.
Hello, it's Jeong Man-sik.
It was hard to find you.
Why did you hide? We're in the same boat.
No, it's not because
we couldn't trust you.
We can't trust my daughter.
Just trust me now.
I never abandon my family.
How about going to China for a while?
Shanghai is beautiful.
You can also have some fun in the water
in Hangzhou and Suzhou.
Aren't I pathetic?
At this age, when I feel anxious,
I have nowhere to go but work.
Because you have friends here.
I was worried
and going to go see you anyway.
No, I'm barging in tonight.
I reported it to the police for adultery.
Right. This was
before the law was abolished.
Whenever I was admitted to the hospital,
he brought her home.
So I told him I was being admitted today.
His car dashcam
caught them doing dirty things in the car.
But there's no video. I think it's broken.
And the police said
audio wasn't enough proof.
The dashcam video's not working?
Ridiculous, right?
I really didn't want to go this far,
but I made up my mind
and broke the door lock on my way out.
Ms. Yang.
Can I come with you?
Is that her?
Yes.
Okay, your husband went in 30 minutes ago.
Let's go in 10 minutes.
Who are you people?
What? What is it?
What's going on?
What?
Hey.
Why are you here at this hour?
What?
He said you were in the hospital.
I came to give him some side dishes.
Maybe I was out of line.
I see him at the restaurant often,
so I considered him family.
Hey.
Did you suspect me?
Do you look down on me
since I work for your dad?
-You two...
-What? What is it?
Whatever.
Forget it. Just leave, all of you.
Get out. Hey, you too.
Don't bring anything here
saying you're worried.
Wow, you're making a joke of me.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Get out.
You should go too. I'll talk to him.
You're not leaving?
I'm leaving, but before I go...
What's she doing?
What? What are you doing?
What?
No, don't hit me.
If you touch her, I'll make you pay!
You're crazy!
I'm going to charge you for this!
You came with the cops!
Sir, this...
Isn't this property damage?
This woman used the golf club...
Stop it!
You're so shameless.
Are you happy you weren't caught?
No, I know what you did in the car.
What? You wonder how much
insurance money you'll get if I die?
You laughed about it.
Are you two even human?
What?
That's the car Yeon-ji rides.
Aren't you ashamed?
You're a terrible person.
What are you saying?
You don't even have any proof.
Hey, that's--
Why you...
Are you okay?
No, don't.
You crazy bastard!
No, wait! You can't do this.
-Hold her tight.
-Please calm down. Hold her.
Calm down. Please. You can't do this.
Are you okay, Ji-won?
I'll come back after work tomorrow.
Don't do anything until then.
Thanks, Ji-won.
But it's my business,
so I'll handle it by myself.
I realized earlier.
I don't think he'll break up that easily.
So I'll see a lawyer.
No...
Don't ever meet him alone.
Just call me. I'll come.
Why are you saying such strange things?
You're acting weird.
I know that.
But you would've gotten hurt badly
if it weren't for me earlier.
Just do as I say this once.
I'll be by your side.
You said you'd meet a lawyer.
You can talk with me.
Ms. Yang can trust Mr. Lee.
He always does what he says.
My fate going to someone else...
I don't think it's a coincidence.
If the stress from her indifferent husband
caused her cancer,
where did the fate of being killed by him
come from?
The broken door lock.
The red high heels.
And the candy tin.
Husband having an affair
with someone close...
Or are those scumbags
after the insurance money?
I'll take care of you when my wife dies.
I know what I have to do.
Ji-hyuk,
I have to seduce Min-hwan.
Because Min-hwan must have an affair
and not care if his wife dies.
JEONG SU-MIN, JI-WON'S FRIEND
No, I have to make him think
that he needs to kill her.
I know it'll upset you,
but I have to do it.
If I don't give the fate of being killed
by a cheating husband to Su-min,
Ms. Yang will die.
Can I do this?
Okay.
Do whatever you want.
I'll help you.
-Mr. Kim.
-Yes, sir?
You take over the meal kit project.
Pardon? But the person in charge is...
You joined the team.
You need a project of your own.
You can do it, right?
I want you all to help.
This isn't right, Mr. Yu!
You chose money over me.
Did you not see this coming?
You can't have it both ways, Ji-won.
Fine. I'll find a new job.
In return,
let me finish the meal kit project.
This project belongs to Ms. Yang and me.
It belongs to the company.
Don't let personal matters--
I gave you the meal kit project
because of my personal feelings.
I don't want to see you. Take the day off.
Resigning would be better.
She took the money and broke up with him?
OH YU-RA
Forget it.
Why are you doing this alone?
What?
My position turned to crap
because of someone.
As I said before,
none of this would've happened
if you didn't see Su-min.
Don't be ridiculous.
You screwed me over to switch to Mr. Yu.
You're right.
I am?
But the situation has changed.
Do you want to have a drink with me later?
Eighty billion won?
The chairman said he'd gladly pay me
that much if I broke up with him.
Of course, it's not all cash.
There's real estate too.
He took care of all the taxes too.
So I don't even know how much I have.
An asset manager? I have that too.
Mr. Yu is pretty angry with me
for taking money from the chairman.
But what else was I supposed to do?
It makes sense.
No matter how rich he is, it'd be strange
to just give her that much.
But if it's under the condition
that she stops seeing him,
that makes more sense.
Still, that's a lot...
JEONG SU-MIN, JI-WON'S FRIEND
Why does she have to call now?
MIN-HWAN
What is it?
Shouldn't you be at home at this hour?
I know you're busy.
Thanks for making time for me.
I've wanted to see you.
When I saw you last time,
I was reminded of working together.
Bye, Su-min.
I loved you.
I die today.
You seem different
now that you're married.
Women act like they won't change,
but they change after marriage.
Ji-won, who's not married, gets prettier.
Jeong Su-min.
You should be alert.
Min-hwan and Ji-won...
They dated for seven years
since they're a good fit.
Besides, they see each other often
at work.
Old feelings could come back, and...
Do you remember
the all-you-can-eat restaurant
near my old place?
We went there often.
Yeah.
On days we went there,
you wouldn't let me eat breakfast
or drink water in case I'd feel full.
Why would you remember
something so pathetic?
Why is that pathetic? It's cute.
Back then, everything felt
precious and priceless.
Money wasn't that important to me
when I was with you.
You know I really liked you.
Well, there was no one like you.
You could put up with me too.
So...
you and Yu Ji-hyuk really broke up?
I thought so, but...
Actually, I almost had
a big accident recently.
Accident?
It was with a dump truck,
so I would've died.
But Mr. Yu came out of nowhere and...
Everything got complicated then.
Complicated?
Yes, horribly complicated.
Do you know
who the driver of that truck was?
No, how would I know that?
It was Su-min's dad.
She knew everything.
Stop lying.
You keep lying and lying!
I want to.
I want to stop it too.
Where are you?
Shouldn't you tell me what's going on?
I'm going crazy stuck at home.
Why won't you come home?
Are you with Kang Ji-won...
They dated for seven years
since they're a good fit.
No.
No way.
He wanted to kill her...
What's going on? Move!
Are you really my girlfriend?
Avocado!
Kang Ji-won.
I love you.
You didn't know she'd stoop so low,
did you?
I didn't either.
I get she hates me,
but how could she try to kill me?
She's crazy.
I didn't just see her true colors
with this accident.
Mr. Yu...
put someone on me.
If not, how could he have shown up?
We hadn't met since we broke up.
It doesn't make sense.
I think I'm going crazy.
I feel like I'm being watched.
I'm so scared.
What do I do in this situation?
So you haven't come to work because...
It was because of me.
I couldn't just leave him.
Fortunately, he wasn't hurt that badly.
So he's been discharged.
But when I told him we were through,
he told me to resign.
She's telling the truth.
Something felt off, and this was it.
Yes, Yu Ji-hyuk is rich,
so she was right to switch over to him.
And she was also right
to break up with him for 80 billion won.
She wouldn't make a good wife
for a rich guy.
If she has 80 billion won,
I shouldn't kill her.
If she dies, her mom and the others
will split the money.
Nothing will come to me.
But if I seduce her again,
that 80 billion won will come to me.
Can you break up with Su-min?
What?
You know how scary she is now.
Come back to me.
I can't do this alone...
Never mind, I should go.
Ji-won.
I'll call you.
I'm sorry. I'm sure you hated to see that.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
If I don't do this,
I don't think I can keep sane.
You like me a lot, don't you?
No, well...
Earlier, Min-hwan seemed
to be regretting what he did.
Min-hwan?
He's probably crunching numbers
in his head right now.
-Hey.
-Are you coming today?
I was just about to call.
I think things will get easier.
I just met with Kang Ji-won.
She has no idea I was involved.
So you just have to take care
of Ji-won's mom and Su-min's dad.
Then she'll come to me
with 80 billion won.
And you can get U&K or Yu Ji-hyuk.
Do whatever you want.
We'll become each other's support forever.
Yeah, I see.
That's nice and easy.
He underestimates his ex-girlfriend.
I told you, didn't I?
Men aren't wary
of the women they've slept with.
Where's Jeong Man-sik and Bae Hui-suk?
When you were younger,
you looked just like that actor.
I looked better.
You were handsome.
What shall we do in China?
Let's kill them.
Pardon?
Is it because of what Min-hwan said?
No, nothing bad can come from it.
If Ji-won wants to return to Min-hwan,
she shouldn't find out
that he tried to kill her.
And even if she's up to something,
she can't prove anything
with those two gone.
Also, it's easier than stowing them away.
Let's get a divorce.
We don't have kids.
Honestly, I have no reason
to live with you.
Nothing good came from being with you.
Oh, right.
You still can't reach your dad?
Did you
meet Kang Ji-won?
Yeah, I saw her at work.
Why do you ask?
I thought about it.
If you and Ji-won get back together...
then only I'll get screwed over.
OUT OF BUSINESS
What's going on?
Did you get a call?
He wouldn't do something like this.
He could've told us.
Are we fired? What's going on?
Eun-ho, I'm sorry.
I had to close Werther
for personal reasons.
It's been great working with you.
I hope we meet again one day.
He closed Werther?
Suddenly?
-This is insane.
-What the hell?
Everyone,
I had to close Werther.
Your severance pay has been wired.
-Closed?
-I'm sorry.
What did you get?
He'll pay a month's salary...
We're unemployed.
What's going on?
How did this happen?
Someone's coming.
Why were they in there?
Chef? Come on in.
Double the pay.
Your boss here suddenly
decided to sell me the restaurant
at double the market price.
It was a good choice.
It's a choice you can make too.
If you help me, this expensive restaurant
will become yours.
What do I have to do?
You have two choices.
One, take the restaurant.
Two, lose your job.
Chef!
My heart fluttered when you contacted me!
When Ji-won turned me down,
it was nice to get comforted by you.
Is something wrong?
I'm unemployed now.
Why?
Just because.
Come on!
Still, you're famous and handsome...
Most importantly,
your food tastes so good!
So...
you may be unemployed for a second,
-but you--
-This industry's small.
The restaurant suddenly closed.
So all the gossipers will
talk about me.
I know that. It's the same with me.
People don't believe us
without even trying to know the story.
If only a decent chef appeared...
Ms. Kang.
-Hey!
-Hey.
Why didn't I think of you?
But I don't know if I can be of any help.
What are you talking about?
Can we talk privately for a second?
-Sure.
-Let's go.
So it was a woman?
Yeah.
Thanks for telling me.
And I'm so sorry. No harm will go to you.
That's not why I told you.
Anyway, I didn't tell Hui-yeon.
Oh Yu-ra bought Werther
and asked Eun-ho to help her.
He said no, and she fired him.
And she didn't tell him
what she needed help with.
I know what it is. Don't worry.
I'll call you back later.
I'm with someone right now.
You have two choices.
One, help me.
Two, go down with Oh Yu-ra.
I'm sure you know which to choose
if you're not a fool.
What do I have to do?
This is Kang Ji-won, Marketing Team 1.
Hello, this is Park Min-hwan
from U&K Marketing Team 3.
I was wondering
if you could meet me tonight.
For the mistakes I've made,
I want to treat you.
I'd be grateful.
I'm always ready.
I hope it marks a new beginning.
You can look forward to it.
Okay.
GENERAL MANAGER YU JI-HYUK
-Just a moment.
-Sure.
Yes?
Park Min-hwan already has a woman.
What?
You said you couldn't get them!
You seemed down, so I asked around.
So I sent limited-edition red high heels.
Along with the candy tin you spoke of.
What's this?
Someone brought it today.
Shall I get rid of it?
No, just leave it.
It reminds me of the old days.
Then I don't need to play
with Min-hwan anymore.
Thanks for waiting.
But I don't think I can do dinner.
If it's because of work, it can be helped.
I'm free tomorrow too.
I'm even free on the weekends.
I'm meeting with you after all.
I'm free whenever.
No.
What I mean is...
I'll never do business with you.
What?
The only thing you know
how to do is sugarcoat things.
You ruin everything you touch,
and aim for insurance fraud.
You're too incompetent to work with.
What really surprised me
is your HR method.
You especially excel
at recruiting female talent.
I was surprised,
since you just got married.
You're amazing in many ways.
Good luck in the future.
What client is such a scumbag?
JI-WON. I'M SO ASHAMED OF MYSELF...
What are you waiting for?
Shall I light the fire?
It's my first time seeing someone die.
But it's boring.
Still, I feel better.
I don't think I fit in Korea.
Nothing goes right here.
Right. About that restaurant,
what do I do with that?
Shall I tear it down?
Okay, fine. Let's divorce.
OH
CALL
Hello, this is Oh Yu-ra.
Hello, my name's Jeong Su-min.
There.
It fits perfectly.
Why is everything working out so well?
I'll be there in five minutes.
Finish up and come down.
Yes, this is Kang Ji-won
of Marketing Team 1.
Hello?
Who are you?
Why would you suddenly call here?
I'm sorry. You didn't pick up your phone.
It's in my purse. I didn't know. Sorry.
I'll get there in about 15 minutes.
Okay.
Kang Ji-won.
Ji-won.
Are you scared?
We need to talk.
Come out.
Let's talk.
Well?
We have a lot to talk about.
You should've known your place.
This is the problem with women.
Was it fun messing with me?
GENERAL MANAGER YU JI-HYUK
Hey, Ji-hyuk's calling.
Will you not pick up?
Then I'll pick it up.
Damn it...
SLIDE TO POWER OFF
You've got a strong stomach.
I like money.
But aren't those rich people disgusting?
They disgust me.
What are you doing?
How dare you mess with me?
Let go of me! Let go!
What? Are you scared?
Why did you make a mockery of me?
Ji-won.
I really wanted to go back to you.
I wanted to try hard this time!
You tried to kill me.
You...
tricked me.
You treated me like crap!
You can kill others,
but your life's that precious?
I thought about how to pay you back.
I could just give Su-min to you,
but how do I send you to hell?
What?
Hell?
Do you want to die?
This was it.
Kill me.
But kill me for sure this time.
Or I'll kill you.
Die.
You want me to kill you, so I will.
Are you laughing?
Just die.
Kill me.
Ji-won, are you okay?
Ji-won, wake up.
Ji-won.
Ji-won!
You disgusting bastard.
Was I destined to die
in Park Min-hwan's hands?
Ji-won!
You can't do this
because you fight better.
I hate using my strength.
But not to you.
-Ji-hyuk.
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry for everything.
Did you try to kill Ji-won?
Why is everyone looking for Kang Ji-won?
I'll try to move Min-hwan.
I'll take care of Su-min
so she won't bother you.
If Su-min disappears,
there won't be anyone to threaten you.
I have to take care of you to start over.
Translated by Suyun Mounce