(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
Thank you.
You're not some young couple anymore.
Why are you thanking him?
Let's get out of here first.
Fine.
I'll trust you for now.
I agree to work with you.
You can take the others.
But not Lu Wuyi.
Why?
She matters to me more than anyone.
Among the relics left in the Ruined Sand,
there's a portrait of a mortal woman
named Di Zhu.
Lu Wuyi looks exactly like her.
From the moment
she was born in the Sacred Spring,
you shaped her face like Di Zhu's.
I never understood this before.
You're Jiu Ying.
You shouldn't be able to obtain
their memories
from the Primordial Sacred Spring.
But now I see.
You created Lu Wuyi to gather
everyone's emotions and memories.
Thus, you controlled
the entire Formless Moon Sect.
You made up the lie of a "fated one"
and sent her to get close to me.
What?
Now that your plan works,
you want to take her back from me?
The plan works?
You actually think Lu Wuyi likes you?
Then why not let her stay with me
and keep watching me?
I'll take all of them with me.
You're nothing more than leftovers
after I devoured
your memories and spat you out.
It was only my power
that gave you this new body.
You've always wanted to know who you are,
but Bai Ze and Chi Wen,
who knew the truth all along,
kept it from you.
Your Master Dragon Deity
knew your confusion and your doubts,
and yet he said nothing.
He simply let you go on
playing the commander,
serving him, fighting for him,
and dying for him.
Just like
he did with Ji Ling.
How pitiful.
I have one more secret to tell you.
Come closer.
This body
won't last much longer.
Heavenly Sticks can see fate and destiny.
Prying into fate comes at a cost.
Every divination must be paid
for with one's own power and lifespan.
Since you're here,
shall we exchange bodies?
SERVE THE SCALES, UPHOLD THE RIGHT
Wangyan, what do we do next?
Destroy the Oracle Stone.
Kill Jiu Ying, who's attached to it.
But when the next full moon comes,
we'll still be summoned back
to the Formless Moon Sect.
If we fail before then…
We'll have
to sever our tails.
Looks like he knows who he is now.
I know who I am too.
Body returns to dust.
Spirit is carried away by the wind.
May you be freed from your obsessions,
and in your next life, live long, healthy,
and in peace.
You left your blade
in Ruined Sand, didn't you?
I'll go with you.
I should've brought it back
to the Shilin Sect for you.
But no one but you can wield
the Mountain Demon Blade.
Go retrieve it.
Is there a problem?
That six-eyed butterfly demon
called himself Yuan Wuhuo.
He looks exactly like Commander Li.
What is it?
Nothing.
It reminded me of back then,
when you sent me to Mount Nandang
to pull out the blade.
That's how I got this weapon,
which has stayed by my side ever since.
I've checked it.
He's not Yuan Wuhuo.
That's good.
What about you?
Are you alright?
You know full well
the Dragon Deity's Power has long blended
with your own demon power.
If you try to separate it,
the backlash will be fatal.
You can't be saved.
I've given all my demon power
to protect my inner core.
I can still hold on a little longer.
I want to walk
this final journey with you.
Don't worry about me.
Wu Shiguang is waiting for you.
Go to Luo'an.
Take back the last trace
of Dragon Deity's Power from Han Ba.
Wangyan,
what kind of secret
do the two dragons share?
Why did they hide it from us?
Probably just something between men.
Don't overthink it.
We've kept plenty from them too.
You came all this way because
you heard I was captured by Jiu Ying?
I was worried you'd get skinned
and turned into a fox-fur coat.
Too bad I was late.
Missed my chance to play the hero.
Hero, what's your name?
Call me sister.
I only have one sister.
Greedy Wolf Demon Hunter
of the Northern Dipper. Si Feng.
I can tell.
That double-flower mark
on her forehead is hard to miss.
Since when did
a thousand-year-old fox like you
get so close to a ruthless demon hunter
from the Big Dipper?
I didn't know that.
Honestly, neither did I.
What has happened?
Were you waiting for me?
I was.
And you are?
What's the matter?
You're at it again.
We've met before. Many times.
If I'd met someone
as powerful as you that often,
I wouldn't have forgotten.
What if your memory was erased?
Master Chi Wen left you a message.
The Oracle Stone can't be trusted.
If you have doubts,
seal away part of your memory
inside this artifact.
Retrieve it later,
and it'll remind you of the truth.
Let me remind you of something.
The first time we met
was because of Han Ba.
Han Ba?
Have you figured out
why Jiu Ying erased the memory
of our first meeting?
No.
I only know I was on a mission.
A mission?
We always act together.
We've never taken solo missions.
That's strange.
But we're heading
to Luo'an soon to find Han Ba.
When we get there,
we'll get to the bottom of this.
I've seen all of Chi Wen's memories.
What did you see?
No one here should sacrifice yourselves.
There's another way.
Just lend me your demon power.
As for returning the deity power,
I have my own plan.
You're free.
Your will is your own.
Whether you choose
slaughter or protection,
that's up to you.
Fuse our reverse scales together
and create the Tenth Dragon Son.
That will be
our final hope for this world.
You're not Chi Wen.
And you're not my brother.
From now on,
you're neither demon nor human.
You are Chi Wen.
The last Dragon Deity in this world.
But you've been carrying
the burden my brothers left you,
the hopes of the world,
and a lie meant to deceive it.
I know you've been waiting for me.
How long must I keep lying?
Until the Tenth Dragon Son awakens
and becomes a true dragon.
Only then will your mission end.
The Tenth Dragon Son?
I'm sorry.
I made you wait so long.
It has been a long time.
Too long.
But at least
you're here now.
Once the Dragon Deity's Power is complete
and you return to your rightful place,
I can finally lay this burden down.
Everyone calls you Master Chi Wen.
But what is your real name?
Before you became
Master Dragon Deity, who were you?
Ji Ling.
My name
is Ji Ling.
Ji, as in "a fleeting life".
Ling, as in "a kindred understanding".
Sir, what's your name?
My name is Ji Ling.
Ji, as in "a fleeting life".
Ling, as in "a kindred understanding".
I knew it.
You are Ji Ling.
Ji Ling.
One day,
you'll admit it yourself.
I'll ask you one last time.
Are you Ji Ling?
Give Ji Ling back to me. Give him back!
No.
I'm not Ji Ling.
You are Ji Ling.
You are
Ji Ling.
Why did you make all these puppets?
Since I became the Dragon Deity,
I've rarely left the Scale Cave.
The Dragon Deity may be immortal
and free to roam the world,
but I… was just an ordinary fox.
You're a fox too?
But
not a noble nine-tailed fox
from Green Hills like you.
I was just a foolish red fox
born by Yumian Lake.
A wild fox?
That's cute.
If I were killed out there by demons,
my disguise as the Dragon Deity
would fall apart.
I've stayed in this cave so long.
I keep thinking about who I used to be.
Back then, I was naïve and childish.
But I lived every moment sincerely.
I was simpler and freer than I am now.
Like the warm summer wind
brushes through the trees.
Back then, I knew little,
so I had fewer regrets.
The worst thing was just
not getting fresh raspberries in winter.
Later, I came across an old spell
in the ancient scrolls of Wanlin Pavilion.
It has a beautiful name.
Severed Silk.
It takes a piece of one's life
and cuts it out,
like trimming fabric
and weaving patterns into silk.
Once separated,
that piece becomes its own being,
bearing the same appearance,
personality, and memories as its owner,
only without life.
So the Ji Ling you met
was created that way.
Are you a demon hunter
from the mortal world?
I'm a demon hunter of the Shilin Sect.
I sent him out to feel the mountain winds,
the life of the mortal world,
joy,
sorrow,
adventure,
and love.
He lived that life
in my place to experience
a colorful life.
He'd go out, then return,
bringing the lively world outside to me,
while I stay in solitude.
Then how did you end up
in the Shilin Sect?
How did you become the Dragon Deity?
When the meteor blast happened,
the earth shook.
I was blind since childhood.
I couldn't see the rocks falling
and failed to escape.
I was buried under rubble
at the foot of South Mountain.
Master Chi Wen saved me.
He took pity on me
and said a blind little fox like me
couldn't survive on my own.
So he brought me to the disaster site
and granted me a healing spell
so that I could help others.
Sadly,
I was too young
and couldn't take human form.
The power he gave me was limited.
Once it was used up, that was it.
So some people
couldn't be saved.
Xizai.
Xizai!
Where's your sacred power?
Save him! Come on!
Save my brother. And I'll let you go.
What happened after that?
Wangyan and the others are waiting for us.
That story is too long.
I could talk day and night
and still not finish it.
Once we return from Luo'an,
I'll tell you slowly.
Promise.
That's childish, wild fox.
In the past,
only Li Jie and the Four Great Demons
knew I wasn't the Dragon Deity.
Now that it's out in the open,
I actually feel a lot lighter.
From now on, I'll call you Ji Ling.
Is that alright?
Can you give me this doll?
I can trade you something else for it.
This little fox
is the most precious thing I own.
Nothing is worth trading for it.
Back then, when I was imprisoned here,
it was the one that stayed with me
through those dark days.
I even thought…
What was it?
It saved me.
When I was at my lowest, it comforted me
and gave me the courage to go on.
How could a rag doll comfort you?
Don't tell me it talks.
It really does.
See? I knew you'd react like that.
No one ever believes me.
But it's true.
Whenever my tears fell on it,
it was like it could feel my sadness.
It would make soft sounds like a real fox.
Awu… awu…
It was telling me,
"Don't cry.
Don't be sad.
I'll stay with you."
That's ridiculous.
If it were real, someone
must've cast a spell on it.
You're messing with me again, aren't you?
I'm not lying.
Maybe it's because you're here.
It's shy.
But I haven't heard its voice
in a long time.
Here.
Isn't this your most treasured thing?
You said you wouldn't trade it.
That's right. I wouldn't trade it.
I'm not asking for anything in return.
I'm giving it to you because I want to.
Right now, there's nothing
more precious to me than you.
Whatever you want,
I'll get it for you.
I want your heart.
Will you give me that too?
Yes.
Master Dragon Deity,
what's gotten into you?
You weren't like this before.
You've got quite a smooth tongue.
I'll say whatever you want to hear.
I'll do anything for you.
I want the stars and the moon.
I'll find a way.
Master Dragon Deity,
something's wrong with you.
You've become a different person.
I haven't changed.
I'm Ji Ling.
Before
or now,
all I ever wanted was for you to be happy.
Get some rest. We leave
for Luo'an tomorrow morning.
You gave me the little fox,
so I'll give you something in return.
But first, close your eyes.
Alright.
What are you thinking about?
I…
I've put it on.
You're not allowed
to run away in this lifetime.
What is this?
This is also something I treasure.
They're Twin Luminous Cicadas.
They come as a pair.
No matter how far apart they are,
if one lights up,
the other will glow as well.
If you miss me, tap it.
As long as I see it light up,
I'll know
you're thinking of me.
Why has your scent grown fainter?
You're being silly again.
I didn't expect the Master Bai Ze
who knows all things in the world
would still need to read books.
I'm looking for an ancient way
to extend one's lifespan.
Master Dragon Deity,
if I can't walk with you
to the very end of your life,
that would be my regret.
You're still calling me that?
In my heart,
you are Master Dragon Deity.
So,
old man, you'd better stay alive.
The last three spirit fragments
of Jiu Ying have been found.
One is inside Wu Shiguang.
One is inside the Oracle Stone.
The last one…
I've checked it.
It's inside Lu Wuyi.
Inside the Star Stone illusion,
none of us could use our powers.
But Lu Wuyi could still use
Word Magic and Frost Spell.
And yet her power came and went.
It was unstable.
It didn't take long
for me to understand why.
Only when that little snake,
Little Nine, was nearby…
That's intense.
…could she cast her spells.
And when Little Nine moved away,
her power vanished.
What happened to my power?
That little snake is Jiu Ying.
So you suspect Lu Wuyi and Jiu Ying
share some unique bond,
which is why she can use power?
Exactly.
I questioned Jiu Ying
in the Formless Moon Palace.
Now I understand.
You created Lu Wuyi
to gather everyone's emotions
and memories.
Thus, you controlled
the entire Formless Moon Sect.
I've also confirmed
that the fragment is inside Lu Wuyi.
I don't think
I can walk this road with you to the end.
Because the end…
The end
means Lu Wuyi's death.
If we want to destroy Jiu Ying completely,
Lu Wuyi
must die.
I know
I'm about to lose her.
So,
I'll give her
anything she wants.
I want your heart.
Will you give me that too?
Yes.
Do you know?
In this world,
no one can see the new moon.
Only I can.
She is
my moon alone.