Are you...
It hurts...
Screw this...!
Is this some kind of trend or what?
Levi, that's the guy!
His level is the highest!
Run!
(Scum of the Brave)
No money to carry into tomorrow, so hungry, getting hit hard
Playing bossa nova and
earning my day-to-day cash
And the thugs
are running wild in the streets
I'm just standing here,
staring at you with my dead-looking eyes
There's not a single thing I can teach you
Yeah...
Let's just keep surviving over and over,
making fools of ourselves
Since we're both not normal
You can't save with "I-love-you"
This town is sick
Gradually, watching carefully,
get through it all
That single moment in slow motion,
the battle's going good
You and me,
we're so arrogant and so uncute
Telling transparent lies
Do you want to be strong?
Want to be loved?
Stay quiet, you fool!
Too early to say the "last of us"
Today's day will soon be memorial
Gradually, watching carefully,
bite into it and hang on
Let's put on a poker face and go
Still the same, you and me,
we're so arrogant and so uncute
Telling transparent lies
You can't save with "I-love-you"
You can't save a single soul
Telling transparent lies
(#7 The Death of a Brave)
Hey!
Let go of me!
Dammit!
It's not what you think it is.
I'm just...
Don't waste my time.
Go.
Get your ass movin'.
Now!
She did track me after all.
They might still be nearby.
Let's track them.
This chick has ether perception
that lets her hunt her mark.
That badge...
What's that mark?
Dragon?
She's actually dead set
on killing me.
Hey, let's not do this.
It's gonna be a mess
if a guard pops up here, right?
Fast reaction you got there.
The enhancement type, huh?
You can say...
The tables have now turned.
One thing, however.
I won't negotiate.
You've gotta be kidding me.
This brat's losing
her damn mind.
Master!
Your beautiful disciple
has come to rescue you!
Couldn't you put on a happier look?
I told you to run.
Where's Indo?
She's fine!
She's surely made
a clean escape by now.
That's not what I meant.
I'm telling you to bring
in a decent backup.
Read the room, will ya!
And now,
I've got an extra block of dead weight,
and that chick is physically
stronger than me.
If I had a real sword,
I'd just chop off a few fingers.
Too bad I only have this
toy with me.
Wish I could figure out what her
ether perception is sniffing...
It's her sense of smell, Master.
She seems to follow scent.
Rather...
She decisively identifies
how things would smell.
For example,
like a well-polished mirror...
No, like dripping watercolor
paint onto damp sand.
Jogamine...
Well done.
Go jump off a bridge later.
Y-Yes!
I'm honored!
It seems my literary talent
has proven useful!
I wasn't praising you.
Besides, explain things
in under two secs next time.
You yap too damn much!
Allow me to treat you...
...with an ultimate move.
This is the bind state when
swords clash with one another.
One wrong push or pull
and you're dead.
A split-second clash.
Which means,
the stage is now mine.
G-Great work, Master!
I've crushed her nose,
which is her key for tracking.
But who the hell is she?
At the very least,
she's not an official guard.
Should I kill her?
Getting rid of her corpse
would be a hassle, though...
Master!
I'd stop if I were you.
If we fight here,
one of us is going to die.
You're strong, huh?
I get that a lot.
What's the deal with her?
She ain't no assassin sent
after me, right? She a mad dog or what?
Sorry about her.
Guess she got a little worked up
after you guys got the upper hand.
She's got a lot of pride.
Aight.
You wanna have at it, too?
Nah.
How about we both
just call it a day?
I'll turn a blind eye to this.
If you actually reflected on this,
then we'll spare you.
But never trespass
on our Academy again!
My master and I will stop you
as many times as it takes!
Well, much obliged.
What say you, Mister Master?
We're leaving.
Yes!
Bye.
My Master...
He called that move
the "drawing in" technique.
Once you lock swords in a bind,
you give it a little push.
If the opponent
reflexively pushes back,
you pull your sword and
break their balance.
If they, instead,
try to pull away,
the bind comes loose,
Yashiro Punch!
and that's when you strike.
Easier said than done, though.
It takes practice and experience.
Master.
Was that a special lecture
to reward my devotion?
Don't make me laugh.
What were you on to end up with
such a dumb, happy-go-lucky brain?
Too much E3?
No, that's not it.
I'm the same as you, Master.
My father often told me
stories about you.
Huh?
I can't describe how moved I was
when we first met that night.
Hurry and get yourself
to the hospital.
See ya.
You don't look as gentle,
so I was shocked at first.
A delinquent-looking loser,
saying the kindest things.
That was my impression.
But it all makes sense once
I delved into your thoughts.
Wait.
What's the name of your father?
Kiyohito Takamiya.
And you'd be right in saying
that he is your master, Master.
Are you... not aware of this?
I thought Mr. Ishinoo had told you.
When my parents divorced,
I went with my mother,
but I was still able to see
my father once a month.
Each time, he told me about how
wonderful the job of a Brave was.
That master of mine?
Talking about how wonderful the job was?
I respect my father, Master.
Why did you decide to become a Brave?
It was seven years ago.
I dropped out of high school
for personal reasons
and got kicked out of
my family's house.
I ended up part-timing under some
small-time Demon King around Ikebukuro.
Back then, the west side
of the Yamanote Line...
...was a battleground crowded
with upstart Demon Kings,
which made it a perfect
hunting ground for Braves.
The one who came strolling in...
...and stole my job...
...was "Nine-Finger" Kiyohito Takamiya.
After my employer was killed,
I was in a bind.
So I had no choice but to become his
apprentice and serve as his assistant.
I believe my father understood
the feelings of the weak.
That's why he held such high ideals.
Even in the line of work that
could be sinful at times,
he still had the will
to pursue what was best.
He always told me happily about
your exploits as his disciple.
He said you had extraordinary talent,
a Brave with a bright future.
Your battle with Lord "Radiance Serpent"
and the Shinjuku 6/17 conflict.
What the hell is this discrepancy?
That's nothing like the master I knew.
The master I knew was cowardly,
bad at handling pressure.
A man who always seemed
to be afraid of something.
And that's exactly why he was
meticulous, ruthless, and merciless.
"Bein' a Brave is a gig
for the scummiest scum."
He used to say that all the time.
"It's not a job you stick with for long.
Once you've made a decent pile of cash,
you should head off to Hawaii,
catch some fish,
and live out your days."
I also think this line of work is shitty.
It's been years...
...since his passing.
Looks like he was lying to you.
An ideal Brave is someone who
likes killing and is good at it.
Still...
It remains true that you saved us.
Aren't those words different
from your own ideals?
Is it?
That's what your old man taught me.
No, Master.
It's you...
Go home.
My head hurts...
Is the E3 causing this?
No...
It's Jogamine's fault.
I should get back to Ed's bar.
Get some beers,
eat some pizza,
play some card games.
My own version of a good world.
(Scum of the Brave)
You're late.
Huh?
What were you doing?
Eating a hamburger.
Liar.
I'm serious.
Ed...
No, where's the manager?
He left so suddenly, saying that
he's going out to eat.
He left with this guy named Maruta.
How does this place
even stay in business?
You should've just gone home.
It's already late.
What are you, a delinquent?
How can I not be worried after
the way we parted like that?
I'm worried about whether
you were okay or not.
You're surprisingly reasonable.
Huh?! Are you making fun of me?!
No, I'm complimenting you.
As in, you've got common sense.
You're a considerate,
decent person.
Shut up!
Your ether perception...
...it tells you where enemies are.
Or rather, it tells you their strength.
Not in images or numbers,
rather a sixth sense type?
Yeah.
My dad said it lets me feel an opponent's
strength and the level of threat.
Like heat or pressure...
...that kind of dangerous feeling.
Well, you were fine against
that monster the other day,
but nearly collapsed in front
of that tiny woman.
There's no other explanation.
Yeah... I was scared.
You probably think I'm not
cut out to be a Brave, right?
Yeah.
You're a good person,
so quit being a Brave.
Like hell I will, you idiot.
My master told me that being afraid of
your enemies is nothing to be ashamed of.
But you have to control it,
lest you die.
Only lots of experience will
get you used to it.
No one talks for Jogamine, though.
She's a special kind of nut.
That brat...
You know...
What's the deal with her?!
When she's not even reading minds, but...
How do you even deal with her?
Ah...
It's not like she is trying
to read our minds.
She'd tell us
if she's using her ability.
Apparently with people
she's just met,
it's hard for her to block their channel,
so she ends up hearing things.
I don't think she'll read you
unless she has to.
Did something happen?
Nothing.
I've only been teamed up
with her since the last training,
so I don't know her well.
But she's not a bad person.
"Not a bad person"?
That's what people would say
when they've got nothing good to say.
Well, I do think that she's weird.
She meddles when nobody asks,
and shows up to help even
when she's obviously useless.
It's like she runs on sheer
stubbornness or something.
But I don't really dislike her.
That Jogamine, I mean.
I do hate her!
I'm telling you this because
you're a good person!
That kind of person...
'Sup, Joe.
Ed Cyrus isn't present
at the moment.
Got back from work?
Did you already screw up?
Shut the hell up.
Oh, right.
Maruta finally paid
a visit here after a while.
Looks like he went out with Ed,
but while they're gone,
let's go grab some food too.
Joe?
Ah, nothing...
Yashiro, what are you gonna do?
What do you mean,
what am I gonna do?
I saw it on the evening news.
I then asked someone
who knows the details.
They found a corpse
with a goofy face...
...in an alley in Shin-Okubo
this morning.
Then it must be...
It's honestly ridiculous.
I saw the photos.
He's stabbed all over, with a
finishing blow to the throat.
His neck was split open like this.
Even if he came back as a ghost,
he wouldn't be able to talk.
I see.
He's already...
Also, look at this.
Apparently the body was clutching it.
Pretty nice, right? So when are we
having the funeral party?
Yeah.
After we've done taking care of
the thing that we should've first.
What? What happened?
You guys look scary.
Pretty sure you're just seeing things.
We'll find the one who killed Ishinoo,
and make them suffer worse than hell.
That's the only thing
bastards like us can do.
(#8 The Sin of the Brave)