[Fenglinwan Hotel]
Qiqi,
I'm sorry.
It's the same old problem again.
It's okay.
I can wait.
Ms. Zhou.
They're all waiting for you
to start the meeting.
Let them wait.
How long will that be?
Wait until the cows come home.
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 7]
What a windfall.
Now I finally get
why you kept provoking the bear.
Turns out,
you had everything under control.
I was just playing it by ear.
Sometimes, you've got to improvise.
Don't be so modest.
If you'd told me earlier we were
doing a straight-man-funny-man act,
I could've played along
even better.
Alright, next time then.
We tracked down the whistleblower
this fast—
honestly, I still can't quite believe it.
No wonder Chief Zhang said before
that if we want
to investigate Lu Zheng's case,
we have to start
with Ye Jian's case first.
That foresight is really incredible.
Every case must
have a crack somewhere.
We just have to find it.
As we keep looking, we'll find it.
But Lu Yibo still refuses to say
who exactly he reported.
So Chief Lu's case
still lacks hard evidence.
Sometimes saying nothing
speaks louder than anything.
You reported Zhou Rong?
Have you lost your mind?
Six months ago,
a police chief died.
I had a feeling that
it had something to do with Mr. Rong.
So I wrote the report letter.
Why?
Because I love you.
Because of my own issues.
I started suspecting
you were lonely
and slept with Zhou Rong.
I suspected you two were having an affair.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I'm not that kind
of woman with no boundaries!
Qiqi, Qiqi.
I already got
the report letter back.
What's the point of getting it back now?
The police have already
shown up at the door.
If Zhou Rong finds out
you were the one who reported him—
we're both finished!
You're really that scared of him?
Who do you think Zhou Rong is?
There's nothing that man wouldn't do.
Let me ask you something.
Are you with me
because you like me—
or because
I'm Zhou Rong's close friend?
I love you.
You're the only one I love.
So we have to
think long-term about this.
Understand?
I understand.
So what do we do now?
Does Zhou Rong know about your problem?
We need to make the first move.
Bro,
I've still got some nuts left.
Let's split them.
I'm not hungry. You can eat them all.
Cut the crap.
Give me your hand.
I'm not the type to hog it all.
Hurry.
It smells so good.
Too bad there's barely any left.
Bro,
he still hasn't moved?
Bro, can we...
We can't.
I know you want to leave
and come back tomorrow.
But what if the moment we leave,
he leaves too?
And tomorrow, the second we come back,
he comes back too?
What should we do then?
It's your turn.
Hello?
Director Fang,
this is Geng from the radio station.
Hello, Director Geng.
Director Fang, here's the thing—
that large-scale
interactive musical,
and prose poetry recital you planned,
"My Distant Horizon, Your Poetry"...
it may need to be postponed.
What?
No.
Why?
So when exactly is it airing?
Well...
I'm still right here, you know!
You can't treat me like this!
Bro, he moved.
Really?
Let's go.
Bro.
Shouldn't we wait a little longer?
Security's just
a little tighter, that's all.
Do you know Warren Buffett?
He makes big money—
money from tens of thousands of people.
And he summed it all up in one
valuable piece of advice:
"Be fearful when others are greedy,
and greedy when others are fearful."
Think about it—
how many people would actually dare
commit a burglary in broad daylight?
When others are fearful—
that's our turn to get greedy.
Let's do it.
In the dark night,
I ride a black horse
through thorns and into the darkness.
The moment you wielded your long sword
and slew the dragon—
it made me see the morning glow
for the first time.
[Incoming Call: Mentor]
Mentor.
Zhang Yi'ang.
How is your investigation going?
Ye Jian's case
and Lu Zheng's case,
any progress on them?
Yes, there is.
But,
on Ye Jian's case,
we ran into some obstacles.
So for now,
we're starting with Chief Lu's case.
Alright, alright.
I know what you're capable of.
I have some good news.
I have some good news too.
Zhang Yi'ang is stepping up.
Go ahead.
Tell me your good news.
We found the whistleblower.
Who is it?
Lu Yibo.
Well done.
The Provincial Department
just confirmed it too—
the whistleblower
was indeed Lu Yibo.
See, it really was Lu Yibo.
Zhang Yi'ang,
follow this lead
and keep digging.
The truth is about to surface.
Mentor, rest assured.
Understood.
Mr. Rong.
Plan A:
Fang Yong once published
a poetry collection,
and it's impossible to find it elsewhere.
The only copy left is an archive edition
[My Distant Horizon, Your Poetry]
at the city library.
[Fang Yong]
I had someone make a replica.
You can take it to him
and ask him to sign it—
it'd also be
a good chance to get closer to him.
[Index]
Isn't that basically piracy?
Is it?
You want me to walk up to the author
with a pirated copy
and ask for his signature?
How exactly am I supposed
to get close to him like that?
My apologies, I didn't think it through.
Plan B:
I was going to name our company's
next residential project
as "Yong Residence."
Then we can invite Fang Yong
to cut the ribbon.
What do you think?
Yong Residence...
Mediocre (Yong) Residence?
Does that mean
only mediocre people live there?
Sorry, I didn't think
that one through either.
How about this—we find a park
and build a life-size bronze statue
of Fang Yong?
That man is alive and perfectly well.
Why on earth would you
build a statue for him?
Isn't that a bit over the top?
-Sir. Sir.
-Let's find another...
Mr. Zhou.
This gentleman insisted on seeing you.
I couldn't stop him.
Mr. Fang.
[My Distant Horizon, Your Poetry]
This copy's printed
way better than my own.
Can I have it?
[My Distant Horizon, Your Poetry]
Mr. Fang.
This is just a sample, actually.
We were planning
to make a gold-foil edition
and have it delivered to your home.
Your writing
is profound
and brings readers a rare sense of peace.
To be honest, just now...
I finished reading it
while lying on the floor.
If you don't mind,
please accept it.
[My Distant Horizon, Your Poetry]
Great.
I'd love to have a chat with you.
All this effort you've put in—
isn't it just to talk to me?
Sure.
Let's talk.
Let's go to my place.
Can't we just talk here?
I have something to show you.
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
♪ Oh Gimme ♪
♪ Dance me in the richness ♪
♪ Raining make it rain ♪
♪ Oh cash is my revolution ♪
♪ Get your head in the game,
we're all smart people here ♪
♪ Don't drag your feet,
even gold slips through slow hands ♪
♪ I beat it, I beat it ♪
♪ Aye aye aye aye yo ♪
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
Bro.
Don't step on the floor.
Are you looking for a corrupt official
or a poor household?
It's a disguise.
The bigger the corrupt official,
the better the disguise.
He can't just leave his money
out in plain sight, can he?
If he did, he'd have been reported
a long time ago
I bet one of these rooms
is packed with cash.
Search thoroughly.
Especially the ceiling,
under the mattress,
and the hidden compartments in the walls.
Don't miss a single spot.
Clay Figure Zhang.
He’s a clean official.
This fat guy must be a clean official.
I searched the whole place upside down,
and only found a few hundred yuan
in the shoe cabinet.
Bastard.
Who are you cursing?
Mr. Fang, you live on the ground floor?
Isn't that a bit damp?
It's fine.
Living on the ground floor is convenient—
easy to come and go.
Military boxing.
Ready to fight.
One,
two,
three,
four,
five.
Your place...
has a kind of
timeless, unpretentious
cultural elegance to it.
You've got a good eye.
What's this for?
Mr. Fang said the frame is nice.
Why don't we give it to him?
It's no use leaving it in the car.
Just put it there.
Put it there.
Please, Mr. Zhou.
Please, Mr. Fang.
[Fenglinwan VIP Exclusive]
Whenever you have free time,
come here to sing and have some tea.
The girls there make excellent tea.
[Fenglinwan VIP Exclusive]
Mr. Zhou,
what do you think of this tea?
Here, smell it first.
This tea
has age to it.
Good eye.
It's a genuine 1950s
old dark brick tea.
Please.
I believe with your
cultural sensibility,
you must have some unique perspectives
on the cultural industry park
that's being developed
in the new district, right?
The cultural industry park
is a government investment project.
I work for the government.
Whether I have personal opinions
isn't the point.
The point is
to get the park project done right.
Of course, of course.
Using cultural industry as the foundation
to forward the development
in the new district.
So, Mr. Zhou,
why bring up
the industry park all of a sudden?
Do you have something in mind?
Our company
has been deeply rooted
in Sanjiangkou for years.
We are also very experienced
in project operations.
And personally,
I'm interested in the cultural industry.
To be honest,
I'd like to do some
practical work in this space.
So,
I was wondering if you...
At the end of the day,
isn't this all just about money?
This industry park
comes with substantial
government matching funds
and tax incentives.
Therefore,
many companies are eyeing
on this industry park.
I personally think
what matters most
is getting it done properly.
My biggest concern is that
once some developers
get hold of this project,
they will just line their own pockets,
cut corners,
and eventually mess the whole thing up.
Mr. Fang,
you absolutely don't need
to worry about that.
No company
can swallow the whole pie alone.
If this project
were handed to our Rongcheng Group,
I guarantee it will be done perfectly.
Then we'll make the pie bigger.
And this pie...
has to be shared by everyone.
This cake,
how exactly do you want to share it?
To be honest with you,
our company has already done
a financial analysis on this project.
Indeed,
it's profitable.
And if we do it,
we won't hesitate
to spend where it matters.
Every angle will be fully covered.
For example,
the "consulting fee"
for your preferred firm?
Are you trying to bribe me?
Mr. Zhou.
This way, please.
How can the water stay so clear?
Because fresh water flows from the source.
Mr. Fang, I misspoke earlier.
That wasn't what I meant at all.
This is the authentic work of Yu Yueran.
That piece of calligraphy you have
is way too fake.
This way, Mr. Zhou.
This is a genuine Yuan dynasty
blue-and-white porcelain
chilong-handled tripod.
Normally, I wouldn't even
let anyone lay eyes on it.
Genuine Tang Tri-Color Glazed Pottery.
Clay Figure Zhang.
The piece may be small,
but is exquisite.
These two round-backed armchairs
you're sitting on
are made of authentic Hainan rosewood.
There's also a large bed inside.
I usually don't even dare sleep on it.
Have a seat.
Actually, I'm
not like most people.
I don't care much for money.
My greatest passion is collecting.
As you can see,
everything I have in this house
is a reflection of my true passion.
Mr. Fang, you are an educated man.
You're on a completely different level.
Unlike us businessmen,
who just pile money up at home.
We feel so shallow
compared to you.
In my whole life,
I've never taken
a single cent from anyone.
And I certainly won't
be making an exception for you.
Most of the things in my home
were given to me as gifts.
My favorite pieces are bronzeware.
But there are only
a few small pieces left at home.
What I want most is a full set
of bianzhong.
If I could have a set of bianzhong
displayed in my home,
I would be completely satisfied.
A set of bianzhong.
Got it?
Got it.
Right turn.
Forward, march.
One-one, one-two-one.
One, two, three, four!
Unlike us businessmen,
who just pile money up at home.
We feel so shallow compared to you.
Bro,
for the first time in my life,
I've ever seen an idiot
telling two robbers
that there's money in the house.
Bro, why don't we find another target?
That fat guy really is a corrupt official.
My judgment was right, wasn't it?
But antiques
aren't liquid assets.
We can't sell them like commodities.
Cash is much more practical.
Rongcheng Group,
I'm taking it down.
Mr. Rong,
a set of bianzhong isn't cheap.
It'll cost at least tens of millions.
[Auction Records for Bronze Bianzhong]
This Fang Yong
has quite the appetite.
Do we have any connections?
I'll look into it.
Go find a way.
Let's try this.
[Gym]
Mr. Rong.
Did something happen at Fenglinwan?
[Gym]
It's nothing.
It's fine.
Everything is fine.
As long as everything's okay.
Lately,
I've been busy with East New Town.
I haven't had much time for you guys.
Since you're here,
let's go get some food together.
Get it sorted.
Okay.
You, step outside for a moment.
Mr. Rong,
I want to admit my mistake.
I made a mistake.
I secretly wrote
to the Provincial Department
and reported you.
Then at the memorial service,
Zhang Yi'ang and the others
recognized me.
You reported me?
What did you report me for?
You're such a man of integrity—
there wasn't actually anything to report.
So I just made things up.
I...
said you were
evading taxes...
said you were a market bully,
and your private life was a complete mess.
Shut up!
So Zhang Yi'ang came
from the provincial capital
to investigate Lu Zheng's case.
Did you mention Lu Zheng?
No.
Absolutely not!
I swear.
I definitely didn't say a word about him.
Haven't I treated you well?
-Why did you report me?
-Rong!
Rong!
I thought...
you and Qiqi were together.
Are you insane?
Mr. Rong.
Take it easy, calm down.
It'll look bad if this gets out of hand.
Mr. Rong,
I lost my head for a moment.
I'm truly sorry.
I was jealous of you.
I was jealous that you're a real man.
I was jealous
that you have four girlfriends.
I was jealous that you have
a wild nightlife every single night.
I was jealous that
you're surrounded by women everyday.
I only have Qiqi.
And I...
I haven't even touched her yet.
Rong,
I...
I'm just not capable!
Mr. Rong, I'm sorry!
Have you taken your meds?
I've been...
seeing a TCM doctor lately.
Rong,
are you not mad at me anymore?
Of course I'm mad!
We've been friends since we were kids.
I never thought it would be you.
Don't worry.
I already got the letter back.
As far as the police know,
I never mentioned you at all.
I'll trust you one more time.
But Zhang Yi'ang
might not.
I have a feeling
he'll come looking for you again.
Then,
if he comes,
what should I say?
Tell him exactly
what you just told me.
Yibo,
telling the truth
is always more useful than lying.
Okay.
Chief Zhang.
I've thought it through.
Please come to Fenglinwan again.
I'll tell you everything.
Okay.
Very good.
Goodbye.
Chief,
working cases with you
feels easier than ever.
Why do I feel like something is fishy?
Could this be a trap?
What do you mean?
Think about it.
Lu Yibo wrote the report letter
and sent it to the provincial capital—
which means
he originally intended to report.
But then he took
the report letter back—
which means he didn't want to report.
When we tracked him down,
he admitted it immediately—
which means he did want to report.
But he hesitated and wouldn'ts say
who he was reporting—
which means he didn't want to report.
Now he's asking us to come over—
which means he wants to report again.
Does he want to report or not?
This guy's living
in constant contradiction.
Could it be that he's terrified
of the person he's reporting,
so he's deeply conflicted?
If he were truly terrified,
he wouldn't have used his real name.
But he didn't report under his real name.
There was no name on that report letter.
It was only because Chief Zhang stepped...
Chief Zhang stepped on a piece of paper,
then we found the report letter.
So,
I'm wondering
whether all of this
is a big misleading.
It feels more like a trap to me.
Chief Zhang, what do you think?
The night
gave me dark eyes,
but I use them to seek the light.
[Fenglinwan]
Chief Zhang,
how should we question him this time?
If you're planning to improvise again,
give me a heads-up first.
I'm worried I won’t catch the setup
and drop the whole act.
No.
Let's do it like last time.
Didn't that work pretty well?
We'll just play it by ear.
It seems
we can only fill in the gaps as we go.
What kind of jargon are you talking about?
You don't watch crosstalk at all?
Let's say,
spend 200 yuan
to buy a little golden piggy.
It squeals when it drinks water,
crunches when it eats beans.
Along the wall,
then toss it outside.
And it gives a squeak.
Guess what?
It's dead?
Is it dead ot not?
Have some tea.
I've figured it out myself.
Actually,
about the report letter earlier,
I felt I owed you a proper explanation.
We can drink this tea now, right?
Yes, yes, of course.
Well,
Mr. Lu
is Sanjiangkou's
outstanding entrepreneur.
I'm flattered.
And we
are also willing to hear your report.
But actually, that report letter
is fake.
Fake?
Mr. Lu,
writing a false report letter
is against the law.
Yes.
That's exactly why I rushed
to the provincial capital
overnight to retrieve it.
I didn't expect
it'd cause such a big misunderstanding.
It really took up
our valuable police resources.
I'm willing to accept
any punishment or penalty.
The provincial capital explosion case—
does it have anything to do with you?
You mean the manhole cover explosion?
That has absolutely
nothing to do with me.
Then what a coincidence
that you just happened to be there
at the explosion site.
What a coincidence indeed.
But the explosion
has absolutely nothing to do with me.
I was a victim too.
I got covered in shit.
What kind of terrorist
gets himself covered in shit?
Wait a minute.
Liu'an Guapian.
Good tea.
It is Liu'an Guapian.
Officer,
you pronounced "Guapian" right.
But the first two characters,
Lu'an.
It's Lu'an.
Yeah.
Right.
Lu'an.
Look at me—
my taste buds got it right,
but my mouth slipped
and said the wrong thing.
It's Lu'an Guapian.
Nice tea.
You...
What... what Liu?
Lu'an Guapian.
Let me try some.
Mr. Lu.
Didn't you understand
what Chief Zhang meant?
There was a hidden message in his words.
Right now, we're simply asking questions.
But if this turns into an interrogation,
it would be a very different conversation.
Understood. Understood.
Chief Zhang truly is a great detective
from the Provincial Department.
Nothing can possibly hide from him.
He's reminding me
to watch what I say.
You're very sharp.
In that case,
let's keep it simple.
Let's put everything on the table.
Is there...
an unspoken reason behind this?
I'm not capable!
You figured that out already?
Well,
it's obvious.
Too obvious.
How could I not notice it?
Just tell us.
We will keep it a secret.
The unspoken reason...
is my private matter.
But regarding that report letter,
it's authentically...
fake.
Is it true or false?
Don't leave us hanging,
okay?
I told you this guy is
a walking contradiction.
Whether it's true or false,
you wrote the report letter,
so we still have to look into it.
We already know
that you reported him.
The question is, why did you...
I did report him.
But everything I wrote
was all made up.
So it doesn't matter who it is.
Since it doesn't matter,
then why are you hiding it?
Right.
Let's just be straight with each other.
Let's talk about him.
I reported Zhou Rong,
but it was a big misunderstanding.
You and Zhou Rong are friends.
More than friends, I assume?
We're close friends. Childhood friends.
Since you are childhood friends,
whether it's true or false,
this just doesn't make sense.
Why did you report Zhou Rong?