(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
Mr. Shen,
I suppose you see Minghui's situation
more clearly than I do.
Miss Xu, have you decided
to work with me?
Mr. Shen,
may I ask something a little bold?
Can I marry you instead?
=Echoes of Gang City=
=Episode 1=
(Mr. Shen, Will You Say Yes?)
(12 hours)
Good morning,
everyone.
(Gang City Financial News)
Today is Tuesday, June 3rd.
The eighth day of the fifth lunar month.
Welcome to the morning
financial news program.
I'm Xu Wanxin.
First, here are today's top stories.
A globally renowned group,
Qingniao, has acquired land in Shanghai
through its AI subsidiary.
Qingniao Group has expanded its business
by developing quantitative technologies.
In just two years,
it has become a global leader
in the industry.
That's impressive.
Minghui needs an investor like that.
How is it?
Have you found out
who's behind Qingniao?
We already have Junlin's investment,
Mr. Hui.
Dad.
Why not have Wanxin and Shen Hao
get married as soon as possible?
That would lock in the partnership.
You can't even handle
your own affairs,
and now you're meddling
with Wanxin's marriage.
Dad.
Sit properly.
Watch the news.
(Gang City Financial News)
What's it? Why the rush?
Ms. Xi,
there's breaking news.
You need to see this.
This can't go on air.
Ms. Xi, if we don't air it,
we might have a broadcast accident.
If there's an accident,
tell Madam Song to deal with me.
Why are you still standing there?
Pull it down now.
Okay. I'll try.
Where's Aisen?
Is he here yet?
Get him to replace Wanxin.
Hurry.
Jiang, switch the anchor. Go find Aisen.
Now.
I'm going.
I can't. I don't have the authorization.
It's too late.
We can't remove it anymore.
Mr. Xu!
Dad!
Breaking news.
CEO of Minghui Group,
Mr. Xu Zhaoming,
while on his way back
from Sun Valley Summit,
(was involved in a helicopter accident
and died)
was involved
in a helicopter accident
and died
at the age of 57.
I'm Song Xi.
Cut to the scene.
Change the anchor.
(Gang City Financial News)
Dear viewers,
I'm now at the crash site
on Sun Valley Mountain.
As you can see,
the area behind me has been sealed off,
and multiple rescue teams
are working at the scene.
As we're informed,
the helicopter
was carrying three people.
A pilot and two passengers.
One of them has been confirmed
as Xu Zhaoming,
President of Minghui Group,
who was here attending
the latest tech summit.
Preliminary reports suggest
the crash was caused by severe weather.
The cause is still under investigation.
Song Xi.
After Mr. Xu heard about Wanxin's dad's
accident, he suffered a heart attack.
Get Wanxin back immediately.
Alright.
Wanxin.
I know this is hard for you.
Dai Anna just called.
Your grandfather heard the news
about your dad.
He had a heart attack
and fainted.
Zhaohui,
I'm saddened by your brother's accident,
but you must pull yourself together.
This is your best chance
to take Minghui.
No matter what it takes,
get Wanxin and Hao married
as soon as possible.
Hao will bring Junlin Group's
support and invest in Minghui
to stabilize the situation.
At the same time,
we'll push you into
the chairman's seat.
Today, Minghui Group President
Xu Zhaoming encountered a plane crash.
Since the market opened,
Minghui's stock has taken a heavy hit.
According to analysts,
unless Junlin Group, which is tied
to Minghui by a marriage alliance,
steps in to help...
If Shen Tingyuan
uses this chance
to force Xu Wanxin to marry Shen Hao,
what should we do?
He won't get the chance.
How's my grandfather?
Wanxin, don't worry.
Dr. Zhang is with him.
He's stable for now.
Wanxin,
with what happened to
your grandfather and dad,
I know
this is hard on you.
Right now, the family and the company
depend on us.
What's the situation at the company?
The stock price is dropping.
If the news of the chairman's coma
gets out,
and the price falls below 120,
Datong Bank
will call in the loans.
It's fine.
Junlin Group is tied to us
through the marriage alliance.
As long as they step in,
everything will be resolved.
Uncle Zhaohui,
shouldn't we try to
handle this ourselves first?
Xu Wanxin, do you really think
being the Xu family's daughter
and a finance anchor
is enough to bring in
funding and resources?
Your most valuable identity
is being Shen Hao's fiancée.
What you should do now
is call Shen Hao
and set the wedding date.
A woman
needs to know when to show weakness.
That's how you save the Xu family.
I understand your concern.
If necessary,
I can mortgage my personal assets.
Please keep our conversation
confidential.
Excuse me.
You are?
I'm Shen Gu.
I heard about what happened to Mr. Xu,
so I came to see you...
To see
if there's anything I can help with.
Mr. Shen,
I'm sorry
I didn't recognize you
after all these years.
Thank you for your concern
for my dad.
I appreciate it.
Miss Xu.
(Shen Gu)
Since you remember who I am,
you should know
why I've returned to Gang City.
I know about your engagement
to Shen Hao,
and I'm well aware
of Minghui's current situation.
What happened between Junlin and me
in the past may drag your family into it.
So I hope you'll break off
the engagement
and choose to work with me.
You don't have to refuse right away.
Think it over.
We can talk anytime.
Thank you again for your concern.
It's been so many years.
It's only natural for her
to be cautious.
Li Yan and you will handle
Qingniao's investment in Minghui.
Have our people contact
Xu Wanxin directly.
No one
is allowed to delay the process under the excuse
of Mr. Xu Zhaoming's death.
Next,
it's time we meet Shen Tingyuan.
We need to keep the initiative
in our hands.
Release the news
that Xu Qiaomo is seriously ill
and force Minghui.
Don't give Xu Wanxin any room to stall.
This time, I'm taking
Minghui completely.
Hello?
Mr. Tingyuan,
our boss has arrived in Gang City.
He requests a meeting
with your entire board.
I'll arrange it.
Welcome to Gang City.
He says,
"Welcome to Gang City."
Is he coming or not?
If this delays plans with Xu Wanxin,
who's taking responsibility?
Mr. Shen, calm down.
Xu Wanxin is yours.
Don't make me laugh.
Who in Gang City
would dare take her from me?
What if I do?
Shen Tingyuan,
after all these years,
you don't even recognize me?
Shen Gu?
Why did you take me here?
I won't let you ruin my reputation
in Gang City.
Wasn't it enough
that you caused my mom's death?
She brought it on herself.
Didn't you think you were capable?
Live well, then.
I'll be waiting for your return.
So
you bought the Jinzhao Tower?
That's right.
Mr. Shen Gu
not only bought back
his late father's company building,
but he also holds
35% of Junlin Group shares
and is currently
its largest shareholder.
This is hilarious.
You left with nothing.
Now you wave some fake documents
in my face?
Sorry.
Our legal team doesn't deal
with anything illegal.
Suspend all cooperation regarding Shen.
Yes.
All of them.
Hello?
What?
Stop all cooperation immediately.
We've received notice
that we must stop all business
with the Shen family at once.
Nonsense!
Take your time to check it.
As the largest shareholder
of Junlin Group,
I'm calling for a shareholders' meeting
to replace the chairman.
This is my welcome gift.
You think replacing the chairman
is something you,
who has no footing on the board,
can decide?
Why don't you guess
who our footing
here is?
Madam Song just informed me
that someone named Shen Gu
has just called a Junlin board meeting
as the largest shareholder
and is requesting
to replace the chairman.
Shen Gu?
Is it the one I'm thinking of?
Madam Song said
he has a personal feud
with Shen Tingyuan.
Since you remember who I am,
you should know
why I've returned to Gang City.
I know about your engagement
to Shen Hao
and I'm well aware
of Minghui's current situation.
I don't want Junlin's affairs
to drag your family down.
So I hope you'll break off
the engagement
and choose to work with me.
(Shen Gu)
(Xu Wanxin)
Hello?
Hello, Mr. Shen.
This is Xu Wanxin.
Can we meet?
Mr. Shen,
sorry to trouble you.
I suppose you see Minghui's situation
more clearly than I do.
I know Shen Tingyuan
has released news
that Mr. Xu is seriously ill.
He's determined
to take over Minghui.
He won't stop.
Miss Xu, have you decided
to work with me?
Mr. Shen,
may I ask something a little bold?
Do you have a girlfriend
or partner?
I'm single.
My dad is gone.
My grandfather is unconscious.
Only a marriage alliance
between Minghui and Junlin
can restore confidence in the market.
But if I marry Shen Hao,
Minghui
will fall into Shen Tingyuan's hands.
I have to protect the company.
It's my grandfather and dad's
life's work.
And you
are now the largest shareholder
of Junlin Group.
So
can I marry you instead?
Xu Wanxin,
do you realize what you're saying?
I'll give you
Minghui's key projects
so you can use them as leverage
against Shen Tingyuan.
You're the largest shareholder of Junlin.
If we marry,
it'll stabilize the stock price quickly.
It's a win-win.
Shen Gu,
will you consider my proposal?
(Gang City Marriage Registry)
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on no distance
could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled
one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending
we face?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪