QUEEN OF TEARS
FOUR YEARS AGO
That's strange.
What is?
They said this was
the best dating spot,
but why is it so empty?
You're right. It is.
RENTED FOR THE DAY
The music…
What about it?
Don't they normally play
happy songs like the ones
in The Little Mermaid?
It sounds a bit too romantic.
Change the song!
I'm sorry.
This playlist was called "Call For Love."
The music changed.
You're right.
How fascinating.
Ms. Hong, these days
it feels like the entire universe
is on our side.
We went to a famous restaurant,
and we were the only ones there.
When we went to the amusement park,
no one else was in that huge place
except for us.
You're right.
Speaking of which…
Since the universe is on our side…
Will you…
marry me?
Are you crying?
I'm sorry.
About what?
Are you that worried?
Don't you worry.
Baek Hyun-woo.
I love you.
I wish…
this moment wouldn't end.
I wish you'd continue
to smile at me
without knowing the truth.
What do you mean?
What don't I know?
Don't be shocked.
We already went to Germany.
We did?
I already received treatment?
No.
You weren't ready.
I'm dumbfounded.
How could I forget that?
What if I lose all my memory?
I'm already sick as is.
That'd be so unfair.
There are times
when people completely forget things
even if they're not sick.
I was the same.
I had forgotten it all.
What is it?
What's going on?
Is there something else I forgot?
I was going to divorce you
without telling you first.
What?
And you found out in Germany.
So it's been rocky for us lately.
So…
you were going
to divorce me?
Yes.
And I knew?
Don't lie.
If that were true,
then you wouldn't be here right now.
I would've broken your bones
or popped your eardrums.
-Hae-in--
-Should I do that right now?
I have no idea what's going on.
Then try to remember
what I did to you…
and how much you resented me.
No, I really don't remember…
So you won't bother trying anymore?
I'd be grateful if you divorced me
without filing a suit.
It was unbearable to live with you anyway.
Hae-in.
You know what kind of person you are.
No wonder I chose to do so.
I could've lived
a comfortable and wealthy life.
Because I hated living with you
more than anything!
When I heard that you'd be dying soon,
I was relieved deep down.
We'd have a clean divorce if I put up
with you for the next three months.
So if you choose
not to take any action at all
and just divorce me,
then honestly,
I'd be grateful.
Will you do that?
-Hae-in-.
-Stop. I remember now.
I remember how much you despise me
and how miserable your life has become.
What is it?
Did you think you'd live comfortably
if you married me,
but found out that wasn't the case?
It must've been entertaining
to watch me not remember anything
and talk nonsense.
No.
-I wasn't--
-I was miserable too!
It wasn't just you.
I was miserable too.
I can't spend my remaining life
next to you.
-Hae-in, wait.
-Let's part ways.
I want a divorce.
EPISODE 8
ALARM
It's a consensual divorce.
So why are we here when you agreed
to divorce without any alimony?
Who's their attorney?
I'm not sure.
This doesn't sit right with me.
It must be him.
He must be her divorce attorney.
-So?
-You don't know anything, do you?
He's…
a terrifying man.
He's just an attorney.
There are many rumors about who he is.
The youngest heir
of a conglomerate family.
A former soldier stationed abroad.
Someone who came here on a spaceship.
Others say he's a werewolf.
His name is Vincenzo.
And he is…
Please show mercy.
Please spare us.
-Please.
-Just this once.
-Please spare us.
He's from the mafia.
The mafia?
You mean the mafia from that Mafia game?
No, the real mafia.
And he's a consigliere.
He's the boss.
I thought he was in Italy.
I heard
he doesn't negotiate in words.
You don't deserve to be reasoned with.
I think Ms. Hong has decided
not to forgive you.
In all honesty,
what you did to her is infuriating.
You tricked her into thinking
that you were in love.
You told me…
So?
She probably wants you dead.
Hae-in, please spare me this once!
Mr. Baek, you deceived my client.
A couple of divorce papers
won't make up for that.
I'm sorry to say this,
but evil should be countered with evil.
No!
Hae-in, it was Yang-gi.
He told me to do this.
That bastard--
That's her plan.
Be quiet.
Can I just leave?
I have a family.
You have no kids
and won't have a wife soon either.
Do as you wish.
Jeez.
First of all, please know
that I'm not here to negotiate.
That's the official paper
regarding the divorce
that Mr. Baek prepared. Correct?
Yes.
-What's wrong with it?
-Look at it.
He wrote the main reason for divorce
as irreconcilable differences.
These darn…
nutjobs.
Isn't that the simplest
and most optimal reason?
Look at her.
She's a wealthy woman
who's known for her good looks.
This department store CEO
was born into a rich family.
The tabloids and rumors make her out
to be someone haughty.
And she's a member
of the One Trillion Club.
Not yet.
Well, not yet.
Anyway, given these facts,
not many would think
that her personality is her forte.
And now,
she's going to divorce a mere director
due to irreconcilable differences?
People will immediately think
that she has a terrible personality, no?
Right.
Then what should we say instead?
Do you have any suggestions?
I do.
"They have become distant
due to their hectic schedules."
But they live under the same roof.
"They have agreed
to remain as good friends."
I don't think they can.
-"They wish the best for each other."
-Wait.
I don't wish that.
From what I know,
none of my clients ever do.
They just say this.
You can write whatever you want.
Are you sure?
Will you not regret it?
No.
Whatever it may be,
it won't be the real reason anyway.
Why did you choose
the subway instead of a taxi or a car?
You know.
When I've had a rough day,
but have no one to rant to,
I take Line Two.
Why?
This line is a loop,
so it goes around Seoul.
Time passes by quickly
when I watch people.
I remain in the subway until sundown.
Then in between
Dangsan and Hapjeong Stations,
I get to see the best sunset in Seoul.
Isn't it pretty?
The sunset helps me forget
how awful of a day I had.
It just makes me want to go home.
Sir.
Let's make a stop somewhere.
He had rice soup, played baseball,
washed his car,
ran laps,
and had rice soup again.
Is it that good?
He had stir-fried pork too.
He eats so well.
Look at you. You're running again.
He runs so well.
What's his deal? Gosh.
-Go slowly. You'll hurt yourself.
-Be careful.
Me too.
They're all working out in pairs,
so why does he run alone?
Is this fun?
Is it really?
GRANDMA'S HOME COOKING
Two bowls of rice soup
and one soju, please.
Coming up.
It won't take long.
Thank you.
What do you want?
One bowl of rice soup and one soju.
What?
One bowl of rice soup
and one soju, please.
"One bowl of rice soup
and one soju." Okay.
You couldn't have sundae and rice soup
because your wife hated the smell,
but you can knock yourself out now.
This is a perk of the divorce.
Just think of the good things.
Look. You no longer
have to worry about men tailing you
or having to rush home.
You had to leave us
while drinking if your mother-in-law
or the chairman called you.
Jeez. That's why you didn't meet us often,
and always had dinner alone.
I know,
but I wanted that life.
What do you mean? You wanted that?
Do you have Stockholm syndrome?
I don't know.
I just wanted
to be by Hae-in's side.
About those pills, sir,
I'll send you an email too,
but they're used
to treat malignant tumors.
It's an anticancer drug.
-Are you sure?
-Yes, I'm sure.
Mom!
EVERGREEN HOPE ORPHANAGE
Hey! You!
You! It's okay.
It's okay. Hey.
You scumbag!
What if my dog got hurt?
Have you gone insane?
Do you know how expensive this dog is?
-What are you looking at?
-Stop it.
I almost got bitten by your dog.
And who are you?
Do they not teach you manners?
Ms. Hong!
Hae-in.
Grandpa.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Are you?
She's the granddaughter
of Queens Group's chairman.
Goodness, I didn't know.
Are you okay?
Let's go to the hospital.
Okay?
Goodness.
Thanks.
Mr. Oh, where's Hae-in?
She hasn't come home yet.
She told me to go home first.
She got off at a nearby elementary school.
You should've kept an eye on her.
I haven't been able to track her
since she's been alone lately.
This isn't what we agreed on.
I'm sorry, sir.
Where have you been?
Why did you take a taxi?
I had to stop by somewhere.
Wait.
Will Mr. Baek keep working for you?
Aren't you uncomfortable?
I don't plan on firing him
if he wants to stay.
After all, we need him in the company.
The one person Queens really needs
is me.
And I'm also
the one you need.
Must I still prove that?
I was going to tell you later,
but I'll just say it now.
I thought long and hard.
I'm going to pass up
on Hercyna.
What?
I appreciate all the help you've given me.
But Mr. Hermann chose our store
because of you, not me.
I wanted to use you out of greed,
-but that's--
-Then do so.
That's why I'm here.
Do you know what I've done in life
to become someone useful to you?
Do I have to know?
Hae-in.
I'm not going to ask you
for anything even if you choose Hercyna.
All I wanted to do was show you
that I could provide you with everything
others couldn't.
You're being blunt since I'm divorced now.
But listen up.
I didn't divorce him
so you could have a chance.
I married Hyun-woo
because he said he'd be by my side.
And I divorced him
because I felt bad about everything
he had to go through.
Can you say the same thing
even if you lost everything?
-What?
-Even then?
You won't need me?
Did you just get home?
You went through so much, ma'am.
-He's always been a nuisance.
-And he still is.
Why isn't Hyun-woo quitting his job?
You should fire him.
Mom, if there's one thing I can't do,
it's outsmarting him.
What do you mean?
He divorced her without taking any money.
What if we provoke him,
and he uses that smart brain
of his to get alimony?
But still,
a legal director has a lot of power.
Don't you feel uneasy
that he still has that power?
I do.
That's why you should get rid of him.
Goodness, why is she calling me?
You have no customers. Good.
Mom, why are you here?
I want to look like a female politician.
-Turn me into one.
-What?
You know that hairstyle they have
when giving a public apology to show that
they're terribly sorry?
But I don't want to look servile.
-There's no such hairstyle.
-Come on!
Give my hair some poof like this.
I see. Poof.
Yes, I need some poof to look confident.
I felt awful
after our previous call.
Marriage is the most important promise
in one's life.
Hae-in must be so distraught.
I'm sure you and your husband
were utterly speechless as well.
I should've taught my son better.
I'm truly sorry.
-Is this a scheme?
-Sorry?
Did your attorney son tell you to do this
so that he could get alimony
and some of Hae-in's fortune?
Sorry?
Don't tell me you're recording this.
You can't use this recording in court
since I didn't consent to it.
Recording? Why would I do such a thing?
Why wouldn't you? Even your son did it.
-Hyun-woo?
-Yes.
He bugged our chairman's room.
I don't know if he wanted
to sell the recording
or use it against Hae-in
for their divorce.
What did he say? Did he admit to it?
-He denied it.
-Then that's the truth.
Does it even matter anymore?
They're divorced now.
I guess you didn't know.
This is exactly why some people
shouldn't marry each other.
They'll only bring each other down.
That's why I was vehemently against them.
You may have been against them,
but they shared
enough happy memories to get married.
What?
I realized that life may seem long,
but happy memories are limited.
So?
They may have parted ways,
but I hope
they'll still cherish
those happy memories.
That's a good idea.
The divorce has already been settled,
so I hope your family
won't try to get anything out of it.
Also, please persuade him to quit his job.
Why won't he? He's so pathetic.
I hope we never see each other again.
Goodness.
Did she not say who she was meeting?
Judging by how she dressed
before going to Seoul,
maybe it was Ms. Kim.
Then why isn't she picking up?
There she is! Mom!
I gave her hair so much poof,
but it's all gone.
Go greet her.
Grandma!
Hello, my dear puppy.
-Were you waiting for me?
-Yes.
-My feet hurt, so I bought some slippers.
-Well done.
I was worried
since you weren't picking up.
Did you have dinner?
Not yet.
Hey, order some Chinese.
Forget it. We should have rice.
Where should I order from? Ting Hua?
No, they're not good.
The Great Wall of China
has better service.
Do you have coupons?
That's the list of customers who purchased
Ronde de Frédic's 101st anniversary watch.
There's one Korean.
Isn't she the chairman's mistress?
Where was it purchased?
Six years ago on Fifth Avenue, Manhattan.
It's a men's watch.
I wonder whom she gifted it to.
She goes somewhere without me
about two to three times a week.
Our cars
are fine. We didn't crash.
-Is this a coincidence?
-No.
I saw you following Hae-in
from the office,
so I followed you.
They're used to treat malignant tumors.
It's an anticancer drug.
Yes, I'm sure.
Is someone you know sick?
Hello?
Mr. Yoon?
CALLS
YOON EUN-SUNG
I reported back to him every now and then
about whom you were meeting.
He told me to look into these pills,
so I asked a friend
who worked at a pharmaceutical company.
I'm truly sorry.
Why are you following her?
She's not your wife anymore.
So what's it to you?
Look. If you continue to follow her,
I won't stop following you either.
And if you try to harm her,
I'll do the same to you.
That's my plan.
So you want to protect her.
Do as you please.
She'll choose me anyway.
You'll get what I mean soon.
Did your family immigrate there
or were you studying abroad?
I was adopted overseas.
My adoptive parents passed away
right before I graduated university.
So I have no family now.
Come in.
Eun-sung.
I could've just gone to you.
It was urgent.
Mr. Na of Bolt One called.
What? What for?
Regarding the land.
There's a military base near the area
where the resort will be built.
Gosh, is that what this is about?
They agreed to move.
If not, their laser station would've made
the construction impossible.
I heard they're not moving.
What?
Why did they change their mind?
MOLIT wants to move, but the MND refused
and said it'd cost too much.
So they canceled everything.
Is the MND more powerful than the MOLIT?
I'm not too sure, sir.
The MOLIT must win at all costs.
Can you still not reach
the senior manager of MOLIT?
No, he keeps texting
that he's in a meeting.
He can't do this to me.
GRANDFATHER
Hello?
Yes, sir.
-Sir.
-What is it?
-The chairman wants to see you.
-No…
Why can't you be quick-witted?
Didn't you see how I rejected
his call for the first time in my life?
Yes, I did.
You should have made up an excuse.
How could you just say yes?
Hyun-woo. Where is he?
Hyun-woo.
Hyun-woo,
it must've been so tough for you.
-What's wrong?
-You know what they say.
Workers have resignation letters
ready at all times.
So why can't you have
divorce papers in your safe?
It's not your fault.
It's our family's for discovering it.
What's this about?
-An issue with the site.
-What?
The military base needs to move
so that people can visit our resort,
take the elevator to the sky lounge,
have some steak and wine,
stargaze, and swim in the infinity pool.
-But they won't move.
-I told you to run the validity test.
I know.
You did say that,
but Mr. Yoon swooped in at that moment
and made such a tempting offer.
So I was too hasty.
I see. Then you should go to him.
-Ask him for help.
-Come on!
He's from the U.S.
He never served in the military.
So what would he know about moving bases?
On the other hand, you were a marine.
Not just the marines,
but the Special Guard Team.
See?
I'm only asking you for help
since you're special.
Please save me.
Honey.
Yes?
What were you doing?
I'm in huge trouble.
I'm missing the last piece
of this 2000-piece puzzle.
Are you serious?
Queens Group,
who ambitiously announced the building
of the largest resort complex
in Northeast Asia, is facing bad luck.
A military base nearby canceled
their plans to move
and therefore, has limited
the resort's height to 180 meters.
This means that the hotel can only build
39 floors instead of the original 90.
The hotel's estimated earnings
will likely drop drastically,
and its investors may demand a prepayment…
Is Soo-cheol still not answering?
No, Father. I think he's trying
to resolve this issue--
He shouldn't have let this happen
in the first place. It's too late!
How is he just as foolish as you?
Goodness.
Hey, you were all here.
Why haven't you been picking up?
I'm here now with a solution.
What is this?
I looked into the long-range radar
near our land.
Having been built in 1994,
it's worn out and needs to be repaired.
Its efficiency rate is a bit over 60%,
and it received Grade C
in last year's safety test.
The government gave us money,
so it'll be fixed this summer.
Raising the height of the radar.
-What about that instead?
-Sorry?
The radar station is 180 m,
and the hotel is 350 m.
So if you set up
a concrete structure
above the station that's 170 m or more,
then the problem is solved.
It seems like the optimal solution.
Right.
Hyun-woo sure is smart.
I came up with the idea.
He just wrote it down as my attorney.
Hyun-woo is quite intelligent.
Why does it feel like
no one is listening to me?
Anyway, make sure
you explain it well to the investors.
You got it. I'm sure they'll be relieved.
Did you not hear what I just said?
The problem has been solved,
so why are you pulling out?
I just don't get it.
I heard Chairman Hong's financial manager
was taken in for interrogation.
About that…
How could you keep
such important news from us?
I wouldn't have known
had it not been for our legal advisor.
Your legal advisor?
As in Apollon? Am I right?
Mr. Baek planned it out well.
No one would invest
when the financial manager
has been arrested.
I can't believe Hyun-woo.
He should take revenge on Hae-in, not me.
Is this the end
since they're all pulling out? Oh, God.
Of course not.
What?
It's the beginning.
Hey, does that mean…
Sir.
Take a look at this.
P INVESTMENT PLANS TO INVEST
900 BILLION WON IN Q RESORT
We, Pione Investment,
will be your sole investor.
It'll be easier to sort things out
if we're the sole investor.
Yes, a sole investor is the way to go.
People say we shouldn't put
all our eggs in one basket,
but it's completely fine
since we trust Eun-sung.
Yes, it's all about who you work with.
And I also value trust the most.
Are you my soulmate or what?
I always say that business
is about those involved.
My entire life is in your hands.
I'm sure this wasn't easy for you,
so thank you for doing this.
I should seal the deal
before you change your mind.
You shouldn't be here, sir.
Hyun-woo, what is this about?
Secretary Jang.
Sir, the Legal Team gave their opinion
regarding this investment deal.
But I don't think you received it.
Please reconsider the convertible rights.
If the owner's risk causes a problem,
then 6.7% of your shares
will be handed over to Mr. Yoon.
You shouldn't be rash about this.
Hyun-woo.
Look, Mr. Baek!
What he just said
makes sense too.
Father!
You can do as you please.
However, I will also pull out
if this falls through.
The trust
needs to be mutual.
She said you'll have to make
a big decision soon.
If someone offers you
a large sum of money and some papers,
she advises that you accept it.
Doing so will save you and your company.
Whoever hurls a monkey wrench into it
will betray you down the road,
so you should ignore them.
Come on.
You must listen to me.
Just like at that hunting ground,
this great shaman has saved your life
countless times.
She sure is good.
Sorry?
It's nothing.
-Hyun-woo?
-Yes, sir.
I don't toss people out right away.
I give them three chances.
But you betrayed my granddaughter,
bugged my room,
and tried to ruin this deal.
That's three strikes already.
-Sir…
-Get out.
Is this broken?
Please.
Thank you.
INVALID ID
Sir, you need to come out.
Mr. Baek Hyun-woo.
Please leave your ID card,
corporate phone,
laptop, and other equipment behind
and leave the building.
It's past working hours.
You can't do this out of the blue.
It's the chairman's orders.
Please leave.
Does the Security Team have no rules?
Are you the chairman's men or something?
It's past working hours. Go home.
But the chairman ordered us--
Just go home.
At least make a deal.
Demand something in return for quitting.
Will you really let them kick you out?
They can't.
The chairman can fire me as a director,
but I'm also a team manager.
He needs a legitimate reason to fire one.
I know the Audit Team
couldn't find any reason to fire me.
That's…
Fine, but why are you still here?
You were so eager for a divorce
that you secretly prepared for it.
So why are you still here
and letting them humiliate you?
When you were with me…
You had to put up with it.
But not anymore.
I know.
I'm only doing this
because I still want to be here.
How are you feeling?
I'm okay.
-Ms. Hong.
-You better get in, or I'll run you over.
Which one was it?
The company? A reunion? A bar?
Don't bother denying it.
I know everything about divorce.
There's only one answer.
A mistress.
Ma'am…
Hae-in was the only woman in my life.
Then don't go!
You're all she has,
so why are you leaving?
I'm not going anywhere.
How could I possibly leave her?
That's why I'm still at the company.
I'll stay by her side
at all costs.
Also…
I'll get to the bottom
of who bugged the chairman's room,
handed the recording to Apollon,
and wanted me out of the family.
About that…
I do have my suspicions.
Ms. Moh?
How did you know?
Everyone knows how much you despise her.
That's not why.
She's scarier than you think.
She's been living under a false identity
and deceiving us for decades.
What do you mean?
Her real name is Oh Sun-yeong.
She had a son,
and he's 34 years old now.
And Oh Sun-yeong is deceased on paper.
So? Insane, isn't it?
Don't you want to team up with me?
I even have a partner named Conan.
Iced Americano all the way, right?
-How did you know?
-I can see that you're the stubborn type.
I see.
He could pass as a shaman.
I practically raised him myself.
What have you found out?
I met with the guard
from Oh Sun-yeong's penitentiary.
She gave birth behind bars
and sent him
to an orphanage in Gangwon Province.
-Where exactly?
-It's…
-Wonsan.
-Isn't that near the hunting ground?
Yes, our villa is there.
Yes, it's very close.
It's Evergreen Hope Orphanage.
"Evergreen"?
That's--
My father and that wench sponsored
and gave out scholarships there
up until a decade ago!
That orphanage
went up in flames ten years ago.
I believe the director passed away too.
Do you know anyone we could reach out to?
-I'm not sure.
-What about him?
Who?
The man who came
to the hunting ground with you.
The one who wanted to buy our dog.
-Mr. Yoon Eun-sung?
-Don't be absurd.
What? You said he looked familiar too.
Whom did he remind you of?
There was this boy at the orphanage.
He was so smart that he received
scholarships from Queens Group.
But he was taken
to the police station once
after poisoning and killing
a neighbor's dog.
And Mr. Yoon looked like him.
He did say he was adopted to the U.S.
That's right. That boy
was adopted to the U.S. as well.
Isn't she the chairman's mistress?
It's a men's watch.
I wonder whom she gifted it to.
She's scarier than you think.
She's been living under a false identity
and deceiving us for decades.
She gave birth behind bars and sent him
to an orphanage in Gangwon Province.
I was adopted overseas.
He was adopted by a Korean family at 12.
She had a son, and he's 34 years old now.
So I have no family now.
POWER OF ATTORNEY
HONG MAN-DAE
RIGHT TO MAKE ANY MEDICAL DECISIONS
Why are you signing this?
Why would you give me
the right to make decisions for you?
When the prosecution investigates
the secret fund,
they might not be convinced
that you embezzled it
just because you have some
of the money under your name.
Anyone could be the financial manager.
Is that so?
See?
This is for my sake.
Will you still not do it?
No, I should.
Today is your birthday,
so this could be my gift to you.
Right.
Yes, I'll consider it my birthday gift.
AUTHORIZER
HONG MAN-DAE
Wait, why is Mr. Yoon sitting here?
He should sit with us.
Well…
It was my order.
What?
It's only right. He's not family anyway.
Why? You sit with us
when you're not family either.
So?
So you can be family
even if it's not on paper.
-If you live together--
-So?
You're saying Mr. Yoon
could become family?
Is that what you think?
No, I never said that.
Hae-in got divorced not too long ago.
What would people think
if he sat next to her?
They'd think she has shallow intentions.
"Shallow"?
Did you seriously just say that?
Really?
Then,
you shouldn't give them wrong ideas.
Who are you to order people around?
Seon-hwa
is the lady of the house.
You're really something, you know?
All right.
Let's not get upset over nothing
on this good day.
Why does she have this?
This was Mom's!
She wore it all her life,
and I was supposed to inherit it.
So how could you give it to her?
Okay. Let me go, and I'll take it off.
Father, why have you gone crazy?
You may have always been a workaholic,
but you weren't like this.
Why can't you make good judgment?
Look who's talking! How dare you?
You've kicked Beom-seok out
and treat Beom-jun like an idiot.
Look who's left now.
You only have this bitch
who's waiting to milk you dry!
Watch what you say!
When my children backed out in fear
that I'd send them to jail,
she was the only one who stepped up!
Maybe she's not afraid to go
since she's been there before!
What nonsense are you spewing?
You know nothing.
I was going to tell you later.
She's been to prison
and even had a child!
She's been living
under a false name all along!
Beom-ja, why are you so mean to me?
I may have been poor,
but I've always strived
to live an honest life.
I'm sorry, sir.
I can't do this anymore.
I'll leave this house.
Come on.
You know Beom-ja always talks nonsense.
You little brat!
You better stop, or I'll send you
to a mental asylum. Got it?
A mental asylum?
Then I ought to do this much.
You!
Let her go!
I said, let her go!
Father…
I'm so sick of you.
Your mom got her revenge on me
by giving birth to you.
How could you torment me to this day?
Just leave, will you?
Leave, I beg you.
Just go!
I'll do that.
You won't be able to save face
after kicking out two of your three kids.
I'm leaving of my own will.
Have a great birthday party today.
I'll at least attend your funeral.
Even still,
I hope you live a long life.
That little…
It's okay.
All right, now.
Are the hair follicles intact?
Probably. I pulled them out
with all my might.
And Mr. Yoon's?
Thank you.
Ma'am.
Are you okay?
No…
I'm not okay, Hyun-woo…
My father hit me
for the first time in his life.
He hit me…
What if Grandfather faints
due to happiness
after receiving my surprise?
Don't push yourself too much. Be calm.
I've been way too calm all along.
I need to change.
Can't you see? I'm Queens' solution now.
I'm their lifesaver.
Still, your grandfather wants
a quiet birthday this year.
You're so innocent.
Don't let him fool you. It's just a test.
It's like midterms or exams.
In that aspect, this is like the CSAT.
Will I be chosen as the heir or not?
It's the play-off.
But I have a hunch.
What? What kind?
That today will be
the best day of my life.
I see.
Wear a pretty dress
and take Geon-u to the hair salon.
I'll be waiting.
Honey.
Thank you.
You fool.
CONGRATULATIONS
ON CHAIRMAN HONG'S FOURTH 20TH BIRTHDAY!
CHAIRMAN HONG'S 80TH BIRTHDAY
We've gathered together
to celebrate the chairman's birthday.
Our family went through
a rough patch recently.
People slandered him and spread rumors.
However,
our hero neither gave in
nor gave up.
He overcame all the hardships.
Everyone, please clap
for Chairman Hong Man-dae.
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
POWER OFF
Dreams come true.
There's Mickey Mouse in the U.S.
and Totoro in Japan.
Queens Amusement Park,
which will be the biggest one
in Northeast Asia,
also has a beloved character.
I created it myself.
It's Chairman Hong, my grandfather.
Me?
Soo-cheol prepared
a great birthday gift for Father.
You're right.
I'm ecstatic to finally be able
to reveal it to you all.
Come on out, Man-sung!
We're planning to sell
this Man-sung merchandise
as toys, golf wear, mugs,
keychains, mats, and more.
And, of course,
we'll issue NFTs as well.
Tell Soo-cheol to stop.
Please stop.
CHEON DA-HYE
I got the DNA results.
Da-hye.
Honey.
Da…
Da-hye.
Da-hye!
Geon-u!
My son can't go to bed
if I don't tuck him in.
Please, Da-hye!
Geon-u.
Let's try some.
Just one bite, Geon-u.
What's wrong?
Geon-u.
Mommy's here.
BEOM-JA
HYUN-WOO
Why are you calling me at this hour?
I'm sorry. It's urgent.
Are you alone, sir?
I'm playing Janggi. Why?
Please just listen if Ms. Moh is with you.
What?
I did a DNA test on Ms. Moh and Mr. Yoon.
There's a 99% chance or higher
that they're related.
Mr. Yoon has been gathering your shares.
He has already taken 9.6%
of the directors' shares
through a foreclosure agreement.
Sir, you must withdraw
the convertible rights now.
All right.
I'll call you back later.
Checkmate.
I got the king.
What's the matter?
Do you have something to say?
You…
Goodness.
Are you okay?
No, you're probably not okay.
That's what the drug does.
Ten minutes in the respiratory system,
and you'll slowly become paralyzed.
So it was true.
How incredible.
Don't worry.
You won't die right away.
If you do, this will be useless.
I can only become your legal guardian
and have a say if you're in a coma.
So…
be in a coma
for two to three months before you die.
Can you do that for me?
See?
Hyun-woo and Beom-ja were right.
So why did you trust me instead of them?
-Happy birthday to you
-Happy birthday, dear Beom-ja
Come here.
I'll take it now. Please smile.
Say cheese on the count of three.
Okay. One, two, three.
Cheese.
What's with you guys?
Don't you know who I am?
Why can't I see him?
Only those allowed
by his legal guardian can enter.
-Move.
-No, sir.
-No, sir!
-Goodness.
Hey.
We're the chairman's children.
So who's this guardian?
-Move.
-No, ma'am.
Goodness.
You bitch.
What have you done?
Give me a minute.
What happened, Attorney Han?
The chairman had a sudden heart attack
and received treatment.
But he's currently unconscious.
No, Father!
And his current legal guardian
is Ms. Moh Seul-hee.
What do you mean?
Right.
The chairman recently gave
the power of attorney to her.
According to this document,
Ms. Moh is his legal guardian
and has the right
to make decisions in his stead
since he's unconscious right now.
If this is proven to be fabricated,
you'll be charged with the forgery, use,
and making of untrue entries
in this official document.
I have a video of him signing this paper.
I'll send it to you.
-I'm dizzy.
-Honey.
Honey.
He must've had zero trust in his children
to give me the right to act in his stead
in case something like this occurred.
You were only interested
in taking as much money from him
as possible.
The chairman chose the company
he raised his entire life
over his own family.
I know what he wants more than any of you.
I'll follow his wishes.
"His wishes"?
Hey, I don't know about that.
But I do know what you want.
You and your son,
Yoon Eun-sung, are going to use
the power of attorney to your favor!
What do you mean?
Yoon Eun-sung? The Yoon Eun-sung?
Correct, sir.
We checked the DNA results.
Yes, Mr. Yoon is my son.
Why? Is that wrong?
Does that change anything?
Hey!
Damn it!
Beom-ja, keep acting cute,
and I might secretly move
your father to another room
and not give you the chance
to say goodbye to him.
Do you not believe me?
This is an unprecedented incident
in the business industry.
The stockholders' meeting
agreed to take the Queens' family's rights
over their own company.
Pione Investment, an investor
in Queens' new resort complex,
purchased 14.7%
of Queens' shares
at the beginning of this month…
…and announced its participation
in the management.
Pione then amassed
a total of 24.3% of the shares.
Once Chairman Hong lost consciousness
due to a sudden heart attack,
Pione exercised the convertible rights
and took 6.7% of his shares.
Now, with a total of 31%,
they've become
the second largest shareholder.
Pione then organized
a temporary stockholders' meeting.
With the power of attorney,
Ms. Moh Seul-hee
sided with Pione Investment.
A shocking 68.8% supported
the removal of the Queens' family,
while only 31.2% were against it.
The business industry is stunned
by this unprecedented event
where a conglomerate family
lost their power
due to opposition from the stockholders.
HONG HAE-IN
What'll happen to the family now?
Who knows?
Even the reporters
don't know where they are.
They're neither home nor at a hotel.
They can't even leave the country
due to the investigation.
You're right. Where could they be?
YONGDU-RI SUPERMARKET
Hey.
-What are you guys doing here?
-Du-gwan, I'm glad you're here.
I was going to text you.
Du-gwan.
How much are the sausages?
How did you open the store?
The passcode is 0070.
Everyone knows that.
Jeez.
I should change it.
The villagers wanted to pay
their unpaid grocery bills,
so we're running the place for you.
Look at this.
-Here.
-We wrote them all down.
They never stopped by
when I urged them to,
so why now?
I guess they wanted to help
after watching the news.
You know what?
It's gloomy today,
so how about some ramyeon and soju?
Sounds good.
All right.
Cheers…
Here.
Be careful.
Gosh, that looks delicious.
Eat up.
Du-gwan.
Why would you close the store
over something trivial?
I'm disappointed in you.
Why would you be in hiding?
Let's be honest. It's not your fault.
Hyun-woo is to blame.
Hyun-woo didn't do anything wrong.
I agree.
He's just a victim of this great typhoon.
Du-gwan.
You should know as a farmer yourself.
Crops don't grow deep roots
if you plant them in the breeze
since they don't need them.
But those planted amid strong winds
are deeply rooted and invincible.
In that sense,
typhoons can be helpful in life.
You're like one of those people.
A philosopher.
Hey.
If you like typhoons so much,
you can experience them yourselves.
It breaks my heart to think that my son
is all alone in that disaster!
-Du-gwan--
-Let me be.
Have some ramyeon too.
What's that?
What's with the light?
Who's here at this hour?
-What?
-Is that Hyun-woo?
Who?
Hyun-woo.
Hey, Hyun-woo!
I didn't know you were coming.
Dad, it was urgent.
Hey, Hyun-woo.
Why weren't you picking up?
Do you not eat well?
You look terrible.
Goodness.
Don't be so distraught.
I'm glad you left that crazy family.
Look at what happened to them
after they kicked you out.
-Karma will always find its way.
-Mi-seon.
-Hold on--
-You bet.
I was so relieved to hear
that the damn family was ruined.
Serves them right!
Anyway, forget about
that sly fox and live a happy life.
The sly fox
is here too.
I see.
You're here too.
It's not just her.
I know,
but I wanted that life.
What do you mean? You wanted that?
Do you have Stockholm syndrome?
I don't know.
I just wanted
to be by Hae-in's side.
Thank you.
Goodness, come again.
Goodness.
Are you okay?
Why are you crying?
My husband.
Yes?
He wants to be by my side.
And is that so sad?
Of course.
Because hearing that makes me want…
to live.
Then live. What's stopping you?
I'm desperate to live too.
I want to stay
by his side.
Gosh. You're drunk.
I want to live.
Desperately.
QUEEN OF TEARS
They might get back together?
Do you have feelings for each other?
Just drink from the kettle!
This is the best twist ever
since The Sixth Sense.
-He looked like Leslie Cheung.
-I heard she's a psychopath.
What?
Was he born to love me or something?
Where is she? Hae-in.
-Whatever happens to me or my family…
-Hae-in is…
has nothing to do with you.
If I can prove it,
I'm going to use
the same tactic Yoon Eun-sung did.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim