(eagle peals)
(upbeat music)
Greetings, brother
My niece is hosting a function
I'll surely be there
Do come brother
Here, sister
Do come
- Sure will.
Check your note
You didn't gift money last time itself
We have to give to brother Pandi's home
- It's in that street
Said he went to buy shampoo,
hasn't returned yet
Hey dude, can we go for bath?
You must definitely come
- You surely must come
Will she offer monetary gift?
Won't I go to her house
and humiliate her, if she didn't
Wedding couple
Groom : P.Sowndarapandi
Bride : M.Prashanthi
Wedding couple
Groom : P.Rajasekar
Bride : T.Soniya
Wedding couple
Groom : K.O.Dineshkumar
Bride : T.Preethi
Wedding couple
Groom : M.A.Ajithkumar
Bride : A.Dhaarani
Wedding couple
Groom : S.Rajendran
Bride : B.Pavithra
Wedding couple
Groom : R.Sivapandi
Bride : J.Nagapandiammal @ Nithya
Pennycuick Izhzham (spelt wrong)
Groom : K. Pennycuick
Bride : `
Sister, we haven't given to this house
It's an old stag's house,
No monetary gain
Invitation will go in vain
Then let's leave
♪ I'm gonna host a wedding feast? ♪
Sister
Here comes the old stag
Off he goes for bride-seeking
Until now, he would have
seen at least two lakh brides
He isn't getting tired
Yo, Penny
What fella?
The whole village is using the usual 'L'
Jackass your house
alone needs a different 'zh'
Buster
When I spend 200 just for the lock
Why must I use a low trivial 'L'?
In all the 'L' letters this
'zh' is the fanciest one
Just mind your own business, numbskull
Go pal, you won't get
a bride even this time
I'll bring her along
with me on my way back
At least to feast in the wedding
Brush your teeth properly atleast today
Look how he's mocking
I'll take my leave
Chow hound, look at him
and his belly big as his vehicle
Azhagu Raja Illam
Sengganudayar saves
M. Nagarajan home. 1991
A. Mokkayyan Illam
S. Pandiyan Illam
Pavunuthaayi Illam
Shush
Why? Who's house?
Come running,
It's Pavunuthaayi's home
Why did it keep it like that?
Come fast, I'll explain
(upbeat music)
Oh yes I have.
- You have?
Hey dummy, bring hot samosas soon,
Along with sauce.
Hasn't come
Hello sir, come on, come and sit down
I've made hot samosas just for you
(subtle music)
(birds chirping)
♪ When I'm frail, I call upon to you ♪
♪ When I pray, I call you my world ♪
♪ When I stumble, I praise you ♪
♪ I sought you in penance ♪
♪ At your holy feet, I found my refugee ♪
Angaleshwari
Sundaravalliyamma
Vadakku Vaachiyamma
Manthayamma
Malayamma
Mudhalakula Karuppu, The Destroyer
Utchampatti Karuppu
Varusanattu Karuppu, The protector
Kottai Karuppu
Sangili Karuppu
The gods who hunt around
bushes and trees with whip
And every god in their vicinity
Our Pattavarum
Twenty-one Rajas,
And our Madurai Meenakshi Ma
The deity in the Hill of Azhagar
Vellakaiyanum
Kara Muruganum
May your merciful gaze fall upon us
Rains be generous
Fields thrive well
Our cattle multiply and grow
And let there be abundance, Lord
(sentimental music)
The Godmother
♪ Lord of the six abodes ♪
♪ Regal bearer of the spear ♪
♪ Come riding your peacock ♪
♪ And remove our struggles ♪
♪ To your struggling devotees ♪
♪ You are the light ♪
Yo,
Nimwit
I'll smash your head and
make sweet balls out of it
Wait, you doofus
Tubby
Is this TV running in your father's veshti?
Let the electricity bill come
From the gold I gave your mom,
I'll pluck one sovereign
How much current, he's burning
He, himself asked for three sovereigns
and left me here for four years
What will you pluck from him?
He will ask,
Even in eight meter Veshti
He will ask for extra two meter.
Born for 2-Idly
If I ever find him
Hmm
I'll aluminum coat the Aiyampatti broom,
Dye the broom from Sadachipetti
Bundle up the broom
sticks from Kuppanampatti
And whack him out
As if Light bulb is the
only thing he's lacking
Shameless idiot
(exciting music)
Pavunuthaayi is coming for collections
(Chaotic panic in crowd)
They must shake for our arrival
Pavunuthaayi is coming for collections
Oh God
♪ Her nose studs are machete ♪
♪ From her ears, swings the thandatti ♪
Pavunuthaayi is coming for collections
Where
Come run with me, She's coming
♪ Her twin nose studs are like machete ♪
♪ From her ears, swings the thandatti ♪
♪ She'll outrun P.T. Usha on the track ♪
♪ She'd knockout Mike Tyson in a punch ♪
When you wanted the money
how you acted all tears and tales
Scumbag
Why does a broken mutt
like you need broekies?
I'll beat your ass up,
you shameless scoundrel
I'll gauge your eyes with
rolling pin and blind you, prick
Hey you
Stop now
Will this bike only run
with your tush twisted?
Here,
Yank the sewer,
and then pick up your keys
♪ The Godmother is on her way, move aside ♪
♪ Pavunuthaayi is storming in, take cover ♪
You ladies, did you think
its a pump or your husband?
Your working this hard on it
Come around my house asking
for money to change the washer
I'll thrash you all with broom stick
Ay, run away
In whose well are you...?
With whose permission
did you turn the motor on?
Jil Jil soap
Oh lord
Except washing your tush,
Must you show everything on YouTube?
Welcome my friends
♪ Rangamma ♪
♪ Ay, Thangamma ♪
♪ Ela, Angamma ♪
♪ She surges like a lion ♪
♪ Rangamma ♪
♪ Ay, Thangamma ♪
♪ Ela, Angamma ♪
♪ She surges like a lion ♪
♪ Her fingers strike like spears ♪
♪ Her stare, flammable ♪
Without giving money back,
he is chilling here
Take that stone
Take that
Throw at him
♪ Mauls rest in her hands ♪
♪ Pandiyamma starts blasting ♪
♪ Stinging bee shaped her birth ♪
Come around town
♪ She is the town villain ♪
♪ The fierce lady who guards ♪
♪ The whole town simmers under her fire ♪
♪ She gulps down a whole chicken ♪
♪ If you take a dip in her well ♪
♪ She'll turn furious ♪
Hey Pennycuick
- What gramma?
You went to see the bride,
what happened?
The bride ran away.
Ha, ran away?
Why don't you marry her?
She still has eight teeth.
Shucks, I'm a honourable lady
Considering the way it is,
What you said might only happens it seems
♪ The Godmother is a local don ♪
♪ She's a Superman draped in Sungudi ♪
Grandma we have liver
Head
Intestines, what do you want?
Oh my god
Gramma, there is only one goat
Empowering Women's Well-being
Hey tubby!
Since I eat like this only,
my heart, liver,
intestines and guts,
Have no toxins
No diabetes, BP or anything
that much strength
Tomorrow, even if I die
I, myself will go and
lay in the graveyard
No dogs will have to carry me.
Granny,
Can I type the number for you?
Are you having trouble seeing?
Would you also want to take the money?
Zip it!
♪ They are killing me ♪
This drawing
♪ They are tormenting me ♪
(bus honks)
Oldie Pavunuthaayi is going
somewhere in full swing
If Sunday arrives
She glams up
like a newly wed woman
Goes and comes nobody knows where
Hey when did you attain puberty?
♪ For my mother ♪
Sitting in ladies seat. Move aside
♪ As a son-in-law ♪
♪ Hey come quick my darling ♪
Oh my
Took 10 generation to send you to school
Why are putting on a clown show?
Study well
Go that way
♪ She's a wildfire in human form ♪
♪ She roams cunningly, day after day ♪
♪ She is a walking Ayyanar weapon ♪
(subtle music)
Hey
What have you done to you hair?
Neymar cutting, Ma
You better go and cut it properly
If gramma sees, she'll kill you
As if I'm scared of her
(sobs)
(thunder rumbles)
♪ The Godmother is a local don ♪
♪ She's a Superman draped in Sungudi ♪
Alike James Bond!
- Oh God
Can't you guys live without gambling
Hey Vesakutta
Tomorrow if you didn't
pay the interest amount
Good grief
I'll boil you in my cauldron
and with that water
only I'll take a head bath.
Holy smokes, this too
Ten
Twenty
Alike Rajinikanth?
Dragging beedi
What are you having?
Pathetic porridge only
Hey
Lady of Sokkampetti
Who's there?
Come here
Here she comes
Sun shouldn't rise for this hag
Wonder what trouble she brings today
Look
Keep your innocent face, okay?
Where is that dog?
He went out early morning
and hasn't returned yet
Even after yanking his veshti,
He hasn't gotten his senses
Tomorrow if you don't pay the interest,
I'll disrobe your saree
and wreck you, despicable dog.
Behave properly
What is the round in your hand?
Give that
Being tiny he holds a lot of money
Says she'll disrobe the saree
of someone her daughter's age
Noble people are dying all around
Yet this wretched hag is defying death.
♪ Life has thousands of events ♪
♪ Every path has some pain left lingering ♪
Aren't you ashamed?
Doing like this
Once she wakes up at dawn
She said, she'll boil me in a cauldron
You called Shoba and Silk in a young age
Is sweet sixteen happening for Pavunuthaayi?
Did she attain puberty just yesterday?
All of us are offering you coconut
Does Pavunuthaayi's
alone have sweet taste to it?
Got a cozy pedestal here,
You're chilling with booze and cigarettes
Mind you,
I'll grab the dagger from your hand
and kill five people
They'll ask who supplied the weapon
I'll point to you and say Karuppan did
they'll dig you up along with your pedestal
and lock you in Madurai jail
there these cigarettes, booze
and other extravagance won't be available
If you can behave be here
Or go back to your place, Kerala itself
Tomorrow morning
before early dawn
If you didn't give me what I asked for
They named me Vesakutta
I'll change that name
into Sai kutta
and will go to worship Saibaba
(thunder and lightning strikes)
(Vesakutta panics)
Hey
Gramma is gonna come
Turn off the TV and go to school
If she comes, she'll kill you
Still two minutes left
Get blasted then
Grub Goblin
(clock strikes)
Ma
Hey Thozhu
huh
Go, check what gramma is doing
why hasn't she come down yet
Just now they started Mottu Batlu
she started nagging
before I come they'll kill off John
(suspenseful music)
Ma
(fluttering)
What?
Ma, come here fast
(overlapping panic)
What happened?
Hey, what Pavunuthaayi's
grandson is screaming like this
(tense music)
What?
Ma
(upbeat music)
What this, she's riding cycle laying flat
♪ Six-feet is waiting for you, granny ♪
♪ Go swiftly, to accompany granpy ♪
♪ Hearse is waiting for you wretch ♪
♪ Go safely, let the East awaken ♪
♪ Oh, Oh my lord ♪
♪ Bier is ready for you ♪
♪ Your supreme rule ♪
♪ Has ended now ♪
♪ Oh, Oh my lord ♪
♪ Bier is ready for you ♪
♪ Your supreme rule ♪
♪ Has ended now ♪
- Are you for real?
Here I come
♪ People from all walks, gather around ♪
♪ Watch the rituals ♪
- How huge a thing you did?
KARUPPA
Got prideful, and acted swiftly
Just last night I asked
I want to do something for you now
Hey here give the coconut
Leave my coconut
Leave my Veshti, I'll get sober
You buy a different coconut
He's taking our coconut,
you keep watching
(thuds)
How mouthy were you?
Ay, tubby
How loud are you watching?
You said you had a great legacy
Now look at your status
That sister also, did
financing and died pitiful
That's why god made her bedridden
There is no way she'll get up
Hey
She'll died right?
Don't know
She'll kick Yemen himself
and bring his buffalo
In her case, only if
she turns into ashes
We can be sure
KARUPPA
Don't let me down this time
How much talk did you talked?
Pinch her sharp
She's down without any sense only
Hey
What is the oldie
gesturing her hand about?
What much is she gonna say?
She'd say how much she’ve lent,
and ask to collect it
If that's the case everybody
in here have borrowed
Why are you adding me with you?
I've returned the money last week itself
Without a guilt she lies.
(vehicle honks)
Look patiently, how's it?
I've graded the photos
What in the hell?
Flowers, belt, don't I look goat'd?
Will be set right?
Hey
Already, I traded all the pictures
you brought to the scraper
I bought the chair you are sitting on.
Then why every week
You keep bringing new photos
Killing me
These are freshly taken, will be good
In this time, its hard to find
bride even for educated man
After 40 years which forest
will I roam to find a bride
Why are you talking aloud brother?
Isn't there any way, tell me a way
Will you do a thing?
Near Thumakundu
Twice divorced, and third
widowed girl is available
One, two, three
I'm fourth then?
For your face even if you get
eight or nine you must be happy
But one condition
For her you must give 12 sovereigns of gold
then only she will marry you
What do you say?
Can we fix that?
For fourth itself I must give 12
I only have two
Where will go for another ten?
Penny
What fella?
You know the matter?
- What?
The corner house Pavunuthaayi
Is in her death bed
Yo, what are you saying?
I'm going there only, come fast
Fourth or eighth, finish the deal
GO, GO
I was planning to borrow from her only
You lather peacock oil or deer oil
However cure the Oldie
If I use those oils, they'll lock me up
Here he comes
Go front
He is an useless fellow
Leave, let him go
Move, let him go first
- What you doing is not right
You all borrowed money from the Oldie
Now you're all lining up for her death
Let the healer heal her
You go
- go slowly
Don't gather up and kill the oldie
Shouldn't you have pulled his pants
Hey Pennycuick, Chow hound
Sit,you sit down
Gramma
Do you recognise me?
Pennycuick
Grandson of Usulamayan
Tell, what happened
Gun
Three people
Oh-ho
Yeah, him too?
That's it.
Okay leave
Everyone hide your face,
Chow hound is seeing
He understood something
Why is he looking like this?
What is the oldie saying?
Hey, without knowing that only
we are standing like this
For that only we called you
You nodded like you understood
Wait man
That's why I brought the healer
In a while, he'll say everything
Stand silently without getting angry
Is he a healer or astrologer,
he's tapping the fingers
Hey, he's whispering something
What you are just leaving
without saying anything
Wait I'll tell
Let me ask what's with him
Am I bound to tell you all?
You say first
Why should I say?
Wait
Tell us
Scoundrels
Shut up
I'm saying, wait
Wait
Hang on
Don't shout I say
She is an outcast lady
Fated to suffer in her deathbed
Won't last tonight
We shall inform her three sons
(crowd chanting happily)
(firecrackers bursting)
KARUMATHUR
(Kamal Haasan song playing)
Heyyy
Wait I'll tell my husband
I'll tell my wife
Get lost
(machine whirring)
(humming)
Dude
From morning he's been
playing Kamal Haasan songs
Ask him to play Thalaivar
Rajinikanth's song
Hey Uppiliyan
What?
Play Thalaivar Rajinikanth's song
From morning you've been
killing us with Kamal Haasan songs
What?
Guys,
Let me ask for a Sathya Raj song
Then you listen whatever you want
What Sathya Raj song?
Where are you from?
Already we are quarreling about Rajini song
Keep your mouth shut
For Sathya Raj song
itself they are causing trouble
If I ask for Ramki song,
they might kill me it seems
They bet me for asking Raj Kiran song
Look, how much time he is searching for!
Yeah right
Wait now
Hey
Thalaivar has acted 170 films
You are searching as if it's Apas film
Wait man, wait
How did it come now?
Sit down
See dude
He played Thalaivar song as soon as I said
He fears me
♪ In all the places ♪
♪ At every moment ♪
♪ Music and Joy ♪
See, He played Kamal Haasan song again
Hey
This is Rajinikanth song, man
In this Rajinikanth plays the
main supporting instruments
Don't you know that?
Supporting instruments?
Haan, this thambura
Ranjinikanth
This is not Ranjini song at all
Hey
He's pulling our legs from morning
Wait ladies, I'll be back
They've started their antics again
I'm talking here,
what are you munching?
Sit down dude
Hey, why are you shouting?
From morning he's playing Kamal Haasan song
You are not questioning him?
What did I tell you morning?
What did you say?
Kamal Haasan song, Rajini song
Ajith song, Vijay song
Don't play any of their songs
Common man,
What's his name?
Sivakumar's sons, two of them
Among them, play the elder one's song
That's it?
Play
Wait
What a great guy!
They aren't listening to MP's song
He's playing common guy's song
Keep quiet man
No one will stay in your function
Hey
Even if we count 8 paisa for a bone
You'd have to cash in one lakh
Trying to leave with an excuse?
(singing)
He's now playing Kamal daughter's song
Oh my god, he caused a huge chaos
I'm gonna smash your set today
Stop, stop you guys
Throw his speaker out
See what I'm going to do today
Wait guys
Can't you guys hear what I'm saying?
Hey
Oh Lord even after 50 years
They've not stopped
this Rajini-Kamal conflict
CHEKKANURANI
Get down fast
Here
You dumbass
How stupid you must've thought I am?
To give this torn note
and try to leave discreetly?
It's valid brother
What? Valid?
I'll smack you
How much do you have?
I don't have any money
Hey
Said you don't have
You have 50 rupees!
- 50 rupees brother
Thought auto drivers are good people
So only I exchanged with you
Hold this
Go fella
I keep running into these sort of morons
Do you want auto lad?
Auto, auto?
No brother
Brother auto?
Auto, auto, auto?
Auto mam?
Did you just call me hot?
What are you talking to a lady?
You prick
I'll whack you with my sandals.
He and his head
Oh lord
She speaks like she just blossomed
Wrinkled prune
♪ Money is God ♪
What's up with her, early in the morning?
Tell me
Bring me four parathas and go
What paratha uh?
Cut the call
Frustrating early in the morning
- Hey man what?
No one is cooking
Oh my
♪ Money is God ♪
♪ Even God himself knows it ♪
Hello
USILAMPATTI
SELVAM FLOWER SHOP
This is how he's weaving
Where did they even learn that?
What disgust is this?
Anyway for the dead body only
What is this?
What is he doing with fevicol?
Hey, why are you sticking it?
What fella?
Who's sticking?
Do you know why I have it?
Shut up and leave
No sense of what certain things are for
And talking nonsense
Brother what's the rate of this garland?
I would have tied it properly, you know
You yelled and it fell down
All these stores and
do you have to chose mine?
Phonepe or Google pay?
Pay?
Cash only
Cash!
Which garland?
This one
What's the cost today?
One, Multiply, six zero, two minuses,
(1x60=)
That's it
Sixty rupees
Sixty rupees?
A good garland itself costs 60 only
A good garland?
Then what garland is this?
Is this even a garland?
If I buy this garland and put on the dead,
The body itself will wake
up and spit on my face
You've tied one for Usilampatti
and one for Sekkanur
You've stuck it
As if tassel would be the one lack,
You also wasted the Tulsi
Thought instead of this being cow food
I'd buy for 5 or 10 rupees
and help you
You are saying 60 rupees
I won't pay a penny for you
Wait, let's settle this
Hey you
If not for making charges
At least pay up for the flowers and twigs
Come to the funeral, and
pick your flowers and twigs
Fraudulent
What is my garland lacking,
for him to yell like this
Would it be cause it is withered?
Let me coax it back
♪ Don't go for flower harvesting ♪
♪ If they see you ♪
Why is he calling?
He's of no customary offerings
♪ Flowers will wage war for you ♪
Hello
♪ You are my mother, and my father ♪
♪ And also the God
who embrace me with affection ♪
Kamal Haasan song is playing
I think Uppiliyan's arrived
What?
As soon as you see your mom's house,
Affection is overflowing?
Ay, radio set has issues
If I turn on the vehicle it
will start playing on its own
If I turn off the
vehicle only it will stop
First know that
Hmm, it will stop?
Upon arrival to your mom's home,
You've begun your antics
Yeah yeah.
- Go now
I'll park the vehicle and come
Always yapping
Kamal hits CD is stuck stubborn,
and won't come out
When I said the news,
and when are you coming
So, can I come just like that?
Whoa, She looks like Sridivya in saree
I can't win a argument with you
Yo, Uppiliyan
Hey Kamal Haasan be near you Shruthi Haasan
That cunning rascal is eyeing her
Should I fly like a rocket for her?
What are you seeing there?
Your brother's family is coming now only
What are you writing?
Bills
Here they comes my
younger and elder brothers
I wonder what they are going to do?
Hey, shut up
Hey, Suruli, What are you doing?
I'm making Nisinda water for mom
Your brothers have come, talk to them
If they come and talk let them
Or let them be
What's this, the siblings
aren't talking with one another
They're not going inside and
checking on their mother either
What happened?
Before four years
It all started when Oldie Velusamy died
The happy family started to fall apart
Pour so the crown is completely wet
Give that
Who's the tie guy?
Is this our Velusamy?
Kamal Haasan's brother Chandra Haasan
Been four years since he died
He's postering for him,
Instead of his father
How much is Chrysanthemum for a kilo?
Forty rupees brother
Forty rupees?
Yes brother
I myself am a top flower seller
For my father's death,
instead of buying from me
Whom did you get it from?
Remove, let's tie it from first
Remove all this, moron
Remove this
Hey
Even if my sister is widowed, It's alright
Suruli
Your brother and your husband are fighting
Hey, you hey
Move aside
Yo, leave me
What is all this?
Why are you drunk fighting?
Hey, why are you beating him?
In my quarter
Hey, leave me
It had 2 ounce, how did it disappear?
Do you think I'm a
filthy leftover like you?
You dirty left-over-liquor rat
What are you looking for?
Hey what bruh
Bro, wait bro, stop
Parrot figurine
My father is a tiger, you fool.
Are you a thug?
- Here take it
You must've built a tiger bier
Their father's body hasn't
even had fully burned
The very same night they
asked to split the property
and messed with their mother
Hey
Hey oldie
Hey you wait bruh
Are you going to come or not?
Selvam is calling you
You don't know how
much tempered I am
You first come out lady,
we have to talk to you
Come, come outside
Hey
What bruh, you alone sat down?
Hey, Pavunuthaayi
Come out
Everything is over now,
Let's settle everything today
Here she came, look
You first come out
Why is she cleaning the door-step?
What, we keep asking
and you are not responding?
Hey lady of Kokkalam
Yeah?
What are you frying?
Smells like Non-veg
Maggots
There's a death in the opposite house
Your husband wants to eat fried maggots?
Is his tongue that tied?
Here,
Bring some over in a side bowl
Are you looking at the stunt she's pulling?
Yeah
Hey Oldie
You
What lad?
The old man is dead now,
Yeah
Split the assets and give us some
We are all struggling
Yeah
If you are struggling,
go hang yourself
Or eat some other thing for your meals
Why are you asking us to eat?
Hasn't even took off the
bindi after your husband death
and you're licking the plate off
You go and eat something else
My husband
My bindi
My food
I'll lick off and eat
Who are you to ask that?
You can't even wash your
tush until eight years old,
You dare question me?
OK, keep your family drama for later
First settle me off
It's getting late for me
What settlement for you?
What settlement huh?
Yeah
When getting married, we talked
that you'd give 25 sovereigns
Now you've only given 22 sovereigns
Rest 3 sovereign you are
dragging it, now and then
What does that mean?
3 sovereign only right?
You take it
What?
Show me the 22 sovereign I gave
Take it whenever you want
See this
Why, why must I show?
I gave the gold for her only
Did I gave to pawn it?
For you to pawn it,
lend the money for interest
and go drinking bootleg arrack,
and eat pork?
Why the heck should
give my daughter and gold?
So, I shouldn't ask dowry?
Keep your daughter with you itself
I don't want her
Hey who are you to leave my daughter?
She will help my household, and be here
You roam around holding yours' in your hand
Then only you'll understand her worth
Whoa
Hey you, are you even an elderly man?
She's disrespecting her
son-in-law, won't you question her?
You keep quiet
She even talk me disrespectfully
You are asking me for justice
Hey oldie
It is norm, that parents
wealth belong to their kids
Without giving us, are you
planning to enjoy all this yourself?
Let me ask,
Why do you need all
this anymore anyway?
Yeah?
If you stay, in each our house for 6 months
Won't one of us feed you?
Yeah, right?
How's what I'm saying?
I'll whack you with my slippers,
Scumbags
Who the hell are you to ask my property?
He got drunk, and was
sleeping around with his mistress
I, sold fried dumplings
Carried stones
Hauled vegetables
Pooled money
Lent money for installments
Saved all this little by little
You want me to give
away all my property
Alike my peers in this town
and wait outside the doorstep in a rope cot
and be begging daughter-in-laws for gruel
Scoundrel
Until the day I die
I will only enjoy all my wealth
If you hear my death news
Come to this home
Or else
I'll thrash you all until this broom shreds
Where are you throwing?
Aunty what are you talking?
Hey, get lost you dogs
Are you even a lady,
I'll see who's gonna do your last rituals
That is the day they left embarrassed
Oldie didn't include
them in any good or bad
After four years today they've come
She's a real tough lady
That too
Expecting when she'll die
So they can split the wealth, useless scums
You toss the deck
KARUPPA
Oh lord
Only 7 rupees cigar was
available, don't get furious god
He's praying with full devotion
KARUPPA
Selvam
You came back to town, Huh?
Go away first
Selvam
Why is it always Brandy for KARUPPAN?
A whiskey
Rum sim
Military
Beer
Why can't you buy him a quality alcohol?
Hey, don't suck my strength
Won't you let me pray?
Go away first
Can't even get side dish it seems
KARUPPA
-Selvam
Can't you buy a good garland for KARUPPAN
You tied it?
What's wrong with this one?
What? Why is he getting this furious?
KARUPPA
Let's ask it straight away
-Selvam
Give me 20 rupees
You wreckless, I'm
going to break your mouth now
WHAT?
Won't you let me pray?
You drunkard
I'll give 20 rupees for you, stupid
Get away first
KARUPPAN, won't lay his eyes on
people who offer him good garland
For your garland only he's going to bless
He lights lamp and comes to pray
Can't even spare 20 rupees
Go and hang yourself to death
Did you see this KARUPPA?
If you had taken my
mother rightly on time
Will he talk like this?
How many days will she challenge Yemen?
Hmm?
Before this oil lamp goes off,
Please take my mother
Don't betray me this time
Chit fund due is up soon
I've got mountain-deep faith in you
Don't let me down
See it through
If you do this alone for me
I'll offer a shared
goat, and Pongal for you
Usulampatti thaluk
Vikramangalam, Kadupatti's
Late Velusamy's wife
Uppiliyan Radio's owner
Kamal Uppiliyan's mother
Pavunuthaayi's demise ceremony's
Light and sound are handled by
Music King, Uppiliyan radios
Everybody is welcome
To give your full support for the funeral
Hey Uppiliyan
-What?
You keep going
For your funeral also, same mic set only
May be I'll reduce 20 or 30
rupees considering your age
♪ Who lit the precious lamp in the street corner? ♪
Look at his shenanigans
He has found a Kamal Haasan
song every situation
Hmm
Is this something a grown-man would do?
What about, even
young-man would do this only
Stop talking,
This is called marketing
♪ Who plants jasmine creepers on fences? ♪
- Who's this guy, dude?
- Don't know who's this.
Don't know who's this
♪ When dawn breaks in the east ♪
Why's he seeing like this?
♪ Does darkness fall in the west? ♪
Hey, from when the Oldie got bedridden
She's trying to tell something
Ask her what's it
Yeah?
-yeah
Which temple's bhasma is this?
You'll end up in hell, doomed bastard
Let us rot.
What kind of torment is this?
Pavunuthaayi has people to cry for her?
Can't figure who this is sister
Have you seen him around?
Who's this guy, seems unfamiliar?
Brother
One minute
Whoa What?
Brother, can you wait here for a minute?
Brother
I'm running late, I need to leave
Brother, you can leave in a bit
I'll bring them, brother
Please be here, you'd be blessed
Please don't leave brother
Hey, Uppili, come here
Don't I have to be near, when
my mother's soul leave her
Acting big on mom's love, come here.
Come I say
Hey Vijaya come here,
-What about?
Want me to say everything here?
What man?
Come
Come quickly
Where is he?
Hey Selvam!
Hurry up
Walking step by step, double up.
Hey, why are you summoning everyone?
Ah.
-Who's this man?
He, himself will say, wait.
Brother, these are Oldie's sons
Like you said me
Say to them also
Hey Pennycuick, What did he tell you?
Wait, he will tell
I'm a goldsmith
Gold Kumar is my name.
In Madurai Gold Bazaar, 37 th store is mine
To the North of Water tank
seventh store, if you ask...
(Unison neglect)
-Wait you guys
Listen patiently for a bit
Brother tell them
This granny had a gold chit,
in our store for eight years
Listen to this
Weekly she'll buy at least a gram
Just last week
She bought 160 sovereign in total
Good lady
Oldie is signaling three,
what could it be?
Is it going to be a gold treasure secret?
She might've lent 30 rupees to someone
Leave that at
Choker 5 sovereigns
Jasmine chain 10 sovereigns
Meenakshi chain 15 sovereigns
Nose pin half a sovereign
Gold disc earring one and a half sovereign
Lobe studs half sovereign,
rook half sovereign
helix stud half a sovereign,
lobe drops half sovereign
Side chain 10 sovereigns,
bangles 4 and a half sovereigns
Stone bangles 14 sovereigns
Gold bangles 20 sovereigns, Meenakshi...
Hey it's not 2 sovereigns,
it's 20 sovereigns
Ah 20 sovereigns
Aaram 22 sovereigns
Small beaded chain 16 sovereigns
Glorisa flower choker 11 sovereigns
Mango chain 8 sovereigns
Total 160 sovereigns
Where does she have it?
Who's this guy?
Going this loud
The Tata Ace is arriving loud
Who's this?
The vehicle is halting in an unusual way
Who's that, came along with band set?
Hey, brother has come
Hey, our guy
- hey, 2 idly bro has arrived
What dude you are
sitting in the vehicle itself
Get down dude
What man, he have arrived?
Yeah, what is this?
Hold the crackers
Hey,
Your father dude
Beat it
Why is it this loud?
Come and watch his atrocities
Here, they've started
Ay, Look there
See him dancing?
That's right, why won't he dance
According to our custom
House, land, and all the assets for boys
Mangalsutra for the
first daughter-in-law and
the rest of the gold will
go to the daughter only
Look the way Suruli's husband is dancing
That's the reason your Oldie
Even with all of us being present
was yearning to tell it to her daughter
All these years
2 idly who was longing 3 sovereigns
without any strain
If he'd get 160 sovereigns, it's right
Hey, what can we do next,
first say that, babbling
What to do?
Am I going to say
anything out of the world?
Split it 50 each for you
I'll help you get this gold
Give me 10 sovereign as my commission
What 10 sovereigns?
160 sovereign dude
See
If you give me 10 sovereigns,
I have saved 2 sovereigns
Totally with the 12 sovereigns,
I'll get married in your grace
If this matter stay between us
Why am I gonna talk about this outside?
Not alone that dude,
Your Mom, that oldie
even if she gets a holed-25 paisa
she'll take it to Gandhi museum
and asks what rate they'll pay for it
That sort of a person
To safeguard gold
She might've hid in an
eight-looped port that ants can't climb
Or a spirit-guided
fort no man can reach.
So,
Until we get hold of the gold,
Your mother must not die.
Now, what are you trying to say
Oh my
What happened?
Wait, wait, I'll be back.
Hey, Selvam,
-Why are you running like this?
Why is he running like
he's bitten by a rabid dog
Might he have killed the oldie
Run fella run
You have Nayantara's picture
and named it Nakma store
Won't you give a snacks packet?
Sine I named it Nakma,
must I give you snacks
Hey, who's this, what is he taking?
Hey you stop
Hubby, where are you running?
Wait I'll be back
Hey, see here
Hey Selvam
Hey, Who's this?
He's Pavunuthaayi's youngest son
Why is he running like this?
Don't know why
Hey Ochchu
My name is not Ochchu, Kamal Haasan
Which hero does your sister like?
Vijay
Don't give up, don't give up Selvam
Next five minutes,
will stand for next 50 years
Hey, Vesakutta
What?
Don't let that lamp, go out.
Come
I asked you for 20 rupees
You said you won't give, go
(Kushi music rises)
Hey
I'll give you 500 rupees
Don't let it go out come, save it
What?
Five hundred?
Here I come
(Kushi music peaks)
Look at the way her son is
Clown family
Hey look there
In front of whom are you guys shaking it?
Hey Thozhu
Come here or I'm gonna kill you
He alone danced until now
I'll pluck your mustache
My darling boy, come here
Hey 2 idly
What's with you?
Look at you and your face
Hey you where did you go?
She won't die
How?
I've hired someone
KARUPPA
Your grace is limitless
What? They are going inside
Daddy
- Hubby
Shut up, I'll kick in your mouth
Where are you going?
Stay quiet
Wait dear, he'll come
- Why are they going inside?
Enough, Let's call the doctor, uh?
Hey, Siddha medicine get up. Go.
Move aside, sitting as if
watching TV in Panchayat
We searched the room thoroughly
We don't know where she've kept it
Hey look there
♪ Where did she bury it? ♪
♪ She hid it from us ♪
♪ Oh lord, she buried it ♪
♪ She totally wiped it ♪
♪ The lady woke up ♪
♪ She unraveled the lumped rice ♪
♪ She grinded rice crackers ♪
♪ Woke up, Grinded it ♪
Garland store Selvam brother sent these
Daily he'll send me 500
in Google pay, he says
He asked me to take and give that to you
What's your name?
Thirupuli, brother
Thirupuli
Daily on my behalf,
I'll pay you 50 rupees wage
2 packs of beedi
And a cutting
Behave well
Come pick all the things
Hey lady, Is it over?
No fella
♪ Affluent Pavunuthayi ♪
♪ Had us roaming miles ♪
♪ She hid sovereigns of gold ♪
♪ Made us go crazy all around ♪
That's the locker
♪ She levied interest for interest ♪
Same as this
There is a locker in our village bank
What if your mom had
kept the gold in there?
Sir
This bank's account holder
Kadupatti, Pavunuthayi's sons..
Their mother is sick
She, in fear
asked us to grab the
whole sole from the bank
and take all the money from her account
Hey
Show the ID proof
Show him the photo
This is a Pavunuthayi
If you give the key
We, all four will grab all the stuff and go
Who are you?
I am
I am th...
I am their legal advisor
Present sir
I've checked the account sir
See this looks like the
bureau we saw at home
Like before we're gonna get
crunches and munches only
Shut up
These guys looks like robbers dear
What?
Call Checkanur police station
Instead of belt, he's
tucked with waist chain
Run away Selvam
Hey lower your lungi
A lady is here.
- She's an Oldie
He is a man, and I
came trusting him, my bad
All these small lads are all putting flex
Hey where is my photos?
A wide smiles like this
'We grieve'
Supers
Hey ma, hasn't it been over yet?
No, you drunkard dog
Hey, what's this, how
much time do I have to wait?
What is this shaking in the front?
This is a gold searching machine
How do you know to do this?
I learned it through YouTube
Hey, we know the route
Hey
- Stand up
Why are you going inside my legs?
- Move that side
Come man, come
Come running behind me
Is it there?
♪ Did our Mom bury it
near the spring-head? ♪
♪ Weekly once she wandered ♪
♪ As though England called her ♪
♪ As if in a jest she slipped
through every house ♪
What machine did you tell it was?
Gold searching machine
Then why wasn't there any gold
The thing is
Here is a light on, right?
- Yes
It must also ring "KIKI"
Show Where?
Ring
Why did you throw it away?
It's ringing man
Hold this
Hey Vijaya jump
- I can hear it ringing
Search well everywhere
Did you find it?
Brother don't come
out without the gold
Where is the gold brother?
It's ringing because it fell
in the water, you dumbfucks
Don't throw and break it
Hey lady, Is it over now?
Hey, no fella
what lady, still not yet over?
What's up with him?
♪ Will it be found in the well? ♪
♪ Will it stare behind, as we run? ♪
♪ Will it be found? ♪
♪ Will it stare? ♪
Is it over?
There was a drunkard who
kept asking 'Is it over' right?
Yes
He died
Look there
- What are you saying?
What this even younglings are dying
But this is laying down
for two days, and daring death
Shucks
Grandpa
We are all Pavunuthayi's sons
Did you see our mother roaming here alone?
Go and look there
♪ Hail to Shiva, glory to you ♪
♪ Oh my heart, belong to thee ♪
Hey, look what's there
Hey
Why did our Oldie came here?
We've searched half the district
If she had any concern about us
She would've split that among us
From woods to hills
She got us begging
I'm like my idol Kamal Haasan,
I live believing 'You can do it, yourself'
Thought it's mom's gold, so I can take it
There's no tower
Today I'm saying, Listen well
If I don't get this gold
I'll butcher her into pieces
and throw her in
the eastbound train
Hey man, keep quiet for sometime
Hey Pennycuick, first
stop looking at the phone
Look here,
Like digging up an old scar,
and making it an infection
you made us roam searching for gold
We might pass away before that Oldie
Tell us what to do
What dude?
Is gold that light for you?
In a country, gold only decides
how money can be printed
You guys are standing
here in Chennakal hill
and are lousy about it
What if 2 idly comes to know about this?
Listen here, the only person
2 idly fears is our mother
He must never find this out
If he finds out, everything is over
None of us will get anything and
have to lick our empty hands
As if the troubles we have isn't enough
We have to lick too?
Look here man, Usulampatti
people have asked
my daughter's hand in marriage
I've give at least 35 sovereigns
My son Kamal Haasan is stubborn to study
I have to admit him in Karumathur College
That'll cost 10 to 15 lakhs
Keep all this in mind
and talk, that's all I have say
Hey Uppili that's why I'm saying
When your mom is still alive
Deal this gold issue, on behalf of her.
A sovereign person adding
3 sovereigns, and finish it
2 idly will take that leave
behind him, your sister will also go
Then, when we get the gold
Leisurely we can split the gold
Yo, the oldie's gold 10
sovereigns is going to her only right
Why extra 3 sovereigns?
Vijaya, as I already said
Here, as house and land belong to the sons
Oldie's gold must go to her daughter only
Go man,
-You keep saying that.
I'm saying what you owe her
First settle his deal
With existing troubles,
don't add more
Until he is in the
plinth, it's trouble for us
Do whatever you want
I'm going to to scroll matrimony
Uppili
2 idly is in plinth, leisurely smoking
He seems to be in a good mood
Let's talk about the gold
and settle it smoothly
Look here Penny
A sovereign each, we
can't give him 3 sovereigns
We altogether can give him 1 sovereign
Go tell him
Yo, you reduced 2 sovereigns in 2 km
That's how much we can give
Look here
The sons are giving what their mother owes
They are already struggling
Tell him to take what he gets
Hey, he is a crackhead
Hey mama, you'll talk up
and down and will settle him
Go, go and talk to him
For that, hey
Abiding you words only
we agreed to give him gold
Now if you won't even talk this, what's it
What will I talk to alone
Pray to your god and go
What's this?
- Oh dude
Go dude go, don't overact
Where is your uniforms fellas?
It's hot brother
What he's asking for uniform and all?
Understand?
OK brother
You always have to be watchmens
If you don't wear your
uniforms in 10 minutes
I won't give you payments, be careful
What dude
You smoking?
I just kept it in my pocket here
Give
What this?
What you want me to give?
You just asked if I want cigarettes
Give me
I asked if you are smoking
Where will I go for cigarette?
If you have give me one
I only have hen's feather
With this...
Hey he bet him
Why did you beat me now?
I was peacefully, smoking my cigarette
You only asked if I want a cigarette
What's this? He's beating him like this
He bet him man
He's picking a stone, he might kill him
I will smash you into nothing
- Leave me y'all
With whom are you messing with?
He's trying to kill you
and you are blinking
Do you know why I came?
- I will kill you
Yo, dude, come here, come
He might kill you, come running
Hey he's beating me
He said he doesn't have cigarettes
- Will you give me cigarettes
Will you give?
Leave me, I'll kill him
I'll give
Here take this
- Wait you
I'll skin you, behave properly
2 idly, I'll boil and eat you one day
Yo, dude penny, stop, wait
- Hey Pennycuick
As if getting beaten up is new to him
- Hey cuick
Hey cuick
Hey, run run
- Yo, dude, Penny
Run run, one day you'll also get some
For 3 sovereigns you
guys are making me beg?
Hey, come here
Ask your mom to make ginger corra coffee
Get lost loser
Wants Ginger corra coffee, prick
See how resilient my son is now itself
Yeah
Yo, penny wait
- Hey dude, listen to us
Suddenly he laid hands on me
I am talking to you and you keep walking
You are talking?
Stay, I'll smash your head and
make sweet dumplings out of it
Why is everyone picking up stones
Why are you guys following me?
Hey, put the stone down
Put that stone down first
- What more should I put down?
Wait let's talk about it
What you are giving is not ONE sovereign
Just a sovereign
Just cause I respect you for that
The sovereign won't increase to 10 lakhs
For just one cigarette he thrashed me
You are trying to catch
fish with empty hook
That won't happen
If you want to catch a big fish
You ought to sacrifice the small fish
Likewise
If you want to get your
hands on your mother's gold
You have to give the
gold your mother owes him
If you want to, listen
or do as it pleases you
For an outsider how will
you give me commission
Dude wait, I'll buy you a soft drink
I not only struggled along with you,
I got beaten up by him too
Hey, I'll do what I said
Hey, Uppiliyan
Give me a beedi, if you have
- What?
A beedi
You want a beedi?
Do you know what is happening?
- I don't want beedi, leave me
I'm gonna kill you, see
Hey man, He's in a fight for a a cigarette
You are beating an old man for a beedi
Won't you be quiet
He's asking 3 sovereigns
He's walking away mad,
It's such head ache
- What can we do for that?
Now we have to give 3
sovereigns, what can we do for that?
Look here, there's
someone just like my wife
Why are they standing here?
What now?
There's lot of work in the house
Why are you standing in the road?
Why are you standing in a pose?
Why are you staring?
You burnt charcoal
(Overlapping chatter)
I'll cut your back nerve
What?
- What...
You formed a gang?
At least your bothers
managed to save their hair
You don't have that talent
Yeah
Yo
Even if you leave your mother like that,
she won't die for another two Diwali
In this you are taking care
of her hospital expenses too
What you have lot of money?
Take your hand off
You were selling flowers decently
Someone told you to open a garland shop,
You believed him saying money will flow
You started weaving garland like shit
You stripped off the
last ounce of my esteem
Look here they'll say, "First born
for the mom, last born for the dad"
I got my share
This village peeps will quote dialogues
and will put all the
responsibilities on our head
What is in your mind?
How do I look for you?
Do I look like a Mad women?
Hey
Why are you pampering me?
I found it
You shameless prick,
I'm yelling and you are laughing
Hey Vijaya
What is this?
Leave my hair
Leave my hand first
What are you doing?
If you plead holding my hand
You think I'll let you?
This seems outrageous
Why are they coming in?
What Suruli?
Looking like you're something rare
Get up and eat this
- No I don't want, I'm not hungry
Get up
You go,
we're here right, we'll take care
Why are we here
We'll take care go.
See
How you eyes have sunken?
Stupid, were you starving?
We came to take care of
our Mother-in-law, you go
Yeah
How great of a person she is
See how she's laying today
Hey urine smell is coming
What to do now?
You are asking me?
Let me see what they are doing now?
She also started eating
Hey, you eat the food
Her daughters-in-law we
are here, we'll take care
I think, she was waiting for us
to come to go
Ewww, shit
Take that saree
Bring that
- Here sister
Hey, Stretch and hold
Sister it stinks
Old hag
She would've done just to spite us
We'll change it down here
You change the jacket
Two of you for saree,
and one for the jacket?
160 sovereigns doesn't come easy
Hey sister
Give a No.5 beedi
Here
Why throwing it?
Enough for you
Sister tea for 10 rupees
Tea powder is itself 10 rupees
What Penny?
Yesternight you got
thrashed by my father it seems
Look here
Like I would thrash your father,
I will give you too
Gasbag
He's a bum, and you got beaten by him
Shamelessly
I'll burn with beedi
Go lad
Give it to him quick
Hey wait man
See what he's talking
Here, take this and leave
Hey, I'll not be the same always
Keep joking like this
-Jo...?
Aren't you embarrassed?
One day I'll become serious
That day I'll see to you
Small boy is embarrassing you
Kundu, you smile now
What you want me to do without laughing?
I'll see for how long you'll smile?
What is he gesturing about?
Hey, play a song or something
In which year are you
watching Doordarshan?
Umbrella Antenna isn't paid,
and this is playing for free
If you want, watch, if not leave
If not leave?
You do not know to cover your customer
Hey you,
Signed news is playing,
Why are you increasing the volume?
Nut-job
Here, have your remote
Go, go now but if you come back,
I'll whack you with slippers
As of today a sovereign
costs sixty thousand (60,000)
Sixty thousand multiplied by three is
One lakh eighty thousand
(60,000 x 3 = 1,80,000)
If I take the same One lakh eighty thousand
Divide by three
Hey, he just now multiplied,
He's dividing again
Hey, he have studied till eighth standard
There isn't a math that stumps him
Shut up and do your work
Our Oldie's gold totally
comes around
One hundred and sixty sovereigns
One hundred and sixty multiplied by
Sixty thousand is
Hundred
Thousand
Ten thousand
Lakh
Total Ninety Six lakhs
Oh my god
Ninety Six lakhs divided among three
Yeah, yeah
Thirty lakhs each
Hey
What are you saying?
In this Pennycuik's
commission is alone Six lakhs
My stomach is burning,
Six lakhs?
- Hey Selvam
Just now I calculated, he came sharply
We don't have to give gold for that 2 idly
What?
I'm gonna kill him
Hold him, I'll open his head
Hey, leave, leave me
Hey, yesterday you
said we have to give him
Frantically, we pawned our
wife's jewelery and we got it ready
Now you are saying we don't need
Are you playing with us
We couldn't figure what
your mother was saying
Hence we decided to give him gold
Yes
Now, to figure what
she's saying
I found a way
He arrived
-He reached
Welcome
He's only a half
We could've picked him by a cycle
Move slightly
Let me close door
Greeting sir
Welcome
-Greetings
What man, What is all this?
You brought perfectly,
he looks the same as in TV
Why are you giving me stethoscope?
That's it
Here sir
What man?
That's nothing, whoever
comes to our village
We give them a doctorate
What custom is that?
Dude, who's this?
Looks like a big doctor
They called me to be a
chief guest for a festival
Only this much people is it?
Everyone is inside
Inside?
you are saying different things
Whatever we say, listen to it
Everyone out
- Doctor has arrived
What about the doctor?
Everyone seems sad
Hey you, lady
Go outside for a bit
Where are you guys asking me to go?
I'm the nurse
Nurse ey?
The Doctor himself came,
what's the need for a nurse
Get out first
Hey?
- yeah
Who said to you I'll understand
whatever this lady says?
Him only.
- Yeah me.
Why?
Mute people understand you sign, right?
Yes
Likewise, our Oldie can't speak now,
Okay
Now, when she signs,
you must understand right?
That's must be right?
Hey, What's this?
I was mildly suspicious when
they specifically asked for you
What?
Everyone of them seems like a crackhead
Yeah
They shut the door also
Ask a few things or they won't pay us
Vinoth?
What happened?
He will ask now.
- Ask then.
Mam
Can you hear?
Can you hear me speaking?
You wanted to say something it seems
Say that
Wait
Say that mam
Sir, see that
Hey hey
Take the note
Admiror
Third son is me, Selvam
She's talking about me
Yes
No
Dmitto minor
Is she saying everything is for me?
See, she's saying no
Sweet flour balls
Is he understanding what she's saying?
How is the guy I brought?
What is this?
Again dmitto minor?
Mam, mam, mam
Yo, wake her and ask
Where is that now mam?
Where is it?
What is this man?
What is this?
Tell him
Doctor is asking
Tell it
Oh my
Keep your mouth shut man
Pressuring her
Call the nurse
She fainted
What, what happened?
Open the door man
First, let the airflow
Open the door
A half-pint sized man came
As he went in, they locked the door
They said the Oldie is suffocating
Now they are again taking him back
Bullocks, something doesn't fit right
Yeah?
It's in three places
Or
It has three shares
All of it are cash or gold
Or something of high value
Oh yeah
She's saying 'Go take that'
That too...
She's urging to do it immediately
Sir sir
Did she say where was that all?
Before that her BP dropped
Sir
Is there a way to ask
her just the location of it?
That...
Does she know to read and write?
We won't get that,
-Let's go do our work
Shut up brother
Sir, not just my mother
In my whole family,
Whatever language you write
It's just a toy figure
Among us, I'm the only one
who knows to read and write
Whatever it is tell me
See Mr. Selvam
What sir?
Look here man
If she had known to read and write
We could write down a few places
And ask her to identify
If not
We could have shown her letters chart
And have asked her to pick this or that
And have found out by that
But we don't have either choice now
Then?
If we want to know
what she's trying to say
There’s only one way
That is for her to say that
Siva Siva
What a torture!
Immediately, take her to a big hospital
Try to save her life
That's the only way
Give me extra ten thousand
Did you find out?
That's all, take it sir
What's this man?
Steal-mongers
They are doing something sketchy
Didn't even finish the work,
he wants extra ten thousand
Hey
They came and went right?
How much was the expense?
Calculate it
See there?
In the total One lakh eighty thousand
Aeroplane ticket
Up and down car
Meeting payment
Tea, coffee, and after tiffin expense
Balance we have
One lakh forty eight thousand
Unwanted expense
Okay, let us do a thing
Let's take our mom to Madurai
Take her to Madurai and?
Hey, he said right?
To admit her in a Government hospital
What Government hospital?
There we have to spare 500,
1000 for ward boys and nurses
He doesn't mean government hospital,
He meant, huge-private hospital
He's asking to admit
her in private hospital
Hey you
Go, call the people
BROTHER
What happened Vijaya?
Come running, it's gonna end
Hey drummers
It's gonna end, get up
Come on, come on, come on
Brother, what can we do?
-What should we do?
Let's see what comes,
we'll take her to the hospital
♪ Dead as rose, Monalisa ♪
160 sovereign
♪ Last coin, Blast in town ♪
(♫ Vishwaroopam title song playing ♫)
♪ Who did you think he was? ♪
♪ What was it that made you smile? ♪
♪ When the seed begins to sprout ♪
♪ The complete self is revealed ♪
♪ Born of fire ♪
♪ He grew each and every day ♪
♪ When the moment finally arrives ♪
♪ His true self is revealed ♪
♪ Do you understand his now? ♪
They are taking the Oldie
What are you saying?
No of you get out,
or let anyone in
♪ Revelation ♪
You people started the drama again?
Intermission
Hey, stop the vehicle
I insist
Stop the vehicle
We are customers
Hey, I'm telling you
to stop the vehicle
Are you doing rowdy?
Stop the song
Do you think it's
a hospital or what?
If only I stop the vehicle, song will stop
Shut up and leave
Where is the Vehicle?
Where is the push vehicle?
See whether she's dead or alive
Where is the push vehicle mam?
What sir?
The vehicle used to
push people around
Oh stretcher?
Yes that Eicher, Where is it?
Sister,
- Nurse
There it is
Hey you wait
Girl come and give me a hand
- Sir, wait sir
Brother
Girl come on
Carefully push
Go fast, go fast
GO, GO, GO
Push
Nurse, Emergency
What's this?
Glucose stand for our mother
Hey you, won't this big
hospital have glucose stand?
Crackhead,
Take that out
Hey, I brought it
cause you forgot
You are yelling at me
Don't you have any respect
for your elder brother?
I'll drink up all the glucose
He's born as the elder and troubling all
Sir, wait sir
How many days was she sick?
Just three days sir
Just three days?
What's the rush you brought her?
You could've brought
her leisurely after she died
We could have saved her easily
Ohhh
Hey, How?
You saw Shivaji movie right?
Yes
In that after Rajinikanth dies
They'll press two
iron boxes in his chest
And press it firmly
Without being able
to handle the heat
The body will wake up in a flick
Yeah
- That sort of treatment
Hey you
If a dead body wakes up
unable to handle the heat
All the dead body burning in the
graveyard must wake too right?
What the heck are you talking?
That's the reason they keep
beating it throughout the night
Yeah?
Dude, Is that why they
buried in the olden days?
Of course
Ohhh
Sir
So can we discharge our mother?
Hereafter, please don't call
me to attend this patient
Sir, sir,sir, sir
What now?
Hey, do you have any sense?
He's saying you
already brought her late
And you are asking him,
if you can discharge her
Go and pay the
amount in the reception
Does Pavunuthaayi
mam have insurance?
Do you have Matrimony?
I'm looking for a good match
Keep quiet
- That's why
What does that mean dear?
Does Pavunuthaayi Mam have
Kalaignar Health insurance scheme
Amma Health insurance
scheme or anything like this?
Dear
My mom, from young is in
Sickle, Hammer and Star
Old man is in Kalaingar party
I'm in Makkal Neethi Maiam
He's in Retta Elai
My sister is in Naam Tamilar
Selvam what are you?
Vijay's party, TVK
Write down as 18
th ward, Secretary
Mam, we don't have insurance
We'll go and get it later
Pay the advance
Give her a thousand rupees
Thousand rupees?
How much will we give?
Fifty thousand
Means?
50,000
♪ The braggart is caught ♪
♪ He's ensnared and ruined ♪
♪ Our mother is an atom bomb unleashed ♪
♪ We are Nagasaki, barely withstanding it ♪
We only have 12,000 left
That's all we have?
Yes man
♪ Our mother is an atom bomb unleashed ♪
♪ We are Nagasaki, barely withstanding it ♪
♪ Forsaking love ♪
♪ Discarding pride ♪
♪ Sold it all, even the groin cloth ♪
♪ Search for it ♪
♪ Chase it ♪
♪ Sprint around, hunting money ♪
Yo, why have you
parked in doctor's parking?
Take your vehicle out
♪ Dreaming of mustaches ♪
♪ Yearning for porridge ♪
♪ You wish for the green ♪
♪ And for the milk too ♪
If Suruli understands
the signals Oldie gives
All our struggles
will go in vain
Here on, don't let
her outside the house
You three ladies, be
with her and look after it
More importantly Suruli,
Must not get away
from your eye sight
Get up, come fast
Run run
Your daughter will
go alone to college
What to do?
- She's a clown
Send her to college from here
For her escort, see
that chow hound
Send him along
Still how much did
they asked to pay?
Oh my fate
Send it
Again?
Yo, If we want 30 Lakhs
we ought to give something
Listen to me...
Hey money ran out
They are asking to pay more
♪ And that demands cash ♪
Penny will come
Give your jewelery
♪ He's ensnared and ruined ♪
♪ The braggart is caught ♪
♪ Our mother is an atom bomb unleashed ♪
♪ We are Nagasaki, barely withstanding it ♪
♪ Forsaking love ♪
♪ Discarding pride ♪
♪ Sold it all, even the groin cloth ♪
♪ Search for it ♪
♪ Chase it ♪
♪ Sprint around, hunting the money ♪
What brother,
You are doing unlikely things
I'll tell you something
Don't tell anyone
Okay
Everything I speak
He hears
Without knowing his god strength
All these days
I've wasted my life
I only asked him to put
an end to Oldie's atrocities
He made the Oldie bedridden
From her son's hand itself
Gave me a job
Daily through Google-pay
Gave me 500
Regularly, gave me the
blessing of lighting his lamp
He chuffed me to bits
KARUPPA
You grace surpasses all
From now on, I'm gonna sit here
make this an eternal lamp
give sacred-ash
for the passers-by
built a poly-technic
a school
and've decided to become a saint
I've also thought a
a name for myself
What name brother?
Kangaroo-Adigalar
Kangaroo...
Is that the pregnant animal?
That's Ricky Pandey's
country animal
If in India one or two
might be in Chennai
Where is it in our village?
What's he saying?
Then what we saw near the lake
isn't kangaroo it seems
My earring screw
back got crooked, shit
I payed chit for 1.5 years and bought it
I don't even know
who's clothes these are
Disgusting
For this 160 sovereign gold
See what all struggles
we have to face
Wretched hag
She's tormenting
To save her
She made us strip off
our jewels ourselves
She've done a lot more trouble
On our early marriage days
Me and your brother-in-law
Wasn't spared from
this old hag's torture
She won't let me nap
a while after noon meal
Go to pluck the weeds
Practice wire weaving
She'll say 'You'll get paid 10 or 20 Rs'
Like this another day
We were on our way
to Malayandi theatre
To watch Vijayakanth movie
(Gibberish)
What?
You said you and him
were going to the movie
I asked, What film?
I am talking out of fury
Your adding insult to injury
You listen to what happened
We were on our way
This wretched hag, came running
"Is money growing from trees"
"You useless"
Said "Olium Olium is playing"
"Come watch that" and stopped us
That wretched thing
Yeah
Hey sister, has she
troubled you that much?
Didn't end just
with those trouble
For her daughter, how cleverly
She have saved all these jewels
Hey sister, if the
Oldie wakes up
We'll know where the gold is,
But if the Oldie says, she'll
give the jewels to Suruli?
Who is she?
-
Hmph, She will say
For that reason only, you
have given all the jewels?
That's right
If that alone happens
I'll cut the Oldie
in a chopping log
and tie her up in a banana leaf
For that only we doing
other people's laundry?
She'll give the gold proudly
to her daughter, you say.
What is she doing?
Hey
What?
Come here
Where is she headed
packing clothes?
What?
Where are you headed?
To the hospital
For what?
Mom needs change of clothes
I'll give it and come
Hey you
There can only be one person
So your brothers are
rotating and sleeping outside
What are you gonna do there?
Then brothers will
need change of clothes
For that we have Pennycuick
Why do you have to
pointlessly roam around?
Be home
I'll send this around
- No sis...
Let me see her once and come
You said you want to
check horoscope for our oldie
Take Suruli along
Huh?
Morning you right?
Aah, yeah yes
Said she wanna go,
and see her blinking
You come Suruli
- You go along
Nothing will happen
What's the hurry for that?
- It's nearby only
To just check the horoscopes
If the Oldie is sick
Shouldn't we check the horoscope
and know what's the issue
Hey white ball, Come here
What?
Here, Give that to me
First take her and come
Hey, this is gift-fund note
Whatever
Go away
She found out
Kaadupatti, Oorani stop get down
Get luggage pass for banana tar
Only stupids will take
luggage for banana tar
Yay, our darling
♪ My muse ♪
♪ Hey dear, my muse ♪
Mm-hmm
♪ Perched atop my guitar strings ♪
♪ Would have snapped the string ♪
Isn't it so?
Yo, Pennycuick
You are insulting me in front
of the girl I'm going to marry
When you hopped only the
limestone in the plinth broke
Is guitar string
necessary for you?
Your willy hasn't
grown properly yet
Before that instagram, reels
Do you how many
strings guitar even has?
Put one on his head
- Go away first
Roaming behind a girl
What are you staring for?
Go away
Him and his face
Why are you grinning for?
♪ Your aunt will hunt it down ♪
Go, stand on a barren
boulder and jump
Brother, here brother
Hand it dear
How is the Oldie?
She's well, she's well
Carefully take and pawn it
Okay dear
I'll take care of everything
And pay the amount
as soon as you can
Nobody had any
doubts here, right?
No one has any doubt,
I'll see to that
Even if a small speck
gets out, it's over dear
I'll reach and will inform you
- Call me when you reach
Don't forget brother
Keep two idlys for 2 idly
I was also like she'll die now,
I'll get the gold
She'll die then,
And waited for four years
But
When she's just about to die
My Brothers-in-law would
save the Oldie it seems
They have that much
fond of their mother?
For them?
Menace, they'll keep a quarter-kilo
meat for four days and eat
Such stingy fellows
They have no love
But something feels wrong
I just don't know, what
If I come to know that
Hello,
Yeah, Nehru speaking
Dude
What? Is his name truly Nehru?
I also have that doubt
Wait I'll ask
Can you do a thing?
Can I talk to you
in the evening?
I'm little busies
Yeah, Thank you
Good day
Hey dude
Is your name Nehru for real?
Not just Nehru, dude
Sawaharlal Nehru
Jawaharlal Nehru huh?
Why did they name you that?
Why means
My father fought
with Netaji, dude
Hey man,
What was the issue between
your father and Netaji?
Hey
He fought along with Netaji
Who are you?
I will tell, listen
Who's this guy, keeps nagging
Hello
Hey
I'm Rajiv Gandhi speaking
Who? My son?
Rajiv Gandhi son huh?
What a surprise, you are
talking with your father suddenly?
What's the matter?
These aunties
Slyly is giving their
jewels to Pennycuick
Where is he now?
Hi friends
Today we've come to
Karumaathur Kanagu Mess
Mam, What did you eat?
My husband will kill me
What if your husband watch?
Freeloader
Go away
The Bull is subdued
Bull? I thought it's goat meat
That much craving
your tongue has?
One lakhs fifty six
Hold this
Mega feast
I ate less only
Why?
I'll slit your throat
What's happening?
Tell me you idiot
Just last week,
She purchased a total of one
hundred and sixty sovereigns.
How many sovereigns?
160 sovereigns
Why is one side jerking?
How cunningly
The gold that must
belong to my wife
You planned to steal, huh?
Mm-hmm
What you are going to do is?
Don't show to them
that I know this matter
Like always be a help for them
Whatever happens there,
without missing a speck
You must ring me
After I get the gold,
I'll take care of the rest
Today, your food
expense is on me
Here
Hey, the matter that
I know all this now
Ever reaches my in-laws ears
I'll chop off all the 21
fingers from your body
Vikram
(means sell in slang)
(To sell)
Hey
Already we are going
through rough patch
and selling everything
What more could we sell to play this song
How many other
Kamal Haasan songs are there
Ask him to change
Hey he came
Sister, I'll call back later
Come come, come running
Come running
Hey, Cuick came
See, how slowly he's coming
Why this much time?
It got delayed in the pawn shop
I thought, you ran away
somewhere with the money
You will think
Sister-in-law gave you clothes
The bundle is opened
Selvam, Check whether
the money is accurate
Brother, doctor came
Doctor
How is our mother?
Mother?
Which mother?
Patient name?
Pavunuthaayi's sons
Oh Pavunuthaayi?
Yes sir
She is in critical condition
Is that so?
We can't see any improvements
in her current status
Very nice sir
But we can not say
anything for sure now
There are talking and going
It is your decision to
continue the treatment or not
However, it's a must
to educate Kamal Haasan
I can't understand a single
word this doctor spoke
Because we are illiterate
Even though we have
ears we count as a deaf
What you say?
Hey
What did the Hindi-doctor say?
There is no issue
She's safe, he said
Yeah?
KARUPPAN saved us brother
- Is that so?
Oh Goddess
SIVA SIVA
How much are
these two hills man?
We might have to ask
the government that
Huh
Yo, with this small potion only
you were calling a Nagar?
Uh, okay
Talk this completely for me
How you have that much money?
Huh
Finish the deal, go
I'm trying to read
at least one bill
I can't understand a thing
The vitals are down
What are you observing?
Hey dude, Why do you look dull?
Hey Dude, What I...
Dude, Mom will
make it, they've said
You be strong
Because of you only we
came to know about this
Let all this get well
With 10 sovereigns, I'll give half
a sovereign extra from my share
You do your marriage well
Okay, but...
We'll play music in
Uppiliyan set for the wedding
I'll myself weave the wedding
garland for the bride and groom dude
Okay, leave that
I'll tie it in your height
Dude, you'll do all that
Hey Selvam
Something happened to mom, come - Listen to what I...
The thing is...
- Hey Moron
What are you talking
with him? Come here
Come here
Hey, what happened brother?
Hey, what happened?
Sir, please come this side
- They are telling something
They'll yell us sir -
What happened brother?
I don't know they are
not saying anything
Can't understand anything
Nurse, bring the CPR
Sir, please listen to us
What brother?
Hey, what the hell happened?
I'm so afraid man
- Doctor is coming
Keep the vitals stable
And monitor the oxygen level
- Sir our mother
What man?
Understand?
Go
What?
What is your name?
Selvam sir
Selvam, I already
told you right?
She's still in crucial state
We have continued the treatment
Informing her
condition to you, right?
Now why you are making fuzz?
It's about to get over
There is no problem right?
She'll talk right?
Talk...?
Are they insane?
What are they talking?
Tell them
I'll explain sir
Sir,
- Doctor sir
- Hey you
We've been saying it hard
to save her from morning
Just a while ago, when asked
if we can continue the treatment
You nodded yes, like
you understood everything
Now you are asking, if she'll talk
It's going to be over
Oh my
Hey
What's this girl saying?
She's saying it's
going to be over
He said that with a griming face
and with so much assurance
So I thought, he was
saying she'll make it
You thought?
Yes, I thought brother
YOU
- Brother, brother
You traitor
Don't beat him
All our money went in vain
I won't leave you without killing
Go away
Hey leave, leave
Go, go aside
Did I alone wish mom should die?
He said that with a smiling face
Seeing that everybody
would think that only
Why would they say
'she's about to die' gleefully?
So, you yourself will
make something up?
Hey, leave me, leave
- Brother
Hold him, you hold him
Hey Selvam, he might
kill you, run away
Let me die
Go
Everything is in shambles
Will we get back
the money we lost
Sir?
You can't understand right?
No sir
Then why did you talk
in English with them?
If someone dark-skinned calls
you sir, you'll get all prideful
You'll use all your
English efficiency
Without knowing whether the one
in front understands what you speak
and talking in the
language you know is talent?
it's a mental illness
Now, speak your English with me
If I speak fluent in English,
will you even understand?
To the attenders
Without being rude
I asked you to talk with a smile
Did I ask you to tell 'Your
mom will die' grinningly?
Okay, Why didn't you
attend that patient?
No sir, If we tell something
They're telling
something different
Ohhh
Have you attended
merely 50 patients?
Within that this much weary?
Call the attenders in
Yes sir
Come sir
Come, come in
Sit down sir
It's okay sir
It's okay, sit
Look sir
For Pavunuthaayi Ma,
The nerve from
the right side brain
Behind her neck
A block is formed
So in that area
Blood flow is clogged
If heavy objects were lifted for
many years this might happen
Because of that
She's affected from Hemiplegia
In the treatment
we give, if the block
with tablets and medicine
can be cured or not
is just a try
Even if we do our part right
Her body condition
Must cooperate
Without understanding this
if you beat one another
What's the use?
This is the patient's condition
If you want to continue the
treatment further, you can
If not
You can discharge
anytime and take her
The thing is, Doctor
Listen Mr. Uppiliyan
Regarding the treatment
You can ask all your
doubts whenever you want
You have rights in the law
Not that doctor
It's hard to save our mother
We understand that
With your high-end
medicine and tablets
Mm-hmm
By injection and all
Continuously
By injecting her
Mm-hmm
What I'm tryna say is
You listen to me carefully
For just five minutes
Can you make our Mom talk?
Your hospital will
get good Reputation
What do you saying?
Hey, Don't talk like a fool
Doctor explained
this only all this time
Keep quiet
Doctor
Say
All these are
Pictures of our mom's brain
Mm-hmm
In this, is there
A chance to see any location?
Discharge her
You mustn't take that, keep
Okay, That Suriyakala?
What?
Today the groom is coming
Brother, talk her for me
He's calculating, airhead
Brother wait, I'll call you back
Hey, enough of you
doing our expenses
Here on, we will do it
Why did you break
the calculator now?
Broke the calculator?
I'll break your face
Brother, He's often
raising his hands
He's not even letting me look
at the bill, smash him better
Go go away
- Smash him
Don't raise your hands Go away
Hey Selvam go
Did you spend any money?
Go, We've spent
It's been just five days
We've spent lakhs and lakhs
It's gone, everything is gone
Sir, what are you doing sir
It's getting late sir
- They are coming to beat me
They broke my calculator too
Can't change the tube for now
That doctor said it
grinningly, what will I do for it
Repair the puncture, we'll see
I'll see to it
Sir time is running
What's gonna happen in 10 minutes
- Why are you doing like this?
You come sir
Is this even fair for you?
- Be patient, we can go
Sir you call him sir
- You tell him sir
You are seeing right?
- He's not standing simply
Call him
Or you get in the vehicle
- Sir
Brother, brother
- Don't play with us sir
They are calling you
Even god can't tolerate it
Brother they are calling
you only, go brother
Why are you doing like this
- Wait, it's almost over
Yo, they are calling you only
For an emergency
You are standing without a care
First go and see what's it
Please, I beg, ask him to come sir
Do you know the value of life
Here, we sell everything we have
to save a life, and struggle a lot
You are standing here,
chilling with a cigarette
Go, first go and ask what they need
Do you have anything important to do?
Why?
Then go and do your
work, we know to handle it
Do my work, here I will
First get in the vehicle
The whole family is begging
and you couldn't care
I'll take a picture of your
vehicle and send to the police
Sir, wait sir, I myself will go
Without knowing anything,
why would you sir?
Check what's up
Check there, why are you seeing me?
What's this brother?
Someone came in and is creating an issue
What to do now brother?
We tried our best
Do it
Brother, check what is up
You are speaking in a phone
Sir what is this sir?
How much time we are waiting sir?
Her life is hanging by a thread,
and you are watching it
They are sorrowful
Do something brother
Brother
She's gasping
Do something brother
Brother
What happened sir?
- Madam
Case declared
Oh my Lord
Kaveri, don't panic
It's over within the auspicious time
Sir
Get down sir
Get up, go out sir
Go sir
Aunty
What?
Is this your first time
witnessing a soul depart?
Her body only doesn't
have any movements, but
From their children asking to kill them
Till I stop her breath
She will know everything
If the care taker says,
"I've spent enough in the hospital"
With ventilation support for them
They'll arrange an ambulance for them
To depart in the place they've lived
They'll ask us to cut it outside their home
If asked why
They'll say they are ending their suffering
Him, saying auspicious time will slip away
Asked to cut in the middle of the road
A being that lived for 60, 70 years
He killed like a dog,
in the middle of the road
and he is happy that he killed
during the auspicious time
In the whole wide world
No parents
with money as a reason
Will ask to kill their children, sir
But how many children
are not saying these
words to their parents?
All this sin
Will get on their grandsons
and granddaughters head
and affect the kids who did no sins
On their way
A small hope that at least
one person would make it
That's why, usually, like this
I do something like
puncture works, wantedly
Doctor
Her vitals are getting stable
Pavunuthaayi
Can you see me?
For the last 26 minutes
Pavunuthaayi ma's body condition
Including pulse and heart beat
is constantly improving
This is a good sign
Okay? Let's see
Okay
Sir
We don't have it in us anymore
We'll take our mom
home and take care of her
Are you kidding?
For three day and night we've
struggled to make her well
What does it mean if you
want to take her home?
What did you do, when
we said she can't be saved?
How much did you guys fought?
Now can I fight with you?
Do as you please
Only if you know the value of life
Sir
Why did he come here?
Go away
Yo
For the next two hours
If the body functions were normal like this
Tomorrow morning we can do a surgery
we can try to remove the block
The soul that almost left is returning back
It will happen only for one in crore
For some reason only
It is yearning to come back
The situation I told you
in the morning is changed
I see a chance to save her
It is a life, man
Sir
The doctor also said the same earlier
We can't do this anymore
We'll take our mother home
We can't discharge her like you say
I'll keep her in observation
for two hours and will only send
You do whatever you can
You pay the money or not
Sister, continue the ventilation
Sir, sir
Hey, who is he say, he won't discharge
You come
Let's discharge and take her home
He will say all this and
will go chill in his AC room
Who's gonna pay the bills
You come
Sister
- Yes
Continue the ventilation for Pavunuthaayi
Haan okay
Sir
Yeah, tell
Sir told about an operation right?
Yes
How much will the expense be?
Around 3.5 to 4 lakhs
Oh
Okay sir
Okay
You gave 4 lakhs advance
And want to seal the deal for forty lakhs
On the day of registration
You have to settle the
full amount in ready cash
Here the cash is ready
Okay
What penguin?
What's the oldie saying?
They are going to
discharge the oldie it seems
What
With who's permission
are they going to discharge?
Who do you want them to ask?
They are pity, they've
borrowed so much money
and spent everything
Then what will they do then?
My foot
Ask them to take care
of their mother properly
Scoundrels
But dude
That's not gold anymore
It's treasure henceforth
What?
Treasure?
Hey, That's my gold
I don't know who will lay
hands on it after 100 or 200 years
He's the lucky guy
The thing is...
They are saying if we
have a little more money,
they say we can save her
160 sovereigns man
We can buy half the land in our village
The gold rate is also
raising obnoxiously high
Now, how much do we have to pay?
How much?
Four lakhs
You are asking like you're
gonna count and bring
Hey dude
Hey, give the money
- Hello
Huh?
- Give it
What man?
- Give that, scoundrel
Hello
- Hey that's my bag man
Hey
Don't keep all the old things in your mind
I won't forget that alone
What?
Listen
To buy the land
I pawned my wife's jewelery
and this is the money
I got after rotation
There is 4 lakhs in this
See here
Penny, somehow we have to save the Oldie
What am I gonna do, doctor has to
Also them
Okay here hold this
Don't give this as I gave
Give, as if you are giving it
What? me?
You itself said
Okay?
- Yeah
Okay this butter milk
It's alright, I'll give
- This is my money right?
Penny go, Finish this well and good
It's my money right?
Go
- Hey lady.
Get it from him
Finish it well
Okay
I'll pay the cash now
Save the Oldie somehow
Will also save your gold
How much sister?
Fifty rupees
Fifty?
Yes
How many butter milk did he drink?
Five
Five?
- Yes
Chow hound
Give me half a cup
Unwanted expense
See how much it have come up
Oh my
- What could have we done?
We can't anymore
Let's pay the rest and take Oldie home
Brother
We've done this far
If we do this operation too
I feel that'd be good
Hey
Already
We have lakhs and lakhs
of debt over our heads
Again, if you ask in lakhs
Where can we go?
Do a thing, insert your
hands directly in my stomach
And pull out my intestines and everything
Anyway we are gonna get 30 lakhs each
What if we get into debt for 3 lakhs
However you see, we
lose from our profit only
If we leave it like this,
we lose from our capital
Hey
Stop with your shitty advices
All the issue is because of you only
If we had known that we can't save her
We could have not paid the second payment
You did all this,
and you're talking like an achiever
Tomorrow if something similar happens to us
Though our children had a chance to save us
and being stingy of money,
and they decides not to
How will we feel?
Oh Lord, you don't have to spend at all
High or low, I'll do something
And will save the oldie
You guys leave this
But one thing
Tomorrow when the oldie become well
and while splitting the gold
The share depends on
how much each have spent
I'll not let her give a single pound extra
I'll create big trouble
See, what he is talking
We all have to share and only spend
What does it mean if you alone spend?
Then give
Huh? where do I have money?
For my daughter Shruthihaasan's wedding
I have a gold chit scheme in
Usulampatti Kondavazhathan Govindhan
I'll give fifty thousand from that
What else do I have?
What are you talking?
What? What is he talking?
You sell your auto and give
Oh?
All I have is one auto
I'll be on the roads if I sell that
I'll pawn it and give 50k
Say that
Why did you break the calculator?
You fifty thousand
Myself one lakh
Total two lakhs
However we still would need two lakhs more
See this,
He's saying to sell my auto
Who will we ask?
Dudes
Oh my
Hey
How do you have this much?
How?
Yo
I'm also getting 10 sovereign share right
I must also do my part right
When the Oldie wakes up
and we get the gold, I'll get married
Give this back as my wedding gift
Hey penny
Even after seeing us all, you
still wish to get married?
Dude
You are peaceful without a wife
What will you do after getting married?
What will he do?
Without unlocking the door
10 months later, he'll come out with a baby
Hey Uppili
Keep quiet brother
Dude you say
Why are you so desperate to get married?
What dude
You asked like this
After roaming throughout the town
When I return home
Without me, myself opening the door
From the inside,
My lady should open the door for me
As "Family head"
With my name
I need a ration card
We have to take a photo as a couple
Frame it
And hang that in our home
As a house without a lady
I have never received an invitation
I also want to get invitations, Uppili
And
for that function
I want to go along with my wife
Eat well there
give monetary gift
and want to listen my
name in the cone-speaker
At night
I'll be somewhere talking to people
'Hey' 'What happened',
'Why aren't you home yet?'
'How much time?'
Everybody will get calls from their wives
Likewise
From my wife I also wants to get a call
Apart from all this, dudes
We'll lay our child in the center
both of us
one after another must patter
And look into each other
And drift off to sleep
For that only I'm running like a dog
I'm putting everything I have in me
If I had my mom and dad
this would have happened
I would have become an a family man
How will that...
Happen
Dude
Without dealing the issue in hand
I'm talking about mine
Hey, pay the amount
But one thing
Your mom
Will come back, I have
a feeling in my heart
If she comes back,
all of us will be well
Tomorrow at 10 am,
operation for Pavunuthaayi
Hey priest
You'll be blessed
Come and get this soon
What's with her,
she's doing the fire pot ritual
Now only you'll offer
camphor, come soon
Everyone is acting weird
Brother, please give for the alms
What he's giving one rupee
Go aside, disrupting early in the morning
Shitface, you're stealing grapes
Pray for my mother-in-law's good health
I came for another prayer
♪ Will it get caught in my hand? ♪
Pray for my mother-in-law
Go
Lord Muruga, bless his
mother-in-law with good health
He's beating me Muruga
How much time will you take?
Shouldn't I have to tie
the garland and bring?
Hold this
How is it?
You weaved?
- Then
I only weaved
Promise me?
I bought it near Pandi Kovil
Then why are you lying?
♪ Yearning for porridge ♪
♪ You want the greens too ♪
♪ And desire the milk also ♪
What?
He's also AANDAVAR right?
You are staring
Prayer fast and come
Hey, don't shake your hands sister
What for you? You'd say
My hands are only burning
That wretched priest
I asked him to come and get that pot fast
He made my hands burn
Look, don't talk
I've ate half a Kg of dirt and
Am sitting in agony
The temple only looks clean
When I ate, it was
all sand and stones
What do you think happened to me?
To all the people I offer alms,
I had to beg
10 kilometers
I went by walk
I don't know what all we
had to do for this Oldie
It's all our timing
Suruli
Yeah, here I come sister
Come here for a bit
Listen to what they are talking
Sister, listen what they're talking
Morning I've to go to the function
So, only I came earlier
You go sister
I'll bring the other jacket before dawn
Ok dear
Ask her sister
Hey you, Suruli
Yeah
Tomorrow your mother has operation
You are not even as fazed as we are
Without a single drop of tear
You are sitting and stitching blouses
Hmm
Every time he beats me asking for the gold
You all said, he's a
man, and he'll be like that
You'd have to adjust
Only my mother said
Why must he have to take care of you?
You learn a skill, and
make a living out of it
And brought me here
My mother, to live comfortably
she brought me here,
Makes me work, tortures me,
that's what the villagers think
But in reality
Mother, even without anybody's support
How to stand alone with courage as a woman
She's preparing me
Today I have a skill in my hand
I'll settle my son, and
lead my life with respect
I have courage
If I cry now
You, "Can't you lead your life without me?"
"Is that how I raised you?"
She'll come and smack me with a broomstick
Do you know one thing
Until the day before my marriage
My mom without anybody knowing
Took me to school and accompanied back
Even the teacher asked
After engagement, when she
can't even attend the exam
Why are you bringing her to school?
For that my mom said
"If she learns a word or two extra,"
"If she learns to solve
few new math problems"
"It might help her some day."
My mom said
If only my sons leave
"I'll bring my daughters-in-law
to the school too"
That's why when you eat and sleep
She gets furious and
yells you to learn a skill
No one understood her except me
She also didn't expect that from anyone
She've gone through a lot
If she comes back, let her
If not let her go in peace
Hey, they said operation is today
And no one has called yet
Hey Abi you are getting a call
Oh my I think they called
- Oh God, she killed me
Check whether they are
calling from the hospital
Hello
Hey lady, from KARUPPU kovil,
It's Kangaroo Adigal speaking
Selvam is not picking up the call
Oil is about to get over
Someone send me the money
You shit, cut the call
Drunkard fellow
Drunkard fellow?
Villagers are praying for our granny to die
Our family members
are doing rituals for her to get well
Do you want her to die or get well?
What is this question?
Let her get well
Really?
Why?
If granny dies, you can watch TV happily
For just TV, should we wish her death?
How great a person she is?
Look at you and your head
Talking like a matured man
Will anyone beat the guy
they are going to marry?
Yeah yeah, I'm going to marry you only
Then who are you gonna marry?
Hey, the light went off, come here
Come man, the light went off
Sir, sir
Sir, is our mom well?
Doctor
Sir, Mam, Madam
Sister
What, you're leaving
without saying anything ?
Why is she leaving quietly?
- Madam
Hey listen ma,
- Madam is our mother well?
Doctor will tell you
- Tell us something
Mam, Sir, sir, sir
How's our mom?
- How's our mom?
Did she make it?
It is a medical miracle
What man?
- What happened Selvam?
What is he saying?
- Tell us
She died, he says
She died
Oh lord
- She died?
Hey,
- What doctor you are?
How will she die?
Hey, your mother is alright
Alright?
- What?
Did you see?
How sadly he is saying that she is alright
Likewise that day, he
said she'll die grinningly
Hey his face structure is like that only
Without knowing this
that share auto guy, bet me
Hey, leave that, forgive your brother
We're all crackheads
You godlike saved her
I bow to you with my hands
Thank you sir
KARUPPA you saved us
He saved our mother, Penny
Wait man
First, let's inform her that,
our mother is alright
Hello
Hey, what happened?
Tell what happened, sister
I'm panicking here
She's .....
What?
She's alright
Maa
Granny is alright
Three days later
Vijaya
Come on
Uncle Chellandi from Madurai passed away
When?
- When?
Just now I got the call
They are taking away the
body, 2.00 in the afternoon
We ought to go, brother
How can we go?
Hey dude
Today only they are
shifting our mom to the ward
What to do?
- What's this?
Okay do one thing
- I don't know
On behalf of us, you
get a garland and give
Okay
They are in the hospital
Tell them, we couldn't come
For expense
Give him thousand for expenses
Thousand?
Isn't 100 enough for the garland?
I'll inform them
He's a good man
- That's why he died
Is Pavunuthaayi attenders here?
Yeah yeah, us
- Come come quick
Hey come man
- Go fast
Hey
Would she've forgotten everything?
I don't know
Wait wait I'll talk
Mom
Can you recognise us?
Mom...
(inaudible gibberish)
W... What mom?
From which shop did you get this from?
Tastes like tangy syrup
You doofus
She speaks
Mom spoke
Our mom spoke
(upbeat music)
Keep crying, but move a bit aside
It's alright, alright
Hey, get away
- You go aside
Hey come here
I'll sit in a corner
I'll kill you, come here
Dude
Sit
When did you come?
Now, is his death important?
Instead of knowing what the Oldie is saying
Why did you come here?
Be patient for a while
Oldie is shifted to normal ward
At this moment they will be asking her
♪ What are you going to say? ♪
Brother
- Yeah
Ask her
Yeah,
- Ask man
ASK MAN
Yeah, mom I forgot to ask
When you got bedridden
You were signaling some
things with your hands
What was that, mom?
Me?
What did I say?
No, no Mom , you only said
Like this
Then like this
Then you said like this
Here, this person
When he came to our home,
you said something to him
What did I say?
Yes Mom, you said
Recall it better, mom
Hey
Yeah
Tell us, tell
What's it?
You remembered?
Hey, do you know how
much money I have spent?
What did I tell you?
- Why are you yelling in funeral home?
Didn't I tell you to see
what's happening there?
Here, you are eating
like a chow hound right?
See they are fighting cause of you
Rather than tussling with you,
I will at least settle the dispute
Hey
If a death happens that's it
Always fighting
Tell us mom
When they brought me down
In the terrace, in my room
Without tuning off the fan
They brought me down
Someone turn the third switch off
Current bill will cost a hefty amount
I got tired of saying that
Did you turn it off
(Conch shell blaring)
Hey move aside
I said move aside
These many people are
beating up one person
Mom, don't play with us
When you were sick
Goldsmith, Gold Kumar came
and said you ordered
160 sovereigns with him
Yeah
Please tell us where it is mom
Gold Kumar?
Yeah
Who is that doofus?
My name is Gold Kumar
In Madurai Gold Bazaar, 37 th store is mine
Yes
This Old man had a gold chit, in our store
Weekly she'll buy at least a gram
Just last week
He bought 160 sovereigns totally
Here, they saved him
Brother
Gold Kumar brother
What Kumar?
Gold Kumar
Gold Kumar eh?
Hey, he's Funeral freak
What freak?
Funeral freak, man
Since his gold
shop had a theft incident
Like this
He dresses in crisp Veshti-shirt
and roams village to village
On his way he picks up visiting
cards and diaries from the road
He'll start
While roaming if he sees a funeral house
He himself will go weep and come
He won't go and speak a word to anybody
If you go and ask,
"Who are you?, What do you need?"
Then only he'll speak
I'm a gold seller
I've given a lot of gold to the dead person
He'll read a bill which
he sold for someone else
He might've given to
some other person right?
He'll read that and go.
- Yes he read
Yeah right?
He'll read that and show
Hey in Madurai, due to him millions of
many families have had disputes
Hey, What is he saying?
He said the same to
me regarding our Oldie
Gold eh?
You
One sixty
How will I know that he's a funeral freak?
My money
- Dude
Dude
- My money
It's all gone
Another death might happen, lift him
Then what you told really was
The fan is spinning
Turn off the third switch
Current bill money will go waste?
Yes
Yes?
Then, hadn't you turned that off yet?
Yeah, that's what is important now
If I tie you up in the
fan and keep it number 4
You'll spin along and die here itself
What?
Then, what did you do
with all the interest money?
Each Sunday in Madurai bus
Where the hell did you go?
You conduct the festival or not
You lift the Karagam or not
For us dancing and singing event is a must
Yeah
♪ Hey dream girl ♪
♪ What's in my eyes? ♪
♪ Your betel teeth smile ♪
♪ The words you say, makes my heart sway ♪
♪ Is it the dimpled smile? ♪
He is my brother
♪ The fire of Kolli hills? ♪
♪ She is coming alone ♪
Granny, how was the movie?
- It is great
It's epic
Go and watch it
Keep your hand on your head,
then only you'll become a trend
Doofus
♪ Emerges as the light ♪
Granny, this is your last shot
♪ In my heart ♪
♪ A drop ♪
♪ Drenches ♪
♪ The soul ♪
She's saying she roamed around
What Selvam?
You are very happy
We saved your mother
For your mother, next 20
years death will not come near
I'll guarantee
Hey you
Shall we go?
If my wife knows she'll kill me
♪ From the hills of Pandi,
From Malayalam lands ♪
♪ From Kasi to Rameswaram,
The ascetic who rules by restraint ♪
♪ Aandiyappa. ♪
♪ Pechiyamma, the
sister of Kazhuvanadhan ♪
♪ Peikamman lives are
contained within you. ♪
♪ The sacred Aadi Friday has bloomed ♪
♪ The noon-day worship awaits ♪
♪ Come forth and accept ♪
♪ Come forth, step outside,
Come out… come out… come out… ♪
♪ Leaving the sanctum, the god steps outside ♪
♪ This is the day judgment is delivered. ♪
♪ When righteousness draws its line ♪
♪ No force can stay contained. ♪
Where is the gold?
She told to turn off the fan, it seems
Pavunuthaayi is coming to the village
♪ For every blow struck for hire, for the gathered mob ♪
♪ This is the hour when wages are paid. ♪
♪ For the crowd that sinned and lived in sin, ♪
♪ This is the hour, the price is finally collected ♪
♪ Leaving the sanctum, the god steps outside ♪
♪ This is the day judgment is delivered ♪
♪ The one who sinned, the god Himself will seize ♪
Dei where is the interest money?
♪ The law, the sacred code, exists right here ♪
♪ Yet justice is not always found ♪
♪ Even the law has its purpose ♪
♪ Today, the truth speaks. Truly ♪
♪ Speaks boldly, declaring what is right ♪
♪ The righteous god will rise ♪
♪ Through every street of the town ♪
♪ When Virumandi comes out ♪
♪ Who dares to come forward to stop it? ♪
♪ Leaving the sanctum, the god steps outside ♪
♪ This is the day judgment is delivered ♪
♪ When righteousness draws its line ♪
♪ No force can stay contained ♪
♪ Who dares to come forward to stop it? ♪
Are you well, Pavunuthaayi?
♪ For every blow struck for hire, for the gathered mob ♪
♪ This is the hour when wages are paid ♪
♪ For the crowd that sinned and lived in sin ♪
♪ This is the hour, the price is finally collected ♪
♪ Leaving the sanctum, the god steps outside ♪
♪ This is the day judgment is delivered ♪
See how they're welcoming her with aarathi?
Did you see?
See here standing here,
we have to blame them
Believing them we gave all our jewels
Ma, Can you hear me?
You wish to tell something it seems
Tell that
It's in three places
Or
It has three shares
All of it are cash or gold
Or something of high value
She's saying 'Go take that'
Hey
All the females alone come up
Is she calling us?
Yes she's calling us
I don't know what for?
Come let's go and ask what
Surprisingly she's calling us up
(intense music)
(upbeat music)
What is she doing?
I don't know
Totally 300 sovereigns
For my sons
How I leave the house and land
With a 10 year old son
My daughter should stand alone
Without expecting anyone
To lead her life, I saved all these
When I came here after marriage
The only mother side
wedding gift I bought was
This Pallanguzhi
This is not just a game
It's a secret to tell a
women how to lead her life
The money we get in
our hands after spending
For the future if we save at least some
One day if something out
of our expectation happen
And we are left to live with empty hands
All these days the life she lead saving
Without expecting others
In her next chance
she'll get that as saving
(coughs)
For a human to live happily,
If he needs money or not I don't know
But for him to live respectfully
he for sure needs money
"Life is to live"
"Money is not that important"
If someone says
that means he has enough money
to not worry about his next meal,
Seeing that if you live like a splurge
Like this only, does our
Mother-in-law have gold
Won't our mother and father give us assets
You will roam around expecting others hands
To work for a living only
a woman needs freedom
If you get that alone
The rest of freedom, no one has to give you
If you change like that
The freedom I understood at 60
The freedom my daughter has at 30
The freedom that my
granddaughter will get at 18
In future her daughter
will get when is born itself
Among the Old people in this village
I wouldn't say I only toiled very hard
But
A little bit
I lived smarter
That's why
The only house in the entire
village with a woman's name
Is this
Here
The secret that I didn't even tell my sons
You know why I'm telling you
To create, To protect, and to destroy
People who told us to worship men
For money and education they
only pointed a women to worship
To make 6 into 100
We can only multiply,
even men know that
Yeah
Even if it's for gold
For me each of you did rituals
You changed my clothes
And did everything my
daughter was supposed to do
Saved and made me
come back to my home again
And since my sons got into debt cause of me
Now
this
I'll split into four equal shares
It is not enough just having a loud
mouth saying 'I'm a women'
You have to live and show
Hey, come, come and take
(upbeat music)
For you, my Murugan
whispered a way in my ears
(bell rings)
Hey
Before these eight-village-priest
We will divorce you and her
Your son will grow with her only
Dear, split that hay,
remove and give your nuptial chain
Here, twist and throw it off
Suruli
Hereafter, I'll be well
Forgive me please
- You will well
Hey, please don't do it
Can't we see someone
who will or not be well
Here take this and go
Can't keep a woman,
shamelessly you're talking
Aunty, please tell her
Hereafter I'll behave well aunty
Not just day
Even woman won't return if she goes
You be
Hey Suruli
Please for give my
Hey
Having a son this house's size,
what are you asking me to do?
If he keeps eating and grew house's size
Why would you not get remarried?
He's a son for him too
Will he stay without getting married again?
Yeah?
Leave this topic with this
Don't continue this
Hey tubby, come here
Oh no
Can you mom get married again?
Who's the groom?
(laughs)
(traditional music)
Pennycuick Izhzham
Groom : K.Pennycuick
Bride : Suru'zh'i
Youngest, bring the garland
Hey
Which shop did you buy?
Bought in shop?
I weave it, man
You weaved?
Give it
It's not believable
Give that first
It took two days to tie
for Pennycuick's height
Dude exchange the garlands
Exchange the garland
My Goddess
Here
You give
Maa,
- It's okay
Here Penny tie
(vehicle engine whirrs)
♪ The stage set forth by The God ♪
Hey
Chin up, and take the nuptial chain
♪ The stage set forth by The God ♪
♪ Everyone will find their half ♪
♪ Who is for each of us ♪
♪ God has it written long back ♪
♪ The stage set forth by The God ♪
♪ Everyone will find their half ♪
(upbeat music)