Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
[All Characters, Organizations, Events,
And Places Shown Are Entirely Fictional]
[Filming Was Conducted In Safe
Environments With Guardians For Child Actors]
[Q. I Know This Is Hard,
But Can You Describe What Happened?
It was just like any other day.
My mom was yelling at me
to bring her more alcohol.
She hit me a few times, so I got scared
and ran into the bathroom.
Dad,
Can't you stop her when she's hitting me?
You just stand there and watch,
so she gets drunk and takes it out on me.
Pathetic.
[Q. Then Do You Remember
What Your Father Was Doing?
Your mom...
How am I supposed to stop her
when she's drunk and raising hell?
She refuses to grant me a divorce
and just acts like a total psycho.
It hurts.
At first, he tried to stop her.
But eventually, I think
he just went to sleep.
So long, wife.
You didn't throw her, did you?
Your mother was drunk
and fell down the stairs.
Be honest. You were sick of her too,
weren't you?
I'll get you a new mom.
And she's loaded.
It's nothing compared to this dump.
From now on, you do exactly as I say.
Or else I'll throw you down there too.
Ah Jin.
Please... call 911.
[Name: Baek Ah Jin, Actress]
[Has Antisocial Personality Disorder
Which Affects 4% Of The Population]
[She Is A Sociopath]
[She Views Others As Tools To Be
Manipulated For Her Own Personal Gain]
[She Deliberately Targeted Men
Who Could Be of Use To Her]
[While She Has Never Directly Committed Murder,]
[She's Responsible For The Deaths
Of Two People - Baek, Heo]
[She Has A Murder Plot
That Has Yet To Be Carried Out]
[She Is The Actress, Baek Ah Jin]
[Episode 1: Her X's]
[July 2016]
The homeroom teacher's having a party.
Let's go watch!
What are you waiting for? Let's go!
- Hey, let's go get some cake.
- Cake?
- Hey, come on, let's go!
- Yeah, hurry up!
- Bring some for me!
- Me too!
Me too!
I got it right up to here, right?
- ♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- ♪ Happy birthday, dear teacher... ♪
- Singwang High.
- Yes, this is Singwang High.
The poster was anonymous, so...
What the hell is this?
I said, what is this?
- Is this for real?
- Who is that?
- It's our homeroom teacher.
- What kind of behavior is this?
It's all over the school's website.
We're being flooded with complaint calls
from parents. It's a total mess.
So, just lie low until things die down,
and we'll contact you
once we've sorted things out.
[Principal's Office]
Are you okay, Ms. Kwak?
Did you like my gift?
Just like you always taught us,
I'm just a poor girl with no guardians,
let alone parents,
so I couldn't get you
anything extravagant.
But I did prepare it with all my heart,
in my own way.
I really hope you liked it.
Happy birthday.
[Sim Sung Hee: Her X]
Ah Jin and I both got one question wrong,
so why am I ranked second?
The art test had a one-point difference.
Your ranks are different,
but you both got the top grade,
so it's not a big deal.
The art practical?
[One Month Earlier]
What's that?
That's Baek Ah Jin...
and who is that with her?
The art teacher?
You're still here?
I left my umbrella in the classroom.
I don't think there was
anything left in there.
Then are you saying
someone took my umbrella?
Yes.
Move. I'll go look for myself.
Come on.
I'll walk you home before it gets late.
Okay.
Leave it to the model student.
Studying even with all this noise.
So, who were you with in the classroom?
It was the art teacher from study hall
last night, wasn't it?
You're pretty nosy, aren't you?
And pretty clueless, too.
In the movies, the nosy ones
are always the first to die.
But you're lucky.
At least in the real world,
you don't get killed for being nosy.
In that moment, a chill ran down my spine.
That look on Baek Ah Jin's face...
her tone...
her true colors, which vanished in a flash.
And I was the only one who saw it.
Congrats to Ah Jin, our top student,
and Joon Seo, who won the writing contest.
Joon Seo and Sung Hee, for the debate,
you two need to step it up.
I'd like to give my place
in the debate to Baek Ah Jin.
All of a sudden?
Why?
I can use my award for early admission
as a Student with Literary Talent.
Really?
Have you spoken to Ah Jin about this?
Yes. I'd really like to participate if I can.
All right, I'll check your eligibility
and let you know.
Good luck with your next classes!
- Thank you.
[2016 President's Cup Debate Participants]
[Sim Sung Hee, Yoon Joon Seo...]
Okay, the topic for the debate is
the pros and cons of the death penalty.
Part 1 is an open presentation.
For Part 2, one person will represent us
to argue for or against it with others.
You guys only need to prepare for Part 1.
Yu Bin, you and Ah Jin
can do the research.
And Ga Yeong,
you prepare the presentation.
I'll write the script.
It's just easier
if the presenter writes it.
- Okay.
- Sounds good.
Is this how you always make decisions?
Ah Jin, we're all okay with it.
This is how we did
the Idea Pitching Competition, too.
Sung Hee's a great leader,
so we have a better chance of winning.
No, it's okay, guys.
I guess I was being too presumptuous.
Ah Jin,
then how would you like to do it?
I heard that teamwork is a big part
of the score.
In that case, to get a good score,
wouldn't it be better if we also split Part 2?
Ah Jin has a point.
All right, then let's each think about
how to split the work,
and decide next time we meet. How's that?
Sure.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
- See you guys later.
- Bye!
Bye.
- Good job today.
- Damn it, I'm so pissed.
Are you on your period? Why the hysterics?
She waltzes in, preaching about teamwork.
That crazy bitch.
Baek Ah Jin? The one who
knocked you out of first place?
Mom.
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
As the parent rep, do you know how much
I donate to your school every month?
You think I can't handle this?
Can you find out what private tutoring
Baek Ah Jin is getting?
What are you talking about?
Teacher Kwak told me she's an orphan.
She can't even afford extra lessons.
Speaking of which, we spent
so much money on that woman.
Now that she's fired, the money's wasted.
And it wasn't just money, either.
She said she needed legal advice,
so your dad even helped her out.
Who on earth did she get caught
having an affair with?
Are you feeling sick?
I think you have a fever.
No, I'm fine.
Just get back to it.
It's after 11. You should go home.
I'm more comfortable here than at home.
Hey, can I borrow your literature notes?
Sure, one second.
Here you go.
Joon Seo, about you dropping out
of the Debate Competition...
Did Baek Ah Jin ask you to do it, by any chance?
No, it just doesn't feel like
the right fit for me.
But we're president and vice president.
It would look good if we competed together.
Having Ah Jin take my place
will give us a better chance of winning.
No, Joon Seo, you're such a good writer.
You competing would be much more helpful.
Can't you just say you'll do it?
Let's talk about this later.
Did Sim Sung Hee give you this?
[Dear Joon Seo. Hi, it's Sung Hee.]
Did that come out of my bag?
I had absolutely no idea.
[You've probably noticed, but I like you...]
[I heard you're single,
so what do you think about me?]
Why the serious face? Just throw it out.
[Please think about it and text me back.
[I'll be waiting! Bye.]
You should at least write back to her.
I'll do it for you.
Hey, did you hear the rumor this morning?
- Yeah, about Baek Ah Jin?
- That she doesn't have a mom.
That rumor from earlier was about
Baek Ah Jin, right?
Yeah, it was.
Ah Jin.
Yesterday, Sung Hee was telling Yu Bin
that you live by yourself without any parents.
And she knows Yu Bin has a big mouth,
so by now, everyone in our class
and the whole sophomore year knows.
What are you going to do?
About the Debate Competition.
There's not much time left,
We've had complaints from parents that
a new member would disrupt the team.
So the principal has decided to stick with
the three original members.
Which parent is it that's objecting
to me joining the team?
This is my dad.
You've seen him on TV, right?
- Yeah, I have.
- See?
Yeah, totally.
And this is my mom.
- Wow, she's gorgeous.
- You look just like her.
- I'm so jealous, Sung Hee.
- Wow, great photo.
- Wow, her family's loaded.
- Really? Is it a good picture?
- I'm seriously so jealous.
- I know, right?
But...
Is it true you don't have parents?
Ah Jin!
I'm so sorry.
I heard you got removed from the debate club.
I guess Ga Yeong's
and Yu Bin's moms complained.
Do you like Yoon Joon Seo?
Did Joon Seo tell you?
Joon Seo asked me to give this to you.
I think he felt sorry to give it to you himself.
[Nobody likes you]
[You're An Annoying Try-hard]
[Stop This Attention Seeking]
Sung Hee.
The homeroom teacher is looking for you.
We've been notified by the debate organizers
that our school's been disqualified.
Apparently, someone tipped them off,
and the organizers don't want controversy.
I'm afraid we'll have to pull out
of this competition.
[President's Cup Debate Competition]
[Debate Competition Contestant Bribes Judge]
[A Singwang High Contestant's Parent]
[Approached A Judge To Secure An Award]
[And Allegedly Offered A Bribe]
[Requesting A Fact-Check On This]
[They've Also Been Replacing]
[And Unjustly Removing Members]
[I Demand The Organizers Act]
Considering the circumstances,
it had to be her!
Since she couldn't go,
she spread a rumor so none of us could go.
Damn it.
Don't worry, Mom.
You know me.
Of all the bitches who've messed with me,
not a single one has gotten away clean.
I'm curious what happens to the bitches
who mess with you.
You spread the rumor, didn't you?
That I'm an orphan.
Thanks a lot.
Thanks to you, school life's
about to get real interesting.
Don't welfare recipients
get free rice from the government?
And your tuition is free, too.
That rice you eat...
is paid for by my dad's taxes.
Thanks.
[Nobody likes you]
[Expressing Futility, Negative...]
You're an annoying...
[Expressing...]
Annoying...
Fuck, the handwriting's exactly the same.
Fuck.
[You checking the books?]
[Studying for a test]
[Okay]
[Where are you?]
Kim Byeong Jin from Class 5.
He's dodging the collection. What do I do?
Stick to the protocol.
[Dowonjang Chinese Restaurant]
Hey.
Don't get it twisted
and think you're someone special.
Okay?
Piss me off, and you'll be the only one
who regrets it.
Got it?
A nobody like you.
So you go to the same school as my Byeong Jin?
Yeah, Byeong Jin and I are practically...
like brothers.
Close enough to lend him...
even 250,000 won of my hard-earned money.
What are you talking about?
Byeong Jin borrowed money?
Don't believe me? Take a look.
The loan agreement.
He said a friend broke his headset, or whatever.
Anyway, with interest, it's 300,000 won total.
He was supposed to pay me back
5,000 won a day,
but that little punk Byeong Jin
paid me for ten days and then bailed.
You're a student. Focus on your studies.
How could you do this?
Listen, lady.
Are you going to pay me back or not?
Just answer me that.
Now, to discuss the meaning
of the Theory of Innate Goodness,
- There are four virtues...
- Joon Seo.
- Forget the money and just get rid of him.
- Please!
Which are Righteousness, Propriety, and Wisdom.
The concept is these virtues are inherent
in our nature as a complete moral system.
It's a mistake to interpret the Theory of
Innate Evil as "human nature is evil."
That since we're inherently evil,
we should just be evil our whole lives.
That is absolutely not the case.
The philosopher who proposed
the Theory of Innate Evil was
the great thinker, Xunzi.
Sorry I'm late.
I'm taking Ah Jin to the nurse's office.
- Whoa, are they dating?
- What was that about?
Quiet.
Fucking hell.
This weather is fucking crazy.
How many raindrops can fall in a single second?
Damn it, I just washed my uniform yesterday.
What the hell?
Don't tell me you two are ditching.
And what happened to you?
Did you take a shower or something?
I was in the rain,
but you're the one who's soaked.
I thought I told you not to act
like you know me at school.
Since you're here, just go to class quietly.
Who the fuck are you to tell me
what to do, you bastard?
And who's the one ditching class right now, huh?
We're not ditching.
We're going to the nurse's office.
Also, those AirPods...
You're not supposed to
let anyone see those, right?
[One Month Earlier]
Aren't these expensive?
For real? You're not going to snitch?
- Why not?
- I don't meddle in others' business.
I guess a model student like you
has nothing to gain by getting involved.
Is there anything you need?
Want something? I can swipe it for you.
I don't need any stuff,
but I do need a person.
A person?
It's a job that's perfect for you.
And it pays, so this works out.
[Bong Soo Hoon - 10,000 Won/Day For 7 Days]
[Late Fee: 10 Percent Per Day]
[Boss]
I'll be in the nurse's office,
then I'm leaving for the day.
I'll check the books tomorrow.
Well, look at you. Lost in thought?
What's this?
"Touch and you die."
Kim Jae Oh, what is this?
You little... you startled me.
Hey! Get back here!
Hey! Somebody grab him!
What? What's going on?
You're dead meat when I catch you!
What was that?
- What just happened?
- What was that?
What's this?
Collecting money? Why would he...
[I'll Check The Books Tomorrow!]
The books... Boss?
[Stick To The Protocol]
- What is all this?
- Sim Sung Hee?
Why would she do something like that to you?
Why do you think?
It's because she doesn't like me
hanging around with you.
Whatever her reason, this is too far.
We should tell our homeroom teacher.
Forget it. We're not kids.
She was already on my nerves
for spreading weird rumors anyway.
I'll take care of her my way.
You should probably lie down for now.
Besides, your hair is still wet.
You're going to catch a cold.
Joon Seo.
Honestly, I'm scared.
I'm scared of what she'll do next.
You'll help me, right?
- Hey, there's Ah Jin.
- Baek Ah Jin!
Baek Ah Jin! Good morning!
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm totally fine. Thanks.
Hey. You left early, so you missed it?
So get this, Kim Jae Oh has been
loan-sharking to other students,
and the ethics teacher totally caught him
with his ledger yesterday.
I hear the amount was insane.
You could hear our teacher yelling
from the hall yesterday.
Totally.
Really?
You're here.
I was gonna give you five more minutes,
and then I was out of here.
You've heard, right?
Hey, for what it's worth,
I didn't say a single word
about you, okay?
So I guess that makes us even-
Thank you.
I knew you'd do that for me.
Hang on. My ribs.
Did you get hit again?
I really don't get it.
Every time your father beats you,
I get so mad at how you act like an idiot.
Don't you ever get sick of it?
If it were me, I would've done
whatever it took to get out of there.
Instead of just sitting there
and taking it like an idiot.
I had no idea you were
so concerned about me.
No wonder.
The way you've been looking
at me felt so different.
You thought I was pathetic,
is that it?
I just let him hit me.
If he doesn't take it out on me,
he'll bother someone else.
Besides,
no matter how useless I am,
a son can't just beat his father, can he?
No. You can.
What's so wrong with putting yourself first?
Kim Jae Oh.
You're not useless.
At least not to me.
- They even have grilled beef patties.
- I was so hungry.
Can I have one more?
I'm starving. I'll take broken pieces.
That's plenty.
Thank you!
Hey, how'd you get four patties?
What can I say? I'm her favorite.
Right. Ah Jin, you're pitching in, right?
For our homeroom teacher's wedding gift.
Yeah, of course I am.
She's going to love it, right?
No. You shouldn't.
Hey, are you crazy?
- What the hell?
- Sim Sung Hee! Ah Jin, are you okay?
- Hey, you're soaked.
- It's okay. I'm just gonna go.
- Hey, Baek Ah Jin!
- Ah Jin!
So, you must be Kim Jae Oh's boss.
You've been exposed...
by me.
So you really are the one in charge.
The one pulling the strings,
making Kim Jae Oh collect money from kids.
Playing the model student in public
while secretly shaking down
kids for money.
If the teacher finds out the gift was
bought with money you extorted,
I'll bet she'd be just thrilled.
Wouldn't she?
Whatever will you do?
You're not going to want to show
your face at school anymore.
- Hey, get back here!
- Sung Hee.
Can we talk for a second?
So, why'd you pull me aside?
It's about the reply to your note.
I'm sure you've figured it out,
but Ah Jin was just messing around
when she wrote that.
I'll apologize for her.
I'm sorry.
Forget it.
Tell Baek Ah Jin to apologize herself.
I know you're mad, but...
I don't want you to get the wrong idea.
I like you.
What?
What did you just say?
You said you like me, right?
I'm saying I like you too.
So, are we going out now?
So, about that...
You know, I really hate it
when people cross the line.
I wouldn't want my girlfriend
to be that kind of person.
What are you talking about?
I've never done anything like that.
It's just that there seems to be bad blood
between you and Baek Ah Jin lately.
As you know, Baek Ah Jin and I go way back.
If you really like me,
then while we're dating,
I hope you'll leave Ah Jin alone.
No, it's not like that.
We're actually really close.
Don't worry. I'm not like that.
Really?
- Yeah.
- Good. I'm glad to hear that.
Any plans for the weekend?
Wanna go see a movie?
Sure, what should we see?
Whatever you want to watch.
What I want to watch?
I'm good with anything.
It's me.
Who is this?
Who do you think it is?
Did you forget my voice already?
Kim Jae Oh?
I got a second-hand phone.
Call this number from now on.
That's all I called for. I'm hanging up.
Wait.
Don't hang up.
I need you right now.
You're always so quick with a comeback,
so why do you let others push you around?
Sim Sung Hee...
I think she found out everything
about the ledger.
What do you mean, everything?
Even that you're the one behind it?
She knows everything?
Plus, she has that phone you lost.
I'll go get it back from her right now.
Don't do that.
She already can't stand me as it is.
It'll only be a matter of time
before it gets all over school.
Everyone in school
will be talking about me.
Shit.
Does Yoon Joon Seo know what's going on?
What's that bastard up to?
You know how he is.
Even if Joon Seo tried to step in,
he can't handle someone like Sim Sung Hee
on his own.
Right now, I just...
I just need you to be there for me.
Baek Ah Jin.
Look at me.
You know I learned to be perceptive
the hard way, right?
Baek Ah Jin, you said it yourself.
That you need me.
You're the smart one.
I bet you've already figured out a plan.
So, tell me.
What do you need me to do?
Guys, hurry up and chip in
for the teacher's wedding gift.
- What about you?
- Hey, Jung Hye Ji.
Five thousand won.
I heard Baek Ah Jin and Sim Sung Hee
had a big fight, pulling hair in the cafe.
- Really? Why?
- Well, it wasn't exactly a fight.
Sim Sung Hee snapped and poured
strawberry milk all over her tray.
Strawberry milk? Is she crazy?
Things are bad between them.
I'll chip in now, too.
Ah Jin. It's okay, you don't have to.
Why not?
Well, we've already collected quite a bit, so...
Is it because of the rumor?
That I'm an orphan.
No, that's not why.
Do you know who started that rumor?
Seriously?
What's with that reaction?
Is something wrong?
It's just... you two got together so suddenly.
So Yoon Joon Seo asked you out
after you poured milk on Baek Ah Jin?
I spilled it, I didn't pour it.
Not a single drop even touched her face.
Whatever.
From now on, don't even bring up
Baek Ah Jin around me.
I'm leaving.
What's with her?
She loved trash-talking Baek Ah Jin.
I like it, I like it
How's it going with Joon Seo?
You scared me.
You two look good together.
What's it to you?
Treat him well. He's a good guy.
[Boss]
[Boss Pwd: 1004, Friday, 4th Period, P.E. Class]
Angel? An angel?
That crazy bitch, Sim Sung Hee.
That bitch has no shame.
God, this is unbelievable.
[Friday, 4th Period, P.E. Class]
Joon Seo.
I already bought our movie tickets
for this weekend.
Thanks.
Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Ugh, I hate P.E. so much.
It's hot and you get all sweaty.
I wish this was a study hall instead.
If you hate it that much,
you want to skip and hang out?
We can just tell the teacher we're going
to the nurse's office, like Ah Jin did.
Just sneak back to the classroom later.
Don't tell the others.
Okay!
- Sir.
- Yes, Sung Hee? What's wrong?
My stomach really hurts.
And I feel nauseous.
Is it that bad?
I tried to push through it, but I just can't...
I think I need to go to the nurse's office
for some medicine.
- All right, go ahead. Can you go alone?
- Yes.
Yes, Seon Hui and I will stop by
this weekend.
Right, right.
All right, take care, Father.
You're always on the phone here.
I was on my way to the nurse's office
and heard you talking.
Are you not feeling well?
I'm just not feeling too great.
Is that right?
Well, you should get going then.
If you don't have a class,
could I talk to you for a second?
[Come To The Art Room]
[Erase This!]
[Sim Sung Hee]
Sim Sung Hee just left the classroom.
Ah Jin, what was it you wanted to say?
I'm sorry. I'm just a little nervous.
It's all right. Just relax and tell me
what's on your mind.
Could...
Could you hold my hand for a moment?
Your hand?
My hands start to shake whenever I get nervous.
I know how much you've been looking out for me.
And I've been giving it a lot of thought.
About that "true love" you mentioned before.
You've got to be kidding me.
Well, back then... I just said that
out of genuine concern for you, Ah Jin-
I understand how you feel now.
What? "How you feel"?
I pretended not to get it because
I was afraid my friends would find out,
but I've regretted it ever since.
It must have been so hard for you
to bring it up first.
No, it's not like that. I just-
I'll do whatever you want.
I think I'm ready now.
Thanks for your help.
It would've taken me forever by myself.
Nah, don't worry about it.
Come on, the bell's gonna ring. Let's go.
Yeah.
Man... It'll probably be fine, right?
What do you mean?
Aren't we done with the supply check?
Not that. I'm on classroom duty today.
I was about to lock up on my way out,
but I couldn't find the lock,
so I just left it unlocked.
You know our classroom's been broken into
a few times, right?
So everyone in class is really sensitive about it.
Then should you be announcing it like that?
Huh?
If the classroom actually gets robbed,
you'd be partly to blame, wouldn't you?
If they don't find the thief and it gets
swept under the rug like last time,
the other students might blame you.
You never know, right?
It's better to be safe than sorry.
It's so hot, I'm dying.
- Changing out of gym clothes is a pain.
- Dude, you reek.
Didn't Sim Sung Hee go
to the nurse's office?
Hey, what happened to my desk?
Someone's gone through my stuff!
- Hey, wasn't that...
- Where's the envelope?
The envelope...
- What's wrong?
- The envelope's gone.
No way. Are you sure?
Maybe you put it elsewhere and forgot.
I'm not mistaken.
I'm positive I put it in my notebook.
That's where I always keep it.
I'm sure it was here right before P.E.
Sim Sung Hee.
Why were you in here by yourself?
I wasn't feeling well,
so I was just resting in here.
Then how'd you get in?
It was already unlocked.
- But I'm sure I locked it.
- The person on duty said he locked it.
If you're sick, go to the nurse's office.
Why would you rest in here?
Exactly.
Wait, didn't you tell the P.E. teacher
you were going to the nurse's office?
Cut the crap and answer me directly.
Did you steal it?
What the fuck?
You've got to be kidding me.
Fine. If I let you search me
and you find nothing,
then what are you gonna do?
If you find nothing!
I swear, I'll make you regret this.
Fine, look.
Look. I said, look.
See anything? Huh? Look!
- See? There's nothing here! Huh?!
- You haven't checked your locker yet.
What, you've even got a padlock on it.
Must be something important in there, huh?
"Important"? There's nothing in there.
I don't want you invading my privacy.
Privacy?
Isn't this my phone? Huh?
You lost it, so I was just
holding onto it for you.
But you never bothered showing up,
so I couldn't give it back.
Then what's this?
- The class president's AirPods and cash?
- No way.
That's seriously creepy.
Unbelievable.
Sim Sung Hee,
you're still going to deny it?
It wasn't me.
I'm telling you, it wasn't me.
I have no reason to steal.
It's not like my family is poor
or anything.
You're a klepto. You used to steal stuff
back in middle school, remember?
Fuck, I wanna punch her.
- Guys, should we call the cops?
- She's crazy.
She's lost her mind.
Don't let them get to you.
This isn't over yet.
It was Baek Ah Jin!
She set this all up, and I fell for it!
Fuck!
Baek Ah Jin...
She's a bigger piece of shit than I am.
You all need to know
what that bitch is really like!
Kim Jae Oh's ledger...
It's actually Baek Ah Jin's.
It was Baek Ah Jin, you fucking idiots!
What the hell are you talking about?
Hey.
That ledger's mine.
Why say it's Baek Ah Jin's?
You got any proof?
I saw the texts on your phone.
The one about a "boss" and "collections,"
with all the kids' names?
Do you think I'm close enough with her
to be texting back and forth?
Fuck, I'm telling you I saw it.
Look.
Where is this so-called text?
Well?
If you're not lying, they should be
on this phone, right?
This is the first I've touched my phone
since you stole it.
Shit. Now that I think about it,
I'm fucking pissed.
It wasn't enough to steal my phone?
You had to go through my texts, too?
That Baek Ah Jin?
She's seeing the art teacher.
I saw them. I swear I saw them!
Holding hands.
They were talking about "true love."
It was really something else.
Sim Sung Hee!
- Hey, hey!
- You think you can say whatever you want?
Is she a psycho or something?
Let me tell you a secret, too.
About who our homeroom teacher's marrying.
The art teacher.
How dare you spread ridiculous rumors!
Hey, please calm down.
Hey, Baek Ah Jin, why don't you explain?
What is all this nonsense about?
The art teacher was really worried about me,
so he referred me
to the True Love Counseling Center.
I think that's what she must have seen.
You heard that and now you're going around
saying you saw something,
that they have a thing, making it all up
and causing all this chaos, huh?
And another thing. Did you steal all this?
Answer me!
No, I didn't! I told you I didn't!
You were the only one in class during gym.
If you didn't steal, why were you here?
Didn't you tell the teacher you were going
to the nurse's office?
That's because...
I was supposed to meet Joon Seo.
Yoon Joon Seo, is that true?
I was in the equipment room the whole time
cleaning with the gym captain.
Yeah, that's right.
- How could you do this to me?
- Seriously, how far will she take this?
How could you do this to me? Joon Seo, how?
I warned you, didn't I?
I told you not to mess with Baek Ah Jin.
Sim Sung Hee, that's enough.
You're coming with me.
Come with me now!
I'm not going! Damn it!
Dude, this is legendary.
Hey, post this online.
- Wow, this is insane.
- Totally insane.
The class president's AirPods and cash?
I'm telling you, it wasn't me.
I have no reason to steal.
It's not like my family is poor
or anything.
You're a klepto. You used to steal stuff
back in middle school, remember?
[Exposing The Truth About Sim Sung Hee,
Daughter Of Lawyer Sim Geun Seop]
[Unlike In Middle School,
Her School Life Was Relatively...]
[With Attorney Sim Geun Seop]
[Worry about your own family first.
The Truth About Sim Geun Seop's Daughter.]
[Submit]
[I Will Hold Your Hand: Legal Counsel]
[Viewer Comments: Worry About Your Family First]
[Look At Your Family Before You Judge.
Teach Your Daughter Some Decency.]
[He's Still Practicing Law After This?
No Shame.]
She's not my daughter!
How could you do this to me?
- Did you have fun with that whore?
- Fun? Show some class, will you?
Class? Try keeping it in your pants!
I asked if you slept with her!
- Leaving early?
- What do you want? Get lost.
See? I told you.
In movies, it's the clueless ones like you
who always die first.
Shut the fuck up!
This is all because of...
Don't you dare say this is my fault.
This is on you.
You're the one who went through my things,
poured water all over me,
and even trashed my lunch tray.
And I just let it happen.
You think I don't know
you're the one who framed me?
If you were a little less stupid,
things might have turned out differently.
What?
Do you really think that was
Joon Seo's handwriting on the board?
But at this point,
who really cares who wrote it?
What matters is that now,
no one will listen to a word you say.
No one will believe you.
And no one even likes you.
You're a fucking psycho.
You really never suspected Joon Seo?
Not even once?
You really thought he actually liked you?
As if, Sung Hee.
You should've known when to stop.
Fight me all you want.
You're the only one who'll lose.
I've got powerful people backing me up.
You don't.
Because you're an orphan. You bitch.
- You think I'm just going to let this go?
- Sung Hee.
I wonder who Teacher Kwak
was having an affair with.
Ugh, now that Teacher Kwak got fired,
all that money we spent was a total waste.
Who on earth did she get caught
having an affair with?
She said she needed legal advice,
so your dad even helped her out.
Did you like my gift?
If your dad gets branded as the
"Infidelity Lawyer,"
his own firm won't even protect him.
Then your father's reputation will be ruined,
and you'll be known as the thieving
daughter of the infidelity lawyer.
Do you think your parents
will still have your back then?
How will you fare,
having to live with that label?
You really deluded yourself
into thinking you could beat me.
That was never going to happen, Sung Hee.
Like you said, I'm pretty much an orphan.
But it's not like I never had parents
to begin with.
Help me.
I just got rid of them.
They were my first X.
[Lim Sun Ye: Her First X]
Sung Hee.
It was fun having you as my target.
Thanks.
For making school less boring.
What do I think of Baek Ah Jin, you ask?
She's always been a great actress, even as a kid.
She always wore whatever mask
the situation called for.
She's a demon.
A demon in human skin.