(Episode 7)
Are you alright?
It's been a while.
I saw you earlier, with
that man at the restaurant.
Found a discarded second-hand good,
taking pity on it.
Such a kind person.
He's nothing like you.
Stay away from me.
Kai-kun, I told you, didn't I?
Serious people are boring.
No matter how much it's fixed up,
if the toy itself is dull,
it'll be tossed aside again in no time.
Who would ever take
someone like you seriously?
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
Who are you?
What did you say to him?
Oh, excuse me.
My shoulder bumped into him
because of my carelessness,
I'm afraid his shoulder will dislocate
or a bone might break.
So I asked him.
Since everything seems fine,
I'll take my leave.
Hey!
- Never mind. I'm fine.
- How?
- You're shaking like this.
- It's said it's nothing.
- Kai!
- Don't follow me!
He's nothing like that guy.
Fuma-san cares for me.
He doesn't hurt me.
He shows me love.
But...
Again...
It's happening again.
It always ends up like this.
I don't need a boring toy anymore.
I've grown tired of you.
I...
I never want to feel like that again.
Never!
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love-"
(Let's meet today?)
(Working on a project
with friends today)
(Call me when you're done)
(Still not done?)
(Fell asleep)
(I'll come pick you up)
(I have plans with an upperclassman)
(Busy)
(Tired)
(I'll call back later)
(I have plans)
(Meeting Rei)
(I'm worried about you)
Kai, why don't you go back home?
Am I bothering you?
No, that's not it.
I'm grateful to you, Rei.
For letting me stay this long.
.Hey, things were going well
with Fuma-san, right?
I even saw him picking you
up from university.
Why are you running away?
I'm not running away.
Fuma loves you, but are
you breaking up with him?
First of all, we are not dating.
And he doesn't love me.
He just thinks I'm a weird person.
Sorry, but can I
stay just a little longer?
I'm looking into a new dorm tomorrow.
You're going that far?
I...
I think Kai wants to cry
but is forcing himself to do something
to keep himself from crying.
You should talk to Fuma-san.
Fuma-san!
Good morning.
I'm going to stop by
the student affairs office,
I'll go ahead!
Good morning, Kai.
Wait.
Sorry.
Please stop this.
Huh?
Ambushing,
touching,
calling my name.
Are you serious?
.What happened after you
left the restaurant that day?
What did that man say to you?
Whatever I do is none of your business.
I'm worried about you, Kai.
Don't you get it?
I'm tired of you.
Huh?
You suddenly disappeared and said that?
It's boring.
I was just having fun,
but you were serious.
'I love you' and 'You're the only one'.
I got goosebumps listening to it.
Why are you saying
things that aren't true?
It's not untrue.
Running errands, making food,
sleeping on the floor...
It's too heavy to even be funny.
The last restaurant was decent,
But I'm tired of having you
feel sorry for me.
In the end, you're just taking care
of an innocent younger guy
and thought you were also innocent.
It's annoying.
I don't believe you.
What you think doesn't matter to me.
Don't go.
It's over.
Not that it ever really began.
- Yay!
- Woo!
Seriously?
- No way.
The top racer actually lost?
Dammit!
Woo! Nice cornering!
Aren't you a bit too hot-headed?
Drinks will taste great tonight, huh?
Not yet. They still don't taste great.
Because of him.
For the disgrace he brought on me,
I'll make sure to get him back.
Ah... But in that last race...
You let that guy ride
a specially designed motorcycle,
but with one glance,
he immediately adjusted it.
Ah... Damn it!
Don't remind me! It pisses me off!
Arashi!
You okay?
Seems like I can hear
a little kitten meowing.
Apparently giraffes moo.
Huh?
His weakness...
is that kitten.
Haa...
I might be done for.
Of course I don't think that everything
Kai said is what he really meant.
That last day, he was acting strange.
He's trying to push me away,
He must be handling
something on his own.
Then go now.
Be persistent until
you can ease his burden.
I want to, but...
I've already been doing that.
I'm scared.
I don't want to hurt him.
If I get rejected more than this...
Rei.
You know, 'idiot' can sometimes
mean 'adorable, ' too."
Huh?
Words don't always equal feelings,
and actions don't, either.
Especially with someone like Kai,
who's so stubborn.
He never says what he really feels!
Even I know that
because we're friends.
But...
even if I understand that,
I can't help him.
It frustrates me,
but... I think you're
the only one who can
tend to Kai's heart right now, Fuma-san.
So...
We're both having trouble with people
who don't mean what they say.
Thanks. I'm going.
Sorry. I spilled a secret.
Idiot.
You meant 'adorable', right?
This time, I meant it literally.
Huh?
I need to move.
Is this what you are looking for?
Another hallucination...
"Idle, lecher, eldest son."
You're real? How?
The management company for
this building happens to be my father's.
I borrowed a key.
Sorry.
You're a real stalker?
I'll sue you for trespassing!
"Idle, lecher, eldest son."
"Has a younger brother
and sister he's close with."
"Seems to want to introduce
them to me someday."
Stop it.
"Porridge with egg, orange jelly."
"I wonder how he knows my favorites."
Stop it, stop it!
"A player but takes racing seriously."
"A narcissist, but undeniably charming."
"Annoying, but makes me smile."
"'Even when tired, he comes to see me."
"He is persistent but always makes me
make me happy."
Stop.
Please stop.
"That's why I get scared."
- "One day, you'll grow tired of me."
- One day, you'll grow tired of me.
- "Because I'm boring."
- Because I'm boring.
And I'm not beautiful.
What should I do so
you won't get tired of me?
Please don't say love to anyone
except me.
Be nice to me alone.
Only take me out for a meal.
Don't leave me.
I'll try my best.
- "So please..."
- So please...
- "only like me."
- only like me.
"I love you, Fuma-san."
Is this just another game to you?
Look at me. Look into my eyes.
It's not fair for you to say it first.
So, I'll say it.
I don't just like you anymore, Kai.
I love you.
It's not just ‘like'.
But it's love.
I...
I love you too, Fuma-san.
I love you.
I really love you.
I hear you.
You finally said it.
Thank you.
I love you...
so please stay by my side.
Am I finally getting
promoted from servant?
Fuma-san.
When are you going to grow tired of me?
Do you want to hear sweet words?
Good night.
Kai, what are you afraid of?
I'm not going anywhere,
I'm staying here.
Understood.
I accept you.
Hey, hey, hey, what are you doing?
- Don't play around.
- I'm serious.
- I won't stop you anymore.
- Wait.
It's not that I don't want
to sleep with Kai.
Actually, I want to do it.
But that's not why I came.
I just wanted to see you.
Though, of course,
I wouldn't mind a kiss.
Don't talk. Just hold me.
Can I?
Don't you want me?
I do.
But I don't just want your body.
I want your heart too.
Fuma-san, hurry...
Hurry and get bored of me already.
Is that really what you want?
Please...
Don't get bored of me.
Don't ever get bored of me.
Kai and Fuma-san are dating...
Really? Like, really?
Mmm.
Whoa!
This way!
Hey, it's amazing!
You were open about your
relationship with Arashi-san, so...
I'm seriously so happy for you!
But, Kai...
Are you really okay with this?
Hey, hey, what's the confirmation?
If you diss me, Kai will get angry.
Are you going to get mad?
Rei, are you coming to tomorrow's race?
Everyone will get mad if
someone attacks their partner.
- What about the race?"
- Oh, I'll be there.
Did you finish your assignments?
You don't know how much
Kai loves me, don't you?
Can we stick to one topic at a time?
My head hurts.
You don't understand.
- Huh?
- Yes.
The topic is always the same.
Kai gets flustered and
tries to change it,
and I just bring it back.
Fuma-san, don't you ever get
told you're too stubborn?
Rei.
Don't criticize my boyfriend.
Got it.
I'll go finish my assignments.
Take your time and relax
before tomorrow's race.
Hey, my adorable protector,
can I kiss you?
No...
Not in public.
Who else would I protect
if not my boyfriend?
"Love in the air,"
Tonight through tomorrow morning,
seasonal winds and sudden rain will
cause temperatures
to drop significantly.
Please be aware of the temperature
difference when going outside.
Thanks.
Text me when you're inside.
In 30 seconds?
Got it.
Good luck with your assignments.
Arashi.
I'll be there to cheer you on
at tomorrow's race.
See you later.
(I'm home!)
Arashi?
What's going on? Arashi?
Ah! Help!
Help, Arashi!
Arashi!
(Can you be the sky
at the end of the line?)
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love-"
Hey, Kai.
Hmm?
What color do you like?
Emerald green.
What's your favorite food?
Mhm...
I like everything.
Rice.
Rice porridge.
Orange jelly.
Kai.
Hmm?
What?
Kai.
Hmm?
My Kai.
Here it is again.
Again.
Kai.
What?
Hey!
Enough.
Ah.
What's with you?