♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my playful charm♪
♪Just to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for you♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode17=
=Lang In Peril &amp; Murong Lies=
Niannian, are you here?
Ye Lang.
I'm here.
Niannian!
Jiang Niannian!
Director.
The surveillance footage
shows no one entered.
Keep looking.
Niannian!
Ye Lang.
Are you still there?
Niannian.
You came to save me.
♪Chasing through the shadows♪
I'm sorry.
I'm too late.
(This can't be an accident.)
(Much like how her three ex-husbands died.)
(Jiang Niannian.)
(I won't let anything happen to you.)
We're almost home.
Who are you?
Young master.
These are medical devices
approved by Mr. Li.
Need to be delivered here today.
Go on, then.
Niannian.
Go get some rest.
Until I'm back,
don't open the door.
Mm.
Go on.
Playing dirty, huh?
You're tough.
But she may not be so lucky.
Tell your boss
if he wants to play dirty,
I'm in this to the end.
But if he hurts Jiang Niannian,
I'll make him wish they were gone.
Get lost.
Ye Lang.
You okay?
Jiang Niannian.
Awake?
Why is she here?
Where's Ye Lang?
There was an issue with an overseas deal.
He flew to Germany at dawn.
What?
Something this important,
and he didn't tell you?
It's none of your concern.
Then get some rest.
Ye Lang left in a hurry,
I've got lots of work to handle.
After all,
the only one who can help him now
is me.
By the way,
among all those women around Ye Lang,
you're the only one I've admired.
Come to me if you need anything.
I can help you.
I wouldn't dare drink what you sent.
That's not it.
He wouldn't leave without a word.
A car crash.
Cold storage.
A heavy object.
That's how my three ex-husbands died.
They're trying to kill me the same way.
(Jiang Niannian.)
(Didn't expect you to be so smart.)
(You've really surprised me.)
Luckily you were sent here in time.
Or it would've been bad.
Do you know
who did it?
Funny thing.
Before I blacked out, I saw you there.
What a coincidence.
Why were you there?
I heard
Niannian was almost killed.
Someone insisted on taking her home.
I was really worried.
Then I saw you collapse.
Is that so?
Where's my phone?
It broke last night.
Being repaired now.
You need to rest now.
Don't worry about anything else.
(Could it be her?)
Ye Lang.
The number you have dialed is powered off.
Why can't I get through?
(Forensic Appraisal Report)
Ms. Jiang.
I've been waiting a long time.
Are you okay?
Why are you here?
You should be glad I came.
Otherwise, what would you do?
I'm here
to give you this.
(Delivery Receipt)
Based on files from Murong Xue,
Vice President of Renxin Hospital,
Zhang Yufeng,
Liu Jian,
Zhou Chen,
my three ex-husbands,
each had business dealings
with the Li family
in cold-chain, logistics
and medical procurement.
(Liu Yexi, God No.6)
Through that,
(Liu Yexi suggested Zhou Chen God No.6.)
they knew Liu Yexi.
She recommend God No.6 to them.
This drug claims
to accelerate metabolism
and slow aging.
Gentlemen,
you must've heard of it, right?
It was this new drug
that caused them three to suffer
(Zhou Chen)
mental damage
(Zhang Yufeng, Liu Jian)
and die in so-called accidents.
I've looked into it.
What Liu Yexi did
was to corner the Li family's suppliers
and build her own power base
to pocket all the Li's assets.
Gentlemen,
you should
watch your backs too.
As for my three ex-husbands' cases,
I've given all the evidence to the police.
They will close the cases
as murder by Liu Yexi,
to end the Li family's PR crisis.
Once their assets are unfrozen,
I'll use that money
to resolve the public fallout.
Niannian,
you're being so thoughtful.
I'm truly flattered.
But,
I really can't take your money.
I've already signed a new contract
with German investors.
(Investment Agreement)
Enough to get us through this.
Try it.
I brought it back
from Germany just for you.
A Black Forest cake.
The chef used their family cherry recipe.
You have no idea
how worried I've been these days
without seeing you.
You must be tired.
Mm.
Ms. Jiang,
how should I reward you?
We'll see
who rewards whom.
You're hurt?
You lied again!
This is your "trip abroad"?
Niannian.
I...
What are you hiding from me?
What happened?
I just...
Hello?
Ye Lang, Xiaodi is missing.
What did he say?
Xiaodi...
Niannian!
We're on our way.
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪