THE WORD COMES FROM THE ANCIENT GREEK WORD "DAIMAI,"
WHICH MEANS "TO SHARE THE SAME FATE"
DEMONS ORIGINALLY EXISTED AMONG HUMANS
AND PROTECTED THEM AS THEIR GUARDIANS
My life feels as if it's shrouded in mist.
Who is a friend and who is a foe?
Or is everyone around me a foe?
I can't tell.
Is the one approaching me through the mist
a devil or an angel?
Have they come to save me
or to destroy me?
The truth is so fragile
that even the faintest mist can hide it.
EPISODE 1 LIVING IN THE MIST
Let us pray.
200 YEARS AGO, JOSEON
Almighty God,
please guide us
to always remember your will
and empower us to apply it
through our words and actions.
It is said
that evil spirits seek to deceive your followers
by quoting the Bible, your holy word.
MAY THIS HOLY WATER CLEANSE ME OF MY SINS AND PROTECT ME FROM EVIL SPIRITS. AMEN.
Evil spirits seek to separate us from God
and steal his power and glory.
To resist their temptations,
we must…
What is that?
It's blood!
It's the devil!
I CAN DO ALL THINGS THROUGH HIM WHO GIVES ME STRENGTH, PHILIPPIANS 4:13
My dear.
Stay away.
I'm incredible as usual.
Catholics believe
that humans have three kinds of enemies.
The first is their own bodies,
which undermine them from within with traits such as laziness.
The second is their worldly lives,
which eat away at them from the outside.
Their third and final enemy
is evil spirits.
You look like you have been starving for days.
Who isn't these days?
Is your wish to be free from hunger?
I do not know who you are,
but not even His Majesty can solve--
The sea is full of fish.
Look how they shine in the water.
What the…
I know. You must be a goblin.
How dare you compare me to such an ugly and lowly spirit?
Then the Dragon King?
I'm not an old man like him.
-The nine-tailed fox? -They shed fur everywhere
and smell like dogs.
Then what are you?
I am a demon from the underworld.
What?
You humans call me
an evil spirit.
Am I so hungry that I'm seeing things?
Goodness, I must be dying soon!
What's that?
Were you serious?
My goodness!
It's not for free though.
You need to make a deal with me.
A deal?
The deal will last for ten years.
And you will never go hungry in that period
since that is your wish.
What happens afterward?
Your body will die,
and your soul will end up where I come from.
What kind of place is that?
You humans seem to call it
hell.
Hell?
My mouth waters just by looking at my own flesh.
Hell can't be worse than here.
-Give it here. -You're a lot braver than you look.
What? How do I look?
Shall we go ahead and sign it?
This thing looks interesting.
What are you doing? It hurts!
"One must sign with one's own blood."
That's the rule.
What's your name?
Park Bok-gyu.
Park Bok… What?
-Bok-gyu. -"Bok-gyu."
Bok-gyu.
What a peculiar name.
Look at this!
Evil spirits deceive and confuse humans in their arrogant yet tempting ways,
undermining them from both the inside and the outside.
However, who has ever seen an evil spirit?
Even if they were to exist,
they are but external forces.
See you in ten years.
I can't believe this.
Thank you, Buddha!
You're thanking the wrong guy.
While it is true that external forces can lead people astray,
all evil ultimately stems from human desires.
So the fault cannot lie in the evil spirits alone.
2023 KOREA CEO AWARDS
Anything without caffeine, please.
Are you a part-timer?
I knew the non-alcoholic mojito would be a hit.
Do you trade stocks?
I mean, who doesn't, right?
If you do, I bet you've heard of Hanmyeong Investment and Securities.
Take it.
There are hundreds of people waiting in line for my advice,
but I'm willing to let you cut in line.
-The reason being? -You're probably making chump change.
All that struggling with the rent and bills
will age that pretty face of yours.
It just breaks my heart.
Let me buy you a drink later. Give me your number.
We will now announce the CEO of the Year
for the F&amp;B Industry.
I ask the winner to step onstage.
You can call my secretary regarding any investment inquiries.
All that struggling to cover drinks and bills with your meager salary
will make you lose your hair quickly.
It just breaks my heart.
Hey, you're one ambitious man.
Hitting on the Mirae Group's princess?
-Princess? -She's an Instagram sensation.
They call her the IU of the dessert world
and Kim Yun-a of the F&amp;B industry.
Mirae F&amp;B has received the highest rank
for two consecutive years.
"The Devil in Hermès"?
Congratulations, Ms. Do Do-hee!
Hello, I'm Do Do-hee.
[EXCLUSIVE] MIRAE F&amp;B'S CHILLING JUICE PACKED WITH SUGAR?
They deliberately blurred the lines between fructose and sugar.
Someone's using cunning tactics.
Who did this?
I'm looking into it.
Who would be the most envious of our performance?
Our competitors or affiliates.
My money's on a power grab within the group.
I'll prioritize that possibility.
Let's head straight to the office.
We can't.
This isn't the time for a blind date.
ALMIGHTY JU
You can't avoid this forever.
-You know how the chairwoman-- -I certainly do.
Hi, Madam Ju.
Are you on your way?
Yes, I just arrived. How's your checkup going?
It's going to start soon.
There's something I've got to tell you. An issue came up at work, and…
So you want to cancel the date?
Let me first take care of work and put a hold on--
Let's put a hold on the checkup too.
All right, fine.
I'll go on the date, okay?
Forget it.
I understand you hate blind dates. That's okay.
I hate checkups too.
I didn't say that.
I like blind dates.
Who wouldn't like to meet someone over a fancy meal?
Is that so?
I'll enjoy myself on the date,
so make sure to get a thorough--
Let's get started.
How long should I stay to avoid being rude?
I would say at least 30 minutes.
Okay. You should go grab something to eat, Ms. Shin.
I'll go and spend 30 minutes sitting like a doll.
I guess you could call Chucky from Child's Play a doll too.
-I'm back, boss. -All right.
Kim signed the business rights waiver.
I suppose he's not a complete idiot.
He knows how to save his own skin.
What the…
What's wrong with this thing? Is it stuck?
Who's that?
Don't tell me you forgot.
Is it today already?
How could you forget such an important day?
I guess I was the only one who cared.
CRIME AND PUNISHMENT
Wouldn't it be amazing
to have unlimited time at the flip of an hourglass?
Hold on.
There must be another way.
We could extend our contract.
No, how about we sign a new contract?
You know better.
There's no point in resisting. Let's have a beautiful goodbye.
I'm not going anywhere!
I won't! Go away!
Don't come near me!
Stay back!
Then again, no human would willingly die.
I'm glad to see you being so human for once in your last moments.
Please give me one more chance.
You have no idea how I got here.
I do know. You got here thanks to me.
Since your wish was to obtain wealth and power,
I would have fulfilled that for you regardless of what you did.
All you did was choose the method.
I'll give you anything.
How about 10… No, 100 other lives instead of mine?
That's not a bad deal for you, is it?
I love my job.
Do you know why?
The deal is fair to everyone.
The only thing that I want
is the other party's soul.
Nothing else.
What was that?
The boss is full of energy today.
He solved a major pain in his neck.
He must be in a good mood.
I can't breathe.
You'll die of a heart attack.
What is hell like?
Is it as bad as they say?
The lazy are sent to endlessly run on millstones
while hellfire burns so intensely it melts your flesh and bones.
But that's all in the past.
That's child's play
compared to where you're going.
You never explained that to me.
You never asked.
You would've ended up in hell even without our deal.
You had nothing to lose.
I'd say you made a pretty smart choice.
This may sound ridiculous,
but that's quite comforting to hear.
EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR JEONG GU-WON
I'm sorry, but we're fully booked.
A customer booked the entire place.
Unbelievable.
She even told him today's my birthday?
You have a male customer, right?
I'm his guest.
Then let me show you to your table.
Over there, ma'am.
What's all this fuss?
He could be Madam Ju's soulmate.
Why not just marry him herself?
I didn't know that people still read print newspapers
outside of planes.
Is it just for show?
I'll have you know
that I'm married to my work.
I have no interest in men…
whatsoever.
Marry your work or your pillow for all I care.
How is it any of my concern?
If you must share personal information,
I'd prefer your bank account password.
Did we go to school together by any chance?
-Highly unlikely. -Did we used to go out?
Then you'd remember me.
So you're not my school friend or my ex.
Then where are your manners?
All human beings
are insignificant to me.
What's up with this handsome nutjob?
I'm keeping my end of the bargain.
You better be too.
Almighty.
Why must I bear this hardship?
30 MINUTES
START
I booked this entire restaurant to have a quiet meal.
Sounds good.
It'll be nice and awkward.
If you want to eat, there are other restaurants.
Then you leave. You obviously know a lot of places.
What's up with this hardcore nutjob?
Excuse me.
I'd like two of these.
I'd also like the strongest wine you have, please.
Certainly, sir.
Garlic steak…
"Do Do-hee."
Myers-Briggs type, ISTJ.
She probably can't empathize as a T.
LOST HER PARENTS AT 11 YEARS OLD ADOPTED BY MIRAE GROUP'S CHAIRWOMAN JU
What is he, a little kid?
I was admiring your youthful spirit.
I do look a lot younger than my age.
You obviously weren't looking for a meal, so tell me.
Why do you insist on staying?
I'm going to stay for 30 minutes just to be polite.
Polite to whom?
You're being absolutely rude to me by staying.
I'm like a mirror.
I'm reflecting your rude behavior.
We should make up excuses on why this didn't work out.
Why don't you say…
you were intimidated by my beauty?
Why are you doing this to me?
It's not like I want to do this.
I'm just following orders from above.
"From above"?
I wouldn't dare defy the sacred word of the Almighty.
Who the hell…
I mean, who are you?
I almost forgot.
We should introduce ourselves properly.
CEO DO DO-HEE
"Do Do-hee"?
Give me yours.
Unlike you, I don't enjoy disclosing personal information.
I understand you were forced to be here just like me,
but we should work together to get through this.
"Jeong Gu-won."
As in "salvation"? It doesn't suit you at all.
"Sunwol Foundation"?
That rings a bell.
My foundation supports traditional artists such as traditional singers and dancers
and regularly produces superb traditional performances.
How are you not familiar with such a reputed institution?
Shouldn't you try to be more cultured?
Tradition, tradition, tradition…
That's all I hear.
I'm all for tradition,
but my life is more like modern warfare
than a little concert at a pavilion.
So what's the sacred plan?
Don't tell me
you got roped into this without any details.
Talk about a blind date.
A date?
You must also be a handful,
considering they tricked you into coming here.
So what exactly is going on here?
A blind date.
We're being set up.
Are you saying
God is setting me up with you?
Calling her God is a bit much,
even for the Almighty Ju's soulmate.
"Almighty Ju"?
Is that who you meant by "the Almighty"?
You must be in shock.
Interesting.
No other human has made me this nervous.
I'm glad at least one of us enjoyed this.
I'm sorry, but we're fully booked.
Sorry to spoil the fun,
but Cinderella's time is up. Bye.
Cold but kind.
Innocent yet sexy.
His whole existence exudes sensuality.
That was close.
Excuse me. I'll be right back.
My precious cake almost got ruined.
What was that?
Maybe he isn't such a jerk after all.
He even prepared a cake for my birthday?
Darn it.
You little bastard!
Who sent you?
What did you do to our boss?
Hold on.
I made a reservation a month ago
and sat through a boring course meal for this.
So let me have a taste first.
It won't come off.
But how could he make such a move on me without any warning?
Or was he being subtle?
That was close.
I should have been more careful.
I must've let my charm shine through without realizing it.
So I was the first woman to make him that nervous?
No other human has made me this nervous.
What's this?
No way. I'm blushing?
My face is all red!
What on earth?
Get it together, Do Do-hee.
Your name literally means "haughty."
This isn't your first rodeo.
There are different types of trash.
What type are you?
Recyclables? Food waste?
Don't you realize what's going on here?
Doesn't seem like I can recycle you for anything else,
nor do you seem nutritious at all.
So you must fall under general waste.
Beat him up.
-What the hell? -What happened?
Where did he go?
You try.
IT'S NEVER TOO LATE FOR YOUR HAIR!
TAKE ACTION BEFORE YOU LOSE MORE HAIR
-Hold on. -Wait a second.
We have to get him together.
Darn it. Let's give it a try.
Time out.
Oh no!
Interesting.
Blabbermouth! Zombie!
Stop pushing.
What's going on here? What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
I'm cleaning up.
General waste is either buried or incinerated.
What should I do with the three of you?
Come on.
Why you little…
Don't do it!
Hey, don't stop me.
I've been so busy with work lately that I haven't dated in forever.
Why am I touching up my lipstick?
What am I expecting?
I must be losing it.
Put it back in.
Again?
How dare they ruin my precious dessert time?
No matter how busy I am, it'd be rude to leave without trying…
the cake.
The party's over.
By yourself?
People eat alone all the time. Can't I celebrate by myself?
-But how could you eat my birthday cake-- -Who says it's yours?
Why would I care about your birthday?
Anyway, leave.
I'm too busy sorting trash to deal with you.
Nice meeting you.
I hope the rest of your day sucks.
One more thing.
Be sure to show some manners if we ever meet again.
I don't want anyone to think you're my ex.
Shouldn't you be more polite when making a request?
That wasn't a request.
ROOM ESCAPE CAFÉ: LOCK UP HOW'S YOUR THING DOWN THERE?
Right.
EXPERIENCE THE WORST PRISON EVER A NEW TALE UNFOLDS
That's me!
-Move it! -Watch my head.
My arm!
Seriously!
How could Madam Ju have set me up with such a jerk?
Did you look into who was behind that article?
As you said, it was an internal power grab attempt.
Who was it?
It was Ms. Noh Su-ahn of Mirae Apparel.
She recently attended a fashion show
and befriended the head of the news outlet that ran the exclusive.
Why can they never leave me alone when all I want is a peaceful life?
MIRAE GROUP
Mirae Group, one of the top ten companies in the country,
is undergoing an internal power struggle.
The Mirae Kingdom was established by the Almighty Ju,
Chairwoman Ju Cheon-suk.
I call her Madam Ju.
A YEAR AGO
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, MOTHER
CHAIRWOMAN OF MIRAE GROUP JU CHEON-SUK
I wish you many years of good health, Mother.
Don't worry.
I'll outlive you.
I hope so.
Noh Suk-min, Madam Ju's eldest child.
The poor crown prince, forever overshadowed by his mother.
Do you still drink like a fish?
I've been sober for more than ten years, Mother.
You look absolutely stunning today, Mother.
Kim Se-ra, the daughter-in-law.
An elegant peacock who constantly seeks approval.
Have you had your face done?
Of course not.
I just dolled up for the special occasion.
You should consider it.
Noh Do-gyeong, the couple's only son.
He learned to become invisible in order to survive.
Mom.
Happy birthday, Mom.
Noh Su-ahn, Madam Ju's second child.
She is so obsessed with Paris that she pretends to live there.
People call her Parisu-ahnne.
Austin and Justin are her twin sons
-born a minute apart. -Austin, Justin.
THE TWINS AUSTIN, JUSTIN
What a load of global crap.
My husband couldn't make it because of his research paper schedule.
He feels terrible that he can't be here.
But he already gave me a present.
By not showing up.
Su-ahn's husband is a professor at an Ivy League school.
People call him Unicorn because he rarely shows up.
Ju Seok-hoon, Madam Ju's nephew.
Happy birthday, Aunt Cheon-suk.
You look neat and tidy as usual.
Well, I'm just too busy increasing your wealth.
Despite being the only other Ju,
he is purely a business partner to Madam Ju.
Are your parents still in Mongolia or whatever it's called?
They're in Peru.
-You're a year older now, sis. -Seok-hoon's father
-Happy birthday. -is the little brother of Cheon-suk.
-You should retire -He and his wife are frugal hippies.
-and travel around like us. -Do they ever wash up?
-I can't tell them apart from the alpacas. -Happy birthday.
If everyone's here, are we ready for pictures?
Where's Do-hee?
She must be running late.
The whole family's here anyway. Let's just take the photo.
Yes, Mother.
There isn't much time.
Forget it.
I'm not taking any pictures without Do-hee.
I'm sorry! My meeting ran late.
You're here.
Mother's been waiting for you.
As if.
I just used her as an excuse not to take pictures.
Do-hee, stand next to Mother.
Why the long face on a happy day like this?
It's obvious why they're celebrating me getting old.
Come on.
At least smile for the picture.
-Here we go. Smile! -And I'm Do Do-hee.
I'm not related to anyone here.
I'm like a virus to them.
But they don't show their claws that easily.
Their smile is their weapon.
Who will claim the throne of Mirae Group?
The answer to that question will mean the end of this war
and the beginning of another.
LOVE THE PEOPLE AROUND YOU TRUST LEADS TO HAPPINESS
Hello?
Is this Ms. Do Do-hee?
Who am I speaking to?
I'm Cha Tae-jun, the head of Mirae Group's financial team.
I'm reaching out to share an important piece of information.
Which is?
It's not something to discuss over the phone.
All I can tell you right now
is that it has the power to make you chairwoman of Mirae Group.
How did you get my number?
This information is priceless.
Please think it over and contact me.
Everyone's dying to drag me into the dogfight.
Peaceful means alone aren't enough to maintain peace.
Find out Ms. Noh Su-ahn's schedule.
WORDS OF THE ALMIGHTY JU
This is it for me.
See you in heaven.
Madam Ju!
Are you okay?
Madam Ju…
Please don't leave me.
What are you doing?
What's with all this drama over my dozing off?
Where are you going?
Do you think this is funny? Do you know how shocked I was?
Why would you be shocked?
I'm old enough to die.
You know what, Madam Ju?
Liars can't enter heaven.
That's why I've already bribed God big time.
I never miss an opportunity to donate.
Why are you doing this?
There must be a reason.
Surprise, you little brat!
This isn't just a surprise. It's a shock.
What's gotten into you?
You know I never celebrate my birthday.
That's exactly why I'm doing it.
So…
How did it make you feel to think that I'd be gone?
Did all our memories
flash before your eyes?
That'd be an understatement.
It was like a whole movie.
A horror movie, thanks to you, old witch.
If I'm a witch, you're the devil's spawn.
How could you be so rebellious all your life?
You even ran away from home in college.
That's because you showed up in a limo on my first day.
CONGRATS DO-HEE ON BEING ADMITTED AT THE TOP OF YOUR CLASS
Congratulations, Do-hee!
Congrats!
Here. Do-hee?
Take this, Do-hee!
What do I do with this?
Do-hee, take this!
Hey!
I didn't want others to look down on you for being an orphan.
What about paying my boyfriend to break up with me?
I didn't like his vibe.
You get what this is, right?
I won't waste my breath.
If you wanted drama, why didn't you go all the way?
You gave him gift vouchers instead of checks.
Gift vouchers were more than enough for that brat.
I swear we got close through our constant squabbling!
That's why I don't have a religion.
You're the only higher power I answer to.
How was the blind date?
Horrible.
Hey, don't make the same mistake I did.
Looks aren't everything.
What are you talking about? Looks were all he had.
Does he look better in real life?
Like me?
Who's that?
The guy I was on a date with
is this guy.
The matchmaker got the hotel name wrong.
"Jeong Gu-won"?
Who's that?
SUNWOL FOUNDATION
Director, don't you think the lighting is too monotonous?
Wipe your drool off before pretending to be busy.
How's Ga-young doing?
That depends on you.
You're her pick-me-up, you know.
What did you tell me in the planning stage of this show?
You said you wouldn't bother me.
That you were confident…
I still think the lighting is too monotonous.
It's a bit off.
Hello?
Is this Mr. Jeong Gu-won?
What's this about?
I'm Shin Da-jeong,
the secretary of Ms. Do Do-hee of Mirae F&amp;B.
And?
What's with the attitude?
We apologize for interrupting your meal today.
We'd like to pay for your meal and offer compensation for--
No need.
So he's a jerk to everyone.
So it was a match made in hell, not in heaven?
Just a second.
-What are you doing? -I'll set up another date.
Forget it.
I won't go on another date to make you get a checkup.
Give that back!
I'm still too young to get married.
You're 28 going on 30.
And you'll turn 40 before you know it.
It's my wish to marry you off before I die.
You're not dying anytime soon.
If marriage is so great, why don't you get remarried?
Right?
I'll leave you two to squabble. Excuse me.
Let me tell you, having someone on your side
makes a world of difference.
You said not to trust anyone.
No one's on my side.
You're right.
You never know who will stab you in the back.
But there will be someone you'll gladly let stab you in the back.
That's what it means to have someone on your side.
Someone you'd understand even if they betrayed you.
I'm no Mother Teresa.
And neither are you.
It's you.
You're that person to me.
Now, I've prepared everything.
Just find someone who you'd put this ring on.
Don't get ahead of yourself, Madam Ju.
Here.
Wear both rings yourself
until you find someone you'd like to give it to.
Am I looking for Cinderella?
A ring is way better than a glass slipper.
It's been over 20 years since your parents passed.
You can stop commemorating their death anniversary.
From now on,
just celebrate your birthday.
Ta-da!
May Madam Ju
keep stabbing me in the back for many years to come.
You can count on it.
What?
On that note,
your next blind date…
Ms. Shin!
I'm busy.
Hey!
That little…
My cake… Damn it.
Wait, you're leaving already?
Yes, I can't seem to focus.
I had no cake after fulfilling a deal.
What kept you so busy?
A date.
A date?
My gosh, she can hear us from there?
With who?
A girl? Did you sleep with her?
I have papers to sign, don't I?
A whole lot of them.
Then shall we?
-Sure. Let's go. -Let's go.
He slept with her.
He definitely did!
Yes, understood.
I have to go.
I have Ms. Noh Su-ahn's schedule.
She's having a staycation at an affiliate hotel in Sokcho.
You can go home.
I'll drive there myself.
Sure, as you say.
I thought you'd decline.
To me, your word is law.
-Since when? -Deep down, always.
I have a loyal heart, you see.
I see.
You're quite the closed book, aren't you?
I'm an INFP.
Should we get some snacks along the way?
I hope you enjoy them.
-Let me give you a ride. -No, thank you.
Why hasn't she called me back?
Do you think you're the only person I can sell this to, Do Do-hee?
CLEANING IN PROGRESS
EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR JEONG GU-WON
REQUEST FOR APPROVAL
BUSINESS TRIP REPORT
Black coffee for you, sir?
I'm going to head out soon.
Will another pitiful soul be doomed today?
Another pitiful soul will be hitting the jackpot.
Sure, but it comes with a steep price.
That's because it's worth it.
Nothing's free in this world.
So who's the bitch?
Calm down.
A celebrity like you should watch your language.
Is she pretty? Younger than me?
If I'd known you could be this rude,
I would've let you die.
I don't think so.
I'm your only human companion who understands you.
What do you mean?
That hurts my feelings.
You two are bound by a contract.
But what I have with him is a genuine relationship.
I had my contract in my past life.
We now have a genuine--
-You still get paid. -So do you.
-You're just a butler. -And you're just an entertainer.
Be quiet, you humans!
What's with you?
I'm Jin Ga-young, the Beyoncé of Korean traditional dance.
I came here
to revive Sunwol Theater in the middle of my world tour.
I'm Star Jin.
Exactly.
Even Batman would only be a loner in a cave without his butler.
-What are you talking about? -What?
To me, you're both equally defective.
-What? -What?
You remember your past life.
And you fangirl over a demon.
You two are in no way normal human beings.
Don't let it get to you, Star Jin.
He's doing this on purpose to distance himself from us.
He's befriended mortals only to be left behind too many times.
I, for one, understand you.
It must be extremely lonely to be immortal.
It's understandable that you never open up to anyone.
So what is it like
to be immortal?
Honestly?
In a word,
it's pretty damn…
amazing.
Perfect looks, eloquence, intelligence, and even a sense of humor…
Living as a flawless predator forever?
It's just fantastic!
I only have one wish.
That this peace would last forever.
Go work on the performance.
You insignificant and annoying humans.
You never take my word for it.
He used to be human himself. He hasn't always been a demon.
I bet he was hot even as a human.
Anyway, so who is she?
Oh, my tea!
She already checked out?
I should have known.
Noh Su-ahn and her whims.
I haven't been here in a while.
Do-hee!
Hurry up, Do-hee!
I really wanted to stay home today.
Are you already starting to avoid us?
I feel hurt.
Don't you have friends?
Hang out with them instead.
No, he doesn't have any friends.
That's why we should hang out with him.
But we can't do anything because it's raining.
Don't worry.
It's just a shower.
It'll stop soon.
Look, it stopped raining!
-Should we go back? Let's go! -Let's go!
I'm reminded of you everywhere I go.
How am I supposed to live?
Did you have to be so hard-working and diligent?
Did you have to be such perfect parents?
It's strangely quiet today.
Something isn't right.
It's finally over.
My cursed birthday.
Excuse me. Did you call for a designated driver?
-Yes. -I see.
PICKUP SPOT: DONGDAE BEACH
17 MINUTES AWAY YOUR DESIGNATED DRIVER: LEE TAE-SU
Who sent you?
Wrong question.
You should be asking why.
Don't you think so?
Don't you want to know why you're dying?
Ju Cheon-suk is the reason
you're going to die.
Where could my prey be tonight?
Someone so desperate,
lonely,
and scared
that they wouldn't hesitate to take my hand.
Found you.
Please, help…
Jeong Gu-won?
What is he doing here?
Could it be
that he's with him?
No, he's not with him.
My life feels as if it's shrouded in mist.
Who is a friend and who is a foe?
Or is everyone around me a foe?
I can't tell.
When I can't rely on
anything or anyone,
all I can do
is trust myself.
Help me.
Are you making a request this time?
Yes, please help me.
Fine.
But before that, you need to make a deal with me.
Don't you see that he's holding a knife?
Is this really the time to discuss a deal?
Nothing's free in this world.
All right.
What is it about?
There's a lot to cover. Do you really want to go over it now?
This isn't exactly tea time, is it?
It'd be crazy to enter into a deal with no information.
Suit yourself.
Fine! I'll be crazy.
It'd be crazy of me to help you before signing the contract,
but that guy creeps me out.
Hey.
Remember our deal?
I have to let go if I want to live.
Gu-won.
This is all because of that name, salvation.
It's gone.
We managed to get out alive.
I thought I was really going to…
What's this tattoo sticker?
-"Tattoo sticker"? -It won't come off.
It's on your wrist right now, but this tattoo is mine.
Are you out of your mind?
Do Do-hee the Nutjob.
Mirae Group's Chairwoman Ju took the orphaned Do Do-hee in.
Ju Cheon-suk is the reason you're going to die.
Are you sure you're not hiding anything?
I can't go to heaven, can I?
I'm extremely lethargic, and I feel like a different person.
I've never felt this way before.
Without your powers, does this mean you'll burn away?
I'm running out of time.
What could you do without your powers?
I'm going to do what I'm best at.
Bewitching humans.
Subtitle translation by: Min-jin Kim