♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my playful charm♪
♪Just to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for you♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 5=
=I'll Never Fall in Love with You Again=
(Li Group)
(Password)
Looks like I underestimated their firewall.
(Logging in)
(Li's Group's Internal Information System)
(Patient Database)
(Li Group has all patient data in Manlong.)
(This time,)
(Age Gender Male)
(I can find Xiaodi.)
(Not this one.)
(Not this either.)
(None of these match Xiaodi's info.)
(Xiaodi.)
(Where on earth are you?)
(A Total of 153 Candidates
Have Been Selected for You)
(003 Health Examination Form)
Blood type O.
RH negative.
Bone marrow DRB1*01:01.
What a pity.
Just another rare blood type patient
who needs a bone marrow transplant
like Xiaodi.
You're trying to leave me again?
Why would I?
I told you
I wouldn't leave you this time.
(After all, only your family)
(can help me find Xiaodi.)
Really?
♪You pull me under,
like a fire burning inside me♪
♪Beneath the black gown,
reborn as a prisoner♪
♪Your love, your rules♪
♪As the world falls, only you stay whole♪
♪Bound in life and death,
mad as doom gamblers♪
Remember what you said.
Even death won't make you leave me.
(Jiang Niannian.)
(This life,)
(I won't repeat the same mistake.)
♪You pull me under,
like a fire burning inside me♪
♪Beneath the black gown,
reborn as a prisoner♪
♪Your love, your rules♪
♪As the world falls, only you stay whole♪
♪Bound in life and death,
mad as doom gamblers♪
Where's Ye Lang?
Come in.
Ms. Jiang.
Ma'am asked you to change and have breakfast.
(It seems in this family,)
(not a single day is peaceful.)
(What an extravagant house.)
Ms. Jiang,
your outfit today
really suits your nature,
using your looks to get what you want.
Wasn't it Mrs. Liu who asked me to wear it?
I thought
Mrs. Liu wanted to show me
the Li family's standards.
That's for Ms. Murong Xue.
That's for the Second Young Master.
Then where do I sit?
Ms. Jiang,
you
grew up in a rough neighborhood,
so of course you don't understand
everyone has their proper place.
If you can't find yours,
then go back to where you came from.
Unless...
When Master gets here,
you serve him breakfast.
As long as Master accepts you,
then you'll naturally earn a seat
at the Li family table.
(A woman must know when to yield.)
(For Xiaodi,)
(I can put up with anything.)
(It's just a bowl of porridge.)
It's so hot.
Wait.
In our family,
when you serve elders porridge,
you can't put it down
without their permission.
So...
Ms. Jiang,
are you
giving up on joining us?
(As if I care about joining your family.)
(There's no one human here,)
(all monsters.)
(Maiden Liu, Servant of the Li Family)
Just wait here.
(How has Ye Lang lived all these years?)
(If not for finding my brother,)
(I would never tolerate this.)
(As expected of the top family in Manlong.)
(My first three husbands
had no such manners.)
Master.
For this morning's porridge,
I had the kitchen prepare broth
from century-old turtle shell.
A few days ago,
we received
glutinous rice from Myanmar,
so we made it with blood bird's nest.
To accompany it,
we have white caviar,
light and fresh,
very nourishing.
Just perfect.
Mm.
(This porridge)
(could cover Xiaodi's
hospital bills for years.)
No manners.
When serving the master,
you must kneel.
It's this outfit.
What are you doing?
Are you trying to burn Master?
Hurry, clean this up.
Come here.
Why is she here?
I'm sorry, Master.
It's all my fault.
I just thought
Young Master values Ms. Jiang,
so I had her serve your breakfast.
We're all family.
Get out.
Then I'll come serve you tomorrow.
This ointment works great on burns.
Thank you, Ms. Murong.
By the way,
do you know which hospital
in Manlong has the best neurosurgeon?
You should ask Lang.
He knows top medical experts
across the country.
I didn't see him this morning.
He didn't come to breakfast either.
Didn't he tell you?
He went to the office early
to prepare for tonight's auction banquet.
Auction banquet?
Mm.
An auction hosted by the Li family.
All of Manlong's elite,
wealthy families,
and medical industry leaders
will be there.
I heard a spot
was specially reserved for you.
You must dress up beautifully tonight.
Got it.
Thanks, Ms. Murong.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
The leading lady is in place.
Tonight,
there'll be a good show.
Miss,
your invitation, please.
Ye Lang invited me.
I'm his wife,
Jiang Niannian.
So you're Ms. Jiang.
I see your name on the guest list.
So can I go in now?
Of course.
But not through this entrance.
Not here.
Then where?
This is the guest entrance.
Aren't I a guest?
Ms. Jiang, you must be mistaken.
You're not a guest.
You're the auction item.
(It's a trap.)
I think you've got it wrong.
Ladies and gentlemen,
tonight's final item
is an absolute rarity.
Spend one night with her,
and you'll have no regrets.
Starting bid,
30 million.
Who'll be tonight's lucky one?
(Stay calm now that I'm here.)
(I'll find a way out later.)
40 million!
40 million.
Any higher?
45 million.
45 million!
Nobody outbid me.
50 million, she's mine.
The beauty's looking at me.
She's coming with me.
I bid 80 million.
80 million!
Top bid is now 80 million.
(Let's see who set this up.)
(Jiang Niannian.)
(Know your place.)
(You're just an auction showpiece.)
(And I)
(am the one who stands beside Ye Lang.)
(Jiang Qingqing, Jiang Niannian's Stepsister)
(Why her?)
(Jiang Qingqing.)
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪