[theme music playing]
LOVE NEXT DOOR
[playful music playing]
Oh.
It's like you've put
your soul into this cake.
Or did I imagine that?
No, you're right.
I mixed it in with the flour and sugar.
I knew it. You're going for an A plus.
But isn't this too much for us to eat?
We have someone to eat our leftovers.
[Mo-eum] What?
[girls clamoring]
[Mo-eum] We're too late.
He's on a serious upward trend these days.
His grades and popularity
have both improved.
-Mo-eum?
-Yeah?
This is how scary academic stress can be.
They've gone blind.
It must be really tough.
I pity them.
[girls continue clamoring]
[exclaims]
"Associate with."
To join someone or something.
"One's mind goes to something."
One's mind goes…
Don't read and walk.
You'll trip.
Even if I fall,
I'll learn another English word.
Who's forcing you to live like that?
This is your fault.
It's been a year since you quit swimming,
and you've already caught up to me.
You're the fourth-ranked student now.
Oh, that?
I raised a monster.
I should've shooed you away
when you asked me to teach you factoring.
But what are you going to do?
I've already mastered
calculus and geometry.
You mathematically suck.
It seemed like your class
had home economics today.
You have any leftover cake?
What? What you got earlier wasn't enough?
I ate it all.
That's so cheap.
I hope it goes to your thighs.
[scoffs]
Wow, are you trying to curse me
before my senior year? Take it back.
I said take it back.
You're not the only one.
I'll be a senior too.
You're a former athlete,
so you don't gain weight!
BELATED
[birds chirping]
What's with my eyes?
I think the fridge has sheet masks.
[quirky music playing]
[Seung-hyo] I took this from the back row.
It's today.
So what? I already answered him.
It's over then.
My goodness.
Hey! I told you not to
open the window looking like that.
Are you Shrek?
It's a mint chocolate sheet mask.
You want to die?
Just eat it instead.
Don't put it on your face.
-It's like putting lipstick on a pig.
-I don't need your input.
Even if they lock me up,
I'm going to kill you today.
[Mi-suk] Seok-ryu, come and eat!
I'll come too, Aunt Mi-suk!
What a crazy sight.
-Don't test me this early.
-[Seung-hyo] Goodness!
[Gyeong-jong] Let's get a divorce.
[Hye-suk] What?
I want a divorce.
A divorce?
That's kind of sudden.
Did you give this decision enough thought?
I've thought about it
for over 20 years.
It's not a surprise
that we ended up like this.
We've spent more time apart
than together in our marriage.
That's…
[sighs]
Yeah, you're right.
It was bound to end up like this.
It was just a matter
of who would say it first.
Let's talk about the details later.
I'm too tired today.
[solemn music playing]
[door opens]
-[door closes]
-She didn't even…
ask why.
[inhales]
[exhales]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Hye-suk] You were home.
I'm off today.
Didn't you say you had something
to say to me?
I'm being reassigned.
To where?
Africa.
Let me know
when you have the papers ready.
All right.
When should we tell Seung-hyo?
-Dig in.
-[Seok-ryu exclaiming]
I know I made it, but it's so good.
Isn't this too much?
I said I wanted my own bowl.
All of our spit will get in.
-It's so barbaric.
-You punk.
Who cares? We're all family here!
Clean your own room
before acting all clean.
-You're the one who lives in a pigsty.
-[Seok-ryu] What was that, you orangutan?
Thanks, Aunt Mi-suk.
-She's thankful too.
-Hey!
[Geun-sik] Mmm.
[Mi-suk] Mmm.
Wow, it's so good.
It's better than
the Michelin restaurant I went to before.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I don't know who that is,
but I bet I'm much better than him, right?
[chuckles]
[Geun-sik laughing]
What? You know who Michelin is?
-Mi-suk! [laughing]
-[Seok-ryu] I'm sure it was a joke.
You lied about being smart in school,
didn't you?
You said you were as smart as Hye-suk,
but you kept falling behind, right?
Don't eat. Give me your spoon.
-[Seok-ryu] Mom.
-[Mi-suk] Yeah?
-Did you add beans to this?
-[Geun-sik] You did?
No, the rice I used already had beans.
I told you a million times I hate beans.
Seok-ryu, they're good for you,
so just eat it. Okay?
You little punk!
-[Mi-suk] Jeez, you're so loud.
-You ate all the damn eggs.
Dad, I need protein.
Your aging dad
needs the protein more, you punk!
-Jeez, be quiet.
-[Dong-jin chuckles]
[Geun-sik chuckles]
-Mom?
-[Mi-suk] Yeah?
Am I chewing on anchovies right now?
-Anchovies?
-I had leftover side dishes to clear out.
Putting anchovies in bibimbap
is like committing a cardinal sin!
It's hard to eat around it too.
They're so small.
Give me your spoons.
No one can eat except for Seung-hyo.
Don't be like that.
-Hold on.
-I worked hard to make this.
[Seok-ryu] Thank you for the meal.
-[Mi-suk] Hey.
-Yeah?
Dong-jin, I love seeing you eat food
instead of that shake.
-[Dong-jin] I'll drink it later.
-[Seok-ryu] Eat these beans.
[Mi-suk] You need protein too.
[Geun-sik] You put everything
you wanted to toss out.
[all laughing]
[pleasant music playing]
Why are you studying French?
[Seok-ryu] It's a French cookbook.
The drawings were pretty, so I bought it.
But I have no idea what it says.
Blanquette de veau is veal stew.
It's a famous French home-style dish.
Hey, you haven't forgotten your French?
I bet I could still read that.
Then why haven't you spoken it?
Then, should I go around saying,
"Bonjour, mademoiselle"?
That was so gross.
I would've stopped being your friend.
Hey. Read this for me.
It's so thick. It'll take forever.
No, not all of it. Just a little.
Read this page first.
How bothersome.
[phone beeps]
[speaking French]
[in Korean] Blanquette de veau
is a dish that symbolizes
French home-style cooking.
[speaking French]
[in Korean] Common ingredients are used,
and it's easy to prepare.
[speaking French]
[in Korean] The finished dish
boasts a sophisticated flavor.
Oh.
[Seung-hyo in Korean]
Coq au vin means "rooster in wine."
With chicken and vegetables
braised in wine,
it's a traditional French dish.
[pleasant music continues playing]
[chuckles softly]
[closes book]
[groans softly]
[Seung-hyo exhales]
So… I woke up,
and your face was so close to mine.
But there suddenly was
a rainbow right there.
It was so interesting.
I couldn't help but touch it.
It's hot.
What?
[amusing music playing]
Gosh, I almost got heatstroke
while volunteering my services.
You asked me to read you the book,
and you fall asleep?
Well, that was because…
Tell your mom I'll put up
an awning here soon.
Why did the rainbow have to appear there?
Where is the light shining from?
That's odd.
[clears throat]
[breathing heavily]
[thuds]
-Hey!
-[Seung-hyo grunting]
Hey, is your skull okay?
Is it broken?
[groans] What was that?
What were you doing? Are you okay?
[grunts]
-[Mo-eum] Gosh, don't be such a crybaby.
-[groans softly]
That's strange.
Hey.
I'm saying this
as an on-site medical professional.
[grunts]
You'll be fine. You won't die.
[Seung-hyo groans]
If I develop aftereffects,
I'll call 119… No.
-I'm going to call the cops on you.
-[Mo-eum scoffs]
It looked like you needed
the cops earlier.
What do you mean?
I mean, your face was red.
What?
Did something happen with Seok-ryu?
Nothing happened.
Darn. I was excited for nothing.
Was Seok-ryu okay yesterday?
I heard Hyeon-jun left.
[amusing music playing]
Did I cry too much?
Did I look like someone who had regrets?
Is that why he isn't bringing up the milk?
She cried so much.
I didn't want to pressure her.
Forcing her to answer seems wrong.
So you're taking another step back?
She already has a lot on her mind.
I don't want to make it worse.
-Drink this.
-No, thanks.
Jeez, just drink it.
This is more refreshing than beer
when you're feeling frustrated.
You'll feel much better afterwards.
-Drink up.
-[soda pops]
Goodness.
-Are you okay? Sorry.
-You shook it on purpose.
For crying out loud.
[Mo-eum] Are you okay?
Do I look okay?
[Mo-eum] Sorry.
[exclaims]
It's refreshing.
[Mo-eum] I know.
If only there was a catalyst
like this for you and Seok-ryu,
there would be zero worries.
Things would feel
refreshing, crisp, and clean.
[sighs]
[exclaims]
What are you doing?
-Hey.
-[Mo-eum exclaims]
-[Seung-hyo] Hey.
-[Mo-eum] No.
-My gosh!
-[Seung-hyo] What on earth?
[thuds]
-Hey… Where are you going?
-[exclaims]
[Seung-hyo] Mo-eum!
Jeez.
Mr. Kang.
Mr. Choi.
I've said it before,
but she really is nice.
I know.
Would you like to sit down?
I was going somewhere,
but I can sit for a moment.
Here.
[Dan-ho exhales]
[amusing music playing]
-You must've been really hot.
-Yes.
[chuckling] Well,
I haven't seen you in a while,
so it feels…
a little awkward.
-Yeah, me too.
-[chuckles awkwardly]
Still, you're a neighborhood friend.
Also, we're the same age.
You even listened to my problems.
How about we drop the formalities?
Sounds good.
Then, should we casually
call each other by our names?
Yes. No, wait.
Yeah, Dan-ho.
Okay, Seung-hyo.
[children speaking indistinctly]
[soda pops]
-Should we go back to how things were?
-That's a good idea. [sighs]
[chuckling] Yes. Right?
[music ends]
[exhales]
[pleasant music playing]
[sighs]
[pop song playing]
EXPIRATION DATE JUNE 29
[sighs]
CHOISSEUNG
[song continues playing]
It's past the date.
It's over.
DAEHAN MILK
[Myeong-u exclaims]
[sighs]
That's right.
I received a personal request.
The pianist Ko Sang-hee
wants to open a bookstore.
-[Na-yun] Isn't she really famous?
-Yeah.
Why does a pianist want to open
a bookstore?
She's always liked books.
Her dream is to open one in her hometown.
That whole area is a field of flowers.
She wants a place
that not only goes well with that
but also features a special theme.
-[Seung-hyo] Mmm.
-Does anyone have an idea? Anything good?
-Come on.
-[Na-yun exclaims]
-Where is it?
-Taebaek, Gangwon Province.
What if the building becomes music?
What?
We'll make a building
that creates sound.
We'll use the wind to turn the building
into an instrument.
-[all exclaiming]
-A bookstore built for a pianist.
But would that be realistically possible?
The risk is…
Overseas, there have been times
when sound was used in the design.
Hyeong-chan,
are you going to the site later?
-Yes.
-On your way back, buy me a recorder.
-A recorder?
-[Seung-hyo] Yeah.
I saw it somewhere.
If you cover different holes
on a recorder, it will alter the pitch.
-There's a way to calculate that.
-[all exclaiming]
I think I need to play it myself
and see how we can apply that
to the building.
-Taebaek, Gangwon Province.
-[keyboard clacking]
[exhales]
My goodness.
Look at his eyes. He's lost it.
[Na-yun] I love that look in his eyes.
A handsome lunatic obsessed with work.
A cute lunatic obsessed with Seung-hyo.
-I'll get going.
-[Myeong-u] Okay.
-Don't forget the recorder.
-Okay.
[phone vibrating]
Hello?
[Hye-suk] Seung-hyo, are you free tonight?
What? Why?
Let's have dinner together as a family.
I see.
Okay.
Then, I'll make reservations. Okay.
I'll see you later.
[line disconnects]
POUR THE BOILING BEEF BROTH INTO THE ROUX
[door opens]
[door closes]
[sniffing]
[Seok-ryu] Oh…
I thought you two went to work,
so I used the kitchen for a little bit.
[sniffs] What are you making?
It smells good.
It's a French dish.
I'm just trying to mimic it.
You want to cook that badly?
Yeah.
The more I try it,
the more I want to do it.
It's fun and exciting.
[Geun-sik] Still,
I wish you wouldn't do this.
It's hard enough for a healthy person.
I wonder how you'll manage.
[Mi-suk] I feel the same way.
Stress is poison for your stomach.
You know from watching your dad
it's not an easy job.
I understand how you feel.
But I'll take care of myself.
I'll eat well, and I'll work out
to increase my stamina.
I promise not to get sick.
[clicks tongue]
[sniffles]
Quit right away if it gets hard.
[Mi-suk] That's right.
If it gets hard,
quit and just hang out at home.
You think we can't take care of you?
-Right, honey?
-You did well.
Whoa, I'm touched.
[Watch on www.kisskh.la or www.kisskh.co to support Admin]
You promised, Mom.
You have to take care of me.
Okay. [clears throat]
Hang out, and if you get bored,
you can just get a job.
There's Saemsong Electronics.
-And there's Kekeo.
-[Geun-sik] There she goes again.
-She's at it again.
-Right?
That's the Mom I know.
She knows how to ruin the mood.
I'm just saying.
It's just in case you feel bored
and restless to death.
-Honey, how does it taste?
-It's good.
-[Mi-suk] Really? Let me try some.
-[chuckles]
[Dan-ho] Yeon-du, did something happen
at kindergarten today?
You don't look happy.
Today, A-ron said to me…
I didn't have a mom.
I bet that upset you.
So what did you do?
I did what you taught me.
I said not all families
have a mom and dad.
I said it's an ideology created by society
about what they think
"normal families" should be.
You did great.
But they're dumb,
so they don't know what ideology is.
Dad, are you sure
you can keep leaving work early like this?
Your babysitter hurt her back,
so she can't come anymore.
I have no choice
until I find a new babysitter.
When is the new babysitter coming?
[Dan-ho] I don't know.
No one has applied yet.
[Jae-suk] How about…
if I do it?
[amusing music playing]
Ms. Jae-suk!
Hey, Mo-eum.
-Mo-eum!
-Hey, Yeon-du. [chuckles nervously]
[Jae-suk] Hey, I'm glad you're here.
Watch the office for a second.
I'm taking Yeon-du out for some ice cream.
No, that's fine. I'll buy it.
No, I want to buy it for her.
Let's go, Yeon-du.
-Okay!
-[Dan-ho] I'll go too then.
I'd really like to go!
Your dad's a bit overprotective.
Are you sure
you can trust me to watch her?
Who's watching who? You?
Yeah, I'm going to
look after Yeon-du for now.
-[sighs]
-You really don't have to.
Come on. What are neighbors for?
We're here to help one another.
Just wait here for a bit.
-I'll be back.
-[Jae-suk] Bye.
-Let's go.
-[Mo-eum] Mom.
-[chuckles nervously] Mom.
-Yeon-du…
[Mo-eum] Mom…
[amusing music playing]
[exhales]
[chuckles nervously]
I'm sorry about before!
After what happened to Seok-ryu…
and after hearing your story,
I must've been swept up by emotions.
I think it was a type
of temporary insanity.
I'm sorry too.
No matter how sudden it was,
I was wrong for failing to avoid it.
Well…
Right.
I was more at fault here.
How about we agree it was
a mutual mistake made by both of us?
-I fully agree.
-[Mo-eum] Okay.
-Good.
-[Dan-ho] Yes.
[sighs deeply]
Okay.
-Also…
-Yes?
I declined your mother's offer
to watch Yeon-du.
No, it's okay.
That's between you and my mom.
Don't worry about me.
Thank you. I'll try to find
a new babysitter as soon as possible.
[exclaims softly]
-[Yeon-du] Dad!
-Hey.
Dad, she bought me a ton of ice cream.
You're so lucky. Did you thank her?
I turned on the air conditioning.
Why is it so hot?
-It's steaming hot. What's going on?
-[Mo-eum exhales]
[AC blows faster]
[lounge music playing in the background]
How's the food?
I came here with our client last time.
I liked it.
Yeah, it's nice.
Yeah, it's good.
That's a relief.
It's usually hard
to get a reservation here.
Thankfully, someone canceled,
and they had one spot left. [chuckles]
I see.
To be honest, we asked you to dinner
because we had something to tell you.
[clears throat]
[exclaims softly]
What is it?
I was reassigned.
I see.
Where are you going?
How long is it for this time?
Africa. It's going to be for a while.
Africa…
If I can, I'll take time off to visit.
It'd be nice if you could go too, Dad.
Seung-hyo. [exhales]
We're getting a divorce.
What?
Our marriage fell apart a long time ago.
We've decided there's no point
in forcing ourselves to be together.
[slow music playing]
[Hye-suk] We think ending things here
would be the best for everyone.
Seung-hyo, all I can say is I'm sorry.
We hope you'll understand.
What's there for me to understand?
It's your lives.
Don't worry about me. Do what you want.
I'm sorry.
I forgot about something urgent today.
I'll get going.
[slow music continues playing]
[sighs deeply]
[Gyeong-jong] You're really
going to Africa?
So you don't care about me or Seung-hyo?
You're the one
who has no respect for my career.
You think leaving your family
to go off alone for years makes sense?
Family?
You have no right to say that.
You pretty much live at that hospital
and rarely come home.
When Seung-hyo and I were in France,
you came to see us only once.
So I'm telling you
to stay in Korea!
My goodness.
-[sighs]
-[phone ringing]
Let's discuss this again later.
-Hello?
-[Se-hwan] It's me.
Can you talk?
[Hye-suk] No, I'm sorry.
I'll call you back later.
Yeah, sorry. Bye.
-Who was that?
-The colleague I'm going with.
I have a work call.
You sure it's for work?
And not another reason for wanting to go?
What does that mean?
You had the chance
to be assigned elsewhere.
But there are civil wars
and always talk of terrorism there!
Why are you bent
on going somewhere so dangerous?
Because Koreans live there too.
Why do this job if it's only to go
to safe and comfortable countries?
So it's solely a sense of duty?
Is that why a woman with a child
would be this stubborn?
[screaming]
Seriously! That's enough!
I'm so sick of this!
-Hye-suk!
-[Hye-suk] What?
You want me to stay home,
raise our child, and do housework?
You should've married a woman
who'd support you instead of me.
Is that all you can say?
I should've never married you
to begin with.
No, I should've never had Seung-hyo.
-Hey!
-You clipped my wings!
You've trapped me here with a child!
If only Seung-hyo wasn't around,
this wouldn't have happened to me.
I love Seung-hyo,
but I can't live as just a mom.
[Hye-suk exclaims]
Seung-hyo.
[exclaims]
[sighs wearily]
[solemn music playing]
[sighs]
[Seung-hyo] Ratatouille is
a representative dish
of the Provence region.
Add herbs and olive oil to eggplants,
zucchini, bell peppers, and tomatoes.
Simmer it into a vegetable stew.
-[Seok-ryu] Ratatouille was a good movie.
-[Seung-hyo] I'm leaving.
[Seok-ryu] Keep going.
[Seung-hyo speaking French]
[phone vibrating]
CHOISSEUNG
Why is he calling me this late?
[clears throat]
Hello?
Sorry?
[mellow music playing]
[sighs]
-Hey, Choisseung.
-[Seung-hyo groans]
-Hey, get up.
-Okay.
Are you the girl
I spoke with on the phone?
Yes.
Well, this young man was drinking alone
and he suddenly passed out.
I had a strong feeling this would happen.
He looked very troubled.
He kept drinking with tears in his eyes.
I tried waking him, but he wouldn't budge.
So what could I do?
I pressed the first number
he had on speed dial, and it called you.
Thank you for calling.
-Hey, let's go.
-[Seung-hyo groans]
-Try to get up.
-[grunts]
-[Seung-hyo groans]
He hasn't paid yet.
What?
[Seung-hyo groans]
Are you kidding me?
[mellow music continues playing]
-Goodness.
-[Seok-ryu] Where's your wallet?
[sighs wearily]
How much is it?
Damn it. You just had to order
two dishes you didn't even eat.
[groans]
I can't go any further!
Not even if my life depended on it!
-[Seung-hyo groans]
-[groans]
Whether you spend the night here
or sober up and go home,
you figure it out.
I'm exhausted.
[drunkenly] I'm not going home.
[in normal voice] Hey, are you waking up?
[exhales]
[Seok-ryu sighs]
[breathes deeply]
I said I'm not going home.
Stop being such a drunk.
You're going to sleep here then?
[drunkenly] Hey.
Tonight,
I had dinner
with my mom and dad.
[in normal voice] So what?
[drunkenly] Well…
It was the first time
since I graduated college.
Your family does it all the time.
You all have meals together.
But for me,
it was the hardest thing to do.
And I did that today, but…
[chuckles softly] Never mind.
[breathes deeply]
We didn't even finish our meal.
[slow music playing]
Hey.
Every time I go to your house,
there's something I really envy.
Your family picture.
In our house,
we have everything…
except for that.
No, that's not it.
We look like we have everything.
But we have nothing.
Choisseung.
[slow music continues playing]
My parents are getting a divorce.
What?
I was always scared…
that this day would come.
When I was six or seven…
[sighs] …and when I was 18…
[chuckles] But…
I'm 34 now.
It happened later than I expected.
[laughs]
[sighs]
[slow music continues playing]
But I'm still scared.
Even though I'm an adult now,
why does my parents' divorce still hurt?
My mom and dad…
I know they have their own lives.
But…
Instead of being happy apart…
I still wish they were happy together.
[sighs]
[sobbing]
[groans softly]
[groans]
[Seok-ryu] Are you sober now?
What's going on?
What happened?
-What are you doing here?
-[sighs]
-Why am I here?
-[Seok-ryu sighs]
[bangs table] Give it to me.
-What?
-Transport and medical expenses.
I had to drag you here from a tent bar
and almost broke my back.
Also, your bill was 47,000 won. Give it.
[groans softly]
Okay, I'll pay you back.
-Do you want it now?
-Forget it.
Do you have a headache? Do you want water?
Yeah, I have a splitting headache.
[groans softly]
Where's the water? Why aren't you…
[Seok-ryu] Hey,
why didn't you toss this out?
It's expired.
This will give you an upset stomach.
[mellow music playing]
Right.
[grunts] I forgot
that I was going to throw it away.
[groans softly]
-[Seung-hyo gulping water]
-[sighs]
[exclaims]
[exhales]
I remember drinking.
But I didn't do anything stupid, right?
You almost did something really stupid.
What?
Tell your mom and dad
how you really feel.
Don't cry alone like when you were seven
after your mom left.
"Don't go." Why is that so hard to say?
Let's go. I'm sober now.
You've been nagging me
all this time to lean on you.
But why won't you lean on me?
I did lean on you.
[Seok-ryu] What?
You held me up on the way here.
You have so much strength.
You were born with it.
I should've just left you for dead
in the streets, you little…
Straighten your collar, you klutz.
[chuckles softly]
This was because of you.
SEOUL FAMILY COURT
[Gyeong-jong] I didn't know the mandatory
waiting period would take a month.
We have to appear in court again.
What are you going to do?
I'll take time off and come back.
-[thunder rumbling]
-[rain pattering]
It's raining.
I have an umbrella.
On our wedding day
and when we registered our marriage,
it rained.
It did.
That's why everyone thought
we'd be happy together.
[slow music playing]
How did we end up like this?
I don't remember fighting all that much.
We didn't even have a chance to fight.
Are you blaming me?
I'm blaming myself.
Take it.
No, wait…
[sucking air through teeth]
Gosh.
I'm sure there's at least one.
[Mi-suk] What? You're leaving tomorrow?
[Hye-suk] It just turned out that way.
It's urgent.
Hey, but still,
there's no reason to be so sudden.
Wait, let me call Jae-suk and In-suk.
-I'll tell them to come.
-Stop.
Please! Don't make such a fuss.
I saw them a few days ago anyway.
I'll be back soon.
Yeah, but still…
Here. These are some cosmetics.
Share it with the others.
It's from France.
Apply it generously,
and don't age while I'm gone.
You brat.
You better call often when you get there.
Call me when you crave kimchi
and when you want to speak Korean.
Call me if anything troubles you, okay?
Fine, I will.
[Mi-suk] Why is it so sudden though?
-[door closes]
-[Seok-ryu] Aunt Hye-suk.
Seok-ryu, were you home?
-I thought I wasn't going to see you.
-Me too.
I would've been sad if you just left.
[chuckles softly]
[exhales]
Seok-ryu, you've been through so much.
[slow music playing]
But I'm not worried about you.
I know you'll do well.
I've always been grateful for
how well you've looked after Seung-hyo.
Check in on him from time to time
while I'm away, okay?
Go on in. Bye.
Goodness. I'm off now. Bye.
Aunt Hye-suk.
Seung-hyo's sad.
Seung-hyo…
has always been waiting
for his mom since he was a kid.
He was like a kid
in a never-ending game of hide-and-seek.
He hid so no one could find him.
But I think he was waiting
for his mom to find him.
Thanks for telling me.
[siren blaring]
[dramatic music playing]
The paramedics are here.
Where's the patient?
[muffled voice] I have a piece
of raw octopus stuck in my throat!
The suckers are stuck to your throat.
We have to get it out.
Open your mouth.
[man] She ate a poisonous mushroom!
Why would she eat that here?
[lady] Over here!
She's been bitten
by a blue-ringed octopus!
A blue-ringed octopus in the mudflats?
[breathing heavily]
What do I do?
I can't do this on my own.
[whimpering]
[Mo-eum exclaims]
I LOVE YOU, MUDFLATS
[exclaims]
Dan-ho?
[heroic music playing]
MFM
Mudflat Man!
[heroic music continues playing]
You take care of the poisonous mushroom.
I'll handle the raw octopus.
[both exclaiming]
[Mo-eum exclaiming]
[exclaiming]
[man grunts]
[Mo-eum] Mudflat Man.
We still have the blue-ringed octopus.
Blue-ringed octopus have
deadly venom containing tetrodotoxin.
We must move her now.
[exclaims softly]
[seagulls squawk]
[mellow music playing]
All of this wouldn't have been possible
without you, Mudflat Man.
[exclaims softly]
[grunts]
[gasps]
You damn lunatic.
[exhales]
I really must be insane.
Yeah, I've lost my mind.
[breathing heavily]
Yeon-du!
-Mo-eum!
-[gasps]
Are you staying
at our house starting today?
You should've woken me up.
I heard you worked last night
and got home this morning.
You need to sleep well
to rescue people.
You're the only one who worries about me.
But where's my mom? Why are you alone?
I'm right here.
-Are you going somewhere?
-Yeah, and you're coming too.
[thrilling music playing]
[chuckles]
[Mo-eum chuckles]
[music ends]
[Jae-suk exclaims]
Yeon-du.
When you go to a bathhouse,
eating seaweed soup and sikhye is a must.
This is wisdom
that's passed down from an elder.
Make sure to remember that.
-Oh?
-[Yeon-du] Mmm.
Don't forget
these stone-cooked eggs either.
-[Jae-suk] You're right.
-Want me to peel it for you?
I can do it.
Goodness, she's so smart.
Ms. Do! Over here!
Goodness! Hey!
Wait, I'll be right back.
My goodness, I don't believe this!
-You're all here!
-[indistinct chatter]
You know how to do it.
You crushed it hard.
[lady] Do you want to eat eggs or chips?
-[kid] Chips.
-Chips? Okay!
Here it comes! Whoosh!
So yummy!
[mellow music playing]
Yeon-du.
Want to see something cool?
All right.
Usually, when you come to a bathhouse,
this is a must too, but I forgot.
Here.
Ta-da! A lamb's head towel hat!
My gosh! You're so cute!
Look. She's got one too.
You're eating so well!
Want me to peel you some eggs?
[Yeon-du] I wasn't looking
because of this.
[Mo-eum] What?
I looked because she has a mom
and I was envious.
I don't have a mom.
[Mo-eum] What do you mean
you don't have a mom?
In your pretty face,
I can see your dad and your mom too.
Yeon-du.
Everyone goes on that trip one day.
Your mom just left a little early.
Hmm.
My dad left for that trip early too.
In return, he sent me a lot of friends
so I wouldn't be lonely.
-Really?
-Yeah.
[gasps] Maybe your mom and my dad
met on their trip.
So on the day
you were looking for crop circles,
maybe they brought us together
so that we could have fun together.
So we could become good friends!
I have fun hanging out with you.
Me too.
From now on, let's have fun together.
Let's have a blast every day.
-Okay.
-[exclaims]
All right. How about we have some fun now?
I'll peel one too.
[Hye-suk] It's been hard
to see you lately.
You haven't been home for a few days.
Yeah.
I just came for some clothes.
I have to go.
I see. [chuckles softly]
Well…
The thing is…
I'm leaving tomorrow.
Okay, have a safe trip.
I'll keep in touch often.
I'll call and text you.
Your birthday's at the end of the year--
You don't have to.
When I'd hear that as a kid,
I looked forward to it.
I waited.
There were days when I needed you.
But not anymore.
[slow music playing]
Seung-hyo.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[exhales]
[slow music continues playing]
[door closes]
[Seung-hyo] What are you doing?
Why are you in my office
and sitting there like that?
Why did you wash your hair at work?
Did you stay out all night?
I was busy with work.
But why are you here? What's up?
I have something to give you.
[Mi-suk] Hey, Seok-ryu!
It's not cooked! You can't eat that!
You want to go to the hospital?
Have some lettuce.
Dong-jin, stop running around
and come here.
It's hot.
-Do we have to eat on the rooftop?
-You have to fight fire with fire.
And it's nice. The atmosphere's great too.
[Geun-sik] Gyeong-jong, the bags under
your eyes are drooping all the way down.
I know. He looks like a raccoon.
They'd mistake you for a friend.
-[both laughing]
-I came straight from the night shift.
Goodness, shouldn't you
get some sleep then?
We cluelessly invited you.
No, it's fine.
[Geun-sik] Yeah, fatigue can't be relieved
with just sleep.
You have to have fun
with family like this.
That's how you relax.
Yes, you're right.
It's nice being together like this.
[Geun-sik] I heard you two couldn't go
on vacation because you were so busy.
Think of this as a vacation spot, okay?
[chuckles]
[Mi-suk] Let's take a picture.
We have some film left, right?
-Forget it. Why take pictures?
-No, it'll be a keepsake.
-You look nice today too.
-Don't.
-Just take a picture.
-It's so lame.
-Seung-hyo, sit with your parents.
-Come here.
[Geun-sik] Let's take one as a keepsake.
Okay.
Goodness, you look miserable.
-[Hye-suk] Is this right? We're eating.
-[Geun-sik] Smile. Get closer.
Hey, smile!
-[Mi-suk] Seung-hyo.
-All right. Smile.
-One, two, three. Cheese! There you go!
-[chuckles softly]
[camera shutter clicks]
[mellow music playing]
[Seok-ryu] I was cleaning out my room,
and I just happened
to come across it by coincidence.
Thanks.
You have one too now. A family picture.
[breathes deeply]
Hey. You sure you don't have to
go to the airport to see your mom off?
You know when her flight is?
[Seung-hyo] No.
Wouldn't your dad know?
-I'll call him.
-[phone vibrating]
FATHER
Hello, I was just about to call you.
What?
She did?
[sirens wailing distantly]
Dad.
What happened?
I just got the call too.
We found Seo Hye-suk's suitcase
at the terminal.
It was taken
to the lost and found center at first.
It had a Ministry of Foreign Affairs tag,
so it was brought here.
Her departure's today.
She was on her way to the airport.
[officer] I see.
I'll try calling her.
[line ringing]
[phone ringing]
[officer] We tried to call her too.
We think her phone's in here.
-[officer 2] Officer Kim?
-Yes, sir?
Just a moment.
[serious music playing]
If she lost her suitcase and phone,
isn't she in big trouble then?
All of her contacts would be on her phone.
Do you know the combination on her lock?
Her birthday is June 17.
It didn't work.
Try your birthday and your dad's.
[Seung-hyo] Okay.
[sighs]
[Seok-ryu] It opened!
What are those numbers?
Their wedding anniversary.
[inhales]
[slow music playing]
[exhales]
Where do you think she is?
Is there any way to reach her?
SE-HWAN
[line ringing]
[phone vibrating]
Hey. Did you arrive yet?
[Gyeong-jong] Hello?
-Who is this?
-Choi Gyeong-jong.
[Se-hwan] Hello.
I'll explain
why I have my wife's phone later.
Do you know where she is right now?
-What?
-[Gyeong-jong] Did she reach the airport?
The airport?
She's departing for her new post today.
I don't know when her flight is.
What new post?
She's decided to retire. Didn't you know?
What?
I guess she didn't tell you.
I don't know
if I should be telling you this,
but Hye-suk's been acting strange lately.
-[gasps]
-[chuckles]
What's with the flowers?
It's to celebrate your retirement
and hard work over the years.
Retirement? Who's retiring?
-What?
-Gosh.
I love the scent of lily of the valleys.
But who's retiring?
Well… [chuckles nervously]
I almost forgot.
When are you going to reassign me?
I'll grab a meeting with the minister
if you don't tell me soon.
Hye-suk…
What are you doing? You're scaring me.
They're so pretty.
I had told her
she wouldn't be reassigned anymore.
She clearly accepted it too.
But she couldn't remember that.
It was like she was hearing it
for the first time.
[breath trembling]
[inhales]
I have to find her quickly.
Do you know where she could've gone?
[In-suk whimpering]
[crying] She's so cruel.
How can she leave without saying goodbye?
The Ice Princess lived up to her name.
How could she just leave a gift and go?
She said she was sorry
and that she'd call soon.
Then, does that mean we can open this now?
But isn't this Chatin?
This is expensive.
Wait! [laughing]
Hey, I'm an expert in cosmetics too.
[Mi-suk] Is this a cream?
Let's see what it says.
-"Suble…"
-[Jae-suk] Toner?
-[Mi-suk] I think it's sunscreen.
-[In-suk] "Suble…"
Damn it!
Hey, this is the land of Hangul!
Why the hell would they use
these squiggly letters?
Hey, I'll call Hye-suk later.
No, I'll ask Seok-ryu later.
Jeez, I can't even see it.
Gosh. Hey, Seung-hyo! Seok-ryu!
I'm glad you're here.
[voice shaking] Aunt Mi-suk, do you know
where my mom went?
-What?
-Please find her for me.
[melancholy music playing]
[birds chirping]
[Hye-suk] But what caused it to break?
[mechanic] I found this inside the washer.
Goodness.
Wait.
Saffron.
You consume so much medicine,
and you still don't know that?
What?
It's not saffron.
-Are you sure it's not saponin?
-[In-suk] Yeah, it is.
I thought it was saponin too.
You left a magazine
written in English in my bag.
A magazine?
I never did that.
Retirement? Who's retiring?
[sighs]
[slow music playing]
[exhales]
I'm sure I had my phone with me.
You can easily confuse the two.
[voice shaking] Yeah.
And they're about the same size.
You can confuse them.
[exhales]
Where did my suitcase go?
[gasps]
Why am I up here?
[exhales]
Damn it.
[slow music continues playing]
[exclaims softly]
[screams]
[Se-hwan] We spoke yesterday.
She was going
to the mountains for some air.
I'm not sure where that would be.
[Mi-suk] The only mountain Hye-suk
could've gone to is Gajeongsan,
where we visited the temple last time.
Dad, it's this way.
Hello.
I'm sorry,
but did you see this person here?
Yes, I saw her earlier.
She came alone.
Where did you see her?
She sat over there for a long time.
-[Gyeong-jong] Thank you.
-Thank you.
She saw her earlier,
so I think she's already left.
[sighs wearily]
Let's go.
Mom wrote this.
It's her handwriting.
[serious music playing]
To be honest, I'm a Catholic.
But since Buddha has
great compassion and mercy,
could you please grant my wish?
Please don't let me forget
my husband and son.
PLEASE DON'T LET ME FORGET
MY HUSBAND AND SON
Mr. Choi, I think she already left,
so don't worry.
Hey, Choisseung.
When we make it down, let's search
restaurants, hotels, and other terminals.
Okay.
Dad, this is Mom's shoe.
[Gyeong-jong] What?
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Do you think something happened to her?
We should look in this area.
But it leads to a cliff down there.
And it's getting dark.
-I'll go down.
-I'll go.
If there's an emergency,
I'd be better prepared than you.
Then, let's go down together.
No, I'll make my way down from the top.
You two come up
through the hiking trail.
[breathes deeply]
Seung-hyo, I promise
I'll find your mom.
Be careful.
[tense music playing]
Let's go look for her.
Hey, be careful!
Sorry.
This won't do.
You're being too hasty.
You could get really hurt.
Grab my hand, and let's go slow.
Don't worry. She'll be fine.
She's the smartest member of Lavender.
Right.
[Seok-ryu] Let's go.
Let's find your mom.
Hye-suk!
Hye-suk? Hye-suk!
-[Hye-suk groans softly]
-[Gyeong-jong grunts]
Hye-suk, wake up.
Hye-suk.
Are you awake?
Honey.
Can you hear me?
[weakly] Yeah.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Are you hurt? Were you hurt anywhere?
[exclaiming in pain]
My leg.
I sprained my ankle.
It started to get dark,
and no one was around.
I wanted to call for help,
but I didn't have my phone.
Why did you come here alone?
-[crying]
-Why didn't you tell me anything?
Why did you lie about getting reassigned?
I thought it'd put your mind at ease.
No.
No, that's a lie.
[sniffles]
I wanted to protect my pride.
I didn't want to be abandoned.
Why would I abandon you?
I knew you weren't in love
with me anymore,
but I wanted to hold on
to even just your shadow.
I've spent decades watching you leave.
That's not true.
Every time I went to you,
you kept moving further away.
I was the one
always shuffling towards you.
I missed you.
When you were in France,
when you were in Africa,
when you were at home in Korea,
I always missed you.
[chuckles softly]
Why could we never say things like this?
How did we end up here?
Goodness.
[Hye-suk sobbing]
-[sniffles]
-[Seung-hyo] Mom!
Dad!
Seung-hyo!
[Seok-ryu] Mr. Choi! Aunt Hye-suk!
-[Hye-suk] Seok-ryu.
-Are you okay?
You came too.
Seung-hyo, it's okay. [chuckles softly]
I'm not that hurt. I'm sorry.
-Did I scare you?
-[exhales]
[Hye-suk] Seung-hyo.
[voice shaking] Why are you
doing this to me?
The divorce.
Deciding to leave
without even consulting me…
Why won't you two ask me?
Why?
Why don't you care about how I feel?
I'd beg Santa Claus every Christmas.
[whimpering]
"I won't cry."
[slow music playing]
"I'll be good."
"So…"
"So please give me back my mom."
[exclaims]
[Seung-hyo] "So…
please let me have
a meal with my mom and dad."
Do you… [breath trembling]
Do you know how hard I tried
to be a good kid?
But I'm an adult now.
I don't even want to care
about stuff like that!
But…
when I see you two,
I still go back
to that day when I was seven.
[breath trembling]
I've spent my whole life stuck there.
Even though I've grown up,
like a fool…
I still…
want to share a meal with my mom and dad.
[in normal voice] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Seung-hyo.
[Hye-suk] Seung-hyo.
I'm so sorry.
I thought you hated me.
I can't just live as a mom.
[pop song playing]
[Hye-suk exclaims]
Seung-hyo.
[exclaims]
[voice shaking] Seung-hyo.
I'm really sorry.
I must've lost my mind earlier.
I didn't mean it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Seung-hyo.
[whimpering]
I love you.
I love you so much.
I've made so many mistakes.
You were always…
so much more comfortable
around Mi-suk than me.
You're right.
I am more comfortable with her.
But still…
Even still…
I always…
[whimpering]
I always missed you.
[Hye-suk exclaims]
[sobbing]
[mellow music playing]
[continues sobbing]
Let's go home, Mom.
I still need you.
[Hye-suk sobbing]
Seung-hyo, I'm so sorry.
I made you feel so lonely, didn't I?
I'm so sorry.
But I love you so much.
[sobbing]
[Hye-suk] Don't cry, Seung-hyo.
I won't leave you alone again.
I love you so much. I'm sorry.
[both sobbing]
[pleasant music playing]
[Seung-hyo] Dad, are you okay?
I'll carry her.
[Hye-suk] Yeah.
She's my wife.
I'll carry her.
[whispering] Take a hint
and stay out of it.
I see.
[in normal voice] Aren't I heavy?
Not at all.
You're as light as a feather.
-No, you're as light as air.
-[chuckles]
[Hye-suk] Stop it.
I've thought about this for a while,
but they really suit each other.
Did you call?
No, they're coming now.
-There they come!
-Where?
[In-suk] Hye-suk!
[Mi-suk] My goodness! You brat!
-[Hye-suk] Wait.
-[Mi-suk] Hey!
Do you know how worried we were?
[Jae-suk] Gosh, we thought
something had happened!
[In-suk] Hey, drink this first!
This medicine is the best
for calming nerves.
Stop it!
Why are you all out here this late?
Don't cause a fuss. Go home.
Goodness.
-Hey. You really want us to leave?
-Yeah.
We don't even get an emotional hug?
Forget it. I'm hot and sticky.
I need to take a shower.
-Honey, help me.
-Okay.
Thank you for today. Get home safely.
[all] Good night.
My goodness.
-Thanks. Go home.
-Hye-suk!
[playful music playing]
Hey, come here. Let's shake hands.
Come on. Hey!
Look at that snob.
She's totally fine.
Lavender, let's call it a night.
-[In-suk] Really?
-Also, you drink that.
-You need to calm down more. Go!
-[In-suk] I will.
[Mi-suk] Seok-ryu, Seung-hyo. Great job.
[Hye-suk exclaiming in pain]
It seems simply like a sprain,
but let's go to the hospital tomorrow
for an x-ray.
Okay.
Also, let's get a brain MRI soon too.
I heard about what's been going on
with you.
You didn't tell Seung-hyo yet, right?
No.
It's probably nothing.
It'll be just to check things out.
Don't be scared.
[exhales]
Even if you're not okay,
I'll stay by your side.
"For better or for worse,
in sickness and in health,
to love and to cherish,
till death do us part."
[pleasant music playing]
We made a vow.
I've forgotten those vows for too long.
You can just start now.
You must be exhausted from today.
Take a shower and rest.
You too.
Wait.
[exclaiming in pain]
[exclaims]
Wait a second. [groans softly]
[Gyeong-jong] Do you…
want me to take you to the bathroom?
[pleasant music playing]
Could you?
Here.
[music ends]
[tap on window]
-[Seok-ryu] What's that in your hand?
-A recorder.
You'll attract snakes
if you play that at night.
I'm not going to play it.
I have to create a model,
so I'm analyzing its structure.
When we took those apart as kids,
a bunch of spit would come out.
Sorry.
I have a business trip tomorrow.
I won't be home.
I see.
-Where are you going?
-Gangwon Province.
When will you be back?
After about two weeks.
Why is it so long?
It's not overseas.
Who goes on a business trip for two weeks?
It's an important project.
Come with me if you're bored.
[quirky music playing]
I mean, that's if you're really bored
with nothing to do.
I don't think that'll happen.
Have a good trip.
Thanks.
All right.
Bye.
[music ends]
[breeze blowing]
[mellow music playing]
[camera shutter clicks]
[teacher] To prepare mussels,
you need to cut and remove
the beard on the inside with scissors.
Then, we're going to blanch them.
Make sure not to cook them for too long.
Okay.
[pop song playing]
[Jeong-min] What about the windows?
[inaudible conversation]
[pop song continues playing]
[sighs]
It's not fun hanging out by myself.
Think of the mouthpiece
as the entrance to the building.
[Na-yun] It'll be made from logs.
We'll make it so when air enters
through the gaps, it'll create sounds.
[sighs]
I'm bored.
Today…
I'll make coq au vin.
[Seung-hyo speaking French]
[Seung-hyo in Korean]
Coq au vin means "rooster in wine."
With chicken and vegetables
braised in wine,
it's a traditional French dish.
[Seok-ryu] What?
Why won't it play?
Is that the end?
[Seung-hyo] Seok-ryu.
[mellow music playing]
[sighs deeply]
Seok-ryu.
[speaking French]
[continues speaking French]
[in Korean] What on earth is he saying?
I know!
[Seung-hyo speaking French]
THAT MILK EXPIRES TODAY
[pleasant music playing]
BUT MY FEELINGS FOR YOU
WON'T SPOIL TOMORROW OR THE DAY AFTER
[phone vibrating]
APPLICATION APPROVED
FOR SOUTH POLE POSITION
-[exclaims]
-[Seok-ryu] Mo-eum!
-Seok-ryu!
-Where are your car keys?
-In my bag.
-Your bag?
-Let me borrow your car.
-Sure.
-Where are you going?
-To see Seung-hyo.
-[door closes]
-Wow.
Has the catalyst finally been triggered?
CHOISSEUNG
MR. YOON
[line ringing]
Mr. Yoon, it's me.
Do you know
where Seung-hyo is by any chance?
[music ends]
[breeze blowing]
[exhales]
[footsteps approaching]
[inhales]
[exhales]
Seok-ryu?
Why won't you answer your phone?
[pleasant music playing]
Ah, I had it on silent.
But what brings you here?
I was bored.
[breathing heavily]
You said I could come.
[chuckles softly]
Were you bored?
Yeah.
Without you, time seems to drag on.
[breeze blowing]
Without you, comic books aren't fun.
Without you, the playground is quiet too.
Without you, every day feels bland.
It's like eating unseasoned soup
or dumplings without soy sauce.
Without you, it's like not drinking
banana milk after going to the bathhouse.
So I was wondering.
You want to go drink banana milk with me?
[laughs]
You still think about food
in this kind of situation?
[pleasant music playing]
[pop song playing]
[breeze blowing]
I don't think I need
that banana milk anymore.
BELATED
BELATED REALIZATION
[pop song continues playing]
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce