(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
Hang in there.
We're with doctors now. You'll be fine.
Stay strong.
You will be fine.
Hang in there, miss.
[Many earlier years.]
Take it slow, miss.
I'm alright.
I'm fine.
What's happened, miss?
How did you get stabbed?
I was about to go home.
Right after the boxing practice.
Then I saw one woman was getting assaulted.
Can't mind your own business, huh?
So I helped her.
They got a knife.
And they stabbed me.
Miss!
I understand that you love helping people.
But you need to be more careful.
You still got a plenty of things to do.
Don't risk your life for the others.
Please let me other people a bit.
Because it makes me wanna continue living.
Dear.
Got angry again?
I can even hear your voice through the wall.
What's going on?
Why don't you tell me that you're coming?
If I told you,
will I hear little angry miss screaming?
It's so difficult.
I saw nothing but numbers, numbers, num... all of them.
They gave me a headache.
Give it a rest.
You are a CEO's daughter.
Are you going to do these alone? Have your underling do some.
I'm still a newbie.
If I do not understand every process,
how can I teach or order anyone to do, right?
I've been sitting for hours.
My body is sore. It's just too hard.
Why can't numbers are easy like music notes?
Such a fussy.
- And now clingy? - Yeah.
Are you tired?
Very much.
I'll give you a massage.
To help you relax.
Can't have a little service, can you?
- How is it? - It's so comfy.
This hand, right? This hand, right?
You're really good at this.
You can do everything.
How can I find another perfect girlfriend other than you?
Hold on.
Let's be clear.
Why do you have to find more?
The perfect one is sitting right here.
Watch your words.
I'm joking. I won't find any.
Actually, I didn't just come here to only meet you.
Your mother called me.
It's about you suddenly asked me to marry you.
We were all shocked and doesn't know what to do.
Your mother probably thought that I want something from you.
So do you want anything?
Yes.
I want to do this with you.
Miss Weiling is ready.
Don't get too angry or else...
Hello, miss Weiling.
I knew it from the start, didn't you?
That Lalin is my daughter.
How could I know?
Back then, I know only Lalin whose named herself, Lyra.
I didn't imagine myself to be this connected to you.
Everything is just pure coincidence.
I do not believe in the coincidence.
I believe this is all your plan.
I understand.
Also our relationship had a rough start.
But It was just a business.
The winner takes it all.
But about Lalin and I...
it's really about love.
Love?
You? Love her?
Really?
Even tho you guys just met?
Do you really know your daughter that well?
Yes, I do.
I am her mother.
Because if you know Lalin well...
you don't have to even ask me how I love her so easily.
People like Lalin.
They can make everyone near them happy.
Even we only know each other for one night,
love can still happen.
I still believe it's too fast.
I still want Lalin to learn more about my company.
I can't let you marry her.
My only daughter.
To let her marry the one who I do not trust.
That's a no-go.
I totally understand your motherhood.
Lalin must appreciate a lot about your concerning.
But if you really know your daughter well,
you can explain it yourself that you don't allow her to marry the one she loves.
I believe...
a person of your degree always got her daughter's happiness before anything else.
Do you remember that day?
The first time we met at the park.
It was fun, yeah?
Fun? It wasn't fun for me.
You dragged me into the park at late night.
We almost got a fine.
We're lucky that night you ran that fast.
You are such a little cheeky miss.
Seeing you happy makes me happy.
Do you like a surprise like this?
Yes, I do.
I like whatever you've done for me.
Even you do the crazy dance in the middle of the road, I also like.
You said it yourself.
How about this?
Don't have to get to point of dancing in the middle of the road,
How about here? Do you dare?
- Are you challenging me? - Yeah.
You'll see.
Dear, enough. It's enough.
I believe you now.
I still haven't finsihed the dance yet.
I believe you that you're bold.
You're the one who challenging me, no?
I believe you.
The way you are yourself,
it's the reason why I like you since the first day we met.
You are quite different today.
Is this the time for official proposal?
Have you talk with my mom? Is she alright with us?
See? I know my mom is not that cruel.
Lalin.
If we cannot see each other,
will you get sad?
Why do you say something like that?
Could it be...
my mom is not okay with us?
What did she say?
Disagree.
There's no way she would agree.
I think this is getting harder than we thought.
Are you giving up?
I'm not giving up.
I think...
if we stick with the truth,
it might hurt us less.
I brought you here tonight.
Just to be happy with you. Just enjoy this moment with you.
Just in case, there will be no more.
I want this bracelet,
to be the reminder of me.
In the day that we cannot be with each other.
Dear.
Listen to me.
I will not let our relationship end like this.
If it will end,
it has to end by us not by my mom doesn't agree with.
Trust in "us".
I will fight for us.
She's here, boss.
Please sit down, miss Weiling.
I contracted you for loaning 50 million baht.
So what's the answer?
My company has met with some obstacle.
My investment plan is not going according to plan.
But I believe,
W Empire is going to make a big profit next year.
I don't care much about your profit.
The loan that you got from me last time,
I still haven't get back any of it.
And also,
it passed the due date already.
I can ensure you. If you allow me the loan this time, I can give you back the money.
So if I let you loan the money and plus the last time you've loaned,
the debt is going to be 100 millions baht.
What do you have to ensure me that you will give back all my money?
I didn't come here empty handed.
It's up to you to accept...
or not.
Your choice.
Quite an interesting statement.
I'll say let's have a meeting next week.
We'll prepare signed documents.
You can just wait for the money.
Mom!
About Lalin and Arisa's marriage,
you wouldn't agree, would you?
We've talked about this already.
I don't want to talk about it.
I also thought about it throughly.
If you aren't gonna let us marry, I'll go back to be Lyra.
How well do you know her, huh?
Arisa!
Is this your plan?
Don't put the blame on her.
This is my own decision.
Lalin.
I think you should listen to your mother.
Maybe it's just not a proper time.
It's my fault for being too rush.
So your mother doesn't trust me that much.
My mom doesn't but I do trust you.
I'm sure that it has to be you.
Mom.
I confirmed my words.
If we can't marry, then I'll go.
Let's go.
Hold on, Lalin.
Just go!
Fine.
Prove me wrong.
What do you me to prove?
Move into my house.
So I can keep my eyes on you.
Let me see that you're being sincere with my daughter.
Alright.
If that will make you trust me.
I'll see.
I haven't seen you smile like this for a long time.
What do you mean?
It seems like a real happy smile.
It's not always like that.
Sometimes smile cannot tell a thing.
People can fake their smiles.
Right.
Now, Weiling...
allows me to date Lalin.
But the marriage,
might be difficult.
We need some time for her to trust me completely.
You need to play the role of Lalin's lover for a while.
I know you can do it.
You are hard-hearted woman.
But be careful.
Because our own heart.
Can become our own weakness.
No need to worry, uncle Mek.
I would never put my heart,
to play in this game.
Lalin is just a pawn in my revenge game.
I got tea to spill, girl.
Have you heard about Weiling's daughter that got a grand opening some time ago?
- What's it about? - Such a drama. The thing is...
She got a relationship with her mother's rival.
It's just love.
What love?
I've heard that Weiling's finance is in trouble to the level that she has to get an illegal loan to avoid the survey.
She got so many funds from the illegals.
Does this mean she use her daughter to pay a debt?
Probably.
Excuse me.
My parents taught me that it's better to shut up if you can't talk about anyone with positive attitude.
Manners 101.
Lalin!
Dear.
What's going on?
Are you alright?
You called me with that voice. I was so worried.
What's going on?
You can tell me.
Please tell me.
It's about my mom.
I don't really know who to talk with.
There's only you.
What's with your mother?
She's not gonna let us date?
This time, I'll fight back.
That's not it.
I just heard that...
my mom's company is going bankrupt.
She got a lot of troubles.
But she won't tell me anything.
I don't know how can I help her.
I'm also bad at doing business.
You are bad.
But I'm not.
I'm willing to help you if I can.
Don't overthink.
But you and my mom are rivals.
But you are my girlfriend.
In my bad day, I still got you.
Your mother is lucky.
She got a daughter like you.
That always cared for her.
If my parents's still alive,
Imma do the same.
Do everything to protect them.
Don't be scared.
I'll help your mother.
Thank you.
There will be a meeting with Petra groups next month.
They will update the interior structure a bit.
They'll change the design, lobby and presidential suite.
In that case, I'll let you take this job.
I'm not into this job.
Just can't let them catch us.
Got it.
Take a look at this, miss.
What is it?
Weiling got no choice.
She has to get help from this woman.
She accidentally fell into a trap like this.
We got to make a move, Mek.
You didn't sign.
Is there anything wrong in the agreement?
Not really.
There's a rumor going around about your company is going bankrupt.
I want to work with the company that got value.
Not the one that is dying.
Hope you understand, miss Weiling.
Okay.
So be it.
Sometimes it's up to people's vision.
If they can see it or not.
Wit.
We need to find someone who can agree to our statement fast.
Got it, ma'am.
But, ma'am...
The bank told me...
if we don't pay the first debt in time,
you might got blacklisted.
That's why we need to hurry.
I won't let myself seeing my company being destroyed.
When I was a kid, am I cute?
Present you are cuter.
By the way, you do look like your father.
Many people say that.
But I'm a loner and won't give up like my mom.
My mom has to face a woman like her.
That is me.
Cheeky.
What about you?
Look like your mom or your dad?
I look like both of them.
I love art and music like my dad.
And a loner like my mom.
Both of them are my role model.
I am like their perfect replica.
I'd say,
your parents must be so proud of you.
I'm also proud of you.
You are so cool.
But you'll be much cooler if you can get along with my mom.
I'm trying.
But your mother has to be open minded too.
And that's seems to be the hardest part.
That's also my mission.
To get you and my mom getting along.
I won't give up.
Here, eat up.
It's your favourite.
That's enough.
You are in my house please act like a guess.
I'm getting to the point.
The reason I allow you to living in my house.
I want to know you.
I want to make sure,
that you are sincere with my daughter.
What do you want to know?
Ask away.
I have nothing to hide.
Who's your parents?
Where're you from?
My parents are dead.
Since I was 10 years old.
I grew up with elderly relatives.
I'm sorry.
And...
about property business,
how did you get into the business?
I always interested in this field of work.
And I wanted to set myself up.
So I studied in this business a lot.
Like I said,
You are my inspiration.
I want to follow your footsteps.
It's not easy.
Before I am myself today, I've been through a lot.
This field of work, you need to be strong.
Need to make a right move.
Then I need you as a mentor.
I'm still a newbie.
In business way.
And in personal way.
How did I fall in love my rival's daughter?
What about...
you guys stop being a rival?
And merge our companies together.
Both of my love ones can be together.
Lalin.
Stop mixing business matters and personal matters.
They'll both screwed.
Dear.
Eat up.
It's your favourite.
You like to eat this a lot.
Dear.
Do you feel awkward staying here?
I'm feeling at ease.
I can be anywhere...
just by your side.
I'm serious right now.
I ain't playing either.
I'm upset here. I'm afraid that you might feel awkward.
I don't know how many more conditions my mom needs.
Even your mother got millions of conditions,
I'll still meet her expectations.
Because I already love her daughter.
Alright.
I might be overthinking.
We'll be holding hands and go through this.
But if you feel any uneasy,
we can move back to your house.
Nah.
I'm not a person who will give up easily.
Until I get what I want.
And what do you want?
Wanna know?
The thing that I want is...
is this!
Dear.
What's the kissing for?
Smell so nice. May I take it again?
That's enough.
My body will get a bruise.
What about the body? Is it nice too?
Imma go to sleep.
I won't let you. Come here.
Please let me kiss.
Is everything okay?
I think I know even you're not telling me.
It's something you that have to meddle with.
I don't mean to be rude but,
I can help you.
Because I love Lalin.
Lalin is stressing out no better than you.
Does she know about this?
She does.
She cared about you.
She's trying any way to help you.
And I don't want her to suffer.
Then how can you help me?
What do you want?
That's exactly what I can help you.
But there must be a trade-off.
What do you want in return?
I'll help you with every loans you had.
Including those company debts too.
In exchange of half of your company sharing.
Isn't it too much?
Do you wanna take over, don't you?
This is only way to save your company.
Is it better to lower your ego and accept my help?
[1 week earlier.]
It's been so long, I thought you already forgot about me.
How can I forget the one who made my life better to the point that I can have my own company?
I also wouldn't dare to forget my lifesaver.
So...
Are you running into trouble this time?
Or do you need more funds?
My company is on the golden era.
I got no problem financially.
I only got one problem.
A person.
Who's it?
The one that borrowed your money.
Miss Weiling.
How come?
You got any problem with her?
It's complicated.
Can't tell you right now.
May I ask you one thing?
Please do not help her.
You didn't sign.
Is there anything wrong with the statement?
Take it as my final request,
The one who saved your life.
After that, you own me nothing.
That's not a little money, you know?
I can't help you this time.
I'll do it gently.
Can't mind your business, can you?
Thank you for saving my life.
It's nothing.
Here.
Take it.
If you are in any trouble,
come find me.
Let me repay you.
I own you my life.
Thank you for saving my mom.
It's alright.
I'll help with anything I can.
I hope that mom will understand your sincerity.
I didn't hope for anything.
What's bothering you,
it's also bothering me.
We're about to live together.
We have to take care of each other.
But be careful.
Because our own heart,
could become our own weakness.
The anonymous shareholder,
Who is that?
Aunt Yuwadee, she's my dad's sister.
But she couldn't quite get along with my mom.
This shareholder...
never interferes the management.
That's why all the decision...
is depending on me.
Their decision...
will affect the direction of W Empire's management.
I don't know what you've been t hrough in the past .
But now, it's time to start a fresh good memory.
I want to both laugh and cry together with you.