(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
[Fate Chooses You]
[Episode 10]
Mr. Lu,
where are we going?
Qiyue Lake.
The water of Qiyue Lake
in Chongling Valley is clear
with rich spiritual energy.
It is extraordinary.
The spiritual plants here
are also growing well.
They're all nourished by the lake water.
That explains why
the trees here
are growing exceptionally well.
I slipped Power-Dissolving Powder
into your tea
to suppress your power.
You are no different from a mortal now.
You won't be able to break free.
I'll ask, and you'll answer.
Will you do that?
This is my senior,
She left the mountain for errands
and hasn't returned for a long time.
You know her,
don't you?
So what if I do?
There's a grudge between you and her.
You're an enemy to her.
One last question.
Was the female cultivator trying to avenge
her husband in the capital
my senior?
Were you chasing after her?
Did she get hurt?
I really am curious
about what kind of sect
could raise two ignorant fools
courting death like you and her.
She deserves death for violating
the rules set for immortal sects.
You want to stand up for her now?
Who do you think you are to...
Write down everything
you've heard
and seen
about my senior.
You think I'll do that
just because you tell me to?
Today, I was captured by you
simply because I had bad luck.
But what about the future?
I am backed
by Lingji Mountain.
Do you dare to kill me?
My senior
prayed for me and got me this amulet.
She said I had a bitter childhood,
but living with her from then on
would be equal to having family.
She wished me all the best in everything,
and peace and joy in my life.
However, in fact,
I do have family.
My mother passed away early.
My father has many children,
all of which are boys,
except me.
Do you know
how I survived
in a family like that?
I had to grovel all day long
and wait on them like a slave.
Whenever they felt displeased,
they would punch and kick me.
Occasionally, I fell into a trance
and wondered
if I was a living soul in this world
or if I had already entered hell.
What are you going to do?
But on second thought,
I assumed...
even hell couldn't be that terrible.
Later,
it took me a great deal of effort
to escape
from that inferno.
If my senior hadn't saved me,
brought me to the sect,
taken good care of me,
and taught me techniques,
I would have died long ago.
To me, my senior matters
more than anyone else in this world.
She's even more important than my life.
Stay away from me.
What on earth are you going to do?
You're crazy!
Given that,
I guess you understand how much
I want to kill you right now.
What...
What did you...
do to me?
I cast the Bonding Curse on you.
The cursed ones will share
the same fate and feelings.
I do want to kill you.
But my senior told me
to be kind to others,
and to avoid staining my hands with blood
because of others' mistakes.
I choose to listen to her
and spare your life.
Now,
will you tell the truth?
I already told you
what you wanted to know.
When will you let me go?
You're better at reading the situation
than she is,
but not as honest as her.
Look.
She wrote
much content than you did.
You only asked if I knew
where your senior went.
My answer was impeccable.
But you didn't tell me
she was with an extraordinary fighter
who helped her out of trouble.
You've seen that fighter.
What is his name?
What does he look like?
Draw his face.
I only got a glimpse of him.
I can't remember his face clearly.
Even if I remembered it,
I wouldn't be able to draw it.
It's fine.
The night is still young.
There is plenty of time for us.
Forgive me, ma'am.
I was thirsty from the journey,
so I poured myself a cup of tea.
I will pay whatever it costs.
It's just a cup of cold tea.
Consider it on the house.
You've finished your tea.
Why are you still here?
Two of my friends are being kept here.
I'm afraid I won't leave
until you release them.
You really are haunting me like a ghost.
Please release them, miss.
You're asking for trouble.
We are both Golden Core cultivators.
Even if we keep fighting,
there's no telling who will win.
Let my friends go.
I don't want to give you a hard time.
You colluded with them
to try to kill my senior.
How is it not giving me a hard time?
Senior Jin,
let me help you.
Forget about me.
Go find Nangong first!
You must memorize
every single word
of what I'm going to say.
Humans are connected
to the external environment.
They exhale the impure
and inhale the fresh
through the nose and mouth.
Cultivators' focus is more on
improving the complete sensory faculties.
Only when a cultivator
senses things that ordinary people can't
will his or her body form a link
with heaven and earth,
take in spiritual energy,
and go to a higher stage.
Mr. Lu, if, as you said,
one can breathe
without using the mouth or nose,
does it mean I can take in water
the same way?
Yes, exactly.
I'm going to teach you
the Fish Drinking Technique.
It means to take in water
like fish do.
Hold your breath and gather your energy.
Let your mind settle at Lingtai acupoint.
Have your energy flow through your body
and reach Hegu acupoint.
Close the heart meridians.
Let your spiritual energy run along
all the meridians
and gather on the skin.
I can feel my vital energy
is circulating.
May I drink water now?
Not in a moment.
Mr. Lu!
Don't panic.
Breathe with the technique I taught you.
You've got this.
No.
The Power-Dissolving Powder
has stopped you from using techniques.
But I didn't expect
you could still resort to sword skills.
I underestimated you.
We'll remember what you did to us today
and make you pay a steep price one day.
She used Power-Dissolving Powder on you?
Not only that.
She also cast the Bonding Curse on me
and tortured me with a little bug,
which almost made me suffocate to death.
Why did she catch the two of you?
What else reason could it be?
Her senior, of course.
The female cultivator
who took revenge for her husband
in the capital.
Forget about this matter then.
Go back to your sects for recuperation.
I will go after her.
Thank you then.
Senior Jin,
you must not let her get away.
Rub your hair dry.
I'll take you to practice more
these few days.
It's not hard to master
the Fish Drinking Technique.
Mr. Lu,
tell me,
after getting the hang
of the Fish Drinking Technique,
will I no longer need to drink water?
Are you thirsty now?
No, I don't think I am.
I'm really not thirsty now.
Thank you for saving my life, Mr. Lu.
I will never forget your favor.
If you ever need help,
I'll come to your aid
despite any danger.
I don't need you to go through any danger.
It'll save me a lot of trouble
if you could
master the Fish Drinking Technique soon.
Thank you, Mr. Lu.
Hungry, aren't you?
I haven't eaten anything for a whole day.
But it's fine.
I'll find something to eat later.
Given your current health,
what can you eat?
Flatbreads.
Dry flatbreads.
Got it.
Wait for me.
Mr. Lu.
Here you are.
Dig in.
Thanks, Mr. Lu.
Anything wrong?
Nothing.
Mr. Lu,
did you make this yourself?
Yes.
Does it taste awful?
Not at all.
It's tasty.
A bit salty, though.
I'll cook again then.
No, No need.
I'd hate to waste these.
Alright.
It's good to eat now.
How delicious.
Spit it out.
Or it'll upset your stomach.
That won't be a problem.
It actually tastes good.
Had better not waste it.
Yummy.
Mr. Lu,
actually, it would
be better if you had made these flatbreads
thinner.
This way, they would be easier to cook.
You know how to make flatbreads?
Yes, a little.
How thin should they be?
About half as thin as this one.
When you mix the flour with water,
put in some salt.
Not a handful,
but a spoonful.
Anything else?
When you knead the dough,
try adding an egg
and sprinkling some chopped green onions.
Then, when the flatbreads are ready,
they'll smell better
with a crispy texture.
If there's a chance in the future,
let me make some for you.
Yes.
[Mingzhu House]
Let's team up.
Young Sect Master,
Are we going
to steal, rob,
or purchase?
Haven't decided yet.
Young Sect Master,
there's a thief.
What exquisite sword skills.
You even made me use magic techniques.
Impressive.
Young Sect Master,
are you alright?
Are you done practicing?
Such long practice
has worn me out.
Food is ready in Cunsu Hall.
Let's go eat!
Fine then.
It's been so long.
Why isn't it our turn yet?
We've waited for a long time.
My mother is in agony.
When will we be allowed in?
Tell me about it.
What's taking so long today?
Next is the patient
with the call sign "Geng."
Yes, here we are!
Young Sect Master, it's our turn.
I've been in line for so long.
When will it
be our turn?
This external injury
of your could be fixed
in any other clinic.
Why did you have to wait in line
with my other patients?
Your wound is almost healed.
B-But aren't you said to be
the best physician?
My master even better.
Why don't you go to him?
Only if I could find him!
Wait.
Just treat your patients.
What is it with you?
How did you get injured?
Someone set off firecrackers
when I was around.
I don't think so.
It was probably gunpowder.
The Human Race's craftsmanship
develops rapidly.
They invented gunpowder long ago.
It can be as powerful as magic.
Goddess Wushuang once wrote a book
called "Unparalleled Secret Magic,"
which records many mysterious techniques.
Unfortunately, this book
has been long lost.
Otherwise,
the Human Race would be much better
than now.
This is news to me.
So you're saying
that with gunpowder,
even little kids can fend for themselves?
Having said all that,
Chongling Valley acquiesces
in letting someone use
such a dangerous thing at night.
Won't you do something?
Aren't you partially to blame?
Then what were you doing
so late at night?
Why did you get in a fight with someone?
I...
What a huge wound.
Young Sect Master,
how much of this medicine
should be taken a day?
I can't read Physician Zhu Yu's
handwriting at all.
To hell with that medicine.
I can't believe he gave me such trash.
Chongling Valley
has become so disrespectful.
Give me a Yangyuan Pill.
Isn't that Immortal Xin
from Xin Xie Manor?
Who is the man beside her?
He's no ordinary man.
Miss Xin!
Does the food here agree with you?
Yes, every bit as good
as that in Zuixian Restaurant.
The taste is excellent,
and...
we don't have to pay at all.
Your friends?
Please meet
Miss Lyu Yunsu.
She is
the daughter of General Lyu Jing.
This is Li Si,
captain of the Dongyou Army.
This is Mr. Lu,
a friend of Divine Doctor Su's.
Greetings, Mr. Su.
Zuixian Restaurant has no branches
in the capital.
The Dongyou Army is stationed
a thousand miles away from the capital.
Have you been to that restaurant?
Never.
Well, you see,
we are from a small place.
We've only heard of the well reputed
Zuixian Restaurant.
So when we eat something nice,
we can't help but make a comparison.
I must've humiliated myself, Mr. Lu.
But your comparison was on point.
The master chef of Cunsu Hall
used to truly
work in Zuixian Restaurant.
So many years have passed.
The current chef there
is probably his apprentice.
Nice to meet you.
You mean together?
Please.
Thank you, Miss Lyu.
Shall we join them?
Sure.
What would you like to eat?
Thanks.
A plate of flatbreads,
and a pot of wine.
Got it!
Just a moment, sir.
Mr. Lu,
won't you eat anything?
Wine is all I need.
There is some.
Mr. Lu.
Is the Dongyou Army's
Left General Sun Wulei
still unable
to hold his liquor now?
The Left General never drinks,
and his name is not Sun Wulei.
He is General Zhang Qian.
Captain Li, judging by your hand,
you don't seem to be a sword user.
I'm better at using short-bladed weapons.
But occasionally, I use swords as well.
A military man using swords?
How do you kill enemies then?
I used to be a scout,
with the primary duty
of reconnoitering the enemy.
Only when I was discovered
or besieged would I really
need to fight the enemy.
In a life-or-death situation,
a sword or a dagger makes no difference.
Mr. Lu, have you served
in the army as well?
She's asking...
Yes, for a while.
So you can read sign language, Mr. Lu?
Yes, a bit.
Please enjoy.
Dig in.
I am Lin Muhan from Lingji Mountain.
Such a pleasure to meet you,
a junior from Xin Xie Manor.
I... I don't know you.
Lingji Mountain and Xin Xie Manor
have always been close.
My father and your master, Xin Xiong,
are bosom friends.
I heard your birthday is...
the ninth day of the ninth lunar month.
So you're the Heavenly Talent
of Xin Xie Manor.
What a coincidence.
I am also a Heavenly Talent too.
That makes this
a meeting of Heavenly Talents.
I wish we could
meet earlier.
Hello, Mr. Lin.
This gentleman...
looks very familiar.
Have we met somewhere before?
I remember now.
We once met at the Safe Haven Inn.
Sir, you were having
a good time chatting with the pharmacists
from Chongling Valley.
I meant to go up and greet you,
but it was a pity
you and your fellows left too soon.
But it's fine.
It was fate that brought us
together again.
Sir,
why not be my friend?
Sir, you're drinking without talking.
That's not respectful.
I'll take it that you don't want me
as a friend.
Mr. Lin, please don't take offense.
Aloofness is Mr. Lu's personal trait.
He doesn't like to talk.
Please don't give him a hard time,
Mr. Lin.
You call him "Mr. Lu"?
Sir, we'll have
half a kilo of beef
and four bowls of plain noodles.
Got it!
Take a seat and wait a moment.
There are new customers.
Tell the kitchen
to prepare half a kilo of beef
and four bowls of plain noodles.
Sorry.
This seat is taken.
Hurry, go.
Bai Zongying,
how dare you hurt
a member of us Lingji Mountain?
Let's go. Quick.
Fine.
Another man who wouldn't talk.
I didn't realize you are such
an amazing fighter.
I really underestimated you that day.
You enjoy the food.
I'm leaving now.
I'm leaving too.
You know that man?
About the one who came in later...
Judging by his clothes,
he's from Tianyuan Sect, right?
He's the personal disciple of Li Mofu,
namely the master of Tianyuan Sect.
he has top-notch powers
and superb sword skills.
I do know him,
but he might not remember who I am.
Sir!
Sir, please hold on!
Sir,
thank you for your help.
Lingji Mountain
will remember the favor you did me.
Sir,
if you ever need help
in the future,
don't hesitate
to turn to us anytime.
Honestly, destiny seems
to have formed a connection between us.
Which sect are you from?
Who is your master?
Have you ever been to Lingji Mountain?
Mr. Lu,
would you like to come in and sit?
Although I can't drink tea,
I could make some for you.
No need.
Maybe another day.
Mr. Lu!
My room was ransacked.
Mom, I want candied hawthorns.
Let's keep going, alright?
Sure.
Candied hawthorns!
Trinkets!
Trinkets for sale!
Fresh vegetables!
Candied hawthorns!
How about a flatbread?
Not now.
It's freshly baked.
Very tasty.
Sir, would you like a flatbread?
Yes, I'll take one.
Sir,
I'll take half a kilo of lean meat.
Got it!
Vegetables.
Fresh vegetables!
Be patient.
It'll be done soon.
Heaven cares for every living creature.
This puppy is innocent.
Why must you commit a sin by killing it?
You finally decided to show up
after following me all the way here.
What?
Do you think
you are a merciful living Buddha
who doesn't descend until blood is seen?
Besides,
who said I would kill the puppy?
You are the one I plan to kill.
You won't be able to do so, miss.
For snatching my captives away
right under my nose,
you really are something.
That said, I'm very curious.
Hadn't you fled like a loser
who lost his home?
Why did you come back?
Do you have a death wish?
I'd like a word with you, miss.
About what?
About my tribulation,
and my path.
I'm not interested.
But what if...
you are my tribulation?
Thank you for walking me here.
You're welcome, Miss Xin.
It was no trouble at all.
Has the intruder
been found yet?
No, not yet.
I can't live stay in that room anymore.
There are no spare rooms
in the valley either.
Luckily, Mr. Lu has
a vacant guest room here.
It's the perfect place for my recovery.
And your luggage...
Just put it here.
Sure.
Thank you.
Have a good rest, Miss Xin.
See you.
[Jiujue Cave]
War Demons' bodies are like half gods'
with unconventional constitutions.
They live long lives
and never feel pain.
Pain is blocked
by the stone marrow
in your bones.
This time, to renew bones,
your old bones will be shattered
after you take certain medicine.
Then, they will be soaked and dissolved
in Dragon Burning Sand.
This is the front leg bone of a ram.
It's indestructible.
It's really working.
The upcoming bone renewal
won't be like how it was when you
renewed your skin and flesh.
When your bones shatter
and your stone marrow vanishes,
you will be struck
by sudden and severe pain.
Have you ever thought about
how painful it would be?
Yes, of course.
This is my wish.
Fine then.
Drink this.
We'll proceed to
the bone renewal in a few days.
Lu,
you are weak now. Walk slower.
Senior,
what happened to Mr. Lu?
Nothing.
He just caught a cold.
A cold?
Exactly.
Just a cold.
I'm fine.
Leave him to me.
Sure.
Slowly.
Are you alright?
Don't drink the water.
It's poisoned!
Don't drink the water!
The water is poisoned!
It's poisoned!
Don't drink the water!
I'm thirsty.
Give me water.
But I can't drink the water.
It's poisoned.
I can't drink the water!
I'm thirsty.
I can't drink the water.
It's poisoned.
I'm thirsty.
I'm so thirsty.
But I can't drink the water.
It's poisoned.
I'm thirsty.
But I can't drink the water.
It's poisoned.
I can't drink the water!
I'm thirsty.
The water is poisoned.
I can't drink the water.
It's poisoned.
I can't drink it.
I can't.
What's with Immortal Xin?
Her body can't retain water.
The Fish Drinking Technique
can't help her for too much longer.
Is there any other solution?
The only way
to break the Spell of Utterance
is to kill the person who cast the spell.