(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
[Episode 4]
Qing Long really hid the ledger with you.
You had a student help you
get rid of the bloody clothes,
making me think you left the city.
Xia Liu Yi, how could you be so stupid?
Who hit you?
Him.
Which hand did he use?
His left hand.
Let your boss avenge you.
I'm not your lackey.
Give me a break, Xia Liu Yi.
You can barely stand.
Stop pretending to be a big shot.
Bring the ledger over.
What?
Too scared to come get it?
You're full of dirty tricks.
I'm not in the mood to play with you.
Don't move.
Boss, he's unarmed.
I never carry a weapon.
Unlike your boss,
who doesn't have any real weapon at all.
It was his left hand, right?
Liu Yi!
Xia Liu Yi.
Watch your mouth
if you're in this line of work.
If you know what's good for you,
say something nice.
If I'm in a good mood,
maybe I'll leave your body intact.
[Heroes of the Streets]
[Screenplay: He Chu San]
What the hell is this?
Wasn't this movie released last month?
It's been switched.
Xu, I really didn't know about this.
You little bastard, you dare mess with me?
Where's the ledger?
Be honest.
Xu, you killed Qing Long.
And you still didn't get
the most important ledger.
The Dragon Head Staff hasn't appeared either.
You can't become the new leader.
Cut the crap.
I've captured you, the traitor.
That's a great achievement.
And I've taken over all the gang's territory.
Those old bastards will have to
accept it whether they like it or not.
Qing Long treated you well.
Why did you kill him?
Qing Long treated me well?
I followed him for 20 years.
I went through fire and raining blades for him.
And what did I get?
In his eyes, there was only you,
a snot-nosed brat.
It makes me sick.
What kind of useless deputy hall leader was I?
I was nothing but a dog at his feet.
When did he ever look at me seriously?
Do you know what he told the elders?
He said you are young,
but both wise and brave,
worthy of great responsibility.
And that I, Xu Ying, am too scheming
to be fully trusted.
Was he wrong?
You bribed Cheng Shi Yong
to switch my sister's medicine,
and forced her to jump off a building.
You even stole my twin blades
and stabbed my brother to death,
framing me for it.
There were so many people in that villa.
Do you really think you could
hide the truth from everyone?
So what?
The brothers from Xiaoqi Hall
who were there that day,
they weren't yours, they were all mine.
Who do you think they'll believe?
Xu Ying.
Even in the underworld,
there are rules of honor.
You killed so many innocent people.
You won't die a good death.
Honor?
Everyone in the underworld said
Boss Long valued honor the most.
Did he die a good death?
Did he?
Did he die a proper death?
Fuck. Xia Liu Yi.
Listen carefully.
Your corpse will be in pieces.
Stubborn bastard, I'll crush you inch by inch.
Kill that student in front of him.
Xu Ying.
Who else are you going to kill?
Mr. Yuan of Xiaoqi Hall is here!
Who dares to fire?
- Boss.
You deliberately had that student lure me here,
and brought people to watch the show.
A prestigious college student.
Award-winning screenwriter, top actor.
Is my new lackey strong enough, Xu?
Xia Liu Yi.
On the road to the underworld,
I'll have you serve as a body shield for me.
Xu Ying.
Betrayed the gang.
Conspired to harm the boss.
By the rules, you deserve
three stabs and six wounds.
What do you have to say for yourself now?
You ask what I have to say now?
I lived and worked for Qing Long,
for all of you old fools,
sold my life for a lifetime.
In the end, all the benefits went to this kid.
Since you won't give it to me,
I'll take it myself.
What did I do wrong?
Three stabs and six wounds.
I... I don't accept it.
I won't accept it.
Boss.
Xia Liu Yi.
You...
You'll never know how Qing Long died.
What did you say?
Explain yourself.
Explain clearly.
Explain yourself!
Explain it!
Tell me clearly.
I, Xia Liu Yi...
I will become the leader of Xiaoqi Hall.
Boss.
Boss!
- Boss.
Boss.
Are you okay?
- How are you?
- Are you okay?
Let's go.
This is a sin, truly a sin.
Liu Yi.
Liu Yi, be careful!
Liu Yi!
My makeup's ruined.
Dong Dong, you've been out for so long.
Did you miss me?
Come on, tell me.
Of course I did.
I don't believe you. You're lying.
How could I lie to you?
What's going on, Cui Dong Dong?
This is my hospital room.
And you're flirting in here?
The boss is really angry.
Has the fierce tiger fallen on hard times?
Didn't meet any beautiful women?
And got outplayed by some student?
You must be frustrated.
But then again,
that student's skin is so soft and smooth.
Even old ladies drool over him.
Want to try a different flavor?
Why not try the flowery road?
You're really disgusting.
Spent a few days with a student,
and you don't even recognize
a buddy of ten years.
No wonder.
This has been going on for so long,
and now you come to me for help.
If that student hadn't come to find me,
I would've bought your coffin by now.
I needed to disappear for long enough.
Only then would Xu Ying fall for it.
I hope you weren't hiding somewhere to cry.
I'm sorry.
I didn't protect them well.
Since Xu Ying is already dead,
there's no need to apologize.
Qing Long and Xiao Man
have already been buried.
Do you want to go see them?
Help me set up a meeting with Mr. Yuan.
I need to see him in person.
He's supporting me to be the boss.
I should greet him properly.
- Xiao Ma.
- Boss.
Boss.
Boss!
Boss, you're awake.
What's your command?
Help me check on something.
Who did Xu Ying come into contact with before?
Catch his trusted subordinates.
Interrogate them one by one.
Boss.
Xu Ying's subordinates
were all thrown into the sea last night.
Not a single one is left.
Who did this?
The elders decided it.
They said those guys were dangerous
and shouldn't be kept alive.
Finally, something useful was done.
Those who used to be disobedient
don't dare to say a word.
It's really satisfying.
I hope this is just to set an example.
Boss, what do you mean?
I don't understand.
Go find Old K alone.
Ask him to help me check
who Xu Ying had contact with before.
Don't let anyone know, including Dong Dong.
Got it.
Make money, big money.
Let's make big money together.
Chu San, I've packed it for you.
Here.
- I'll get going, Fei.
- Okay, take care.
- Got it.
- Take it slow, watch the road.
Chu San, your fever has gone down?
Look at his little face, it's so skinny.
Go up.
Brothers.
From now on, this nightclub
belongs to Xiaoqi Hall.
Xiao Ma, come take a look.
Did we hang it wrong?
Can you fix it?
Come. Stand over here.
Chu San.
Stop studying.
Take a break.
Chu San. Come on.
Dad made you some soup for your brain.
Chu San, have some soup.
Thanks, Dad.
Your frown could crush a fly.
Your eyes are sinking in.
How long have you not slept?
Stop sleeping.
Get up and keep working.
Boss.
What are you doing?
Work time.
Qi.
That Xia Liu Yi is really arrogant.
He not only seized our nightclub,
but also beat me into this state.
He even said that he would treat you like a dog
and drive you out of Ganglong.
Hello?
Boss, it's Fei Qi.
Hello, Qi.
Xia Xiao Liu, what do you mean by this?
Do we have some kind of misunderstanding?
No, no, no.
We don't have a misunderstanding.
Today is just a meeting gift.
My brother appeared to me in a dream.
He told me to cut down you, old dog.
He wants me to send you to him.
From now on, the stall belongs to us.
Impressive.
Qi, what do we do now?
Trash.
You're asking me?
Who should I ask?
Speak.
That Dual Blades Xia from Xiaoqi Hall
apparently seized another stall
from Hesheng Society yesterday.
He was already wild when he was a top enforcer.
Now that he's a boss, he's even more lawless.
I heard he also opened a shady company.
It's having its opening today.
Yes.
Let me tell you, this Fei Qi is part of
the Ho family from Hong Kong Island.
He's opposing Fei Qi.
Isn't he afraid of being caught?
Both of you, shut up.
From now on, no talking
about the triads in this clinic.
Your shop didn't have this stupid rule before.
Now we do.
What? Not following the rules?
Then don't come here for cupping anymore.
Dad, school starts today. I'm heading to class.
Got your backpack on?
Feeling better?
Don't worry, Dad.
Then don't carry too many books.
- Got it.
- Be careful on the way.
- Come back early.
- Got it.
[Xiaoqi Trading]
Mr. Yuan, do you like it?
Good.
Great, Mr. Yuan.
Wishing you wealth.
Mr. Yuan.
- Mr. Yuan.
- Mr. Yuan, wishing you wealth.
Mr. Yuan, wishing you wealth.
Wishing you wealth.
Everyone will have wealth!
Mr. Yuan, wishing you wealth.
Come, come.
Everyone gets some.
And me, Mr. Yuan?
Thanks a lot, Mr. Yuan.
Live a long life.
Abandon.
What are you looking at?
Spotted a babe?
Where?
Me!
Come on, you too.
Mr. Yuan, wishing you wealth and good health.
Good.
[Xiaoqi Trading]
Everyone gets some.
Chu San, don't laugh.
Hold his hands down.
Don't move.
You look...
much more impressive than when you were here.
You should be very satisfied
with your life now.
A ruthless gangster like you saved me twice.
I've repaid you twice.
We should be even now.
We...
Shouldn't have any more entanglements.
Boss, Fei Qi has gone into hiding with his wife
and kids in Hung Hom for two weeks.
We haven't caught him.
How did you manage that? Can't you think?
I'll go catch him now.
Hung Hom is Fei Qi's territory.
His men are everywhere on the streets.
You're asking for death.
Xiao Ma isn't very bright.
Are you the same?
Kowloon is already ours.
Only that coward Fei Qi is left.
We can deal with him later.
He brought it on himself
by challenging my brother.
Boss, don't chase a cornered enemy.
Do you understand?
In the past two months,
we've taken so much territory from Fei Qi,
and opened so many shops.
Even if you want to be a workaholic,
you still have to let them rest.
The company is running now,
so give them some time off.
If the brothers have the chance to earn,
they need time to spend too, right?
Rest?
Want a break?
No, Boss.
Time off?
For the boss, I'll go through anything.
You got hit just yesterday.
It doesn't hurt anymore, huh?
It's fine, just a small injury.
All right.
Tell your guys that bonuses will be doubled,
and they get two days off.
In a few days...
Are you kidding me?
Who am I making money for?
All of them are heartless.
Not only do we give time off,
we're hiring more people too.
Especially those who are smart,
can read, can handle accounts,
and can manage people and shops.
I think your apprentice is pretty good.
- Got any discs?
- Fuck!
You came here just to watch videos?
Do you have any ambition?
Come, someone!
Coming!
Hurry!
Come over quickly.
Move faster, be quick.
Greet Liu Yi.
Hurry. Come.
Liu Yi.
Boss Xia.
Pick whoever you like.
Today, I'll cover everything.
Damn.
How did she sneak in?
- She collects garbage.
- Are you an adult?
- I'm an adult.
- Didn't I tell you to send her back?
I'm not leaving.
I-I-I'm not going back to Cao Dong.
I I want to be a prostitute.
I... I...
A stutter.
What are you doing,
bringing someone like this here?
Send her back to the boat.
Wait.
Boss.
I'm very smart.
I'm not going back to Cao Dong.
From Cao Dong?
Don't mess with me.
No minors allowed here.
If she doesn't work, am I supposed
to let her freeload off us?
I'm not running a charity.
I want her.
You said it yourself.
I choose, you pay.
Xia Liu Yi, I really...
Boss.
Get lost.
Time for me to be happy.
- Move.
- Go, out of the room.
Hurry. Don't look.
Don't look. Move it.
Don't look. Hurry up.
Stop.
Stay here for the night.
Sleep.
Tomorrow, get the money from Cui Dong Dong.
[Children's Day]
Hao.
Do I look good in these clothes?
You're his sister.
He thinks you look good in anything.
That's true.
Damn kid.
He Chu San.
Sir.
Sir, out for a morning workout?
Chu San.
Y-You guys...
He Chu San.
That day on the bus,
did you peek at me?
I hadn't even said which day,
but you shook your head so fast.
Fei's beef offal.
Why aren't you speaking?
I'll beat you to death.
What are you doing here?
I came to get my blade.
The knife? How do you know it's here?
Stay here, don't move.
I'll go get it for you.
Let's go. Lead the way.
Let's use the back door.
I never use the back door.
The past feels like a fleeting dream,
and it's hard to recognize my feelings...
Sirs, are you here for a consultation?
Here to present a banner.
[Medicine Cures All]
[To: Mr. He, From: Xia Liu Yi]
Mr. Xia.
Chu San!
You... He...
Dr. He.
A miracle doctor.
Thank you for your care before.
I've come specifically
to present a banner
and a red envelope.
You need to show respect.
Do you know what respect means?
Sorry.
Say it again.
Mr. Xia, you're too polite.
You're being too polite.
Forget the banner and the red envelope.
Dr. He.
Just call me "Xia Liu Yi".
He Chu San.
Take me to get the knife.
Knife?
Dad, don't worry.
You eat first. I'll grab the knife.
Come with me.
Dr. He!
Where do we hang this?
Hang it...
Where did you put it?
In the pickled vegetables jar.
What the heck?
Do you know you've committed a mortal sin?
This was given to me by my brother.
Bow! Hear that?
Come back and bow before me.
I'm not your underling.
Not my underling...
My ears are getting calluses from hearing this.
Take me to your room.
What do you want?
Of course, there's something I want.
Why do you have so many questions?
This room is even more run-down
than I remembered.
Join Xiaoqi Hall.
I'll buy you a sea-view apartment in Hung Hom.
You can even bring your dad over.
You can live comfortably.
How about it?
No thanks.
You're pretending to be high and mighty.
One day, you'll regret it.
Your bed is still so comfortable.
How's your injury?
Xia Liu Yi.
Did you sleep well?
It was okay.
How's your injury now?
My injury?
It's healed already.
With my build, I just need a week.
I healed completely in just a week.
You...
[Medicine Cures All]
[To: Mr. He, From: Xia Liu Yi]
Mr. Xia, the acupuncture points
I apply pressure on
might hurt a little.
Endure it.
It'll hurt?
I never cry out in pain.
Boss.
What are you doing?
You...
Get out.
- Boss.
- Out.
Dad.
Take it easy.
Mr. Xia, your tendons are torn.
Here, the blood and energy are stagnant,
and the tissues are sticking together.
If we don't loosen them,
they'll hurt even without touching them.
Chu San.
Hold his hand down.
Don't let him move.
Careful, you...
All right.
Go get the car.
This place is even scarier than
Xiaoqi Hall's torture room.
What are you looking at?
It's just one injured arm.
I don't need you to compensate me.
If it weren't for you saving me twice,
you wouldn't be hurt like this.
You helped me out.
I can't just watch you die.
But you got hurt.
You can't wield dual blades.
H-How do you be the boss?
Being a boss isn't just about wielding blades.
You also need to use your brain.
Do you understand?
Bye.
Xia Liu Yi.
Would you be willing
to come to my graduation ceremony?
[Medicine Cures All]
[To: Mr. He, From: Xia Liu Yi]
Dad, I'll take it down for you.
Nah, just leave it there.
Dad.
Aren't you the one
who hates the triads the most?
Chu San, if I forbid you from speaking to
Liu Yi and his buddies, can you do it?
Dad, I...
All right.
I know you can't do it.
Actually, Liu Yi isn't bad at heart.
It's a shame he went down the wrong path.
Some matters are doomed fates.
They're all destined.
What I can do as a father is bear it with you.
But I really worry.
You are influenced by the company you keep.
Dad.
Perhaps it isn't Liu Yi influencing me,
but me influencing him instead.
You've grown up.
Scar Li, leave the shop to me.
The goods from me, Sha Jia Jun,
are sourced from that person.
Not at all inferior to Xiaoqi Hall's.
I'll take all your goods of this quality.
Don't move! Police!
Sha Jia Jun.
Big boss of the Sha gang.
Smuggling and drug trafficking.
Organizing mafia activities.
You are now officially under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can be used
as evidence in court.
A mere inspector dares to mess with me?
Do you even know who's behind me?
You chief inspectors should be serving me tea.
Is that so?
Then you might as well say it straight out.
I'll send him in to keep you company.
Mr. He, your son is truly
a remarkable young man.
I heard he even got
an acceptance letter from Citibank.
It's all because of his own hard work.
He has loved reading since he was young.
He doesn't even watch television.
Yeah.
So, do you have any secrets
in raising children?
I wouldn't say I have any secrets.
But I do have some experience.
Chu San, what's the matter?
Is someone coming over?
No, no.
Chu San, come over.
Let me take a photo of you.
Yes, let's go.
Go up there.
Come on, Fei.
- Come on.
- Give it to me.
Be careful.
Watch your step.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Don't break Mr. Hua's camera.
Got it.
Come on.
Smile a little.
Today is your big day.
Smile.
Hey, how about I do it?
- Okay, okay.
- You go over.
Okay.
Dad, wait a minute.
I'm here.
Everyone is here, and you're still at home.
Sorry, I mistook you for someone else.
It's okay.
Come over quickly.
Did you hear me?
Chu San, what are you doing?
Come over quickly.
Yes, come quickly.
Come on.
Stand there, and you'll be fine.
Straighten your clothes.
So handsome.
Okay, come on, look over here.
Okay, smile.
You look great. Look here.
Three, two, one, smile.
Smile.