♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 15=
Today
Is mother's birthday.
Commander.
Why are you here?
Chu Zhao has something to do.
He already left.
He wrote a letter
to you.
Osmanthus candy.
Eat one when you're sad.
You'll feel better.
Cheng Lisu told me.
Thank you.
Commander.
Do you
actually dislike osmanthus candy?
But back at Xianchang Academy,
you carried it with you every day.
How did you know
about that?
I heard it from others.
It's true.
When I was young,
my mother gave me a pouch.
It was filled with osmanthus candies.
I carried that pouch everywhere.
Seeing this,
she often made me more candies.
Yet after growing up,
I stopped liking sweets.
But my mother
made those candies.
So, the candies
must have been delicious.
Sure.
Very delicious.
If you don't want to smile,
you don't have to.
People
have moments of vulnerability.
Okay.
It's truly sweet.
Commander.
Have you ever
given osmanthus candy to others before?
I did once.
It was the last candy
my mother made.
It wasn't my first time
receiving candy from someone.
I gave it to a blind girl
contemplating suicide at Yuhua Temple.
(This is osmanthus candy.)
The last one
remaining in this world.
Though it's inedible now,
its sweetness remains.
If it was the last one,
why did you give it away?
To me,
that candy
represented desire and hope.
It was better to give it away
and pacify someone else.
Is tonight's moon
beautiful?
The moon is bright.
The breeze is gentle.
It's quite a serene scene.
Commander.
Let me give you candy too.
Eat this,
and you'll feel better.
You're regifting my own candy
to me?
Commander,
your words completely
ruin the moment.
If you're going to Jiyang,
go as a new identity.
But last night you said
you didn't think of a good one.
Yet we must go
to Jiyang at once.
Commander, I know
Chai Anxi is in Jiyang.
We must go.
I have an idea.
I'll go
to Jiyang first as a scout.
You can go
once you get a suitable identity.
The identity is secured.
It's done?
I'll use that.
But how?
Do your arrangements.
I have my resources.
Yes.
Mr. Feinu
seems awkward.
Commander.
Are you planning
to use some dishonorable identity?
Do you like me?
No.
I don't.
Good then.
Good?
What's good about it?
For the trip to Jiyang,
I'll pretend
to be Qiao Huanqing,
nephew of Cui Yuezhi,
a loyal subordinate
under the princess.
Qiao Huanqing was lost as a child
and was adopted by a kind merchant.
Cui Yuezhi
has known where he is.
So, he wrote to invite him
back to Jiyang.
However,
Qiao Huanqing
just got married.
So, I'll be impersonating...
Mrs. Qiao.
Qiao Huanqing's wife's name
is Wen Yuyan.
She's a renowned, talented woman.
Qiao Huanqing likes her very much,
often boasting about her.
Therefore, he'll undoubtedly
go to Jiyang with his wife.
Alright.
If we're acting,
we must make it look real.
But I have a question.
Look,
I don't
look like a talented lady
whatsoever.
Maybe I should go to Jiyang first
as your vanguard.
Feinu will
have someone else do that.
Your current mission
is to transform yourself
into a good lady.
Be an average lady
at least.
You should
at least know some talent.
Show your strongest skill
and practice it.
Done.
This is your strongest skill?
Sure.
This character's eight strokes
best showcase foundational skills.
(If I weren't afraid)
(you'd recognize my handwriting,)
(would I need to hide my ability?)
Commander.
I'm trying my best.
Let me draw maps instead.
That's where I excel.
No one could possibly surpass me.
You're supposed to play Mrs. Qiao,
not General Qiao.
Among these instruments,
is there any you're good at
or passable with?
The ones you know aren't here?
Complete amateur.
Then focus on guqin skills.
At least learn one piece
to bluff others.
Alright.
Will you teach me?
♪Constant yearning,
still vivid as our first meeting♪
♪Endless gazing.
Step by step, falling deeper♪
♪How to untangle this love,
buried deep within dreams♪
♪My heart, unyielding as stone,
remains true♪
♪Awaiting the crescent moon's
reflection in your heart♪
Your nervousness
might make me think you fancy me.
I...
You are
good-looking.
Being so confident isn't surprising.
But don't get me wrong.
I'm just worried my bad playing
will embarrass me publicly.
Then practice harder.
Hmm.
Don't tense your hands.
Drooping naturally.
Just go with it.
♪Shadows hustle. Scenes reappear♪
♪What is there to fear?
We'll move forward together♪
♪Through endless dawns and dusks,
to eternity♪
♪Awaiting the crescent moon's
reflection in your heart.♪
♪Splendor fades from your eyes♪
♪Crimson threads entwine like rings,
binding our first vow♪
♪Time lingers as you and I share
overlapping palm lines♪
♪Zither and harp
accompany our dancing dreams♪
♪The brocade moon writes our vow,
keeping this promise♪
Commander.
Any improvement?
Your posture looks good now.
My playing?
The playing
is very loud.
Weird.
Why does the sound
differ so much from Commander's?
Commander Xiao wants you
to cross-dress,
disregards your injuries,
and forces you
to practice.
This is really too much!
Miss Song.
My injuries healed long ago.
I'm good now.
He.
Stop speaking for Commander Xiao.
The scent of blood on you
won't escape my notice.
I have a keen nose.
I prepared
a tonic for you.
Later,
I'll check your pulse.
The quack, Cheng Lisu, can't be trusted.
He actually said you fully recovered.
No need for that.
Mr. Cheng is a good physician.
I'm good.
His diagnosis must be accurate.
He.
My medical skills are good.
You're avoiding treatment.
Let me check your pulse.
No, you don't...
Let me do it.
No need, Miss Song.
Let me help.
No need.
Let me do it.
Come on.
No, really.
I...
Miss Song.
Well, let me explain.
Well, Miss Song...
Huaijin.
Don't worry.
I spent a fortune hiring
a makeup artist.
She'll make Miss He
outshine everyone.
I don't care.
Look...
What happened?
Miss Song knows.
About what?
You. Come with me.
All of you
go in and wait.
Utterly outrageous!
Miss Song.
Though I didn't mean to hide the fact
that I am a woman,
I did deceive you.
If you're angry,
vent your fury on me.
You may even hit me.
I won't fight back.
Please.
Are you asking for a beating?
After all,
it's my fault.
Do you think
I'm angry
about your deception?
Aren't you?
Of course not!
I understand your plight.
A woman in the military faces hardships.
Your caution is justified.
I'm only upset
that you don't trust me
or tell me the truth sooner.
Had you told me earlier,
I could've started
to nurse you earlier.
He is skilled in women's health,
but I'm much better than he is.
Moreover,
I can smell the blood on you.
Did you just start your period?
Yeah.
How could you
touch cold water yesterday?
You're used to disguising yourself
as a man,
but don't forget
you're a woman.
That's self-responsibility.
Miss Song.
Thank you.
I know you're kind-hearted.
I trust you, actually.
But I've been hiding it
for years.
It's become an ingrained habit.
It's hard to say it out.
However,
one day,
I'll stand openly before all
as a woman,
telling the world
that I'm a woman,
but I'm no less capable than men,
and I'll become a great general.
Good point.
I will also prove to the world
that women
can practice medicine.
What right do they have
to criticize us?
If given the choice,
who would choose to be a domestic woman
being judged by a man?
You are
an extraordinary woman.
You're wise and brave.
Why haven't they come yet?
Huaijin.
Well,
since she knows
He Yan is actually a woman,
will she
poison her in a fit of rage?
She won't.
How can you be sure?
Didn't you see how mad she was?
- She even ordered you.
- Don't worry
- Be careful.
- I will.
Alright.
Are you two okay?
We're perfectly good.
Are we good, Yan?
Sure.
We're good.
Are you alright?
I...
The expensive makeup artist
you hired
can be dismissed.
I...
Any objections?
None.
Thank you, Miss Song.
Mmm.
Commander.
He Yan...
She's a woman?
Impressive.
- You...
- Stop.
Do you deserve to stand beside Yan?
Yan?
I knew Miss He
much earlier than you.
Commander.
Well,
how do I look?
Will my beauty kill everyone?
Kill everyone?
How about
I give you a sword?
Board the carriage
to avoid being spotted.
Sure.
Nobody knows
you're leaving.
Mmm.
Sit properly.
You're now Wen Yuyan,
a noble lady,
not a soldier.
Don't fret, Yan.
We have days of travel ahead.
When we reach Jiyang,
you'll already master the role.
Since we're impersonating others,
we must do it flawlessly.
No slip-ups allowed.
As for me,
I'll reluctantly act as the steward.
You
clearly look like a maid.
Cheng Lisu.
Now that you and Huaijin
are pretending to be a couple,
your forms of address
mustn't be neglected.
You should call Huaijin honey
as a wife.
Naturally,
Huaijin should call you honey
as a husband.
Why don't you practice
to get accustomed?
What a terrible idea!
What's wrong?
This is all
for the task.
Don't be shy.
Come on. Give it a try.
Try it.
- Ho...
- No need.
I believe
you'll do well.
Boring. Not fun at all.
(Jiyang City)
Look there.
Where's Feinu?
He has other matters to attend to.
Then let's go to the Cui Mansion first.
Once we're settled,
it'll be easy to do things.
What do you say,
Honey?
It made sense.
Still no trace of Chai Anxi?
Not yet.
Xiao Jue's men keep watching us.
It restricts our movements.
Chancellor Xu gave us
sufficient men.
When they entered the city,
I already told them
to monitor all city gates.
Chai Anxi must still be in the city.
Sufficient men?
It seems Chancellor Xu
sees Chai Anxi as a big threat.
Xiao Jue has arrived.
You investigate his motives.
His position in Jiyang
restricts him.
He might come
as a new identity.
This time, we'll monitor Xiao Jue.
Given his familiarity
with Chai Anxi,
he'll locate our target before us.
We'll use him to get what we want.
Understood.
(Cui Mansion)
Escort Mr. Cheng and Taotao
to put luggage in the backyard.
Huanqing, Yuyan,
follow me, please.
Master, they've arrived.
Uncle.
Come, Yuyan.
You're truly blessed.
Indeed.
Huanqing and you make a perfect match.
Thanks.
Exactly.
(Cui Yuezhi, General of Jiyang)
Wonderful.
Right.
Your arrival
is a blessing to our family.
What an outstanding man!
Look at his face
and his stature.
He looks like me,
right?
Absolutely.
Obviously, we're a family.
You're right.
I also think
I look a little like you.
You are uncle and nephew, after all.
You two are related.
Look,
this is Yuyan.
Uncle.
Yuyan
is a beautiful lady.
Her future children with Huanqing
will surely be stunning.
True.
Am I right?
Yes.
By the way,
tomorrow at the mansion,
I'll host a banquet
to welcome you both.
Colleagues and their families
will come.
It helps you make connections.
I have no children,
but I'll tell everyone
that my family already has a successor.
Thank you, Uncle.
Master.
Huanqing and Yuyan
had an exhausting journey.
Let me take them to rest first.
We have plenty of time
for small talk later.
Alright.
Come.
This way.
This
is the most beautiful courtyard
in the mansion.
Look.
There are hills and rivers.
Well,
this is actually the best chamber
in this courtyard.
When I heard you were coming,
I had people
prepare everything well.
Moreover,
I specifically
prepared a surprise for you.
Please come in.
You are
a newlywed couple.
I had craftsmen
decorate it as a bridal chamber.
Take a look.
Do you like it?
Thank you, Ms. Wei.
I like it very much.
My husband will certainly love it too.
If you're pleased,
so will I.
I will
leave you two alone.
Your steward Mr. Cheng
and Taotao
have been properly accommodated.
Thanks.
- I'll take my leave now.
- Hmm.
Surprise!
Commander, look.
Don't look.
Why not?
Don't ask.
But I want to see it.
It's just an erotic art picture.
It's nothing special.
Come on.
No big deal.
You
never feel shy.
It's drawn
for people, isn't it?
There's no shame in it.
Only hypocrites
pretend to be a prude.
Well,
those who follow sages' teachings
are true gentlemen,
for example,
someone like you.
Oh really?
Do you think
a true gentleman
behaves like me?
Commander.
Well,
I haven't closely watched
this yet.
It's destroyed.
What a pity!
Shall I find an artisan
to restore it for you?
No need.
Forget it.
This drawing
is not that good.
I've seen superior ones.
If I acquire some,
I'll share them with you.
Come back.
Did you
get any news?
Commander.
I contacted our men
who arrived earlier.
Chu Zhao hasn't located Chai Anxi.
Our men also failed
to find Chai Anxi.
If Xu Jingfu is behind this,
he will try to kill Chai Anxi.
We must find Chai Anxi
before he does.
Chai Anxi campaigned with his father.
His left leg was injured.
Though he was treated,
in the end,
he suffered from rheumatism.
Jiyang's warm, humid weather
may aggravate his old injury.
Monitor all apothecaries.
Understood.
Commander, let me help Feinu.
Focus on perfecting your role
as Mrs. Qiao.
Don't expose us at tomorrow's banquet,
or they'll drive us out of Jiyang.
Don't...
Don't worry.
I'll do it flawlessly.
Honey.
I heard
about what a lovely couple looks like.
The husband
helps his wife fill in her eyebrows.
Could you
do it for me?
You said we mustn't expose ourselves.
So, we need
to act perfectly.
Are you
really doing my eyebrows?
Are you scared?
Scared? Why would I be?
I just fear you'll fail.
Don't move.
W-What's wrong?
Why
is your face so red?
Red?
Is it?
Maybe the weather here is too hot.
I haven't adjusted yet.
- Hmm.
- Oh.
Is that so?
Of course!
I thought
you...
Well,
what?
Nothing.
Let's go.
Wait, that's not right.
The banquet doesn't start
until the afternoon.
Enjoy it.
Here, My lord.
Jiyang,
surrounded by mountains and rivers,
is easy to defend but hard to attack.
To achieve a quick victory,
we must storm the southern gate.
Thank you
for sharing the secret tunnel
leading into the city.
Though long abandoned,
this tunnel could be useful
to Wutuo.
Mr. Maningbu
and I are old friends.
Naturally, I should help him.
You're absolutely right.
Mr. Maningbu
sent me word the other day.
He cannot visit Wei himself,
but asked me to convey his gratitude.
He also said
if you ever need assistance,
Wutuo will help without reservation.
Actually,
there is something
I need your help with.
I'm glad to help.
Just say the word.
A man named Chai Anxi
currently resides in Jiyang.
Could you
get rid of him discreetly?
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪