Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Whether you're light or a lie,
I can't pull myself away ♪
♪ In this game,
truth or lie no longer matters ♪
[Queen of Darkness]
[Episode 7]
An Ning, open the door!
I'm warning you, you troublemaker.
Open the door now!
If I break it down, - Open it now!
You'll regret it even more!
- Open the door now.
- Come on!
Open the door!
I know you're inside, come out.
- Open the door.
- Stop pretending.
Open the door, An Ning!
Open the door!
Just open it!
If you don't open up, I'll break it down!
Sis, if you want to thank me
for saving your son,
there's no need for
such a grand gesture.
I... I...
Focus on the serious matter first.
Doctor.
Yes.
Draw her blood.
What's the meaning of this?
Why draw blood?
As Ti Cha's wife,
keeping yourself clean is basic.
We've arranged annual physicals
for you before.
This year is no exception.
Then why didn't you notify me earlier?
I had a drink today.
The sample wouldn't be valid.
High blood alcohol concentration
is indeed unsuitable for testing.
If you want blood,
try another day.
An Ning.
Mom wants to draw your blood
for your own good.
A little alcohol isn't a big deal.
It'll dissipate in just an hour.
We can ask the doctor to
wait a bit longer.
You awful woman.
Don't you dare play tricks on me!
Until the test is done,
no one leaves this house.
Steward.
Take all the alcohol from her room.
Yes.
Mom.
An Ning
she never drinks
but today.
Right when we need her blood test,
she downs so much.
Could it be she's figured something out?
And she's deliberately stalling now.
If she really knows something,
she'll keep finding ways to delay.
If she has something to hide,
no matter what we do,
she'll always be on guard.
We'll have to think of another way.
An Ning,
you're the best at brewing medicine
in the family.
Hurry and get it ready.
Xuan is waiting to take it.
My new nail art is way too sharp.
You don't mind, do you?
You troublemaker.
Trying to slack off again, huh?
How do you make such a mess
just brewing medicine?
Useless.
Clean up and get dinner started.
You better protect this thing.
If something goes wrong,
you can't afford the loss.
Before tomorrow's banquet,
you must bring me the results.
Madam, Miss.
Don't worry.
Even if you manage to
get the blood sample back this time,
they'll still find new ways to
harm you next time.
That's none of your business.
Give it back to me.
I do mean well, really.
But you don't have to rush to
cozy up to thank me.
Since you know they want to harm me,
why won't you let me save myself?
Even if that doctor
took the blood sample,
they can't harm you.
Ridiculous.
During my time in Song Pa's house,
have I ever hurt you?
What happened?
Didn't you tell me to trust you?
Then tell me,
why help me?
What grudge is between you and Song Pa?
You tell me nothing.
How can I trust you?
♪ Surrender to fate,
no clear direction ahead ♪
♪ Night tempts, craving her surrender ♪
♪ Never stopping the fight ♪
♪ For a gentle gaze awaits at the end ♪
♪ Surrender to love and find the way ♪
♪ Even if fate tries to forget her ♪
♪ Never despair ♪
♪ For the heart burns with endless light ♪
♪ Waiting for dawn ♪
♪ Fly away, hear she says ♪
♪ The maze in the abyss starts to clear ♪
♪ Yet night keep on whispering ♪
♪ Surrender to fate,
no clear direction ahead ♪
♪ She will rise as the dawn
that breaks the darkness ♪
♪ Never slowing down ♪
So it was you.
♪ Waiting for dawn ♪
Feeling nervous?
Have a drink, it'll calm your nerves.
It also makes the show
more fun to watch.
Inspector Huo wants to
see how I get crushed
by the Song family?
Is that so?
Then you're bound to be disappointed.
No matter what happens,
I won't be bullied anymore.
I believe you.
Let's wait and enjoy the show.
Congratulations to Mr. Song for
regaining the dock.
With this dock,
it's only a matter of time
before you become the richest man.
I heard
it was Ti Cha's wife
who got it back this time.
Ti Cha sure is a lucky man.
He married such
a beautiful and capable wife.
Sir.
Just so-so.
An Ning really is good at everything.
But she's always saying
she didn't come from a great family,
and that she's not worthy of our Ti Cha.
Well, things are better now.
She helped our family get the dock back.
She
won't have to feel guilty towards
our Song family
for not being able to
have a child anymore.
Even a hen I raise lays an egg every day,
yet she still can't have a child.
Getting scolded like that by her in-laws,
how does she even have the face
to stay here?
The Song family's loaded.
Even if she gets scolded,
she gets to spend the money.
If it were me,
I wouldn't want to leave either.
She's been scolded like crazy.
How can she put up with that?
Must be a turtle reborn.
Sir, you're right.
What are you talking about?
What nonsense...
Inspector Huo, long time no see.
Let me propose a toast.
But that glass is way too small.
I can't see your sincerity.
Uh...
Smooth talker.
Finish this bottle first.
Then I'll call it a real toast.
W... wait.
This...
Can't drink?
Let me help you.
Hey, wait, what are you doing?
That's an expensive bottle, you know.
Perfect for washing your mouth out.
Are you crazy?
Everyone.
Today,
I brought you all here
not just to cheer for An Ning's success,
but also to ask you to be our witnesses.
Madam, the doctor is here.
Let him in.
There wasn't any mistake, right?
From collecting the blood
to sending it to the testing center,
I handled every step myself.
Don't worry.
There's absolutely no problem.
An Ning.
Do you want to know
what's inside this bag?
I truly never expected
you're so treacherous.
You've lied to every single one of us!
Stop wasting words on her.
Open it up.
I'd like everyone here
to be a witness today.
This woman standing here
is not An Ning at all.
Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
She is just
an impostor.
That's nonsense!
Still talking tough at your final moment.
Listen.
This test report in my hand
is a genetic comparison
between your blood
and An Ning's blood sample.
Ti Cha.
Expose this fraud.
A face can be faked.
But DNA doesn't lie.
I won't let anyone trick the Song family.
Guys.
We.
Chose the most reputable testing center.
Based on the analysis of
the blood sample,
this...
This DNA...
DNA
shows a perfect match.
Sis.
Mom.
The tested person's DNA
aligns with the sample.
[Genetic matching index: 99.99%]
99.99%.
What does that even mean?
How could that be?
That's impossible.
You really are An Ning.
No... no way.
How did you handle this?
You told me
to bring the report sealed
as soon as it was ready.
No one was allowed to take a peek.
Not even me.
The Song family totally shot themselves
in the foot.
They tried to frame their daughter-in-law,
but ended up
embarrassing themselves instead.
I heard
they wanted to destroy
their daughter-in-law.
And take away all her shares.
So this so-called wealthy family
is actually this despicable?
Wait, what are you saying?
Mom.
What on earth is going on?
Could it be
I got it all wrong?
No way!
It must be her stirring up trouble.
Mom, mom.
Still dare to lay a hand on me?
Listen,
I've already signed
the donation agreement.
If I die,
my shares will automatically
go to the welfare institution.
An Ning.
Haven't we treated you well enough?
How could you accuse us of trying to
harm you?
Sis, you wronged me.
But I wouldn't wrong you.
Mom, you might not know this yet.
The necklace around your neck
has already been replaced
by her with a fake one.
Officail Website : dramacool.club  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
♪ Mist coils around the sleeping forest ♪
♪ Memories scattered
through cracks of darkness ♪
♪ How to escape this real-feeling dream ♪
♪ Lies reflect in water's gleam ♪
♪ Traces of existence
can never be erased ♪
♪ How to find the self I can't reclaim ♪
♪ Fly away, hear she says ♪
♪ She'll fly out from
thorns of woven lies ♪
♪ Pierce the fog,
shatter this dream tonight ♪
♪ Burn like fire ♪
♪ Just burn like fire ♪
♪ The maze in the abyss starts to clear ♪
♪ Yet night keep on whispering ♪
♪ Surrender to fate,
no clear direction ahead ♪
♪ She will rise as the dawn
that breaks the darkness ♪
♪ Never slowing down,
for tomorrow cannot be stopped ♪
♪ Surrender to love and find the way ♪
♪ Even if fate tries to forget her ♪
♪ Never despair,
for the heart burns with endless light ♪
♪ Waiting for dawn ♪
[Copyright of this short drama
belongs to]
[Shanghai Chuqi Weishi
Culture Media Co., Ltd.]
[and Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[Co., Ltd.]
[Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[holds exclusive global online
and broadcast rights]