(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
Shen Gu,
will you consider my proposal?
Miss Xu, Mr. Xu is in critical condition!
He needs to be sent
to the hospital now!
=Echoes of Gang City=
=Episode 2=
(I Saw You in My Dreams)
(Gang City Central Hospital)
- Doctor.
How's my grandfather?
He's out of danger now.
Mr. Xu is nearly a hundred years old.
His heart and lung reserves,
as well as his recovery ability,
are very weak.
The surgery
could have caused severe complications.
Fortunately, Mr. Shen brought in
the country's top specialist
from City A yesterday,
so the operation could
be carried out in time and effectively.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Don't let us keep you.
Don't mention it.
You're putting in so much effort
for my dad.
Are you looking for a way
to get close to the Xu family?
Uncle Zhaohui,
he saved Grandfather.
He suddenly turns into
the largest shareholder of Junlin Group.
Who's to say
he won't set his sights
on our family's assets next?
Wanxin,
I have a good assessment of people.
You should
keep your distance from him.
Since Mr. Xu's stable now,
I won't disturb you further.
See yourself out.
I'll walk him out.
Wanxin.
Uncle Zhaohui.
(Third Floor, Operating Room)
You should stay
and wait for Grandfather.
Mr. Shen.
I'm sorry about that.
I apologize for my uncle.
You don't need to apologize for anyone.
Wanxin.
There was an incident
while your dad's body
was being transported back to Gang City.
Mr. Shen helped coordinate everything.
The body has now been placed
at the funeral home.
There are also a few documents here
that you need to sign.
(Gang City Public Mortuary,
Department of Health)
(Family Confirmation and Signature)
(Xu)
Excuse me.
I need a moment.
Uncle Zhaohui.
Hello, Hao?
What are you doing?
I'm busy preparing for the wedding.
At a time like this?
Don't say I didn't warn you.
My father is hospitalized.
Even Shen Gu showed up to help.
No matter how busy you are,
you should come by.
This is an important stage
for you and Wanxin.
You need to show your sincerity.
Shen Gu?
What is he doing there?
What is he doing here?
You should know that better than anyone.
Mr. Shen, I'm really grateful
for everything you've done
for my grandfather and dad.
My uncle's words don't represent me.
So,
have you considered
my proposal?
Sorry.
Hi.
Hello?
We are the Legal Department
of Qingniao Group.
Okay. I see.
I'll check it immediately.
Thank you.
Okay.
(Qingniao Group Investment Contract)
(Dear Miss Xu Wanxin,)
(please accept our condolences.)
(Mr. Xu Zhaoming)
(had signed an agreement with Qingniao Group
before his passing.)
(Due to unforeseen circumstances,)
(Qingniao Group)
(has reassigned the liaison to you...)
(Xu Zhaoming)
(and will continue the investment.)
(Please contact us as soon as possible.)
(Total investment is 5.2 billion.)
Arrange for the company to notify Xu Wanxin
about the partnership
as soon as her grandfather's
surgery is done.
Shen Gu,
I need to warn you about this.
Aren't you worried
that with Qingniao's contract,
she might not marry you?
What matters now isn't marrying me.
It's helping her get through this.
Mr. Shen,
will you say yes?
Yes, I will.
Mr. Shen,
below us is Gang City.
(One day earlier)
Shen Gu,
you pushed me to the front
all these years
while you expanded the market
behind the scene
and laid groundwork in Gang City.
Was it really
all because of Shen Tingyuan?
Or was it because
you wanted to stand before
Miss Xu Wanxin as soon as possible?
Answer me.
Because you're a good actor.
Boss,
Mr. Xu's plane has gone off radar.
CEO of Minghui Group, Mr. Xu Zhaoming,
was involved
in a helicopter crash
and died at the age of 57.
We've also received news
from Gang City.
Chairman Xu collapsed into a coma
after hearing the news.
This sudden and heavy blow
will definitely impact the company.
Both the stock market
and internal operations will be affected.
Change the flight path.
We're returning to Gang City.
Wanxin is dealing with too much
right now.
Shen Gu,
I understand how you feel,
but going back now
means facing Shen Tingyuan
ahead of time.
This isn't the best timing
for both you and Qingniao.
Are you sure?
Rerouting will take time.
Request an emergency landing.
We return as fast as possible.
So you finally came back.
The company has reached out
to Xu Wanxin.
And then?
She proposed to me.
And I accepted.
Shen Gu,
do you know that forging
official documents is illegal?
As you can see,
we're legally married now.
From this moment on,
I am Xu Wanxin's rightful husband.
I can stand by her side openly
and do everything for her.
But
no one asked you.
I just felt like saying it.
Are you going to tell her
that you're the founder of Qingniao?
Qingniao's cooperation with Minghui
has always existed.
I don't want things between us
to get complicated
because of this investment.
Wanxin has too much to deal with.
When everything settles,
I'll tell her.
Mr. Lover, you should be acting
in romance dramas.
Anyway, congratulations, Mr. Gu.
You got what you wanted.
Wishing you and Miss Xu Wanxin
a pleasant cooperation.
No.
A happy, long marriage.
I'll take that.
(Shen Gu, Xu Wanxin)
Congratulations.
Everyone,
today
is my daughter Lin Shuyi's
18th birthday.
Before she leaves for Europe to study,
I hereby announce
a marriage alliance
between the Lin and Shen families.
Mr. Lin.
I entrust the Lin family's trade
to you.
Thank you, Mr. Lin.
You look beautiful today.
A union of two families.
A pact will be signed.
May your marriage be everlasting
and you be perfectly matched.
The peach blossoms in full bloom
reveal the perfect time for marriage.
May your descendants flourish
like trailing vines,
generation after generation.
Let your vow to grow old together
be set down in writing,
like a blessed union
inscribed on a romantic red leaf,
and recorded
in the Book of Devoted Mandarin Ducks.
Here is the certificate.
You're here.
Wanxin.
Come.
Let's talk outside.
This is my favorite soup.
You're the best.
Don't change the subject.
It's only been half a day,
and you've gotten married.
What happened?
Didn't we say
we'd figure things out together?
Grandfather might wake up soon.
If he finds out you married Shen Hao...
It's Shen Gu.
(Shen Gu, Xu Wanxin)
Shen Gu?
The Shen Madam Song mentioned?
Why?
He was the one
who proposed cooperation first.
He came back to Gang City
because of Shen Tingyuan.
After I learned
he's the largest shareholder of Junlin,
I proposed marriage to him.
I need his power
to fight against
Shen Tingyuan's takeover.
But
it's only been half a day.
You made a huge decision just like that?
Do you even know him?
Do you know his past?
Do you know his real intentions?
What if he turns out
to be another Shen Hao?
It's just a contract marriage.
We've agreed
that we can divorce
once our goals are achieved.
No matter what,
I can't let Uncle Zhaohui
and Shen Tingyuan succeed.
I have to stabilize Minghui
before Grandfather wakes up.
I have to protect everything
my family has built.
I just hoped you'd get married
for love
and to someone truly worth it.
I know.
It's strange.
The man in my dreams
was Shen Gu.
(Gang City Marriage Registry)
Please confirm the validity of your documents
and verify that the names
and ID numbers
match exactly.
- No problem.
I call upon all persons here
present to witness that I,
Shen Gu, take thee, Xu Wanxin,
to be my lawful wedded wife.
- I do.
Alright.
Please sign the form.
(Shen Gu, Xu Wanxin)
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on no distance
could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled
one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending
we face?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪