(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(Lee Je Hoon)
(Jang Hyuk Jin, Bae Yoo
Ram, Kim Eui Sung, Pyo Ye Jin)
(Taxi Driver 3)
(This drama is a work of fiction.)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Children and animals were
filmed under guidelines.)
One.
- Two. Three.
- Four.
One, two, three, four.
- Move it! One.
- One.
One.
One, two, three, four.
- Hey.
- Comsec.
The training's pretty brutal, right?
Tell me about it.
Rookies are supposed to get stuck
with the tough training, you know?
Speaking of which, I have a
drill the day after tomorrow.
Seriously? It wasn't on the schedule.
Yes. It's a joint operation
with the artillery unit.
A combat tactical drill for
a B24 point-of-origin strike.
A combat tactical drill? I
guess we can't talk for a while.
Yes, looks like it.
When you get your training bonus,
you owe me barbecue and drinks.
Nice try. You're buying.
Talk to you when you get back.
Roger that. Good luck out there.
Okay.
According to an intelligence report,
the risk of a localized provocation
by North Korea's army is increasing.
The objective of this drill
is to ensure we are fully prepared
for a surprise North Korean attack.
Assume the North will attack
with their most elite forces.
Effective immediately, per
this drill's security protocol,
all personnel will
surrender their cell phones,
and conduct an inspection of
all personal firearms and gear.
Master Sergeant Yoo, stay.
The rest of you, dismissed!
On your feet!
Salute the Commander!
- Unity!
Unity!
Dismissed!
- As you were!
Here.
- What is this, sir?
- Tomorrow, your team skips K43.
You'll move to Sector B24 instead.
Sector B24, sir?
I've marked the coordinates.
Report to me as soon as you arrive.
Any questions?
No, sir.
Unity.
Dismissed.
Tomorrow, your team skips K43.
You'll move to Sector B24 instead.
A combat tactical drill for
a B24 point-of-origin strike.
Unity!
- Sir, I'll drive!
- Just get in. We're out of time.
Yes, sir.
You'll move to Sector B24 instead.
B24.
They're going here at this hour?
(Sector B24)
It's all getting torched anyway.
Did you have to bring so much?
I prepared everything as
instructed by General Oh.
General Oh, I swear.
The MDL explosion?
- Good prep.
- Thank you, sir.
- What was that?
- Sir? What is it?
Didn't you hear that?
I didn't hear a thing, sir.
Never mind. Let's unload the vests first.
Yes, sir.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
You really can't tell the difference.
Be careful, sir! It could go off!
It even weighs about the
same as the standard vest.
But sir, isn't blowing up
all eight of them a bit much?
You arrogant jerk. You
must've lost your mind.
I'm sorry, sir. I'll drive!
Blow them up?
(C4 military-grade explosive)
Unit, attention!
Salute the commander!
Unity!
At ease!
About-face!
Commence training!
- Commence!
This live drill prepares us
for North Korean provocations.
You will all advance as far as
the northern perimeter of the GOP.
Upon arrival at Sector B24,
equip vests from the barracks
and move out immediately.
But sir, isn't blowing up
all eight of them a bit much?
This is a critical mission,
so give it your absolute all,
and get the best rating. Understood?
- Yes, sir!
Get in the passenger seat. I'm driving.
- Move it!
- Yes, ma'am.
Get out.
- I said, get out!
- Yes, ma'am!'
Everyone, dismount the truck.
Move it! Out!
- Yes, ma'am!
Effective immediately,
you will all return to base.
- We must have misheard you, ma'am.
- You heard me, didn't you?
Everyone, return to base!
- Yes, ma'am! Understood!
This is Training Headquarters.
Team Alpha, do you copy?
Team Alpha?
Team Alpha, acknowledge
transmission immediately!
I repeat. This is Training
HQ. Team Alpha, do you copy?
- Team Alpha, answer me!
- Let me.
This is the Commander.
Master Sergeant Yoo, what is your location?
I know what you were planning to do to us.
What?
What did you possibly hope to gain
by sending your men to their deaths?
Master Sergeant Yoo Sun
A, what are you talking about...
What were you planning to
do with those bomb vests?
She's lost her darn mind.
If you can't answer me, then I'm going
straight to the Military Prosecution
with what you've planted here.
Hey, Yoo Sun A! You
know this is insubordination!
(Ministry of National Defense
Initial report: Explosion near MDL)
Let's do this.
Master Sergeant Yoo Sun A!
Are you really disobeying a direct order?
Are you?
You're no longer soldiers.
Get ready to be dishonorably discharged.
You're not getting out of
here with that stuff anyway.
Yoo Sun A, think this through.
I don't know what on
earth has gotten into you,
but you're almost up for your pension.
If you get discharged
for pulling a stunt like this,
how is your mother supposed to get by?
Let's say we've acquired
critical intelligence,
but on our way back to base, we
run into an unavoidable problem.
What do we do with the intel?
Your safety comes before the intel.
If your safety isn't guaranteed,
you abandon the critical intelligence.
If you stop right now,
I'll make this all go away.
Master Sergeant Yoo,
let's just drop this. All right?
Cut the nonsense.
That road only leads to North Korea.
What are you going to do,
defect to the North with it?
This is your last chance.
If you don't surrender right now,
Master Sergeant Yoo Sun A,
you'll be seen as an armed deserter.
(Military Demarcation Line)
Darn it!
But if, despite all that,
you find yourself in a
life-or-death situation,
you pass on the intel
using our team's protocol.
What is that protocol?
(Landmine)
Find the bird's nest in
the closest tree due west,
and secure the intel inside it.
If anything should happen to me,
I'm trusting you to find this.
Captain Kim Do Gi.
That crazy wench.
That darn commie jerk just won't listen.
What should we report to the command?
Weren't you listening?
That commie jerk smuggled out weapons
to try and sell them to the North,
and ended up getting killed in an accident.
Yes, sir. I'll write up the
incident report just like that.
Darn it.
The general will ream me out for this.
Master Sergeant Yoo
Sun A gave up her life
to save her comrades.
Exactly.
And that's what makes
this even more infuriating.
And nobody even knows
she was murdered so unjustly.
The jerks who did this to
Master Sergeant Yoo Sun A
are still out there, walking free.
But we know the truth.
So we have to fight.
It's going to be a tough fight.
And it won't be over quickly.
You know that too, Captain.
But if you're doing this, Captain,
I'll see it through with you.
The methods you're used
to, Master Sergeant Park,
won't work on these people.
Sir?
For people who defy all common sense,
we have to be unreasonable right back.
It's the only way.
(Taxi Driver 3)
Are these the people you called?
Yes, they are.
They are ecological survey specialists.
Then why did you lie about being a general?
What? I never said such a thing.
Hey, you said he pulled rank.
When we asked who he was,
he just said he was a general.
He said if we didn't open the
gate, he'd just turn around and leave.
I didn't say I was a general.
I said, "I'm Jang Seong Cheol."
My name is Jang Seong Cheol.
Besides, if you won't open, what
can I do? I should turn around.
I ran a check on you too. Nothing came up.
I'm not surprised you couldn't find me.
You see, I am
a ghost agent. I exist,
but on paper, I don't.
But you said he's your son.
This is technically classified.
I'm his team leader. He's like a son to me.
And he's like a father to me.
Why that...
Then what's this?
We didn't want to show up empty-handed.
So, you're all here to research birds?
- Yes.
- And your affiliation?
That's classified.
You took the motor pool logs, didn't you?
- Yes.
- For your darn bird investigation?
- That's classified.
- Hey!
Birds are pretty free-spirited, aren't they?
Are these guys messing with me?
- Hello?
- Colonel Kim Tae Hyun.
This is Major General Jo
Sang Hoon from Special Ops.
- Sir, Unity!
- Right. Keep up the hard work.
Did the people I sent make it there okay?
The Black Eagle Team. You're
the one who sent them, sir?
It's of national importance, so
make sure you look after them.
Help them with anything
they need. All right, carry on.
I know what you were planning to do to us.
What did you possibly hope to gain
by sending your men to their deaths?
Master Sergeant Yoo Sun
A, what are you talking about...
What were you planning to
do with those bomb vests?
If you can't answer me, then I'm going
straight to the Military Prosecution
with what you've planted here.
What kind of person could even
think about killing their own soldiers?
That Master Sergeant Yoo
Sun A was really something else.
So courageous.
You should've told us this was happening.
Why did you just leave without a word?
You even ditched your phone
and were completely unreachable.
You knew we'd be worried sick.
I'm sorry.
It was too personal. I
couldn't ask you guys for help.
That's even more
reason to ask for our help.
Hang on a second.
Driver Kim called us for a personal matter?
He even sent us a page.
This is basically a job
request from Driver Kim. Right?
- It's totally a job request.
- Exactly.
- A job request?
- I even had to
return to the military.
How much is the taxi
fare going to be for this?
Captain, so you're saying
these people came here in a taxi?
All right, it looks like
everyone's caught up.
I think we have some work to do here.
What's our first move?
We need to find them.
Who did this, and why.
We've found two so far.
The colonel and the first lieutenant.
You need higher command
approval to form a temporary unit,
and plan a joint operation.
You're saying a general is involved.
Someone who would go as
far as killing their own allies
just for personal gain.
Do you have anyone in mind?
One person comes to mind,
but he's in no position to be
doing something like this right now.
- Either way, I'm in.
- Me too.
Just don't make us worry like that again.
I'm docking the taxi
fare from your paycheck.
I'm sorry, Captain. I have
no idea what this is about.
I'm on board too. What a great plan.
Radio Operator!
The power's out! Go check it!
You can't just flip
random breakers like that.
Look, I know it's a hassle.
That's why I brought this order.
Look there.
See the wire? There's
a bird's nest on the wire.
If you leave that on, what happens to us?
That's not it. If we cut the power now,
our security will be compromised!
This is wrong, I'm telling you.
Just a little more! A little more.
Just stall for time.
If you turn it on now, I'll die!
- He'll die!
- Hey, Radio Operator.
It's still not working. Hurry and check it.
I'm just checking on the nest right now.
- Tell him he'll be dead instantly!
- We might as well just die.
We're out of time. Should we die?
Bury me at the National Cemetery!
- I...
- Do you want to end up in the brig?
- How much longer?
- All right. Five seconds!
- Five seconds!
- Five seconds. Not six, five.
- Hey, Radio Operator.
- Yes, I'm checking it right now.
- Aren't you done yet?
- Three seconds.
- Okay. Transfer complete.
- Okay. We're done here too.
We did it!
The PC is booting up. It's coming up.
Hey, the comms are back up. You did great.
I've secured all the data we need.
Man, that was tough.
You've got what it
takes to be a true soldier.
- Let's go.
- A true soldier! One, two, three.
Captain, who did you call? What do they do?
I still have absolutely no idea
what you're trying to accomplish.
Sometimes in life, things
happen that defy common sense,
and you must be the one to
respond. Remember I said that?
Yes.
Whatever you see, Master Sergeant Park,
I need you to look the other way.
And trust me.
If that's an order, sir, I'll do it.
Then again, I didn't understand
what you were saying anyway.
(Citizen happiness, national prosperity)
(Lunar calendar, October 10)
It is done!
November?
There's not much time left.
(Colonel Kim Tae Hyun)
(Command center)
The person you are trying
to reach is unavailable...
(Bird investigation)
This is the 2802nd Unit's
roster for the next operation.
(Unit 2802, Additional deployment roster)
Hey, this is classified
information. How did you get this?
They're restarting the
operation that failed
because of Master Sergeant Yoo.
Under the guise of a training exercise.
Shouldn't we stop this exercise
immediately, Driver Kim?
What do we do now, Driver Kim?
Driver Kim?
- Why is everyone calling you that?
- Master Sergeant Park.
Yes, Driver Kim Do Gi. No, I mean, Driver.
No, Captain. Yes.
Master Sergeant Park, you will
return to your original unit today.
But sir, I'd like to stay and help.
I have a job for you back at your unit.
Can I ask you for a favor?
Of course. If it's for you,
I'll do anything you ask.
- Go Eun, I have a favor to ask you.
- Yes? What is it?
(Command center)
I'm sorry to keep calling you.
I wonder what has our
Tae Hyun in such a hurry?
A new investigation team
has arrived at the base,
and more than a few things
about them are suspicious.
Above all, this guy, Kim Do Gi,
was the late Yoo Sun A's commander.
With something this big planned,
we can't afford any suspicion.
Weeds must be pulled out from the root.
(Establishing military discipline)
Hello, is this the Human Rights Center?
I have something to report.
I'm heading over right now.
Hello?
Is anybody here?
(Special Warfare School)
Go Eun. Go Eun, are you okay?
I'm okay.
(Lieutenant General Oh Won Sang)
Come in.
Unity!
I have selected the elite
personnel you requested.
You're more proactive than I expected.
And your training evaluations
are always top-notch.
- You've earned your reputation.
- Thank you, sir.
But I haven't been briefed
yet. What is the mission, sir?
I have a special mission in mind,
and I'm thinking of entrusting it to you.
Pull this off, and I'll make
sure you get promoted.
Intel confirms an inspection tour
near Kaesong on December 13.
(Predicted Route and Operation Plan)
Take a platoon under your
command, send them in,
and take his head this time.
I don't see an extraction route, sir.
Extraction?
According to this plan,
they'll run out of fuel infiltrating.
- Extraction will be impossible.
- Right.
You don't have to go.
Send your best soldiers.
Don't worry about the rest.
Without an extraction route,
the entire team will be killed, sir.
For this kind of mission, the
fewer people know, the better.
Captain Kim Do Gi.
You know about pigs, right?
You fatten them up just
for a single slaughter.
Those men you're
training... They're all pigs.
You use them for one thing only. Only once.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Is this
an order, sir?
I'm not in a position to ask favors, am I?
Crystal clear, sir.
I'll begin preparations at once, sir.
Unity!
Good. That's how you get ahead.
Unity.
(Indomitable Spirit, Absolute
Loyalty and Obedience)
(Special Warfare Command)
All personnel are on
standby for deployment, sir.
- About today's operation...
- Yoo Sun A.
Park Jae Won.
- Yes, sir.
As of today, the entire
company is on leave.
Sir?
I must have misheard you, sir.
You did well in the last evaluation,
and I still owe you a reward.
So this is it.
From this moment on, until
you receive another order,
no one is to return to base.
Under any circumstances.
Understood?
- Sir?
- Yes, sir!
Yes, sir!
- Unity.
Unity.
It was the man I suspected.
After his dishonorable
discharge for sexual harassment,
our records show he's raising
snakes and chickens in the country.
He's a civilian now.
A civilian is controlling the military?
Seriously? How is that even possible?
The impossible is happening as we speak.
He knew our every move.
The men who attacked Driver
Kim and me were soldiers.
That means he already
has his hooks in the military.
This is far more
dangerous than we realized.
My fellow citizens.
Today, in Sector B24 near
the Military Demarcation Line,
the North Korean Army launched
a large-scale armed provocation.
Our brave soldiers of
the Republic of Korea
have fallen in an attack by the enemy.
This massive, deadly
attack by North Korea
is an assault on our freedom, democracy,
and the foundation of
our constitutional system.
It is a crime against humanity.
Our government, in
accordance with the Constitution,
and the procedures established by law,
to ensure the security of the
nation and the safety of its people,
and under the authority of
Article 77 of the Constitution,
and Article two of the Martial Law Act,
declares emergency martial law
throughout the Republic of Korea.
I hear you were promoted
to general. Congratulations.
It's all thanks to your support.
- Thank you so much.
- Is that what matters right now?
Saving our country is what matters.
A dream you dream alone
is nothing but a delusion.
This is going to happen. It's inevitable.
All we have to do is create the pretext.
Here.
My dear boy, Kim Tae Hyun...
Yes, sir.
Are the preparations
proceeding without a hitch?
Yes, sir. As instructed, we have
twice the required personnel.
Listen.
You can't afford any mistakes this time.
I will not fail you again.
Those soldiers we're sending...
Their only purpose is to train
hard and die a worthy death.
Yes, sir. That's correct.
Those boys will be fertilizer for
the boundless growth of our nation.
Ensure they get a good burial
plot. Somewhere with a good breeze.
Yes, sir. Understood.
Hey. Get me a glass of water over here.
- Hey, Tae Hyun. Self-serve here.
- Right.
- I'll get it.
- Thank you.
- Darn it.
- Gosh.
- Darn it. Hey.
- Goodness.
I'm so sorry.
I'll get you another cup right away. Sorry.
- It's fine. Don't worry about it.
- I'll get you another one.
- Unity!
- Unity.
What are you doing, saluting a civilian?
- Go on.
- Take care, sir.
You wouldn't take my offered hand,
and now you send this surprise gift.
You mean the Black
Eagle Investigation Team?
General Oh. We still have
Black Eagles in our country.
It is a wonderful surprise, isn't it?
Let me ask you something.
There are no Black Eagles in our country.
The people you sent will
soon meet the same fate.
(Jo Sang Hoon, 1st sweep)
(1st sweep: Yeouido 40, Press
200, Secure holding for minimum 500)
Good thing they didn't notice
we switched out the body cam.
So, they're going to kill us, right?
Yes. We're the Black Eagle
Investigation Team, after all.
They'll send soldiers to the
MDL's northernmost point,
then shell their position
and kill all of them.
Then they'll frame the
North Korean Army for it.
As a pretext, they attack the
North, forcing them to retaliate.
And just like that, it's war.
I'm sorry, but that
sounds completely insane.
The idea that their goal is to start a war,
and for the military to do
it under civilian direction.
An official notice is already
out. For all of our arrests.
Gosh, they don't waste any time, do they?
They plan to start their
operation at 10pm tonight.
(November 29, 2025, at 10pm,
Target sectors R-D4, XG-07)
- Then it's time to start our war.
- Yes.
(Command center)
(Special Mission Unit Rules of Conduct)
Company, attention!
Salute the company commander!
- Unity!
Unity!
As you were!
Sir! For the infiltration drill, all
82 personnel are accounted for!
- At ease.
- At ease!
At ease!
Through this live combat infiltration drill,
we'll prove we can counter any
provocation with one fatal blow.
It will prove we are more
than capable of doing so.
Show them what we're made of. Understood?
- Yes, sir!
About face!
Commencing infiltration
drill, effective immediately!
- Move out!
Team Beta, upon arrival at sector B-24,
put on the op vests stationed at
the rally point and await orders.
Understood?
- Yes, sir!
(Bird investigation)
What's this?
Unity!
- Unity!
At ease.
Unity!
Transmitting fire-mission data now.
Origin, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4,
3, 2, 1, 0. Altitude, 150m.
Sector B-24, 18 high-explosive rounds.
I repeat. Sector B-24, 18
high-explosive rounds. Over.
Seagull One, applying fire data.
Seagull Two, applying fire data.
Seagull Three, applying fire data. Over.
ETA to sector B-24 is 10:30pm.
All Seagull units, prepare
to fire. Report when ready.
Seagull One, ready to fire!
Seagull Two, ready to fire!
- Seagull Three, ready to fire!
- We're ready, sir!
Awaiting your command, sir.
Put on your op vests now. Move!
- Move!
- Fire at 10pm sharp.
- Order from command.
Artillery, time on target 10pm. Over.
- Fall in!
This is Team Beta. All
personnel are wearing op vests.
Awaiting orders.
This is Team Beta.
All personnel have op vests
on. Awaiting orders, do you copy?
Fire on all of them, pigs and
vests. I want them obliterated.
What is this?
Hey, what's that? This is crazy.
What is this operation?
What is this?
This is Team Beta. Do you copy?
This is Team Beta. Respond.
- Just cut the comms.
- Yes, sir.
One minute to fire.
It's a great strength to have you,
my comrades, at my side for the new world.
We have 30 seconds.
Colonel Kim.
What?
- Did you hear that?
- I didn't hear anything.
I don't think I heard any artillery fire.
Hey, what happened?
(Warning)
Are you certain you relayed
the correct firing time?
Why don't I hear any darn artillery fire?
Because we didn't fire, sir.
What did you just say?
Say that again, you jerk!
I'm sorry, sir, but we
cannot follow that order.
You scum, do you have a death wish?
We cannot fire on civilians, sir.
(Warning)
Civilians?
All artillery units are pulling out.
Captain, a civilian vehicle is approaching.
What are you talking about?
- What's going on?
- Captain.
- Stay sharp. On alert.
- Hey, stay sharp! On alert!
- Yes, sir! On alert!
- Hey, get them!
On alert!
- There's a box truck coming down.
- What on earth?
- Hey! Muzzles up!
- It's coming down!
- I think it's a bus!
- It looks full of civilians.
Stay calm and don't
cross your lines of fire!
Sergeant, it looks like a civilian vehicle.
There are civilians inside.
- Stop!
- Stop! Sergeant!
- What's the situation?
- A bus has come in.
- Hold your position.
We'll hold our position
and wait for orders.
Hey! Give me remote
access now. I'll do it myself.
They're saying there
are civilians in Sector B24.
Hey, who cares if they're
civilians or soldiers?
We'll just say the North Korean
Army killed them all anyway.
Darn it.
What are you doing?
Give me remote access!
Inside that sector,
there are civilians.
Hey, you got a death
wish? Patch me through now!
Give me remote access now!
- Connect him.
- Connecting now, sir.
Connection established.
- What was that?
- There's a one-star here.
This is insane.
- We're all going to die, aren't we?
- Something's definitely wrong.
Goodness.
Now,
the great undertaking begins.
- Let's go!
- Hurry up!
- Looks like it's starting.
- Right. I'd better get my shots.
- Okay, camera on. Get in there.
- Right.
Go.
(Elements Guerrilla Concert,
With our comrades-in-arms)
What is this?
Here you go, Elements light sticks.
Here you go.
Elements light sticks for you too.
(Elements Guerrilla Concert,
With our comrades-in-arms)
Here, take two. There you go.
- Thank you.
- Here.
Attack!
I said open fire, darn it!
What are you waiting for,
you jerks? I said, open fire!
You scums.
(32S 7808)
Welcome.
- Hello.
- Elements, bringing you happiness.
- We are Elements!
(Elements Guerrilla Concert,
With our comrades-in-arms)
What are you doing, you jerks?
They say they can't obey the order, sir.
Hey, Tae Hyun.
Tae Hyun!
What are you doing, you jerks?
Hey, stupid idiot. Get out!
(Elements Guerrilla Concert,
With our comrades-in-arms)
So pretty.
Okay, Elements, it's time to go.
(Elements Guerrilla Concert,
With our comrades-in-arms)
Die!
Shots fired!
That's a reassuring sight.
Those guys must have realized it by now.
That what they were
chasing wasn't a dream,
but a delusion.
They're the ones who saved us.
(Elements Guerrilla Concert,
With our comrades-in-arms)
- Captain Kim.
- Yes, sir.
That Black Eagle ecological survey
must have been quite the ordeal.
- You've been through a lot.
- Thank you, sir.
It's good to see you all.
- Unity.
- Sir.
Unity.
Master Sergeant Park Jae Won
went to a lot of trouble to
swap all the bombs for fireworks.
But you know...
Do you really need that many fireworks?
I wasn't sure how many
they'd need to set off.
Gosh, that's a lot of fireworks.
(Elements Guerrilla Concert,
With our comrades-in-arms)
All right, then.
Shall we go take care of business?
Let's go get those jerks
before they all run off.
We'll be on our way, sir.
Unity!
Unity.
That jerk!
I told you we should've
bailed before this got messy.
But won't accepting that note
cause problems for us later?
Just say you never got it.
The CCTV at the burger
joint could have caught us.
Then say it was folded so
you didn't see what it was.
I put it straight into my
pocket, so I didn't see it.
I'll drive.
All right, Generals!
You're all under arrest.
Take them all in!
- What are you talking about?
- What unit are you with?
- Hey, freeze!
- Hey!
- Come with me.
- Get off me, you jerk!
Move it.
Let go.
(Deluxe Taxi)
Those jerks.
Chief Choi, stop the car!
(Deluxe Taxi)
Chief Choi! Chief Park!
Go Eun!
Hey, can you get up? Can you stand?
Gyeong Gu, are you okay?
- What about you? You okay?
- Is everyone okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- This way.
- Chief Choi...
- Yes?
You jerks!
Hey! Why?
Hey!
You worthless scums.
- Die!
- Go Eun!
- You...
Do you have any idea what you've ruined?
This was an operation
to save the country from a crisis! Darn it.
A man who claims he'll save the country
treats the people who live
in it worse than insects
in reality.
- Isn't that the bigger problem?
- Hey, you think that matters?
What's the big deal about that?
You people
are destined to lose.
- Driver Kim!
- Do Gi!
Damn it.
We won't know how this ends
until we get to the end.
When the desperation and
courage of everyone come together,
it's a force to be reckoned with.
Gosh.
Take one more step,
and see just how this ends.
Do you want to see?
- Do Gi!
- Driver Kim!
Driver Kim!
Give up!
You should have
just kept your head down where you belong.
Why?
Why on earth did you
all crawl in here to die?
Why?
- Driver Kim!
- Do Gi!
- Make one move.
- Driver Kim!
- I'll kill him!
Don't!
We will never
lose to people like you.
- Driver Kim!
- Do Gi!
- No!
(To save one life is to save the world.)
You have a big appetite, Chief
Choi. Why aren't you eating?
- I'm full.
- Already? And you, Chief Park?
Who taught you to grab the drumstick first?
- I raised this chicken myself.
- Thank you.
This guy's something else.
- Let's have a drink.
- Okay.
- Cheers.
By the way,
has this thought ever crossed your mind?
- What?
- What thought?
If everything that happened
to us never happened,
what do you think our lives would be like?
Do you think we ever would have met?
I doubt we would have met.
We'd all probably be working
hard at our separate jobs.
That's true. We're all
dedicated to our work.
You never know.
When, where, or how we
might have crossed paths.
That's right.
We could've gone on a trip one day
and happened to run into each other.
- Okay, I'm taking it now.
- Okay.
Dad, scoot in a little closer.
Okay, big smiles now. One, two, three.
One, two, three.
Okay.
It came out great. Should we
get a picture of the three of us?
Oh, dear.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, would you like
me to take a picture for you?
Thank you so much. That would be great.
- Smile.
- Okay.
One, two, three.
I'm so sorry.
Or what if we went to a restaurant
from TV and ran into one another?
You're not late. We
were just getting started.
- You guys started eating?
- This place is seriously good.
I can't wait to see your wedding dress.
- I come here sometimes.
- Oh, really?
- You know that one?
- It's good, right?
- Yes, it's really good.
- Right?
- Have some meat.
- No, you go ahead.
- Oh, gosh.
- What is it?
This place is amazing.
I've been here before.
Or we could've just bumped into
each other walking down the street.
Are you okay?
Yes. Thank you.
- No problem.
- All right.
Thank you.
- Right.
When you think about it,
I guess we would've
met again, no matter what.
Somehow, I feel like we were bound to meet.
I guess it was meant to be.
- Here, have a drink.
- Thanks.
Me too.
- All right, how about a toast?
- Yes!
Cheers.
Go Eun.
Yes?
Could you take care of the bill?
Sure.
You look exhausted. Trouble
sleeping again last night?
No. I think I'm coming down with a cold.
When that happens, it's better
to just get some proper rest.
I'm fine.
I actually feel better when I'm working.
You sure don't look like it.
(Rainbow Transport)
You get a steady paycheck,
so you better earn it.
Is killing one little wench that hard?
Finding an agency that kills
people is harder than you'd think.
Turn on the TV. Hitmen are a dime a dozen.
You're just
making excuses for your own incompetence.
I'm sorry, ma'am. I'll
try looking a little harder.
About your missing sister, Rim Bok Ja...
Someone says she was seen
overseas. I think we'll find her soon.
Hey!
What's this "sister" nonsense?
I've never even laid eyes on her.
Instead of her appearing suddenly
demanding half the inheritance,
getting rid of her quietly
overseas is a lot cleaner, isn't it?
I believe I've found a contractor.
The meeting spot...
Didn't you say it was by the port?
So why are we driving
further up into the mountains?
I think there might be
an error with the GPS.
- Rerouting.
- That's strange.
We're probably losing service
because you drove us out to nowhere!
There's a taxi right here.
I'll go see if it's in service.
(Deluxe Taxi)
Is this a pottery studio?
Pottery...
An axe?
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
I'm a little lost.
Is this taxi in service?
His leg.
I just saw the taxi here, so...
- Need a ride?
- No.
I don't want a ride.
You saw something you shouldn't have.
Something you shouldn't have seen.
Gosh.
What? Isn't this a pottery kiln?
Wait a minute.
I know
this is going to sound incredibly strange,
but I've actually been desperately
looking for someone just like you.
What's taking her so long?
Hey!
Haven't we
met somewhere
before?
If you have time,
would you like to have
a glass of wine with me?
I have a feeling
you and I would really hit it off.
Don't you think?
I think we already have.
It's hot.
Okay, the feed's clear.
But wine? That seems a little risky.
(The Murder-for-Hire Case)
(Rim Bok Sun, Ma Sang Hee, secretary)
(This drama is a work of fiction.)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Special thanks to Jeon
So Nee and Kim Jong Su)
(Taxi Driver 3)
(Operation for 5283 is complete.)