STUDENT: Hey, Philip.
PHILIP: Hey, dude.
STUDENT: What's up?
Did you pass that midterm?
PHILIP: Not really.
WOMAN: Hey, Philip.
MAN: Hey, what's up, Phil?
MEGAN: Thanks for lunch.
I'm really glad you guys
got to see the new clinic.
MOM: Are you kidding?
Think we'd come to Boston
and not see our girl?
We're so proud of you.
Hey, Phil, I need your
help on my cadaver.
Okay.
I've been trying for, like,
six hours to find the
posterior thoracic nerve,
and if I don't dig it up soon,
Lenhoff is gonna cut me open.
Yeah, I know. Posterior
thoracic is a bitch. Um,
I need, I need... Janet!
Janet, love,
we need you.
Come here.
Why don't I like
the sound of that?
It's all in the interest
of science, dear.
Trust me?
Sure.
Put your left hand up.
Tom, pay attention.
You just dig behind...
Sorry my hands are cold.
Dig behind the scalenus
medius, then you move aside
the brachial plexus,
and then slide down
to the serratus anterior.
And there you have it.
Posterior thoracic.
You finished, Philip?
Yes. I thank you.
Science thanks you.
Tom here thanks you.
I thank you.
All right, you guys.
I gotta go study, okay?
TOM: Sure.
Bye.
Any thoughts on why we're
seeing shortness of breath,
lethargy and dizziness
in a 7-year-old?
Eisenmenger Syndrome.
I mean, that would go with
the pulmonary hypertension.
DR. JANEWAY: That's a bit
of a leap, Mr. Markoff.
But assuming your
hypothesis is correct,
then why are we seeing
the low heart rate,
the diminished reflex
and a lack of affect?
Perhaps the fact
that a 7-year-old
boy is alone
and his parents wouldn't
bother to be with him
when he's in the hospital.
Hmm.
Personalizing, Philip?
No, sir.
BOY'S MOM:
Here you are, baby.
I had to go all the way
to the CVS on Commonwealth
to get you the cherry kind.
It'll be right here waiting
for you when you wake up.
There's a lesson for you all.
Things are not always
what they appear to be,
and even the
remarkable Mr. Markoff
isn't perfect.
All right, guys.
Next patient.
I only torture you,
because when every major
hospital comes clamoring
for you to do your
residency with them,
I want you to realize
that this place
recognizes your talent
and is gonna push you
to be even better.
Also, I... Well, I kind of
like torturing you.
(LAUGHS)
Oh!
Oh! Sorry.
Don't turn around.
What part of "don't turn"
didn't you understand?
Sorry.
Um... He is locked in.
Um, I think he's
looking at you.
Uh, no. He is definitely
(CHUCKLES)
I don't think so.
KATE: Damn.
He could not get cuter
if he was holding a
teddy bear and a puppy.
Mr. Markoff?
PHILIP: Yes?
I need your genius.
He likes you.
(LAUGHS)
MEGAN: Butene... Aromatic?
(SIGHS) Cyclooctene...
Antiaromatic.
PHILIP: Ah.
Aromatics are tough.
Yeah. (LAUGHS)
Um...
I can never figure out
which electrons to put where.
You wanna know a trick?
Don't memorize, diagram.
I'm Philip,
by the way. Markoff.
We actually met the
other day for a second.
Well, we didn't really meet.
We just kind of bumped.
(LAUGHS) Yeah.
Um, I'm Megan McAllister.
So, that's cool.
You're helping out
at the clinic.
Yeah. And you're
going to med school.
That I am.
That's cool, too.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Um, yeah, I should
really be going,
'cause I have to study.
I have this huge test
in 17 hours.
Wait. You've got
a test tomorrow,
and you are studying?
Yeah. That's what people do.
No, not me.
(LAUGHING) Um...
Okay, so what do you think
I should be doing?
I think you should be
cutting loose, airing
out your brain.
Right. Right.
So, when I fail
the test tomorrow,
can I write that theory in
at the essay portion of my
medical school applications?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Uh... So, where
are you applying?
Here, he asks hopefully?
Hmm?
Probably, but I
probably won't get in.
They really would be
lucky to have you.
You don't even know me.
Oh, my God. That's true.
Wow. Okay. Then come on.
I'll quiz you on the way.
On the way where?
729. I got your
page number.
On the way to the place
I always go the night
before an exam.
You know what?
I really have to study,
and I'm not that, you know,
"run away with a guy I've
only known for 30 seconds"
type of girl, so...
Okay. (CLEARS THROAT)
Um... Okay.
SUNY, Albany, summa cum laude.
B.U. med school, second year,
top 5% of my class.
Not bragging.
I love animals.
I don't like birds, though.
I am an unapologetic member
of the Young Republicans,
but I also don't really
like to talk politics.
Sometimes I work too hard.
And when I was little,
I really hated wearing
full-length pants.
Strange, I know.
(LAUGHS)
And in case you haven't
noticed, I really like you.
So, I'll pick you up at 8:00?
I, um, have to change.
Don't do that. Never
do that. I like you
just the way you are.
I meant my clothes.
Right. Clothes.
All right. I'll pick
you up at 7:30, then.
Okay.
All right.
So the trick
to roulette,
or at least my theory is
you gotta feel the numbers.
You know, you gotta really,
really kind of get in
sync with the wheel.
Are you hearing
yourself right now?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Yeah, it works. Watch.
Here. I'll show you.
DEALER: Final bets, please.
Place your bets,
place your bets.
Is this you hearing or
feeling the number?
(MEGAN LAUGHS)
Okay, I got it.
All right, black 22.
Oh!
Aww...
PHILIP: Well, it
doesn't always work.
I don't think
that theory works.
Or maybe someone
was distracting me.
So now it's my fault?
Yes, of course
it was your fault.
Fine. Blame it on me. (LAUGHS)
You're a bad person.
WAITRESS: Your drinks, sir.
Thank you.
MEGAN: Oh, my gosh.
That's a very pink drink.
I have to be good.
It's a school night.
All right.
Trust me, though.
The rush is gonna
be good for you,
it releases the endorphins,
gets your brain working.
Cyclopropene.
Uh... Aromatic?
There you go.
(LAUGHING)
See? You know this stuff.
You just got to
trust yourself. Okay.
Oh, okay.
Take these.
Close your eyes.
MEGAN: Okay.
And really feel them.
Feeling them.
Right.
DEALER: Last chance.
Final bets.
MEGAN: I want that one.
PHILIP: Red seven.
MEGAN: Yes.
Oh, my God!
DEALER: We got a winner here.
That's insane. Look at that.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
(LAUGHING)
I know this is probably
way too late, but you're
not dating anyone, right?
Well, I was dating
Leonardo DiCaprio,
then he moved to
Hollywood and got all
famous, so I dumped him.
Right.
Yeah.
So, I think we're good.
What are you
doing for lunch?
When?
I don't know.
The next 50, 60 years?
Well, I have to check
my book, but...
Okay.
Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What? Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, just wait.
Hi.
Mmm.
Welcome home.
Yay!
PHILIP: All right.
MEGAN: Let's go inside.
It's cold.
You're still cold?
Oh!
Heat. Yay.
You cold?
Yeah.
Give me your hands.
My mom used to do this
to keep my hands warm
when I was little.
This may be the
cutest thing ever.
Have you told your parents
we've moved in together yet?
Philip, I'm...
Look, it's important
to you, okay?
So it's important to me.
I know. And I'm gonna
tell them. I promise.
Okay.
I just don't wanna
deal with the
"You're so young.
You've only known him
for six months.
"Are you sure about this?"
Blah, blah, blah.
But I promise you,
I'm gonna tell them.
Okay.
Hey, I have an idea.
Uh-oh.
How about we
stop unpacking...
Mmm-hmm.
...order Chinese food
and study together?
Well, that sounds nice.
But I got a study group
tonight I got to go to.
Microanatomy.
Boo.
Right?
And the worst part is,
it's probably gonna
go all night,
so I wouldn't wait up
for me either.
But we can celebrate tomorrow.
I'm a med school
widow already.
I knew this would happen.
You're not. Stop.
Well, can you at least
drop these off for me?
(SIGHS)
What, are those
applications?
Yep. I only have
one more to go.
All right, all right.
Well, you're getting
into B.U.,
so I wouldn't stress it.
I like you.
I like you, too.
Do you really have to go?
Yeah, I do.
But I will kiss you
right when I get home.
Okay?
Okay.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Bye.
MEGAN: I feel like a tourist.
PHILIP: Just, you know,
squint your eyes, and then
pretend you're in Paris.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Say what?
It means I'm freezing
my butt off.
Oh, does it?
Well, here. Put your
hands in my pockets.
What are you doing?
How's that?
Is that better?
Mmm... Much better.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm gonna start
calling you Pocket.
How about that?
What's in here?
Uh...
Driver, will you stop
the carriage for a second?
What's going on?
You trust me?
Should I?
Megan McAllister,
I love you with
all of my heart.
Will you marry me?
Philip, there's nothing I want
more than to marry you, but...
But what?
I haven't even graduated yet,
and you're still
in med school and you
haven't even met my parents.
Well, let's go.
Right now. Tonight.
We can leave this second.
We'll go to New Jersey.
Driver, do you think
this horse can make
it to New Jersey?
I think the horse is gonna
get really tired and sick,
but then we'll drive.
They're gonna go crazy.
Babe, I know this might sound
a little old-fashioned,
but I really want
their blessing.
I want them to be
happy for us.
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
Philip, it's just my parents.
It's gonna be fine.
They're gonna love you.
SUSAN: Megan.
PHILIP: Hey.
MEGAN: Hi.
Honey, hi, hi.
MEGAN: Mom, Dad,
this is Philip.
Hello, Philip.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I was told you liked roses,
Mrs. McAllister.
My weakness. Thank you.
And please, call me Susan.
Susan.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Oh, and I was told your
weakness was Pinot Grigio.
I guess my
secret is out.
I haven't had this one.
Thank you.
So, let's go inside.
Lunch should be ready
any moment.
MEGAN: Yeah.
Come on in.
MEGAN: Let's go.
Wow, Philip,
you really must rate.
Mom doesn't bring out
the silver for just anybody.
SUSAN: Well, it just
seems a shame to keep
something so pretty...
(SOUND OF HEARTBEAT
DROWNS OUT CONVERSATION)
Philip? Philip.
Philip?
Yeah. Thank you,
I'd love some.
Mmm. Looks so good.
(DAVID CLEARS THROAT)
So, uh, Mr. McAllister...
Ah, ah, ah.
I'm sorry. David...
Better.
I hear that you have
an awesome short game.
You play?
Oh, yeah.
PHILIP: Mr. McAllister, you
know why we came here today.
Yes, I do,
and I'm sure you can imagine
some of the questions I have.
Absolutely. I mean,
"What's the rush?" Right?
Yeah.
"Aren't you too young?"
Mmm-hmm.
"What about your studies?"
And "How do I know
I can trust you
"with the person that I care
about most in all the world?"
Yeah, that about
sums it up.
Well, sir, with me,
what you see is
pretty much what you get.
You know, uh, I grew up
near Syracuse, parents
split when I was a kid.
I'm not rich
and no handouts.
I had to work my way
through school.
Summa cum laude
from SUNY, Albany.
And I love your
daughter very much.
You sound like
the American dream.
Isn't that
a good thing, sir?
Mr. McAllister,
I would like very much
to spend the rest of my
life making Megan happy.
You know,
there's no rush.
You guys could live
together for a bit,
really get to
know each other.
We have been living
together for a bit.
Really?
I mean, it just works
great, you know?
He's amazing, and he's
at the top of his class,
and he helps me
and we study together.
And it's crazy, but we're
just great for each other.
PHILIP: He'll still
charge you.
DAVID: That's exactly
right. By the hour.
Megan, you managed
to find a young man
(CLEARS THROAT)
capable of crushing it
300 yards off the tee
and keeping it in the
middle of the fairway.
DAVID: Okay.
SUSAN: Okay.
SUSAN: Bye, baby.
Love you guys.
Love you, too.
Nice meeting you guys.
DAVID: Drive safely.
PHILIP: Okay.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
MEGAN: Yes!
I told you.
I told you, Pocket.
It's gonna be happily
ever after for you and me.
It's amazing.
We did it.
Okay, so, ask me again.
What?
Come on, please ask me again.
All right.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Megan McAllister,
I love you with
all my heart.
Will you marry...
Yes!
Yes, yes.
Okay.
(TYPING)
That was fast.
Well, I couldn't
wait to meet you.
Mmm. Charmer.
I like that.
PHOTOGRAPHER: Nice. Great.
Is my tie okay?
Yeah.
Some of this?
Can you remind me
what this is for again?
It's for the website.
We have a website?
It's going to be
a pink website.
Yes.
There we go. Smiling.
What happened?
PHOTOGRAPHER: You look
like Ken and Barbie.
Did he say "Ken and Barbie"?
Yeah.
Is he making fun of us?
No, it's a good thing.
PHOTOGRAPHER: Great.
You're a beautiful couple.
MEGAN: This is going to be
the wedding website to end
all wedding websites.
Babe, this is looking so cute!
Hey. Oh, are you busy?
No, I'm not busy at all.
I'm just looking
at genetic notes.
But go ahead.
Tell me about this website.
Well, it's going to be
where we're registered
and everything, obviously.
But then there's going
to be pictures, and there's
going to be a countdown.
It's like a rocket launch.
(LAUGHS)
There's gonna be a quiz
for all our friends to take
to see how well they know us.
Doesn't really
matter how well
other people know us.
It's about how well
we know each other, right?
God, I like you.
I like you, too.
We should get married.
(GIGGLES) And I'm so excited
to finally meet your family.
Um...
Babe, I wanted to talk
to you about that, okay?
I talked to them, and
I don't know if they're
going to be able to make it.
What are you talking about?
It's our engagement party.
Yeah, I know.
Philip, we're
getting married.
Don't you think
it's strange that
I haven't met your family?
Well, we're a strange family.
MICHAEL: Look, we're all nice
to you now, Philip, but if you
mess with our little sister...
Yeah, okay, I promise.
I will be good.
You have nothing
to worry about.
MICHAEL: You better be.
Hey, what are you
doing with my fiance?
Nothing. They're just
scaring the ever living
crap out of me.
We like this guy.
I told you.
He's a good one.
And look, I found
my maid of honor.
MICHAEL: One of 19.
Not to mention the
three flower girls,
the two ring bearers.
But you're my favorite.
Thank you.
MEGAN: No, I know it's not all
about just the one day.
It's about spending
the rest of my life...
Sorry, can you guys
excuse me for a second?
Yeah.
Now, which one of you boys
wants to get me a drink?
Philip. Oh, it's so
good to see you.
Oh, this house,
it's so beautiful.
Philip...
Philip what?
Hey, I didn't scare
you off with all the
wedding talk, did I?
No, no, no.
Okay, sorry.
I'm Philip's mother.
Oh, my gosh! It's so nice
to finally meet you!
My parents cannot wait
to introduce you to everyone.
Okay, don't move.
I'll be right back.
She's very beautiful.
I see your father's
right at home.
He's already good friends
with the McAllisters?
You're still keeping
score, huh, Mom?
You know, if it makes
you feel any better,
Dad's never met them
before today either, okay?
The happy family
together again.
Well, I'm not seeing
your brother,
so I'm guessing
that he wasn't invited.
Guess whatever you want.
(SWING MUSIC PLAYING)
(SOUND OF HEARTBEAT
DROWNING OUT SOUNDS OF PARTY)
Hi. Come here.
MEGAN: So I was thinking,
for everyday, we could do the
Kate Spade Sag Harbor
dinner plates in
the polka dots,
and then the salad
plates in stripes,
because the stripes
and the polka dots
look really good together.
Mmm-hmm.
Especially on the deck of
our beautiful beach house
that we're gonna
have one day.
Nice.
And for when we invite
the head of the hospital over,
who neither one
of us can stand,
I was thinking we could do
the Royal Doulton Etoile
or the Spode Indian Tree.
What do you think?
Uh... Well, I think the guy
that comes up with these names
has way too much time
on his hands, personally.
Oh! And I got the
countdown going. Look.
I mean, I know it's cheesy,
but it's cute, right?
You know, gotta have it.
And it's in pink.
Jan. Janet,
a friendly face.
That is exactly
what I needed.
Hey, Phil.
You're in scrubs?
You look cute.
No.
Where were you today?
You missed a whole bunch
of stuff on the test.
I missed a lot of stuff.
But I don't care.
Because I've got you,
and you're gonna
give me notes, 'cause
you're a good friend.
Sorry, friend.
No, wait, wait, wait.
Philip, you're drunk.
We're friends, right?
Sure, we're friends.
But you're getting
a little close.
Philip, stop.
What? Come on.
No, knock it off!
Don't you
say no to me.
Yeah? Watch me.
Really?
What's wrong with you?
What would your fiancee
say about this if she
found out about you?
What did you say?
You threatening me?
Uh...
Rhinestones.
Okay.
Umm.
Wow. Does that come
with a light switch?
Let's look at some
other dresses.
(LAUGHS)
Are these those
disposable phones?
The ones that
can't be traced,
they can't be tracked,
anything like that?
Yeah, no ID,
no nothing.
All right, thanks.
It's a lot of dress.
I like the way it moves.
Really?
Moves? It's like a tsunami.
Oh, my God. I am
never getting married.
When you meet somebody
that makes you feel like
Philip makes me feel,
and you will, you'll
do anything to show him
how much you love him,
even wear a
tsunami dress.
SUSAN: Oh! Wow, okay.
We've got cakes to taste.
Go, get changed.
Quickly, quickly.
We have to go!
Don't touch anything.
We'll be back in an hour.
We are going to
find a dress.
Yes, we are.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
MEGAN: Mmm. This is good.
SUSAN: That's yummy.
You like it?
Megs, you cannot
go with this one.
MEGAN: Why not?
Because all of your guests
will die of pleasure,
and you will have that
on your conscience.
I'm serious. This is so good.
SUSAN: Give me some.
Let me see.
It's perfect.
Mmm.
It's so good.
It's like raspberry
something.
You guys, look.
My fiance misses me.
Oh... He's the
best boyfriend.
Just a little
bit more of that.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Looks like a very
interesting project.
Yep.
You can put my number in any
of these phones, if you want.
KATE: Hope it's
not much longer.
I know. Let's
hope that she...
Wow.
Good "wow"?
Staggering "wow."
I just want you
to love it.
You are going to be
the most beautiful bride ever.
I'm getting married!
(ALL SQUEALING AND LAUGHING)
Congratulations!
It's great. This is
the one for sure.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I need to see some ID.
That's me, man.
Brian Stevens.
Yeah.
TOM: Hey, Phil.
Hey, man.
How you doing?
Janet, can I talk
to you for a sec?
Uh... Sure.
Cool. All right.
So, listen, I just
wanted to apologize
for the other night,
'cause I was really drunk.
No, I was out of line.
Forget about it.
It's not okay.
But I just want to
let you know,
if you even think about
messing with me
and my fiancee,
I swear to God...
You understand?
Okay?
Yeah.
All right. Good? Okay.
PHILIP: All right, guys,
I'm out. Got to get to class.
Later, dude.
All right,
see you.
DR. JANEWAY:
And that concludes the
scintillating video portion
of our presentation.
You will see that
offspring four
is not sharing the same
characteristic with
offspring seven.
Mr. Markoff,
from which parent did
offspring four receive
chromosome 13?
The father, obviously.
That locus is linked to
congenital blindness
which doesn't appear
in the maternal line.
Nobody likes a smartass,
Mr. Markoff. Thank you.
DR. JANEWAY: All right,
any questions? Yes, sir.
STUDENT: Would the same hold
true from what we talked...
Philip, call me back, please.
I just tried to take out
some cash, and it says
the account's overdrawn.
Come on. Don't worry about it.
I'll pay, my treat.
Hey, baby, it's me.
Can you call me back? Bye.
I'm sure there's an
explanation. You should call
the bank or something.
ATMs screw up
all the time.
I've called Philip three times
in the past hour, and he
hasn't called me back.
KATE: He's probably in class.
I'm telling you, it's
just a bank screw-up.
You guys are starting
a life together, Megs.
If you're gonna marry him,
you have to trust him.
Okay?
Yes.
The strawberry
and the grape.
(GASPS)
(PHONE RINGING)
See? Drama queen.
Hello?
PHILIP: Baby?
Where have you been?
I'm at the Dean's
office right now.
Listen, Megan, I'm so sorry
about the whole money thing.
I got this NIH grant,
and the check came late,
but I'm getting it
Monday morning, so
I'll put the money back in the
account first thing, okay?
No, it's okay.
I mean, yeah.
No, no, no, no.
I'm totally serious.
We're supposed to be
a team, you know, and
I want us to be able to tell
each other everything, okay?
No secrets. Look, sweetheart,
I gotta let you go, okay?
But I wanted to call and let
you know that I am very sorry.
Your fiance is
a big, dumb idiot,
and that it's all
taken care of.
Thank you.
Okay. I love you so much.
I love you, too.
Bye.
Oh! Yay!
To my best friend's wedding.
Hmm... Red Sox, huh?
My favorite team.
Come on in.
Sweetie, you got
some mail.
It's from B.U.
Hello, Dr. McAllister.
It's really thin.
"Dear Miss McAllister,
thank you for this
application. We..."
(EXHALES)
KATE: No?
Oh, man!
But...
(WOMAN GIGGLES)
You're way too cute to be shy.
Oh...
Is that what you're into?
You want me to tie you up?
No. You.
But how am I gonna
give you a massage
if my hands are tied?
I don't want a massage.
Okay, well, I don't
do bondage, so
I guess we're in a bit
of a standoff here, huh?
All right.
Get down on the floor.
Hands behind your back.
You don't have to
do any of this.
All the way down!
I'll give you
whatever you want.
All the way down. Shh...
Put your hands
behind your back.
All right.
Give me your hands.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Please, please, please!
Look, I don't have
a lot of money.
I don't have a lot of
money, okay? Please,
I'll do whatever you want.
Please, don't!
Trisha Leffler
from Las Vegas.
I know where
you live now.
This is an ATM card, right?
Yeah.
What's your PIN?
4-3-2-1.
It's 4-3-2-1.
Please don't hurt me.
Oh, no!
Shut up. Shut up.
Don't say a word.
Do you understand?
(PEOPLE LAUGHING
OUTSIDE THE DOOR)
There you go.
Before I leave, I'm gonna
take a little souvenir, okay?
Mmm?
Yeah.
Shh...
(MUFFLED CRIES)
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
(MUFFLED CRYING)
Thank you.
Such a gentleman.
So after, he cut off your
panties with a knife
to keep as a souvenir?
He took my phone and deleted
the messages he left for me.
BENNETT:
May I see that phone, ma'am?
FRYE: How'd he get
your number?
He replied to my Craigslist
ad, and I texted him back.
So then, this entirely
anonymous person, who
could've been anybody,
you decided to invite
him up to your room?
I'm usually a better judge.
What were you
advertising, Miss Leffler?
Massages.
So, if we check your
record for any priors,
we're not gonna turn up any
solicitation, prostitution?
Look, I'm not the
criminal here, okay? He is.
And I hope you nail
his preppy ass.
I'm telling you,
what he did to me,
he's done it before,
and he liked it.
Liked what?
(SNIFFLING)
I don't know.
Humiliating me.
The one with the Red Sox cap,
just like the lady said.
BENNETT: Calm, attractive,
non-threatening.
A psycho who likes to
rough up defenseless women.
Couldn't ask for
a better cover.
(FRONT DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
MEGAN: Philip? Baby?
Hey, I thought
you weren't coming
back till tomorrow.
I needed to see you.
Why, what happened?
What happened, baby?
I didn't get in.
I knew it was a long shot,
but I thought maybe if
I was an undergrad...
Listen, listen,
they're idiots, okay?
Yeah, but they
accepted you.
You see? That
proves my point.
It's not funny.
I know.
Listen, I'm gonna transfer
wherever you go, okay?
No, I don't want
you to transfer.
I worked really hard,
you know? I really did.
I know.
And now I just
ruined everything.
No, baby, you did not ruin
anything, okay? Look at me.
You didn't ruin anything.
B.U. was our plan. We were
supposed to be together.
And we will be.
No matter what happens,
we're gonna be fine.
Can we just stay
like this forever?
We can stay like this
for as long as you want.
It's just you and me, Pocket.
Nothing else matters.
You really got to
go away again?
Final fitting.
No.
Yes.
No final fitting.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Call me when you
get there, okay?
Okay, I will.
Bye.
"Dear Miss McAllister, we
regret to inform you that..."
Well, I guess
that decides it.
On to plan B.
Megan, you're in.
St. Kitts.
This is fantastic!
It's such a great program.
Look, baby.
Mom, that's a
million miles away.
I can't move
a million miles away
from my husband.
Well, if he
loves you now,
he's going to love you
in five years after
you graduate, right?
Mom, I really
don't want to
disappoint you.
Honey, you could never...
Baby, you'll never
disappoint me. It's just...
It would be such a waste.
You are so bright
and so compassionate.
You would make
an amazing doctor.
I've thought
about this a lot.
If we can't go to
medical school together,
then I'll just wait.
I can always reapply
later if I want to.
But for now,
this is what I want.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
MEGAN: Hey, guess where I am?
I'm so glad I got you.
So, listen, I was thinking,
what about a beach
wedding? We'd have a
beautiful sunset ceremony.
I was just sleeping.
Can I call you later?
You were? It's the
middle of the afternoon.
I know. I've been
working hard.
Okay, yeah, I'll call
you later. I love you.
Okay.
Bye.
So, what's up?
What did he say?
Did he like your idea?
Yeah, he loved it.
He was just studying.
But he liked it.
SUSAN: It's gonna be amazing.
Hold on one second,
okay, Mom?
MOM: Okay.
I gotta go.
Why? What's wrong?
You okay?
I'm fine.
Then why do you
have to go?
Um...
I'm going to see a guy
I met on the train.
What guy? Is he cute?
What's he do?
He's a student.
In?
I don't know what in.
You gotta know
something about him, honey.
Where's he from?
I promise I will get
you the whole 411.
Okay, have fun.
I love you, Julissa.
I love you, too.
Are you Brian?
Yeah.
You're beautiful.
You're not so bad yourself.
Ready?
Yeah.
Umm...
What do you do
here in Boston, Brian?
I'm a grad student.
In what?
Sciences.
Wow, that is so cool!
I'm actually doing grad work
myself right now in New York.
Drug and alcohol
counseling. I figure,
nobody knows the territory
like somebody who's been
there themselves, right?
Get down on the ground.
Put your hands behind
your back right now.
(SCREAMS)
(CRIES OUT)
Just get on the...
(SCREAMING)
FRYE: Julissa Brisman,
New York City.
BENNETT: Massage table,
no forcible entry.
Sound familiar?
One difference. CSI
said there was skin
under the fingernails.
She fought back,
so he shot her.
He's stepping it up.
Yeah.
DR. JANEWAY: Mr. Markoff?
What...
(EXHALES)
Whoa!
I scared you.
Oh, Dr. Janeway.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm a little jumpy,
I guess.
I've been staying awake
two nights in a row
memorizing genetic sequences.
Trying to impress me.
Always, sir.
How's your fiancee?
Good, great.
I mean, uh, we've
both got school.
(CLEARS THROAT)
And then there's the wedding.
So, it's a lot.
I bet.
Well, I'd better get going.
But have a good evening.
You, too, Philip, and
try to get some rest.
Okay. Yeah, I will.
Hey.
Hey. I'm sorry.
You didn't give me a kiss
when you got in.
I know, I didn't
want to wake you...
Oh, my God.
What happened to your neck?
A woman went psychotic
in the ER tonight.
It was crazy. She went nuts.
She hurt a nurse, so I had to
step in and do something.
My hero.
Wash up and come to bed.
(WOMAN CRYING)
We may have just
caught a break.
A friend of Julissa's
just called,
got me into her phone.
We have the text
she got from the last guy
she had an appointment with.
Now, if digital forensics
can get an IP off that,
we can get an address,
maybe even a name.
That'll take, what,
a couple of days?
At least.
(WOMAN CRYING OUT)
How'd he meet her?
Another ad on Craigslist?
Looks like that.
I don't get it.
This day and age, girl's
in a friggin' hotel room,
a guy she doesn't
even know... I just...
Mrs. Flores,
Detective Bennett.
Sorry for the loss
of your daughter.
She was a good girl.
I'm sure she was.
She was just getting
her life together.
Who would do this?
Who would do this
to my baby?
Used to be able
to see who the
bad guys were, right?
Now it's all texts and
emails and websites.
The creeps are hiding
in our houses, and
we don't even
know who they are.
It is 7:07 and
once again, here's Matt.
All right, Meredith,
thank you. And now to
a story out of Boston
that's gonna terrify anyone
who's ever placed a classified
ad, especially online.
Wow, this is in Boston.
What's that?
MATT: A man is apparently
targeting women
who place ads on
the popular website...
This guy's right
here in Boston.
...Craigslist. Police say
he's already killed one woman
(PHONE RINGING)
and attacked
another in Boston.
Hello?
SUSAN: Hey, Megan, it's Mom.
Listen, I was
watching the news,
and I saw this story about
this Boston hotel killer.
No, we're not staying
in a hotel. We're here,
home, studying.
Me and Philip are safe.
Okay.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Bye.
PROFILER: Of course,
the profile is never exact,
but a pretty clear picture
is emerging of what
we're looking for.
We're talking about a guy
with an inability to
form close emotional
relationships with women.
Probably sexual issues.
A loner. A guy who shies
away from the crowd.
Maybe later. Come on.
What's up?
Let's go.
You didn't even
give me a chance.
PROFILER: A man with no sense
of status, accomplishment.
Let me get this straight.
We're looking for
a big, blond loser wearing
a Red Sox cap in Boston?
Is that what
you're telling me?
Let's get right on
that one. We should have
that settled by morning.
Thanks for the crack
work, Detective.
Maybe somebody
will ID the photo.
We got a blurry photo
with the same damn guy
wearing the same friggin' hat.
This is just going great.
REPORTER: Police are now
hoping someone out there
recognizes this man
from all the surveillance
photos in the various hotels.
They are trying to get onto
his track this morning,
but so far,
they have no leads.
But police say
the warning is out
to women now
that this man is
still on the loose,
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
especially if you post
ads on Craigslist. Matt.
Who is it?
MARCELO: Marcelo,
superintendent.
I need to
talk to you.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
WOMAN: Nice.
All right, that's it for me.
I'm cashing out. I'm done.
I'm sorry, I gotta go.
I've got another date,
ladies. I'm so sorry.
CASHIER: $5,300.
VOICEMAIL: You have
three new messages.
MEGAN: Hey, Philip. I need to
talk to you. Where are you?
MEGAN: Philip, call me.
I need to talk to you, okay?
VOICEMAIL: Message deleted.
MEGAN: Baby, where are you?
Call me as soon as...
No, no.
VOICEMAIL: Message deleted.
Hey, your client
there yet?
He called and said
he'd be, like, 10 minutes.
All right, well, text me
when he gets there.
Promise. Love you, sweetheart.
I love you, too, babe.
You're a young one.
Come on in.
It's just a lap dance
like the ad said, okay?
That's all I came for, yeah.
Lie face-down on the floor.
Lie face-down on the
floor right now! Put your
hands behind your back.
Listen to me. I do not
want to kill you, okay?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Who's calling your phone?
I don't know.
Honey, take a seat.
Don't move, don't move.
Get off! Get off!
(SCREAMING)
What the hell's
going on here, huh?
INFOMERCIAL: ...just
call the toll-free
number on your screen
for a free personal
enrollment kit.
You're under no obligation
to enroll, and no
salesman will call.
It's so easy to afford
peace of mind.
The hunt for the man being
called "The Craigslist Killer"
has spread this morning
from Boston to Rhode Island.
Police in Warwick near
Providence are investigating
a robbery attempt
that may involve the
same man who killed two
young women in Boston.
Boston police
say the murderer
apparently targeted...
I thought you
said, "No secrets."
What are you talking about?
Where have you been?
What do you mean?
The super came by.
You haven't paid the
rent in three months.
If there's something going on,
then I need to know before...
Before what?
Before you marry me?
I missed some bills, Meg.
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm studying 20 hours a day.
I've got millions of tons
of crap that I'm dealing with
and professors on top of that.
But you know what?
You're right, you're right.
I screwed up.
I screwed up, and I'm...
You know what?
I'm sorry that I'm not the
perfect guy you thought I was.
I never asked you to
be the perfect guy.
Then what are
you asking me?
What do you want from me, Meg?
I should've told
you first, okay?
And I didn't. I just...
I get in my own head
about things, and...
It's been a really hard
time for me, you know?
It's been a hard
time for me, too.
I know, I know.
Look, I am...
I'm sorry, babe.
I am so sorry, okay?
I haven't been there for you,
and I'm gonna be, all right?
Baby, look at me.
It's my fault, okay?
But I am trying my best.
I'll go down to the
management office tomorrow.
I'll take care of it
right away, first thing.
I promise, okay?
God, I love you.
I don't want to mess
this up, babe. I don't
want to lose you.
I'm not going anywhere.
You promise?
Yes.
Good.
Just, you need to
let me in, okay?
I have no idea what
I did to deserve you.
Lady got lucky.
Husband was in the lobby,
came to check on her.
Hey, blow that up
for me, would you?
Lieutenant? We tracked
an IP address for that
last email to Julissa.
Whoever sent it
lives in Quincy.
He who kills by the Internet
fries by the Internet, right?
He's not frying yet.
It's an apartment complex,
so the killer could've
been using somebody
else's wireless signal.
All right, then I want a full
tenant list for that building.
I want six units down there,
six invisible units.
And I want 100 copies of this
picture blown up, all right?
Let's hope the coffee's
good down in Quincy.
BENNETT: No, no, no, no, no.
Listen to me, listen to me.
I don't want you hanging
out in the mall on a
school night, all right?
You understand?
Okay, all right.
You got a ride?
Do I know him?
Okay. All right.
Great, I love you,
baby. I'll see you
back at the house.
This guy is
driving me crazy.
I mean, he's turning me
into my old man here.
I'm two seconds
away from locking my
daughter up for good.
Gotta let her go
at some point.
Do I?
FRYE: There's got to be
800 units in this place.
Great. All we've got to do now
is wait for a guy to waltz by
who looks like a
vicious, loner killer
with emotional issues.
You're kidding me, right?
This guy could be anybody.
You got another picture
I can look at? Anything?
Well, if you see anyone,
just give me a call.
Hey. Before
we go...
What? What?
What are we having
for dinner tonight?
Making something good?
I don't know yet.
You don't have
to cook tonight.
No, I want to.
PHILIP: Okay.
Laundry time first, though.
FRYE: IP came up with a name.
Son of a bitch!
"Philip Markoff, residing
in Quincy, Mass."
BENNETT: Are you kidding me?
I mean, come on, you put
a baseball cap on that freak,
we've definitely got our guy.
He's a med student at B.U.
Four hundred and
seventy-eight friends.
Who the hell would
want 478 friends?
"Religious views:
It's complicated."
"Relationship status:
Engaged."
Quite a catch,
this fella, huh!
We can always bring
him in, question him.
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. We, uh...
We stop by, he's not there.
He hears we showed up,
he's off to Brazil.
I don't want to spook him.
You know, we just sit tight,
keep him under surveillance,
get a positive ID
from the masseuse
and nail him.
REPORTER: And the hunt
for the so-called "Craigslist
Killer" is intensifying,
with police hoping to catch
him before he strikes again.
Jeff Rossen has the
latest now from Boston.
See? This is way better.
JEFF: The police are literally
going hotel to hotel now
here in the Boston area...
Wow, this is everywhere.
...showing these
surveillance photos around.
MEGAN: That could be anybody.
They're worried he's
planning his next attack.
I'm gonna be right back.
Yeah, are you all right?
Yeah.
JEFF: Over the weekend,
investigators pored
through nearly two...
If you're still mad,
I'd just rather we called
the whole thing off.
(EXHALES)
ACTRESS: You
certainly have an...
ACTRESS: Until I met you...
Hey, you know what?
ACTRESS: ...I didn't know it
was possible either.
Let's get out of here.
What?
I don't know. Let's go
somewhere, yeah?
You and me, right now.
I'm getting my cabin fever.
Those crazy stories
on the news, and we've
been studying so much...
I know, but I have
an exam, and if I want to
reapply to med school,
I can't fail my senior year.
Okay, then we'll just...
Let's bring your
books, you know?
We can bring your books,
and you can study. You know?
We can check into a hotel,
we get some room service.
We can order some movies,
we can do some other things.
We should go to Foxwoods.
Oh...
No, no, no, we should
go to Foxwoods. It'll be
like a pre-honeymoon.
I don't know if it's
a good idea to be
gambling right now.
No, no, no, we're not
gambling. There's a spa.
We can go to the spa
and just get away
from all this noise.
Really?
Doctor's orders.
Okay.
Yeah?
Here we go.
Who are you, pretty lady?
Next victim?
No, no, no. Not his MO.
What's with the suitcases?
FRYE: Skipping town?
Get a picture. I don't
want to make our move
until we get a positive
ID from Trisha Leffler.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
Seems a little jumpy.
If I had a pretty girl like
that hanging on my arm,
I'd be a hell of a lot
happier than he is.
FRYE: Maybe nice girls
aren't his type.
Hang in there, sweetheart.
We're not gonna let
you out of our sight.
Looks like they're
heading out of the city.
Detective Frye, requesting
State Trooper assistance.
Pursuing suspect south
on Congress Street.
Late model SUV.
Where the hell are
you two going?
Babe. Babe, would you let me?
What? We're just...
Hey, let's speed up.
You want to go?
Let's get there fast.
Why not?
Uh... Maybe not?
You're the thrill-seeker
of the family, remember?
I'm just the sweet,
little girl from Jersey.
Fine.
They're making a move.
Heading for the 95.
Screw the positive ID.
All right,
this is it. Call it.
We're taking him down.
(POLICE SIRENS WAILING)
What?
Why are they pulling us over?
I wasn't even speeding.
Out of the car.
Out of the car!
Get out of the car!
Hands on the dash!
Engine off.
BENNETT: Take her. Take her.
What is going on?
FRYE: Get out of the car.
Keep your hands up.
What did I do? What...
Wait!
Philip Markoff,
you're under arrest for the
murder of Julissa Brisman.
MEGAN: What?
BENNETT: On the ground.
That's crazy! Stop!
Philip, tell them that they
have the wrong person!
FRYE: We need to take you
back to Boston and ask
you some questions.
Your car will be towed
to the station.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against
you in a court of law.
What is going on?
You have the right to
speak to an attorney.
I love you.
If you cannot afford
one, one will be
appointed by the court.
Do you understand these rights
as they've been read to you?
Yes.
Bag.
This guy keeps an awful lot
of books under his bed, huh.
FRYE: I used to do the
same thing in college.
Cheaper than buying shelves.
This, on the other
hand, I did not have
under my bed at school.
Whoa.
We got him.
Bingo!
Nine millimeter. Bag!
Grab the other side.
We're gonna lift it.
Tell me you never hid your
socks under your mattress?
Trophy. How many
you got there?
Thirteen, 14,
15, 16. Sixteen.
Only three reported.
Obviously, the others didn't
want their mothers to know
what they do
for a living, right?
With all due respect,
detectives, you're
embarrassing yourselves.
All right?
What do you got?
You got superficial
resemblance to what?
An out-of-focus
surveillance video?
Well, we got flex cuffs,
16 pairs of women's panties
and a nine millimeter.
All right, well, you've
got some party favors,
and you've got
some unwashed laundry,
and, yeah, I bought a gun
to protect my fiancee.
I mean, we live in
a sketchy neighborhood, sir.
BENNETT: Is that right?
We spoke to the
owner of the gun shop
up in New Hampshire.
He says he sold the gun
to a "Brian Stevens"...
...whose ID happened to
be in your top drawer.
You want to explain to us
why you purchased a weapon
with somebody else's ID?
Sir, I'm a straight-A
medical student.
And I'm getting
married in a month.
I mean, would you guys
care to explain to me
why I would go around
and shoot prostitutes
in hotel rooms?
What, you still
don't believe me?
Ask around.
MEGAN: You have no
idea how wrong you
are about Philip.
BENNETT: Do you know where
he was between 9:00 and
11:00 p.m. on April 14th?
He's dedicated
his whole life
to becoming a doctor
and helping people.
So, you don't know
where he was between 9:00
and 11:00 on April 14th?
He's a medical student, okay?
He spends thousands of hours
at the library and the lab,
and I'm sure there's people
there that have seen him.
We'll be sure to
check that out.
There's nothing to check out.
This is a huge mistake, okay?
Philip is not a killer!
Did you know that
we found handcuffs,
a nine-millimeter pistol and
16 pairs of women's panties
stuffed under your mattress?
Did you know that?
I'm marrying Philip
on August 14th.
You don't think
I know my own fiance?
You don't think that
I would've known if there
was a gun under my own bed?
I don't know what you know,
Miss McAllister.
Look, am I under
arrest or something?
BENNETT: No.
In fact, you're free to go.
But you can't go back
to your apartment.
And your car's been
impounded as evidence, so...
If I'm free to go,
then I'm going.
Are you telling me that
one of our top students
is the Craigslist Killer?
No, no, we're just
investigating at this point,
checking out his story.
So, you're saying
he was actually here
studying, being a student?
I'm saying he was
actually here being a star
in all of his classes.
Look, Lieutenant, I don't know
if you know just how hard
it is to be a medical student.
It's not physically
possible for someone
to do as brilliantly
as Philip has done in
one of the most competitive
programs in the country,
and then run off to
Rhode Island and
commit these crimes.
Not physically possible.
(DOOR BUZZER SOUNDS)
(INMATES YELLING COMMENTS)
(CAR HORNS HONKING)
DAVID: How did these people
get here? How did they know?
Dad, what...
Do not talk to them.
I want you to go
inside straight away.
(REPORTERS CLAMORING)
Oh, God!
DAVID: You guys are
on private property.
Go, go, go!
DAVID: You must step off
of my property. Now!
GUARD: Seven! Seven! Seven!
(COUGHING)
They won't even
let me call him. I mean,
he's in there all alone,
and I can't even...
I can't talk to him.
I can't do anything.
Baby, I'm so sorry.
You know what,
when this is all over,
I'm going to make sure
that he demands an apology,
because a doctor cannot
have an accusation like
this hanging over his head.
This is ridiculous.
Look, we don't even
really know what happened.
Of course
we know what happened.
They arrested the wrong guy.
That's what happened.
I'm just saying, there's
a lot of the story that
we still don't know.
Oh, my God. You guys are
just like everybody else.
You really think
that he's a killer?
You think that he's a killer,
and I've been living
with him this whole time?
No.
And I didn't know?
That I'm that stupid?
I mean, Mom, come on.
If somebody came to the door
and told you that
Dad is a killer,
would you believe him?
Oh, my God!
Sweetie, we just feel...
Unfortunately,
you are here today
because you were given
the wrong information,
as was the public.
Philip Markoff is a beautiful
person, inside and out,
and couldn't hurt a fly.
A police officer in Boston,
or several, is trying to
make big bucks
by selling a false story
to the TV stations.
What else is new?
Philip is an intelligent
man who is just trying
to live his life.
So, if you could leave us
alone, we would appreciate it.
We expect to
marry in August
and share a wonderful
and meaningful life together.
Thank you.
Our boy sure
picked the right girl.
TOM ON TV:
I have known Phil Markoff
since sophomore year.
I can't even put into
words the disbelief
I'm feeling right now.
He was a great guy.
I mean, he was not someone who
would ever even own a gun.
REPORTER: As Markoff is
without resources, it's the
taxpayers of Massachusetts
who'll be footing the
bill for his defense.
Doing the honors will be
well-known public defender,
Robert Grossman.
A public defender?
That's insane!
His parents aren't even
paying for a lawyer?
Dad, do you know somebody?
We have to help him.
Although Markoff is being
kept away from the media,
his attorney continues
to publicly profess
his client's...
We got him. He's got
a public defender.
BENNETT: Is that right?
2005, a guy gets his
underage girlfriend pregnant.
Trying to dodge
statutory rape,
he and his buddy kill her
with a knife and a brick,
and toss her in the gutter.
Cops have fingerprints, DNA,
confessions from both.
The buddy gets 20 years.
Ken Braniff gets Grossman
as a lawyer, goes free.
He's, uh, walking
the streets of Boston today.
That's not true. Is that true?
Robert Grossman can
make an alibi out of two
sticks and a ball of twine.
Then we need to make
a preemptive strike
on Markoff's alibis.
SUSAN: Was that the door?
MICHAEL: I don't know.
(KNOCKING)
No reporters on the property.
I'm gonna call the police.
They are the police.
How are you, Megan?
MEGAN: Fine.
Good to see you again.
Detective Bennett, Boston P.D.
She was lucky. She got out
with only two busted ribs.
He hit her so hard in
the face, she's still
having trouble seeing.
You guys have the
wrong guy, okay?
Philip isn't capable
of killing anybody.
Are you sure?
Everybody knows
that the Boston Police
Department is the
worst in the country.
This isn't about
the Boston P.D.
We're trying to figure
out who murdered an
innocent young woman.
We have a positive ID
from a woman he beat up
and robbed in Rhode Island.
(SIGHS)
I believe in Philip,
Lieutenant.
Did you know your
boyfriend posted on
a sexual fetish website
under the username
"Sex Addict 53885"?
Took it right off
his hard drive.
You guys could've
put that on there.
Digital forensics can
prove that Philip
made these postings
long before he killed
Julissa Brisman with
a nine millimeter.
Her skull fragments were
found embedded in the
wall in the hotel room.
She died choking
on her own blood.
Sex Addict 53885 was
into, and I quote,
"Submission and humiliation."
All right, I'd like
you to stop this now...
BENNETT: No, no, no.
No, I'd like you to...
Also on his list
was "friendship and
experimentation
"with transvestites
and transsexuals."
I said that's enough!
That's not Philip.
He's got a description
of himself here.
"Born February 12th, 1986.
"6'4", blond, athletic.
Eight inches, cut."
DAVID: That's enough!
MICHAEL: You guys are
out of here.
Does that physical description
match your absolute
knowledge of your fiance?
DAVID: Detective,
stop this now.
Get out of here.
Is that your perfect fiance?
Don't put that...
Get them out of here!
SUSAN: You've done enough!
You stop this now.
SUSAN: Megan!
You want to bully people?
Get out of my house.
Leave our home now.
(VOMITING)
(CRYING)
BENNETT: You sure you
want to do this to Megan?
I thought you loved her.
I didn't do it.
You can spare
everybody a lot of pain.
You want her to
see you like this?
How ugly you are?
I didn't do it.
It's going to be
a circus, Phil.
There's going to be pictures.
The media, they're going
to turn you into a monster.
You understand?
Phil, talk to me,
all right?
I mean, I don't get it.
You had everything.
A beautiful girl who
loved you, a bright future.
If you'd played your cards
right, years from now,
you'd be a rich doctor having
dinner parties on the Vineyard
with your wife and kids.
Right?
You'd be living the dream.
Instead of rotting in here.
Help me out, Phil.
I need it to make
sense for me.
Why would you do this?
Why would you
hurt those people?
throw it all away?
We've been talking
about Philip Markoff
and allegations about other
killers leading double lives,
and frequently, the women
who love them, or at least
who always seem surprised
when the cops come calling...
That is not going to
make you feel better.
It won't?
No.
I tried going over it
in my head, and...
You know, what didn't
I see? He was...
He was a med student.
He worked late.
He was on his
computer late at night.
How is that different
from any other guy at B.U.?
It's not.
How was I supposed
to make that leap?
Megs, he fooled
everybody, okay?
He seemed like
the perfect guy.
Maybe I just wanted him
to be perfect so bad that
I only saw what
I wanted to see.
I loved him so much.
It's okay.
He made me feel like
no one ever made me feel.
Come here. I'm sorry.
(DOOR BUZZER SOUNDING)
Number four.
Megan.
Did you get my suit
back from the tailor?
He was going to fix
the button thing in the cuff.
Philip, stop.
The wedding's only
a couple of weeks away now.
Stop it!
I came here today because...
I need you to look me in my
eyes and tell me the truth.
Can you do that, Philip?
Please?
I love you. I always will.
Please, just tell me.
Please?
Maybe...
Maybe
the person who did this, maybe
they didn't feel like they
deserved all that they had.
Maybe they didn't feel
like they deserved someone
as amazing as you.
You're amazing.
I love you.
Maybe
they felt like all they
deserved was to be punished.
I saw a picture of the gun.
And the underwear that you
put under the mattress.
Our mattress.
How many girls were there?
Sixteen? Did you...
Were you safe?
Do I need to get tested?
I mean, getting tested
is a smart policy for anybody.
Please don't do that.
It said on your site that
you were into bondage
and cross-dressing.
Did you do that stuff?
Megan, sweetheart,
maybe you can't
believe everything you
see on the Internet.
This whole time.
You've been lying to
me this whole time?
You've been looking in
my eyes and lying to me?
I mean, what did I do?
What did I do
to deserve this?
What did...
What did I do?
I'm done here!
No, no, no. Megan!
Baby, baby, baby!
Baby! Baby, baby,
please come back! Please!
I'm scared! I'm scared to
death in here. Please don't.
Please. Please don't...
Please.
I'm never going to
see you again.
I love you, Pocket.
(DOOR BUZZER SOUNDING)
* Tell me what you think,
tell me what you feel
(CRYING)
* Is this thing a fake,
or is it for real
* Is it what you hoped for,
what you dreamed
* Is it something strange,
that you never seen
* Does it lift you up,
closer to the light
* Does it send you raging
into the night
* Where did it begin,
will it ever end
* Where the sun sets
and the river bends
* Where the river bends,
is a place I've been
* The water's not as blue,
* And the grass,
well, it ain't so green
* The current gets strong,
it can pull you down
* You gotta swim hard,
if you want to turn around
* But I don't want to
go there,
* Baby, not with you
MEREDITH: We'll begin with
these new details in the
death of Philip Markoff,
the accused Craigslist Killer.
NBC's Jeff Rossen
is in Boston.
Jeff, good morning to you.
JEFF: Hi, Meredith,
good morning to you.
This morning, we're
getting our first look
inside Markoff's cell.
And just to paint the
picture for you here,
police say he had photos
of his ex-fiancee spread
out all over, it appears.
According to investigators,
this is the last thing he
was looking at before
he committed suicide.
After he stabbed himself,
he wrote messages to her
on the wall in blood,
in a spot where he could
see it, but she couldn't.
It was her name, and then
he wrote something else,
which they believe may
be a secret message.
MEGAN: And... Um...
A big oak tree
in the front yard.
It's got to be big
enough to build a
tree house in, though.
Yes, for our three kids.
No, four. Four kids.
Four kids? Watch out.
That's four
college educations.
Two med school,
two law school.
Okay.
Yes, but, lest we
forget, their dad is
the head of surgery
at an internationally-renowned
teaching hospital.
And Mom just had
a huge breakthrough
in cancer research.
Okay, so make it five kids.
Okay.
Four boys in a row, and then
after, a girl, so she could
be really protected.
Well, if she looks
anything like her mother,
she is going to need it.
I'm crazy about you,
Megan McAllister.