(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
♪Wandering alone♪
♪Walking far by dusk-lit streets♪
♪Your eyes are as cold as clouds♪
♪Faintly coming into view♪
♪The city lights♪
♪Lit up that single moment♪
♪I can't hide or stop missing you♪
♪I can't forget those moments♪
♪Losing you♪
♪Like the seasons in my memory♪
♪Without winter♪
♪Walking down the long, dark street♪
♪Snow will never fall again♪
♪Our old story was torn♪
♪Into scattered pieces♪
♪Replaying every single scene♪
♪After you left♪
♪As if our documentary♪
♪Lost winter♪
♪The breeze speaks of good times♪
♪Pure white devotion♪
♪Send out a letter♪
♪Carrying my longing♪
=The Double Game=
=Episode 2=
Are you really Jin Chanchan?
The one and only Jin Chanchan.
(Jin Chanchan Studio)
A true top name.
The industry's top star.
I love what I do.
I get it right
every single time.
I only take
the intense and thrilling ones.
After all, I care about depth.
The job you mean
is being a blogger?
What else?
What did you think?
People like Lu Jianchuan and Xu Shulin
actually let their daughter-in-law
work as a blogger?
What's wrong with it?
Honest, brave, and responsible.
Way better than some spoiled rich kids.
Then do they know
about your shining identity?
So, you need
to keep this secret for me.
What if I say no?
Then Xu Shulin will get an anonymous tip
about this report.
She'll be prepared.
Do you think my in-laws
will start to suspect you then?
You're good at bargaining.
Fine.
Let's keep our secrets.
Everyone,
these elders gave their youth
to society,
but some companies
leave them unable to get by.
Feis' Billiards Club
claims to coach,
but under the guise of elite coaching,
it runs improper side deals.
Let me ask you, Mr. Fei,
how murky are things
at your pool hall?
(Influencer Yu Qiaoqiao
sees someone new)
(Influencer Yu Qiaoqiao)
Be good.
That's it for tonight.
(Lu Tingyu, Lu Tingxiao's half-brother)
The driver
will take you back.
You'll go see that old lady?
You promised me
you wouldn't touch her.
(Oh, my gosh.)
(She knew and still got involved.)
(What a bombshell.)
Don't worry, babe.
You know me.
I feel sick just looking
at a dull woman like Lin Zhi'er.
Who knows?
Older women have their appeal too.
(These two are shameless.)
(I pity the lawful wife.)
(Wait. Who did he call the lawful wife?)
(Lin Zhi'er?)
(That scum is my current husband,)
(Lu Tingyu!)
Who could stand that blockhead?
In a few days,
I'll throw the divorce agreement
right in her face,
kick her out,
and marry you, okay?
Stop it.
(Trying to ruin my business?)
(No way.)
You two really have no shame.
Your scheme is right in my face.
Why are you here?
If I weren't here,
how would I hear
your plotting behind my back?
Isn't that right, Mistress?
Who are you calling that?
You meant me?
Of course.
You're his secret lover.
He's married to Lin Zhi'er,
which is me.
If you're not the mistress,
who is?
Lin Zhi'er,
being illegitimate doesn't give you
a free pass to be rude.
Apologize to Qiaoqiao now.
Apologize for what?
You flaunt her in front of me.
And you want me to apologize?
Tingyu.
And you.
I don't usually hit women.
But if you mess with my business,
I can make an exception.
Lin Zhi'er,
I'll teach you a lesson,
or you won't know your limits!
- I'll...
- You...
Lu Tingxiao.
You're the brother
who was raised overseas?
Lu Tingyu,
getting bold, huh?
Now, you bully women.
None of your business.
Flirting around at our front door?
Haven't you brought enough shame back?
Why do you care?
You're my brother,
not my dad.
Don't say I didn't warn you:
Cheating
may catch the attention of a blogger.
Some self-media bloggers
are known for showing no mercy.
They twist the story
and love stirring up drama.
Isn't that right,
Zhi'er?
Tingxiao's right.
Those top bloggers
love exposing cheaters and mistresses
and acting like vigilantes.
Who are you taking a jab at?
In a relationship,
the one unloved is the mistress.
You...
Give me my card back.
I'm taking the card.
That's part of my marital assets.
Lin Zhi'er,
how dare you!
What?
I dare kick you both out.
- You...
- Save it.
The card's gone, and so is the car.
Get lost. Don't shame yourself here.
(Guzhi Cafe)
Yan, new car?
Aunt Hui, I'm heading in.
Sis.
Two pieces of good news.
Lin Zhi'er and the Lianxin Island case.
Which one comes first?
Of course, the case.
The Lianxin Island client's money is in.
This money
(Online Banking)
is enough to live it up.
What about Lin Zhi'er?
After the car accident,
she vanished.
But I found surveillance footage.
She's still in Liancheng.
(Camera 01)
And it gets even juicier.
Lin Zhi'er has a secret stash.
For years, money only went in.
Today, it suddenly went live.
A huge sum was transferred out.
It looks like
she's getting ready for a new life.
An orchestrated identity swap.
But how was she so sure
that on that day, there'd be
someone just like her
at the scene?
Show me the client's account
of the Lianxin Island case.
(Online Banking, Transfer)
Exactly the same
as Lin Zhi'er's.
I get it now.
Lin Zhi'er is the one who hired us
to probe Lianxin Island's
illegal fundraising.
Why would she do that?
Maybe for the investigation.
Maybe she wanted to lure me there,
so she could hit me
and make me take her place there.
This is so complicated.
So,
are we still digging into this?
Of course we are.
But
right now, the key thing is
to celebrate your birthday.
Sis.
Birthday girl,
I'm taking you out for some fun.
(Happy birthday)
Happy birthday.
Let's drink!
Drink!
Sis, I just used your husband's card
to order some...
Lu Tingyu is such a playboy.
Feel free to use his card.
Got it.
So, what did you order?
You'll see in a minute.
Come on, let's sing.
Okay.
(Happy birthday)
Boss.
You've run this place well.
Thanks for holding things down here.
It's only what I should do.
Though I've become
the CEO of Luzhou Group,
the core business
is still under Lu Jianchuan's control.
We'll stick to the plan
and seize the power step by step.
Yes.
By the way,
with the expansion this year,
I also took over the KTV next door.
How about I show you around?
Go to work.
I'll look around.
Okay.
Sis, let's get loud!
(How many sides)
(does she have?)
Hurry up.
Come on.
Come in.
Hurry up.
You're the new one?
What are you waiting for?
Where's your mask?
Stay sharp.
Tonight, take good care
of the ladies.
Qing,
are these all your friends?
Why are they wearing masks?
They're all my mask friends.
Everyone present is a friend.
What to call you?
I'm Tiantian.
Guess my sign.
I'm made just for you.
How cute is that?
I'm Taiyang.
I'm good at dancing.
My name's Liang Xuan.
I can crack walnuts with my arms.
Powerful.
That's really impressive.
So cool.
My name's Xiao Ting.
No special talent.
♪This door♪
♪Lets in the sky outside♪
♪With a voice even lighter♪
♪Than how you just greeted me♪
♪I know now♪
♪What the chill in my body means♪
♪The moment salt hits the wound♪
♪My heart still beats so naively♪
♪To complete♪
♪A joy that needs no brave pretense♪
♪How cruel sincerity can be♪
♪Like a door with no key♪
♪Maybe you just passed by♪
♪The tears in my eyes♪
♪You looked like you had nothing to say♪
♪Then got so good at being cold♪
♪That's why a smile feels so precious♪
♪Maybe you just passed by♪
♪The tears burned into my heart♪
♪Let's say silence was just for show♪
♪Even if I've grown another year♪