Taste, beauty and aesthetics
are seemed to be abstract thing
to say and hard to understand.
As a matter of fact, everything
is based on its principles.
The livings with their outstanding beauty
are likely to have a higher chance
to survive and preserve their species.
Beauty is one of various
traits to indicate good genes.
Humans are social animals.
Some humans with good taste will
be seen better than other humans.
This is the reason why
taste becomes a hidden
factor to help categorize
classes in society ingeniously.
To be a special someone in this day and age
comes with many privileges.
Many people want to be
special persons by many ways,
either to have good taste
or being tasteless.
Bambi, an ordinary teenage girl,
is someone who is yearning
for something special.
(Notifications: Try out for a drum major)
An A-list new actress like Kimiya Issaranee
has turned from being a
model to be an international star.
You're so great at this.
I got started in this industry
because of Ms.Duangtawan.
I feel truly grateful for her because
she invited me to be a muse of her brand.
(Kimiya's makeup look)
Girls, let's go to drum major's try out.
Didn't you put too much
makeup under your eyes?
That's right, I don't think the facial
scan machine would recognize you.
Well, it's a try out day. I
need to look extra cute.
Please, join me. I know you want to.
Am I right, Model?
You want to?
I'm cool with anything.
She wanted to, let's go.
Please?
Alright everyone, I'll
announce the finalists now.
The first one, Khaocheum.
Dollar.
Yogurt.
Model.
And the last one,
Peanut.
The finalists can stay and learn the moves.
We'll have the grand opening
of drum majors this Friday.
For those of you who didn't make the cut,
you can stay to be our staffs if you
want to, got plenty of works to do.
Let's go.
Model.
Hey,
it's okay.
If you can't make it, then
we won't be a part of it either.
Or should we ask them?
You think it'd work?
I think I'll try.
Pin?
Can you give me another
shot? I really want this position.
I don't think your appearance is
quite suitable for a drum major.
What kind of appearance is the right fit?
I think you look…
Too much. It's so
unnatural. It's hard to explain.
You can be a staff member this year
and we'll see how it goes next year.
Let's go.
Is it cute? I Super cute.
Did you post it? Come on.
You think that
my makeup isn't too much, right?
It's looking good, you're looking good.
Come on, be proud of it.
See? It's cute.
I see, okay.
Bambi, we've got something
to do. See you tomorrow.
Don't forget to tag me in the
pic, see ya. I See you. Bye.
So cute. I Let's have a look.
I want this one. I Sure, let's go.
For those of you who're
looking for a cram school,
I'd like to recommend
The New Standard Prep.
It's more than a good place to learn,
it offers good friends and good community.
More importantly,
Mr.New is the nicest tutor here.
Join me in the class. I See you.
For those of you who're
looking for a cram school,
I'd like to recommend
The New Standard Prep.
It's more than a good place to learn,
it offers good friends and good community.
More importantly, Mr.New
is the nicest tutor here.
Join me in the class. I See you.
Hello / Hello.
Hey, my face is big. So ugly.
Excuse me. I Sorry.
Hey.
Yeah?
What do they teach here?
Right, they focus on SAT and IELTS tests to
submit for international courses in colleges.
Is it costly?
Here, have a look.
It costs 30,000 baht per
person for private class?
Well, international courses, you know?
If you're looking for the similar
courses, you can check out other places,
they have similar lessons.
What?
Why did you choose this place?
I
I see.
I didn't pay for it, they ask
me to promote the place.
But my classmates are
all in for good connections.
It's quite costly but you got
a whole new group of friends.
Like you've never hung out with before.
I think it's great.
You're right. They all
look like somebody to me.
Is that Thara's son? A minister?
That's right. His name is
Diesel. He's in my class.
That's Lukjan, an heiress of
airline business, you know her?
So pretty.
You think? I Yep.
And…
You are…
My name's Pure.
I see. I And you're?
I'm Bambi.
Bambi, alright. I Yes.
Good. See you later.
Bambi, okay. I Bye.
What're you doing?
I'm playing this.
Can I try?
Nope. It's 30,000!
I think it's too expensive.
Well, it's private tuturoing class.
I checked out this place and
it's not like the other places.
It offers good friends and good connection.
So you want to join
because you want to study for find friends.
You have friends in school.
Can you just be patient?
You're in 11th grade, you'll
graduate soon. I That's right.
Cram schools are all the same.
Listen to your mom.
If you earn money, you
can pick your own school.
Hey, you free this afternoon?
I'm so bored, let's watch a movie.
What's wrong?
I saw it yesterday, spill it.
I…We decided to be drum majors.
Pin asked us to join.
She was worried about
not enough people to fill in.
But you said that you wouldn't do it.
Well, she asked us to, I
wouldn't dare to say no.
Come on, it's fine.
Don't be mad. We can
watch a movie after practice.
Please? I Or you want to do something?
Right, you want to do something?
Hey! Bambi!
You're heading to a drum major practice?
I was about to ask you.
Why did you decide to
be their staff member?
They told you to do
this and that, so tired.
And you got nothing in return.
Sure I do. They'd see my face so
often and I'd get picked next year.
There must be some other way.
Sometimes we don't have a lot of choices.
Hey, we ordered milk tea
and rider's here, can you pick up for us?
Please?
Where is he?
Milk tea's here, everyone.
You want some?
Which one's for me? I Less sugar.
Where's the less sugar one? I Where is it?
Hey!
It just a quick break, Yogurt and Model.
You two asked for another chance from me.
Can you show me that you really want it?
Thank you, Ms.Duen.
What Duen?
It's nothing.
It's just a long time ago.
Spill it, come on.
Tell. I Tell us.
Alright, alright. Bambi and I used
to be classmates back in the day.
Peanut!
Hi.
Mom, can you take my jacket home? It's hot.
Are you sure? I Yep.
Did you forget something.
Thank you, Ms.Duen.
Why did she wear the same clothes as her?
Enjoy your movie.
Thanks, bye.
Are they siblings?
Let's go.
In a world full of special someone,
Bambi has never realized that
her ordinary life would be her weakness.
Can you hold it for me?
Sure.
Bambi, can you hold it for me?
Thank you, Ms.Duen.
Stop making jokes about Ms.Duen.
She raised me.
Let's go.
Why did you want to throw them away?
Don't care about what other people say.
Be confident.
If we're confident, then
we can wear anything.
We're not celebs, we don't
have to follow other people.
This is nonsense.
The sadder part is that the adults see
your crumbling world as nonsense.
Bambi has tried everything to
run away from her ordinary life
and she's always seeking
for something special.
Holy! Aint that too harsh?
Whatever, it's nothing.
Model won't wear dress made
from recycled items anymore.
She's gonna be a drum
major instead, what a bitch!
What? Who would keep
this dress? It's too huge.
Bitch! You weren't supposed to wear
this uniform today. No shame at all?
So what? I still can shine.
It's something new, you know?
That TikTok clip you
posted of me this morning,
it's famous now,
thousands of people liked it.
Film me another clip, okay?
1…2…3…
What? Who would keep this dress?
Model won't wear dress made
from recycled items anymore.
She's gonna be a drum
major instead, what a bitch!
You're the one asking for another chance.
No shame at all?
What? Who would keep this dress?
We don't have so many choices.
Hey, I'll keep the dress.
Everyone, let's go to the gate.
What is it?
The contest for recycled items
dresses are next Friday, right?
Like a queen.
Hello, kids.
Your princess will tell you a story.
Do you want to hear it?
Search: Bambi Princess of Trash.
Do you believe that
school for princess is real?
You don't, do you? Let's have a look.
Hello, kids. Let's eat like a princess.
I'm trying to watch my weight
so I'll have this one and this
little rice. I And eat it like this.
Oh my, Bambi girl,
you're just right. So right.
The only thing wrong about you is
you wore this dress on the wrong date.
And now you got a new
content and it went viral.
#Princess of trash.
Let's eat with the princess.
Hello?
You want my princess attitude
when trying your new dipping sauces?
Sure I can.
Hello, today, Princess Bambi will review
dipping sauce in cheddar cheese flavor,
made from the real cheese
from the Netherlands.
Looks so good.
Let me cut it in pieces.
Hello, today, Princess Bambi will review…
Thank you Princess Nong Nune.
Hi, you're so pretty, can
I get a picture with you?
Thanks.
Bambi dear, I really love your videos.
Everyone,
we're activists from environment
club in Thada Wittaya School.
We disagree with the contest of
recycled items dresses tomorrow.
Who're with me? Please raise your shoes.
From what I saw last year,
what did we do after the contest?
We threw away the dresses.
Who picked up trashes from
last year would understand.
We don't want the recycled items contest.
Raise your shoe if you're with me on this.
Come on, do it with no shame.
No fake recycled items.
No fake recycled items. I
Why're you so dramatic?
They organize this contest
every year. They'll take care of it.
I picked up the trash
and it's tired, you bitch!
You don't like it?
No fake recycled items.
Hello?
What? I'm going ot POPA?
Okay.
We are Strawberry Morrakot.
And the Best Alternative
of the Year award goes to…
BOY MARX.
I knew that I would win this award.
Hi, I'm FLUKKARON,
please say hi to my vlog.
We're so happy to win Girl
Group of the Year award.
And we're sorry for all
the mistakes. Thanks.
We're about to shoot our first series.
Please support us.
Thank you to all of our fans
who've supported and encouraged us on this.
Princess of Trash.
I listened to your podcasts all the time.
Thank you. I Can I get a picture with you?
Thanks. I Thanks.
Wait, what's your name?
Hold on one sec.
Yo! Bambi!
Mhong! I Bambi!
Long time no see. I I know.
How many years?
Since covid,
I've transferred school closed to my house.
And I help out my mom
with her noodles stand.
So busy.
You should come by.
It'll be my treat.
Why're you here?
I'm a trainee in Bangkok Banger.
Trainee? I Yep.
It's because of you.
Are you heading to an after party?
You want to join me?
I can take you.
You sure?
No!
Why, bro? Why can't you let her in?
She's on on the guest list.
I can't let her in.
Well, she's here already.
Look at her dress, please let her in.
That's fine.
It's okay.
I'm sorry I can't help you.
Are you heading back?
If so, I'll send you off.
It's okay. You should get in. I You sure?
See you later.
Your arm please?
You can't get in.
Why's that? My name is on the list.
Men can wear tank tops.
Excuse me?
Did you just assume my gender?
Huh?
They all know that I'm not really men.
And this is not a regular tank top.
It's Helmut Lang.
You're a man, so no. Look at this!
Fine.
Fuck.
I'm here, you have a jacket?
Security guards are tough crowd.
Women can wear spaghetti
strap. Why can't you just let me in?
I'm sorry, this is my friend.
Show me your hand.
Sure.
You have to wear this.
Nope. I Seriously?
So tasteless, why do I have to wear it?
Sorry. I Not wearing it.
Pure.
Bambi?
I'll follow you.
So cool.
The best screen couple
and you can get me in.
I just met you not long ago
and now you showed up here at POPA.
I thought you wouldn't recognize me.
Sure I do.
You drunk?
Who're you with?
You want to join me?
Bambi Princess of Trash.
Everyone.
This is Bambi.
Introduce yourselves, okay?
Namkhang.
I'm Diesel, make yourself comfortable.
Hi, I'm Lukjan.
You're so pretty.
Are you an actress?
Or an influencer?
I'm Bambi.
I got to go to POPA because of this dress.
Oh, this dress.
Is it made from trash?
Nope, just the materials.
School's project.
So brave.
Lukjan, I just ordered
Long Island iced tea for you.
You know me so well, Namkhang. Thank you.
Thank you.
Unlike you.
The fuck?
I haven't introduced myself.
I'm Tokyo.
I go to the same school
as Pure and Namkhang.
Honestly, I thought you
went to an international school.
I was an exchange
student to the US for a year.
It's not that hard to create an international
school's kid attitude, you know.
Look at these.
Kanjiko Hiroshi.
Just one and you're wide awake. I Awesome.
Give me one.
Hey, take one.
I'll get this one and you get this one.
It's fine, just liquor is
quite strong for me already.
You're weak.
Fine, don't take it.
I'll get it.
Let's play Truth or Dare.
You need to play.
Love it.
Let me start.
Lukjan, Truth or Dare.
I have nothing to hide. Truth.
What's your body count?
Seriously? I That's so spiced up.
Nine.
Huh? I Since when?
Nine people? I What?
What is body count?
What?
Let me explain this to you, New Girl.
It means how many
people have you slept with?
Like among your body count guys,
I'm the number one, right?
So cocky. I Why're you so full of yourself?
I'm cocky.
What about you? What's your body count?
Hey, it's my turn. Let me ask.
Nope, I'll ask Namkhang.
Namkhang,
Truth or Dare, honey?
Truth. I Okay.
Have you ever slept with Pure?
Dude what the fuck!
No!
We're just friends.
What kind of question
is that? Be nice to Bambi.
Now it's my turn.
Bambi, Truth or Dare.
Dare.
Okay. I So brave.
She's bold. I She's coming.
Well,
make out with Diesel.
No..no, I won't.
I'm cool with that.
It's just a game. I That's enough.
I'm fine. I Enough.
What the fuck! You're so protective of her.
Let me suggest
both of you to make out.
Is it that our Pure is so pure
that she's never kissed a girl?
Hey! You want my foot to kiss your lips?
You can make out with
her like you did Namkhang.
Namkhang.
If you're so protective of
her, then kiss her already.
I really want to see.
Let's do this.
Kiss!
What're you waiting for?
Go, kiss her like you kissed Namkhang.
So spicy.
Take her. I Can I change it to Truth?
What? I Come on, New Girl.
You didn't want to do anything.
Don't be such a party pooper, my gosh.
I'll shove this into your mouth.
What's your body count?
Woah! I really want to know.
You're just jealous.
Come on, we want to know. I That's enough.
It's even worse.
How many?
Guys, shut the fuck up!
I need to use a bathroom.
What? I Come on.
Bambi,
Where are you going?
I think I should go.
But you just got here.
Let's head back, they're waiting.
You want me to hear terrible
words from your friends?
Come on, don't be so
sensitive. They're drunk.
I don't get it.
I want to be their friends, I try to be nice.
But your friends treated
me like I'm a clown.
I don't feel like I don't belong anywhere.
I don't like my school.
My friends betrayed me.
You don't get it.
Of course, I do.
I know that they are such assholes.
But they're really good friends.
When I first started
to join the cram school,
I didn't feel like I truly belonged.
They called me
a fame-by-luck star
or something like that.
I don't think the speaker would remember it
but the listener never forget.
I chose this life.
I need to get used to it.
How did you get used to it?
Let it fly pass my brain.
Think of the horrible words
as bubbles like in comics.
Let them fly pass you.
It could really help.
You sure?
Short girl.
How does it feel?
I still feel something.
But I feel better.
That's enough.
I'll use this method.
Thanks.
What's next?
I'll head back, come on.
Going back? I Yep.
Hey, New Girl, you back?
My name is Bambi.
Yay! I Yay!
1…2…3…
Super drunk! Super fun!
Lukjan, you need to sit with me in
the front. It's so packed in the back.
Nope, I'm gonna sit with Name.
Hey!
Wait,
Bambi, you know how to drive, don't you?
But I just drive in my neighborhood.
What kind of this fucking song?
You won't like it?
Tokyo, can you change the song, please?
I want to listen to Name's song.
I can sing in private for you.
Let's take IG's story.
Get the phone.
Holy shit!
Shit! Oh my gosh!
Bambi.
What did you hit?
Bambi!
Who did you hit? I It's gonna be in news.
Did he dead? Go check on him.
Bambi!
Are you okay? Are you alright?
Namkhang, you need to calm down. I Lukjan,
you need to call your house. I Calm down.
Call your house. I I can't.
Focus! I Are you out of your mind?
Why? I I hit someone once,
my grandma will kill me.
I can't call my house.
Focus! I Bambi!
Are you okay? Are you alright?
Is he dead?
Your dad… / I didn't mean to.
It's okay, calm down. I I didn't mean to.
Police? I Calm down.
Please. I My grandma can't know about this.
Police?
What're you doing? I What the hell?
Police. I Hey! What did you do?
No. Stop, you can't do that.
I'll handle this.
You're going to call the police?
Are you out of your mind?
You need to calm down.
Stop yelling.
Did he dead?
My family can't know about this. I Focus!
I didn't mean to. I Focus, okay. Focus.
I didn't mean to! I I know,
but you need to focus.
I drove a car and crash someone.
I didn't mean to.
Thank you so much,
please take care of this.
Yes, sir.
Your dad handled this already.
Thank you so so much.
You think he'll make it?
I drank too much last night.
And guess who's having Omakase for brunch?
My freak in grandma!
Hey! Diesel!
Good shot!
(Show cancellation tonight. He's injured)
(Thank you everyone for your votes)
It's all cleared.
Where should we go tonight?
How's the uncle?
Hello, this is 191 Bangkok,
what's your emergency?
Hello?
What's your emergency?
Hey!
Hello?
Hey?
Can you hear me?
Are you okay?
It's fine. It's nothing.
I'm sorry.
This is not a joke. You
can't just call for nothing.
This is the wrong thing to do.
It's all done. I Thank you.
Bambi.
You study here, too?
Let's go.
I don't think the speaker would remember it
but the listener never forget.- Pure.
Yo! Aloha! How to say your username?
Kwamfhundanupha.
My name is Dream.
Do you remember what you told me?
Do whatever I want.
I want to ask about music.
How to start on this?
Can you moan right into my song?
I don't think so.
I really like the song you played for me.
Can I get that song?
Nothing comes for free.