[Disclaimer:
All depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
We're in trouble, Master.
Khem's disappeared.
Your instincts are strong.
Focus your mind on Khem,
and follow wherever your gut leads you.
I have cherished and protected you
for over 80 years.
How could I let you be taken
by someone else so easily?
Master,
can you please stay with me for now?
At least until I fall asleep.
I've got to thank Chayod
for giving me the idea
to forge this realm.
Since you're so bent on shutting me out,
I shall make you come to me instead.
Stop it, Ramphueng.
You know my name?
Always so eager to stir up trouble.
I was minding my own path.
It is you who came to provoke me.
The more lives you drag into your chaos,
the greater the weight of sin upon you.
You think sin frightens me?
You can never lay a hand on me.
Stay out of my way.
Even you can feel worried, can't you?
Your spell is going to be undone
before long.
Do you think my power ends here?
Stop it, you damn ghost!
Aw, little ones.
How adorable.
Good,
now that you're all here,
I'll wipe you out at once.
You think you possess the power
to act against me?
We got you.
You couldn't see it, huh?
Boo!
- Boo.
- Boo!
- Master!
- Master...
Come on, wake up!
Master!
Master...
She almost got you.
Are you harmed, Master?
- Master!
- Master...
Master...
Why are you here?
Did something happen to Khem?
He is doing well.
I just came to say farewell.
You have always felt my presence,
and it made me feel touched.
Our bond has endured a long time.
Even if I can't see you,
I can sense that
you've always been around our son.
Is it finally your time
to rest in peace?
I am truly grateful
for everything.
Thank you for the love
you've shown me and our son,
even knowing what was to come.
I never saw it that way,
neither in the moments
I shared with you,
nor in the time
I had left for ordination,
hoping to extend our son's life.
All I did was with love,
and I did it willingly.
No need to cry.
Let us part with happiness.
Have you said goodbye to Khem yet?
Our son has grown up so well,
and he's always been cherished
by everyone.
Now that I've found
the person who can help him,
I feel at ease.
Hasn't Grand Master Sek
passed away long ago?
- Master!
- Master...
There is another person,
someone even more blessed
than Grand Master Sek.
Master!
Master...
And what matters most is that,
though he may not realize it himself,
I believe we can place our son's future
in his care.
Then I can be at ease.
You'll finally rest.
May you find peace in another life.
I shall follow you one day.
Please don't hurry.
If there is another life beyond this,
I hope our paths cross once more.
Right.
I hope so, too.
The warding shield is still intact,
and Ramphueng has yet to breach it.
If so,
how did she manage
to draw you into her realm?
What were you doing before that, Master?
I left my body to go save the villagers.
What do you guys know?
Don't keep me in the dark alone.
Ramphueng seized the chance
and pulled Master's spirit away
while it was outside the house.
And?
Should he leave his body once more,
it shall be pulled into her realm again.
So that means...
he can't leave his body ever again?
I still have to
watch over the villagers.
I'll never know when
or what might happen
to them again.
Then from now on,
you can leave this duty to me and Thong.
Right, Master.
We've got this.
You don't need to
project your spirit anymore.
We know every nook and cranny
of the village.
You have nothing to worry about.
Okay.
Guard yourselves well.
If danger comes,
flee at once.
You are my family.
Do you understand?
Yes, Master.
Our duty is to keep an eye
on everything.
If anything happens,
we'll let you know right away.
There's no danger.
You should rest now, Master.
We can rest assured
that everyone is safe.
Be a big girl, Dotty.
Don't be too big, though.
Auntie Kaew asked me
to give this to you.
This smells so good.
Look, Jet.
Jet and Khem are up to something.
They're watering all the plants
and polishing the floors
until they shine like mirrors.
And they're making tons of food.
It looks so good!
Hey, you're dropping everything.
What's wrong, Jet?
So, you're annoyed
just seeing Charn walk by?
No!
I'm just thinking
if I should tell him the truth.
Why would you?
Didn't you want to keep it a secret?
Well... Uh...
I don't know.
He helped us without even asking.
You know how nosy he usually is.
I'm afraid his curiosity might kill him.
Go ahead.
I'm fine with it.
But,
Jet, don't you actually hate him?
Well...
I mean...
He's just annoying.
I don't exactly hate him.
I just feel that he can be trusted
if we need more help.
Aw,
since when did you guys become besties?
What are you talking about?
Right,
why is Master sleeping in so much today?
I'll store the food
in the cabinet first.
Come on.
Grand Master,
I hope your grandson likes me a lot.
Your legs are fine.
I suppose you can stand on your own.
Khem,
are you flirting with Master?
Jet!
Master,
Khem got up really early this morning
to clean the house.
He even made some food.
And?
Uh...
Well, I mean...
May I stay here
until the semester break ends?
Please.
Please, Master.
I promise I'll help lighten your load,
and I will never cause you
any trouble, Master.
Please, Master.
He won't give you any problems.
If anything happens,
I'll handle it myself.
If you want to, just stay.
No need to make it complicated.
Yes!
You'll soon pick up
the dialect so well, man.
Hey!
Thank you, Master.
What?
Are you not returning to Bangkok, Khem?
You sure you'll return
after your birthday?
Yeah.
That's a relief.
I was worried
you'd give up on your studies.
Gosh,
that was like a whole podcast,
but that's what makes you feel relieved?
Are you not surprised that he's cursed?
Well,
at this point, I'm getting used to it.
Though it feels unbelievable,
I've witnessed it with my own eyes.
I can't change that fact.
Khem, you're really strong,
to have come this far.
Thanks, Charn.
As soon as I return to Bangkok,
let's have a meal together.
Alright, everyone.
Put your hands together.
I shall now begin the ritual
of calling your vital force.
And then our voices say:
May fortune come.
This is an auspicious day.
Together we gather, together we pray.
The venerable shaman
declares it a blessed day.
This is an auspicious day.
Together we gather, together we pray.
The venerable shaman
declares it a blessed day.
It's a day of fortune, a day of light.
With the offerings adorned with delight,
we now summon the vital force
through this rite:
May your vital force come forth.
- Bye-bye.
- Have a safe trip, guys.
- Get home safely.
Have a safe trip, kids.
I'll see you soon.
Thanks for everything.
- Tell me when you're back.
- Sure.
Have a safe trip.
Let me know when you're there.
Bye-bye.
Goodbye, guys.
- Come back again, okay?
- Safe journey to you all.
Here are the monks.
- Namaskar.
- Sadhu.
Behave yourselves, alright?
- Good luck!
- Good luck, guys.
Have a safe trip, guys.
We've really made so many friends
at this camp.
I'll come again next year.
Let's go, guys.
- Come on, let's go home.
- Let's go.
Guys,
we're leaving.
- Goodbye.
- See you later.
- See you.
- Thank you so much.
- We'll see you later.
- Okay.
Are you serious?
It's not too late to change your mind.
I've made up my mind.
Can I please stay here, too, Master?
By choosing to board the same boat,
you accept that if danger comes,
you're ready to give your lives
for one another.
You think you can handle that?
I can.
Give me that.
What the heck is in here?
It's freaking heavy.
It's books.
For killing time.
If it's too heavy,
just hand it over to me.
Hurry up.
We need to prepare the offerings
for Master, too.
Come on.
It's so damn heavy.
Wait up.
Jet, Charn...
Whoa...
Shit.
Grandma Si had some stuff,
so I borrowed a few.
Also,
there was a banana grove on the way,
so I cut some more.
They should be useful.
Wait, did you even ask them
before you cut these?
I didn't...
What?
I didn't fail to!
You're afraid, huh?
Do you want anything
to go with your coffee, Master?
I'll bring it over for you.
No.
Just get that done.
What's with him?
One minute he's nice,
the next he's cold.
Whoa,
it truly shows that
you're arts students.
Let's take it easy next time.
My fingers are in pain.
Come on,
we need to give it our all, you know.
If you want to stay here,
you have to be my disciples.
I'll teach you some magic, too.
Alright.
No need.
Charn will do it alone.
Why, though?
To become my disciple,
you must honor me as your master
without any hint of disrespect, harm,
or impure motives.
If you break this vow,
no one will be able to save you.
Understood.
Alright.
With all respect,
I, Charnvit Panichakorn,
offer myself
to serve as your faithful disciple
and vow never to bring
dishonor to your name.
Come here.
May your life prosper
in the four blessings:
longevity, beauty,
happiness, and health.
And may all your desires be fulfilled.
Go into the forest
and look for red pieces of paper
rolled like this.
Whichever roll you find first,
take that one.
Okay, Master.
Be careful.
The forest has a territory holder,
you know.
You'll go with him, Jet.
What?
Why do I have to?
Jet, Charn, good luck.
Come on. Follow me.
Hurry and come back.
I'll have something tasty
waiting for you.
Hey.
Do you know how to make alms flowers?
Uh...
Yes.
He should've told me
he didn't want me as his disciple.
My hands are all messed up.
Wait and see,
I'll make these flowers
as weird as possible.
Have you found any?
Not yet.
You should help me find one.
Why are you scared?
It's not even dark yet.
Because it's not dark yet,
Phrai, the territory holder,
is still awake.
Phrai?
Who's that?
Is there really paper in here?
The wind may have blown it away.
Charn...
Jet!
Behind you.
What's behind me?
Phrai,
this is Charn.
Hey, Charn,
this is Phrai.
On three, we'll run.
I haven't counted yet!
Charn, wait up!
Jet!
Jet, Charn!
You're back?
Whoa...
Here, Master.
I found it.
You asshole!
Master's up here.
That's Dotty.
Where are your glasses?
How are you supposed to see?
It's alright.
I have another pair upstairs.
Keep this with you.
It'll guard you when you're in danger.
But you must not break any precepts.
Thank you, Master.
So, what about me?
Am I getting one, too?
I've given you
a wooden Buddha amulet, haven't I?
But...
does that mean
I did all that for nothing?
I should at least get something.
What do you want?
Well...
I wanna see Thong and Ake again.
Can you please...
remove the spell blocking my sight?
Jet...
Jet's here!
Hey, Thong, Ake!
Jet, did you bring anything for us?
Here.
There you go.
Yay!
Thong, Master might not be
very happy with that.
I got one for you, too.
I got it.
Jet,
will you really not be able
to see us anymore?
Master's so mean.
Why isn't he helping you at all?
Don't blame him.
My dad told him to do it.
Not even he could go against it.
But it's okay.
I believe that
even if I can't see you two,
I'll always feel your presence
beside me.
Let's hug.
Are you sure about this, Jet?
It's not something that can be
switched on and off so often.
I am, Master.
What about your dad?
Can he handle this?
My dad wanted you to block my sight
'cause I was always talking to ghosts
and had no human friends.
But now,
I do have friends.
Besides,
I've grown up, too.
My dad should understand that.
Alright, let's do it, then.
Close your eyes.
Focus your mind
on the center of your body.
Open your eyes slowly.
Don't rush it.
- Jet!
Take this.
There you go.
- Jet...
- Take this!
Take it easy.
Jet's not used to it yet.
- Okay, Master.
Take this.
There you go!
You haven't grown up at all, have you?
You're actually older than me,
I believe.
I suppose I should call you...
Uncle Thong and Uncle Ake!
Come here!
They're Master's kuman thongs.
Don't be scared.
I can feel it.
Hearing Jet's laugh,
I bet they must be so adorable.
Take this.
- Here!
- Hey, come on.
It tickles.
Take this!
Khem,
why didn't Master
let you take him as your master?
I wonder that, too.
I still don't get it.
When Master mentioned impure motives,
what exactly did he mean?
I mean, you wouldn't hurt anyone.
Well...
I mean,
I'm asking to be his disciple
because I want to survive.
That's probably an impure motive,
right, Jet?
But the reason I agreed
is that I want to help you.
Isn't that impure, too, then?
Oh, he's right.
That sounds right.
Hey.
You are suspicious, man.
Anything you're keeping from us?
Tell me.
No!
Well...
that's the story.
What's wrong?
Say something!
Oh, my God.
I'm in shock.
So you've actually known him
longer than I have.
And you've been in love
since your past life.
I don't love him.
It was Khemmika and Pawat.
Is this a coincidence
or destiny?
If Jet hadn't brought you here,
you wouldn't have met him.
Exactly.
Destiny is doing its job too well.
I feel like I'm living in a series.
Come on,
stop it.
Anyway,
perhaps he thinks
I just recalled being Khemmika,
so he might assume
I'm still attached to her feelings.
That's why he didn't accept me
as his disciple.
- But you're into...
- What?
No buts.
I've known you for ages.
You think I wouldn't notice?
You can usually tell
what's real and what's not.
Yet here you are,
totally agreeing with him.
Be sincere with me.
Give me an honest answer.
How do you feel about him?
I mean...
I...
I like him.
Gosh!
I knew it, man!
I'm totally invested.
What I feel for him
and what I want him to help me with
are two separate things.
No matter what, I have to survive first.
As for Master,
I'm not expecting anything anyway.
He probably has no feelings for me.
So...
what if I tell you...
he might think the same way?
Really, Jet.
Master was coughing up a lot of blood,
yet the first thing he did
was rush to see Khem.
Right, Thong?
Yes, and there's more.
When you and Charn went into the forest,
Master quietly stopped
on the porch steps to watch Khem.
It's true.
We're being honest.
Do you still want to expect nothing?
Well...
it's still...
impossible anyway.
Impossible, my ass.
Not nowadays, Khem.
I agree with you, though, Khem.
Even if he truly has feelings for you,
he has his duties to uphold,
so he must follow his precepts
and maintain a distance from you.
Especially living in the same house,
he might feel uncomfortable around you.
I think...
it'd be better if you gave up now.
Are you a Debbie Downer or what?
Come on now. Let's go to sleep.
Khem, just sleep.
Don't listen to him.
Come on, let's sleep.
Good night.
You had bandages
on your fingers last night, didn't you?
Right.
Khem,
are they healed now?
Yeah.
They were already healed
when I woke up.
Must've been some miracle salve.
What?
Leave already.
Grandma Si is probably starving now.
Let's go.
You're not gonna
change your mind, Master?
I've told you I'm busy.
Sorry, I'm early.
The traffic was light,
so I got here quicker.
Jet!
Let me tie your wrist to welcome you.
May you grow and prosper.
May you be healthy and joyful.
It fills my heart with joy
to have you around.
Sadhu.
Wait, Master had a girlfriend?
Don't take it the wrong way.
I said it was a rumor.
Then,
why were people spreading it?
Well,
they were childhood friends.
And before he became who he is today,
he was super wild, man.
A tech-school boy, you know.
With that look,
everyone had something to say about him.
They wouldn't spread that rumor
if there wasn't some truth to it.
Here's the thing.
Master's dad and Prim's were close,
so they'd often visit each other.
That's why people thought
they'd get married.
But that's all there was.
When I moved in with him,
Prim had already gone for her studies.
Nothing ever happened.
Even now, they're not alone.
You saw it yourself
that her brother was in the car.
Her younger brother?
Yeah.
That was Pong.
He rolled down the window
to say hi to us.
Don't worry.
I think...
there's nothing between them.
I stayed up all night thinking.
I was thinking...
I'm going all in on your ship.
What?
Is anyone going to board a ship?
Come on, that's not it.
It's like...
shipping people, Grandma.
Gosh,
how do I explain this?
The gen gap is huge.
Like rooting for a couple?
What?
You know?
Of course I do.
I heard Chompoo
talked to her friends about that.
So, what couple are you talking about?
Uh...
They're around here.
I mean, one person in that relationship
is close to me.
He's not so sure
if his crush has feelings for him.
And they're pretty different, Grandma.
Each of them
also has their own duties to handle.
So I figured...
it's better to be prepared.
Why would you stress out for him?
This is not your business.
It's got nothing to do with you guys.
But if you want him
to get what he wants,
there might be a way.
Will it really work?
Yeah! Trust Grandma Si.
If Master has feelings for you,
he'll think about you all day and night.
He's coming.
But are we really doing this?
We've come so far.
Hey.
I told you to get baby powder.
This is all there is,
or you'll get flour instead.
Khem, give me your hand.
Do it now.
Cast the spell.
Bring me a damp towel.
Uh...
Do you want to
wipe it off yourself, Master?
You do it.
Sit here.
What spell did you cast?
It was...
a spell from Grandma Si.
What kind of spell?
Tell me what kind of spell it was.
Uh...
Is there any way to help her?
Jet, are you with Master?
Ramphueng's messing with us.
There are 40 subjects of meditation.
But it takes time to master each one.
You came all the way here.
Is there a reason for your visit?
I need your help, Master.
Oh...
You're Pong, right?
Master...
What about breakfast?
I'm not hungry.
I feel like
I've been making him uncomfortable.
I think...
I won't bother Master anymore.