Officail Website : kissasian.be  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Whether you're light or a lie,
I can't pull myself away ♪
♪ In this game,
truth or lie no longer matters ♪
[Queen of Darkness]
[Episode 18]
You're such a scoundrel.
Willing to be Song Pa's lackey
just for profit.
I look down on you.
Because the price they offered
was tempting enough.
So,
you can only end up
as a stepping stone.
I really regret not
seeing your true colors earlier.
Thinking back on every time
I spent with you,
I feel sick.
Good thing you see the truth now.
Sign this confession.
For the sake of what we once had,
I'll make your prison life
a little more decent.
[District Court]
Do you think that's possible?
I'd rather die
than give you what you want.
I'll make sure you can't even be a lackey,
just a maggot in the filthy sewers.
I've heard too many
of these tough talk.
In the end, they all gave in.
If you have the guts, then kill me.
Otherwise,
I'll make you pay a thousandfold,
a hundredfold.
Still so defiant.
What are you planning to do?
I'll make everyone see
the once untouchable heiress
stark naked
and utterly humiliated.
Huo Xiao.
Let me go!
You heartless jerk!
You shameless jerk!
Don't touch me!
I don't need you to remind me!
Inspector Huo is really ruthless.
Striking right at the weak spot.
It seems An Ning will
hate him to the core this time.
I didn't expect it either.
That he'd go this far.
Whether it's real or not,
you need to find a way
to turn them completely
against each other.
Leave it to me.
Two rapists were just brought in.
If...
Pretty girl.
What are you guys doing?
We heard you messed with
someone you shouldn't have.
Inspector Huo
asked us
to keep an eye on you.
I've never had a taste of
a rich young lady.
I'm warning you.
Stay away from me.
I advise you
not to fight it for nothing.
Exactly.
Just give in obediently.
And you'll suffer less.
To get out of this situation now,
I can only use my wits.
I know
I have no way to resist now.
So I'll just accept it.
But
I only want to be with you.
If I have to be with someone
as ugly as him,
I'd rather die.
You don't want to share me
with others either, right?
Yeah.
I'll go first.
You wait a moment.
Why should you go first?
Didn't we agree I'd go first?
Take a look at yourself in the mirror,
what kind of loser are you?
Get lost!
Didn't know you were this useless.
You just let others walk all over you
and do nothing.
What kind of man does that?
Did you hear that?
She likes me.
You dare to show off in front of me?
I want to be with her first, I'll go first!
You dare play tricks on me?
Tell me.
Who sent you here?
It was...
It was Jiang Meng.
He told us to act
under Inspector Huo's name,
and come after you.
Miss, you've had a hard time.
Miss.
I've already submitted the evidence.
It proves you have nothing to do with
the gang crime.
We can leave now.
I thought you'd chicken out
and wouldn't dare
show up for the meeting.
You
inviting me to watch the stars?
No one else is around.
Just be honest with me.
Are you really defecting,
or just playing tricks?
You're asking this question.
So you already doubt me.
Does my answer still matter?
You're a smart person.
Then you should know
never use someone you don't trust.
Officail Website : kissasian.be  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
So what?
Planning to dump me once I'm not useful?
Being a dirty cop
and a lackey at the same time.
Aren't you afraid
that one day the payback
will come for you?
Even if that day comes,
you won't live to see it.
In this world,
whoever laughs last
gets to define black and white.
Inspector Huo got silenced
over a gang crime case.
While I
cleaned out the dirty cops,
got promoted and made a fortune.
This is your final end.
Is that so?
I'm afraid this ending
will be reversed.
The rapists have been sent in.
The money is in your account.
Once Huo Xiao and An Ning completely
turn against each other,
clearing all my obstacles,
then you'll be promoted
to superintendent.
I'll always remember who my boss is.
And the higher I climb,
the easier it is for you to do things.
Check Huo Xiao's situation tonight.
No problem.
You don't even realize the end is near.
No wonder
you've never amounted to anything.
Alright, you win this time.
We'll see.
Chairman An Ning
is under police investigation
for gang crime.
A criminal
actually became the chairman
of our group.
That's truly a disgrace to us all.
From now on, I'll take over as chairman.
- Good.
- Fine.
- That's great.
Alright.
You're really putting on a good show.
Twisting right and wrong
and stealing someone else's position.
Too bad though,
your show has fallen apart.
[Investigation report on the
suspected involvement] Here's the
[of the chairman of Longxing Group in
organized crime] investigation certificate.
It proves I have nothing to do with any
gang crime.
Someone's clearly
spreading false rumors.
♪ Stay in the line ♪
♪ Breaking the line ♪
♪ I'm the only queen ♪
♪ Roaring like a lion ♪
♪ To show my claw ♪
Mr. Song.
We suspect you and Jiang Meng
have engaged.
[Assistance Investigation Oder]
in power-for-money transactions.
Please assist in the investigation.
There's no solid proof at all.
This is pure slander!
I went through the same thing, didn't I?
If you're really innocent,
you can also get out,
safe and sound like me.
Unless you've got something to hide.
The innocent have nothing to fear.
I believe
the police will clear my name soon.
♪ It's what I came here for ♪
♪ I'm gonna take it out ♪
♪ Take it, take it ♪
Go.
Hurry up.
♪ I'm gonna take it out ♪
Good thing you're okay.
I trust you.
That's why I dared to
put my life in your hands.
I hope you're not keeping anything
from me.
I'm looking into Ye Hong's death too.
I suspect it's tied to
Song Pa and Jiang Meng.
Just give me a little more time.
Is that so?
Then I'll wait for your explanation.
Miss, why did you come back early?
I came back early to surprise Dad.
Where's my dad?
Dad!
Huo Xiao.
I'll kill you!
Dad.
Huo Xiao killed you.
And I, because of my amnesia,
stayed by the enemy's side.
I was fooled like a fool.
Even.
I developed feelings
I shouldn't have for him.
Dad,
I'm sorry.
Now I remember everything.
I swear
I'll avenge you.
No matter what it takes,
I'll make him
pay for what he did in full.
Did you
find out something?
You're the one I trust most.
I know you'd never lie to me.
Right?
Officail Website : kissasian.be  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
♪ Mist coils around the sleeping forest ♪
♪ Memories scattered
through cracks of darkness ♪
♪ How to escape this real-feeling dream ♪
♪ Lies reflect in water's gleam ♪
♪ Traces of existence
can never be erased ♪
♪ How to find the self I can't reclaim ♪
♪ Fly away, hear she says ♪
♪ She'll fly out from
thorns of woven lies ♪
♪ Pierce the fog,
shatter this dream tonight ♪
♪ Burn like fire ♪
♪ Just burn like fire ♪
♪ The maze in the abyss starts to clear ♪
♪ Yet night keep on whispering ♪
♪ Surrender to fate,
no clear direction ahead ♪
♪ She will rise as the dawn
that breaks the darkness ♪
♪ Never slowing down,
for tomorrow cannot be stopped ♪
♪ Surrender to love and find the way ♪
♪ Even if fate tries to forget her ♪
♪ Never despair,
for the heart burns with endless light ♪
♪ Waiting for dawn ♪
[Copyright of this short drama
belongs to]
[Shanghai Chuqi Weishi
Culture Media Co., Ltd.]
[and Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[Co., Ltd.]
[Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[holds exclusive global online
and broadcast rights]