(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Oh!
I've always wanted to try one of those.
Is that right?
Mmm.
This is really good.
What's "delicious" in Japanese?
- Uh, oishi.
- "Oishi? Oishi."
Oishi, right?
- Oishi.
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, no.
- You need to.
- Hiro, come on.
Cha Mu-hee handles things so well.
Even though Hiro is acting like a diva,
she sees the best in that guy.
You're right.
No matter what Hiro says, she's smiling.
I don't think he's funny at all
if you ask me.
If she's faking that smile,
Cha Mu-hee's a truly talented actress.
Was the hot dog that good?
I've worked with you for over five years,
but today's the first time
I've seen you finish junk food.
I know, right?
I downed that whole mountain of calories.
I was just copying her "delicious,"
but ended up finishing the whole thing.
If you enjoy the food,
the calories don't count.
Just look at it that way.
That woman's a bit strange, you know.
She's always smiling.
Even when I act cold and distant,
she keeps smiling.
God knows what's so amusing.
And she gives me stuff like this.
She's up to something.
You reckon?
It looked like she was just
genuinely enjoying herself.
Genuinely enjoying herself?
With me?
Yes.
It looked like she was on a date
with a guy she likes.
In moments like that,
there's something different
about a woman's smile.
I guess you could say it glows.
She was glowing?
Because of me?
A four-leaf clover.
Hmm.
Oh.
Her legs will fall asleep
if she stays like that.
Oh, wow, she found one.
She's so happy.
Did you have a good day?
You looked like you had
a lot of fun on that date.
Yes, I had a lot of fun.
I ate delicious food and took some photos.
But watching the sunset
was my favorite part.
Aren't you cold?
I can tolerate
hot and cold weather pretty well.
It doesn't feel cold at all.
Normally, I don't like the sunset.
It makes me feel sad.
Today's so beautiful and magical.
I love it.
What's different about today?
I've been alone a lot,
and the sun going down reminds me of that.
I think I'm happy
because I'm with someone.
Of the many sunsets I've witnessed,
today is by far the most beautiful.
I guess you'll always remember
this moment.
Perhaps forever.
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
I'm just wondering.
From now on, will Producer Park be filming
the interviews instead of Producer Kim?
Producer Kim has already left.
He's on a plane to Seoul already.
Oh?
An emergency came up,
so he had to go back there.
I… I hope that everything will be okay.
Ah, it's…
I won't go into the details,
but you don't have to worry
or think about it.
And just so you know,
the production crew has no idea.
Another producer is going
to come here quickly.
Until the new producer arrives,
we'll keep this between us.
Sh.
Will we be filming more, or should we wait
until the new producer gets here?
- Oh--
- No, no, no. Tomorrow's shoot is canceled.
Uh, are we still going to see
the aurora borealis?
That won't be canceled, right?
Mm-hmm. The Northern Lights.
It's the main reason
we're shooting in Canada.
- We have to get the shot.
- Of course! Can't leave until seeing it.
Absolutely!
Seeing the aurora borealis
can't be guaranteed, Mu-hee.
Uh, this time of year,
the probability is around 60%.
Since tomorrow's shoot is canceled,
our chances to actually catch it
have been reduced significantly.
If we're lucky, we'll see a glimpse of it.
- Oh?
- Yeah.
Don't worry.
Luck's on our side. I know it.
We'll see the Northern Lights.
I believe it.
- Huh?
- Don't be a downer.
What can we do?
30%? Those are decent odds.
Aurora borealis is kinda hit or miss.
No point in worrying about it.
They said it's unlikely.
I really wanna see it.
And I was hoping we'd see it together.
Well, you can sleep in late tomorrow
'cause we're not working.
Wait, hold on.
We won't be shooting tomorrow.
Let's grab a drink tonight, then.
Go get the soju
and some instant noodles, Yong-u.
Why would you pair soju
with instant noodles?
I have better food in my room.
Let's go. We'll have a night in.
Wait, in your room?
Sure. Um, why not?
Wait a minute. I'll change
into something more comfortable.
I'm only going there to drink.
I'm not there to exercise.
Too clubby? Like I'm headed out?
Where are my clothes?
Oh, hey.
Soju is in the fridge.
Thanks.
Why don't we ask Ho-jin to join us?
Is he in his room? Does he want a drink?
He's not here.
What?
He wanted to use his free time
to go to a bookstore.
He's read all these books already,
and now he's out to get some more.
That guy's awesome.
That's Joo Ho-jin for ya.
He reads tourist pamphlets
in different languages.
How do you like your squid?
Medium rare?
Congratulations.
Your books are selling
like hotcakes in Canada.
I hope you get rich.
I heard this place is
a popular local spot.
That's why I wanted
to try the hot dogs here.
Here you go. Enjoy.
Thank you.
- Thanks for waiting.
- Oh.
- Hope you enjoy it.
- Thank you.
Oh wow.
Oh!
This is so great.
Hmm. His vision's pretty good.
This one's in Korean.
What kind of books do you like?
Joo Ho-jin, you're back already.
Yeah.
I had a few drinks with Yong-u
since we're not shooting.
But we cleaned up.
When he gets drunk,
he falls asleep right away. He's out.
Just leave him like that.
Well, I'll get going.
All right, see you.
Have a good night.
Those are my glasses, I think.
Was he checking me out or what? Weird guy.
Did he want me to stay?
Well, he could have just
asked me to stay for a drink.
Goodness.
- Cha Mu-hee.
- Oh, shoot. Yes?
You left your phone.
Oh! Thanks.
And please give me my glasses back.
Oh. I'm sorry. I didn't know.
I accidentally left with them on.
I was just reading a book.
I borrowed them because my vision is bad.
They are the right prescription.
I even forgot I was wearing glasses.
They're nonprescription glasses
for protection.
Ah! You have good vision. I'm glad.
They're a little bent.
Uh…
Want me to lend you that book
because you liked it?
There's a version of this
where borrowing the book
would make it less embarrassing.
Okay, please get it.
I'll get it. Just a second.
I forgot the key.
There is no 24-hour concierge here.
No one's awake to help us. It's too late.
Yong-u is still out. I tried calling.
He gets like this when he's drunk.
You should go back to your room.
Sleep a little bit.
You're just going to stay out here?
I saw a sofa I can sleep on
in the hallway.
Well, I'll wait for an hour or two.
He might wake up.
All right, I'll try calling him again.
My key.
I also left the room key inside.
I hope you're just messing with me.
It's a real problem.
Seriously.
You're sleeping here tonight?
It'll get too cold.
It'll be fine.
Go and knock on the writers' room door.
I will. Good night, then.
Oh, I'd better just stick around here too.
Yong-u should be awake in an hour.
I don't wanna be rude and wake up Ms. Cho.
I didn't really read that novel earlier.
What's it about?
It's kind of a, uh, mystery novel
they turned into a movie.
Oh, I'm sure that book's great.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
One of the characters gets killed,
but there's no murderer.
And that's the big reveal. Ah!
You spoiled the best part!
Damn it, Ho-jin.
You wanted to read the book?
No, please keep going.
In a peaceful, crime-free village,
a minor event changed it all.
An unmarried guy committed a petty crime
and got ostracized.
Everyone in the village shunned him.
One day, he gets beaten to death
by a widow, his neighbor.
They're trying to find out why.
They start by examining the villagers.
One by one. Then, bam!
- And, well…
- I wasn't scared at all.
Really? You were just acting scared,
were you?
In the end, the dead guy gets resurrected.
You're making that up.
- I swear it's all true.
- You're lying.
- Oh.
- Oh, you're up.
I must have fallen asleep. I was so tired.
What about Yong-u? Is he awake?
Were you able to get into your room?
Not yet.
- I'd better go wake him up, then.
- There's a market in town.
You're welcome to join. Wanna go together?
Yeah, sure. I'd love that.
Stuck in my throat
Round and round
I wanna speak out
But no one's there
Echoes of my voice
Answer alone
Tell me the truth
What don't I see?
Stuck in my thoughts
I walk till I fade
I feel the love…
- Wanna try an apple?
- These look good.
But why am I blue…
Ho-jin, I got carrots.
Round and round, my life just goes on
I greet the breeze
And nod to the trees
I hear the winds reply
Miss!
You can't walk under the ladder.
It's considered bad luck.
Something bad might happen.
I'm sorry.
Why did the woman at the market say that?
Walking under an open ladder
is considered bad luck here.
People take it seriously.
Is that so? What am I gonna do now?
Should I throw salt over my shoulder?
I'm superstitious. It's gonna work.
I had a feeling you'd believe that.
I saw you found a four-leaf clover.
You did?
I really hope to see the aurora tonight.
A four-leaf clover can bring you luck.
Lucky enough to see the aurora borealis.
So I was gonna get seven. Lucky seven.
I wanna find them by the end of today.
So far, I have five.
Fingers crossed, okay?
If I don't find them in time,
we won't be able to see it.
I understand, but does that mean
if we don't see the lights,
it'll be all your fault?
Hey, what makes you say that?
That's kind of cruel.
Why? You put that on yourself,
saying it was on you if we see it or not.
I just agreed with you.
It doesn't help if you agree.
Just empathize instead.
You could comfort me by saying,
"No, Cha Mu-hee,
it wouldn't be your fault."
Or "I believe in you!
Yes! You'll find 'em tonight."
Just say, "You can do it! I know you can!"
So an aurora
is a luminous event that occurs
when charged particles collide
with, uh… with the atmosphere on Earth.
For the record, let me tell you,
the clovers have nothing to do with it.
What a relief.
And also,
as for finding two more,
I wish you luck, okay?
I get it. You don't believe in this.
I thought so, okay.
Honestly, anticipating anything
brings feelings of anxiety.
That sort of energy is a waste
and doesn't change things.
Isn't it natural to be anxious
when things might not work out?
Still, you can believe
and start with that hope.
It could really happen.
Isn't that how your mind works
when you start anything, Joo Ho-jin?
What I'm saying is,
I want to find seven
and show you how beautiful the lights are.
Don't be so skeptical. Have faith, okay?
All right, then. I hope we see it.
KIM YOUNG-HWAN
For real?
Don't just say that! I'll be hurt!
This deadline's killing me.
Hey, send a photo. Give me an update.
If he had started writing earlier…
What's going on?
Praise doesn't help someone
who's already famous
and could have a Nobel Prize soon.
He still wants more.
He craves support and constant love.
I need five minutes.
Grab your things and go.
I'll join you. Gotta run a quick errand.
He said he'd be real quick.
Why is he taking so long?
Ah, yes. I got lost.
Now I know where to go.
A short walk and…
You got lost again?
Sometimes your head's in the clouds.
You can be pretty zoned out.
You leave your room key, go the wrong way…
I won't deny that
since I'm trying to find you right now,
but give me a second.
Tell me. What does the place look like?
Uh…
Oh.
Well, the Calgary Tower is close.
Then wait by the tower
and keep breathing deep breaths,
and I'll come rescue you, princess.
Princess?
Wait, it's the other way.
Joo Ho-jin!
I can't believe it's you!
Shin Ji-sun?
I can't believe I'm meeting you by chance.
I was thinking it couldn't be you.
What a surprise.
Why are you here?
I've taken over Jeong-su's place
as the producer.
I came straight from the airport.
Oh, so you're replacing him.
Yes.
I'm glad this happened. Do you have a car?
I have to go meet with writer Cho later.
Yes, it's close.
Cha Mu-hee!
Hi, there. It's nice to meet you.
I'm the new producer, Shin Ji-sun.
Hi, I'm Mu-hee. It's nice to meet you.
Look forward to working with you.
She was coproducer for
the South Korean season of Romantic Trip.
A famous producer from South Korea
with succesful shows under her belt.
A female producer named Shin Ji-sun.
And the shoot?
Are we starting immediately?
Shooting starts tomorrow,
which means you have today off.
I'd better work out all day,
then hit the sauna.
I got fat from sharing food
with that zombie. That zombie.
It's true that
you tend to gain weight very easily.
Tell her you don't eat much
out of fear of gaining weight.
I don't want to reveal my weakness
to that zombie.
By the way,
did it really seem that way
to you, Nanami?
It doesn't look like
you've gained much, no.
- I'm talking about Cha Mu-hee.
- Cha Mu-hee?
Oh. Did my comment
about her liking you bother you?
No, it's not that. I'm just worried.
I think I'd better keep my distance
and treat her more coldly.
Yes, for her sake.
I stepped out of the airport,
and I was so cold. I had to get clothes.
I asked the cab driver to stop
so I could buy warmer stuff.
Then I looked around and, suddenly,
that's when I spotted you.
Isn't that great?
At nighttime, it's cold here.
But if you need me
to get you anything, I will.
I didn't do a good job packing.
I need lots of things.
I got here in such a hurry.
With you here, I can relax and not worry.
Hmm.
So glad I found you.
What brings you both out so early?
Oh, we just went shopping for groceries.
At the store?
Even here,
you have to go buy bread, milk, and eggs?
You're as organized as ever, Ho-jin.
You're someone we can count on.
Well then, Mu-hee,
Ho-jin must've made food for you.
He's a good cook, right?
Oh.
Well, I don't know.
I haven't been able to try it.
You can just ask him to cook for you.
He knows his way around a kitchen.
All this talk of food is making me hungry.
How long before we get to the hotel?
Well, it might take another half hour.
Wanna go to a restaurant instead?
Oh, that's fine. I'll eat at the hotel.
It's because you stood under the ladder.
Now you have bad luck.
You look so sad.
The "happy you" won't last.
Just the lonely one.
So you lied about the key
so you could be with the guy you like.
It was in your pocket.
The whole time.
I know you're curious.
Something's up with the wedding, right?
Why are you here? What's going on?
Come on. Tell me. Why is she here?
What's going on with her wedding?
It's her wedding. Tell me!
What… what about your wedding?
What's that?
Um, why did you come to Canada
if your, uh… your wedding
is scheduled for next week?
Ah, yes. Uh…
They needed someone to come quickly,
and I was the only person available.
So I packed my bags, and here I am.
Is Hiro at the same hotel?
Would it be okay if we go there now?
I have to say hello to him.
I should go right away.
My manager knows I'm here.
He's on his way.
You two go ahead
since you have work to do.
Oh. We would have dropped you off first
if you had told us.
I'm sorry. We'll see you later
at the hotel, I guess.
Ho-jin, let's get going.
Hey.
Take your jacket.
I don't need it. You hold on to it.
You're gonna be okay, Ho Jin?
You ran away, and she still followed you.
You didn't know she was planning
on coming here, did you?
I really didn't know.
I'm not gonna wear it. Take it back.
He really didn't know.
I'm aware of that.
He didn't know she was coming,
but he also didn't comfort you.
Which means you're nothing to him.
Has it been a fun experience?
How's the shoot going?
What about your wedding?
You're here even though
you're getting married next week?
Are you guys all set?
What's left to prepare right now?
We have the ceremony, and then that's it.
Jin-suk's fine with that?
He didn't mind at all that… you came here?
You know Jin-suk.
He listens to me
and just keeps going on as always.
Why would he say anything now?
Let's just get it over with.
If we don't do it now, we never will.
Both of us will get cold feet.
So tell me, why do you wanna do this?
Hmm? You said you wanna get married.
Forget it.
Thinking about all this
gives me a headache.
Anyway, we're working together now.
I look forward to this project
with you, Ho-jin.
Hiro's assistant, Nanami,
speaks English very well.
Please ask her if you need help
and if any problems come up, okay?
Mm.
Oh, thanks for the tip.
Yes, I'm at the hotel, Ms. Cho.
There's one more left to find.
It's the zombie.
Oh.
Why are you here?
Everyone's waiting over there.
They wanna see you.
What are you doing here?
Why did you come here?
Meeting. Your meeting.
Over there. You have people waiting.
Waiting. Now waiting.
Meeting?
You came to meet me?
Waiting.
You were waiting for me?
Why?
Ugh, I have no idea what he's saying.
Look.
We're colleagues who only meet for work.
You can't crash my day off like this.
That's too much.
He seems like he's in a rotten mood.
I don't have the bandwidth to handle this.
Go ahead.
The aurora borealis shoot
is tomorrow night.
There's no guarantee though.
You need to be lucky to see it.
So I've been trying to find
a bunch of these.
I want to see the aurora borealis
with the person I like.
But…
the girl he likes has arrived,
and she'll be at the shoot.
I collected a bunch of four-leaf clovers
for good luck.
Now he'll end up
seeing the Northern Lights with her.
So that's why…
I don't want the Northern Lights
to appear anymore.
Even though it's good for our shoot
and the story of our show.
I am still hoping they won't show.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I should head out now.
Thank you for listening.
Thank you. Arigato.
Aurora.
Clover.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I have absolutely no clue.
What could she be so sad about?
Hi, I'm, well, Jeong-su's replacement.
You can call me Ji-sun.
Glad to be working with you.
Shin Ji-sun! Shin Ji-sun! Whoo!
Shin Ji-sun! Whoo! Shin Ji-sun! Yes!
Shin Ji-sun! Whoo! Shin Ji-sun!
Yes. Yes, good!
Also, we have a chance
to see the Northern Lights tomorrow night.
The forecast says the sky will be clear
and our chances to see it are high.
It's never been this good.
So tomorrow, we're all gonna see it.
Go, aurora borealis!
Aurora! Whoo! Aurora! Go!
Aurora! Yeah! Aurora! Whoo!
Aurora! Aurora!
Whoo! Aurora! Aurora! Yay!
Oh, where's Hiro tonight?
He's not here with you?
Oh, he happens to be at the hotel.
He needs to do his evening workout.
Aurora.
Clover.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
It's really bothering me.
Aurora.
Clover.
I'm sorry.
Ho-jin, try this. It's good.
- Joo Ho-jin, have another bite.
- Thank you. It looks good.
Yummy.
By the way,
I heard Producer Shin
is getting married to your brother, right?
It'll make her your sister-in-law?
Ho-jin and I have known each other
for a long time, so it's fine.
Good. You're having a small wedding
on Jeju Island.
That means going to South Korea
before Jeju.
You'll need to travel two days
to get to your wedding.
So who's replacing Ji-sun when she leaves?
In Canada, I'm in charge.
I'll stay here while we're here.
Really?
Our families are
the only ones planning on attending.
It's really a small party,
so we can have it a week later.
I see. You're pushing it back?
Great! Works out well for us!
If the wedding happens
when we're all back in South Korea,
we can attend and celebrate,
especially since
the younger brother's here.
You've postponed your wedding
to fill in last minute?
Ji-sun, your work ethic's remarkable.
How is it that you can like
the same woman for such a long time?
Isn't that incredible?
You asked if I felt like an actor
in a romantic movie,
but this movie is not romantic at all.
It's rather terrifying.
If I had to pick a genre for it,
it'd be horror.
- Horror?
- Yep.
You mean, like The Quiet Woman
with Do-Ra Mi?
Even though I hope it'll die,
it stays alive
and just starts over and over again.
It keeps following me
even when I'm done with it.
I really wanna get it over with.
Like a zombie that you try to kill,
but it comes back to life
to chase after you again.
I always think, "I want this to end,"
but I can't do it.
Yeah, that must be scary.
It must be terrifying.
It keeps haunting me.
I hope I can escape
and be done this time, once and for all.
I've been trapped.
I can't believe this guy!
Your brother's crazy!
When he asked me to officiate,
I had to prepare a whole speech.
How dare he send me a text like that!
Suddenly the ceremony's postponed!
I'm sorry, Mr. Kim.
So, uh, my brother
hasn't called you personally?
Not at all.
Wait, is it nighttime over there?
Oh, I'm bugging you
in the middle of the night! I'm sorry.
Please, go to bed.
I will. You should rest, Mr. Kim.
Okay.
Look at him.
She's just fine, and he's moping.
I hate this.
You're exhausted
'cause you thought this would be over
once the wedding finally happens.
So why is she here?
Did they have a fight?
Have you asked her?
I, um, didn't ask,
but there's a problem, I think.
It'll pass eventually.
Ji-sun is the type of person
who can handle and love my brother
and accept his free spirit.
Ah…
I guess she's… she's a great woman.
You think her getting married
will change how you feel?
She'll be in your family.
You'll see her constantly.
What happens if the truth comes out?
Things have gone too far.
Don't you think clearing the air
before they get married
would be the most healthy
and ethical thing to do?
Mu-hee, are you trying to console
and encourage me again?
I'm gonna be fine,
and this isn't really helping right now.
No, uh, I feel bad for you
because you couldn't escape from her.
Then stop getting in my way
and move aside so I can run away.
What if you ran with someone else instead?
To protect you from her and keep you safe.
Have another person nearby
so you can avoid her
and have someone by your side
because you're scared.
Don't you think I've tried
to be close with someone else?
Please go away.
Unless you wanna be used
and fill in for her as a rebound.
You're so mean.
Just stay in that zombie-like love
until you die.
NA JIN-SUK
- It's so pretty!
- Absolutely!
And to think
this almost wasn't going to happen.
We'll put the monitors over there.
Let's double-check the setups.
Looks like it's gonna snow.
And it's cloudy.
Not sure if we'll see the aurora borealis.
If we won't see it, that's it, then.
I hope there's plenty of snow tonight.
Mu-hee, Nanami is going to translate
for you tonight. Just this once, okay.
Oh, why?
Ho-jin's refusing to work tonight,
or what?
No, Ho-jin got into an accident
on the way here. It's nothing serious.
- What?
- What kind of accident?
Did he get hurt?
No, everyone's fine.
It was a fender bender.
He said it'll take a while to deal with,
but he didn't want us to be delayed.
We'll have to make do
with Nanami's interpretation
for tonight's shoot.
Hmm.
I hope he was okay
if it was just a fender bender.
Mu-hee, don't worry about it.
She said he wasn't hurt.
I'll give him a call to double-check.
I believe it's my fault.
I really hoped everything would be ruined.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have said that.
We're ready to start shooting.
- Okay.
- Ready.
Good, let's start.
Nanami, you just need to make sure
they can communicate. Thanks.
Ay. I mean, yes.
The weather isn't good.
Uh…
He says it looks like it's about to snow.
Oh, um…
Snow.
Ah, it looks like it's going to snow.
Mm.
Okay, let's wrap up tonight's shoot.
Bummer, we didn't see the aurora borealis.
- No Northern Lights?
- It's just not easy to catch it.
Okay, well, if we wait one more hour,
could we see it then?
- It's such a shame, otherwise.
- No, we can't. It's already 1:00 a.m.
Look at the sky.
There's no way we'll see it.
Wrap up. Everyone will catch a cold.
- Disappointing.
- It's already gotten so late.
We'll head back to the hotel.
Let's gather everything.
But we're here and set everything.
It's so sad.
I can stay behind
and shoot the aurora borealis
if it happens later.
It can be used as stock footage.
Are you also disappointed
that we didn't see the lights?
No, glowing.
You said that she glowed
when she was with me.
Of course! Yes!
Sure, I'm very ambitious.
I'm gonna blow up
and become really famous.
She seemed different today.
My interpreting probably fell short.
Your interpreting?
Yes.
I guess I failed
to convey your words accurately.
Ms. Cha Mu-hee
always heard you talk to her
through somebody else.
You're right.
She always heard someone else in her ear.
So it wasn't me?
PAPAGO♥
I heard
you got into an accident. I'm worried.
Are you okay?
Please let me know,
no matter how late it gets.
I'll stay up and wait.
Please let me know when you're back.
Shin Ji-sun,
I have a late-night snack for you. Oh.
She went somewhere?
Oh.
NA JIN-SUK
- No!
- Ji-sun, don't hang up. Listen.
I'm really sorry.
Let's get married
like we said we would. Please.
- It's not over yet.
- Oh.
You heard that?
- Mm.
- Don't you dare tell this to anybody.
If you do, I'll murder you.
I just got back.
Are you still awake?
Do you want to meet me outside?
Joo Ho-jin!
Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I was running late
because the other driver got injured.
Oh, good. I'm so sorry.
For what?
I cursed you 'cause I was angry.
Do Ra-mi appeared,
said mean things about you, we danced.
It's my fault you were in that accident.
I'm really sorry.
It was the other guy's fault.
He bumped into me and drove straight ahead
without looking at the road.
So, don't worry
because your curse did nothing.
Although what's been helpful was
the four-leaf clover.
They're beautiful.
You know, I am seeing the aurora borealis
thanks to you.
Well, I'm humble,
but I do deserve some credit for this.
Although I put the clovers in the garbage.
Which means they didn't bring us any luck.
That's not true.
There is still one left.
You still have it?
You kept it instead of throwing it away?
I saw how much effort
you put into your collection.
How could I throw it away
without your permission?
I guess, um,
we get to see the aurora borealis
'cause I wanted to see it so badly.
I helped
just a little bit.
You looked for a clover?
I was able to spot it
while the accident was sorted out.
I was pretty excited to see it too.
Our dream has come true.
It's nice to see it together.
It's so pretty.
Shall we get back inside?
It's getting late.
Let's stay a bit longer, Ho-jin.
We've been here for a while.
Uh…
Well…
The Northern lights rarely appear.
What if we never get a chance
to see this again?
We should stay here until we pass out.
She had her key card.
Do you mind staying here
just a little longer?
Okay, let's stay.
We won't get another chance, right?
Joo Ho-jin,
I heard this story somewhere.
There was a woman who taught her boyfriend
how to use chopsticks.
He wasn't good at it, so she taught him
how to use them properly.
Then she told him,
"If we ever break up,
you will be reminded of me
whenever you use chopsticks."
It's a true story. That's what he did.
That's brainwashing, what she did to him.
We're seeing the aurora borealis together.
So from now on,
you will think about me
whenever you happen
to see the Northern Lights.
Don't be scared.
The aurora borealis
will never occur in Korea.
Aren't you relieved?
Knowing her,
she'll do it in South Korea too.
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
Oh!
Three leaves.
She makes it look so easy.
Oh! A four-leaf clover!
Hey! Look!
I found one!