=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 15=
Father,
did you keep me away all these years
for that evil spirit?
All my siblings died young.
You knew the reason all along.
Since you knew that,
why keep dealing with the evil spirit?
It's all to satisfy
your own desires.
Father,
how could you keep doing this?
Driven by the evil spirit,
you didn't even care that your kids
were devoured by it.
I am your father.
Who do you think I did this for?
In the Royal Court,
we were always looked down on,
so we were driven here.
If I had not bargained
with that evil spirit,
how could we rise again?
And how could you
ever become
the Young Priest?
Father,
rising again was your wish,
not mine
or my siblings'.
Since you
have betrayed Cangshen,
I should resign in shame
and leave the Royal Court.
How could you say that?
Nonsense?
Resign?
Did your siblings
die for nothing?
Their deaths were not because of me.
They died because of you.
Master Yili'er,
you say Luda rose this far
because you dealt with an evil spirit.
I don't think so.
Perhaps it was the other way around.
Maybe Song Xingyu saw long ago
how insatiable you were
and how you tried to make your son
the High Priest.
So, he used you.
If that is true,
then did I
kill my own kids
with my own hands?
If there's nothing else,
I will go back and rest first.
This late-night spectacle
has truly wearied me.
My kids...
Have you heard?
Last night, at the House of Yili'er,
all their treasures
vanished overnight.
What a pity.
Indeed.
By morning,
the concubines and servants
- Gentlemen.
- had all left.
Now,
only Master Yili'er
and Young Master Luda remain.
The other Young Master
also drowned.
I spoke with Father last night.
He will return with me
to the Capital to atone.
He will never return to Youzhou.
You trust Cangshen that much?
Cangshen
is, in truth, a kind of faith.
You have convictions too.
You should know this.
When one's faith is firm enough,
it can rival
all the weapons in the world.
The power of Cangshen
lies in one faith shared by millions.
Seventeen,
you once believed
in the Aphorisms of Cangshen.
Why now...
In the Aphorisms,
Cangshen's greatest blessing
is to spread the Chong People's line
to every corner of the world.
You marched south and seized
Great Liang's land and its people.
Is this what your faith asks of you?
I know that between the two nations
lies deep hatred.
But I hope
more of the Liang People
will come to worship Cangshen
and become Cangshen's people.
Each should do their own part,
with no more strife.
Seventeen,
have you ever wondered
how I knew you last night?
Young Priest,
we were never friends.
One day, we may be foes.
So,
let's part here.
Take care of yourself.
Greetings, Your Lordship.
You hurried back.
Anything wrong with Her Grace?
Your Lordship,
Song Xingyu was seen in Youzhou.
So, Her Grace went to Youzhou
because of him.
Did Her Grace catch Song Xingyu?
He got away.
Understood.
Your Lordship,
there is also a spirit
by her side.
His identity is unknown.
Are you sure it's not a mortal?
It is a spirit
with strong spirit power.
Naan!
Put me down.
Tell me where Song Xingyu is,
and I'll let you go.
I don't know.
I truly don't know.
I believe you don't know.
But the Sovereign won't.
Fine, I'll talk.
Put me down first.
You...
Greetings, Your Lordship.
Why are you in such a panic?
Your Lordship,
while I was on law enforcement duty,
I ran into Song Xingyu.
I did all I could
to stop Song Xingyu,
but he still got away.
I was anxious
because…
Because I wanted
to report this news
to you at once.
Please believe me.
These...
I got
these things
from Song Xingyu's hideout.
Please accept it.
Please believe me.
Kneel. Hurry.
Kneel, now.
Kneel.
Greet the Right Hand.
Quickly.
Please forgive him.
He is a newly formed spirit.
He's still confused,
unaware of the rules.
He...
(The Right Hand?)
(Is he Simu's subordinate?)
Farewell, Your Lordship.
Every time I see the Right Hand,
it drains away
ten years of joy I've saved up.
How dare you
look at the Right Hand?
Is the Right Hand
really that important?
Of course.
He's only inferior
to Her Grace.
He's the most trustworthy
The most trustworthy.
He's known
Her Grace for centuries.
Those two
rely on and respect
each other;
their hearts beat in unison.
As the saying goes,
their bond runs deep.
In the Void,
all spirits think
they're a pair.
For all these years,
while Her Grace was away,
the Right Hand handled
the Spirit World like a co-ruler.
Even the Left Hand lacked that honor.
The Right Hand truly is a model
for all male spirits.
From the sound of it,
the Right Hand and Her Grace
are quite close.
Does Her Grace like him?
Of course.
The Right Hand is handsome,
highly capable,
and utterly devoted to her.
She fell for him long ago.
Otherwise, why would she trust him
with the Void?
If that's the case,
the Right Hand is trouble.
Yes, yes.
He is hard to handle.
If you go to the Void,
don't anger him.
Or you'll end up
being annihilated.
That is not right.
You threw me off track.
Why are you asking so much?
Come on.
I don't know where Song Xingyu is.
But
you need to follow me
back to the Void.
What?
(Fragrance)
(Wine)
Why did you leave alone?
You didn't even wait for me.
Don't overdrink today.
Last time…
Once my spirit power is back,
I will make you suffer for it.
I've suffered enough
in the Mortal World.
It seems
you'll have me sample
the Void's suffering.
If you insist on punishing me,
let me use this
to make amends.
You had no five senses
on the city wall.
Things are different now.
Though you can't taste it,
you can smell its fragrance.
Not enough to spare your punishment.
Then you should think
about how to punish me.
It does seem too sweet.
I have a sweet tooth too.
Simu,
do you want a taste of sweetness?
Why not trade our five senses now?
The joys of this world fade too fast.
Better not be greedy.
To hold one at this moment is enough.
You can
keep me by your side.
You can exchange them
whenever you want.
Or,
come back to Nandu with me.
The food, wine, and views there
will surely please you.
We'll see.
Great Ancestor,
I've searched all of Youzhou.
No trace of Song Xingyu.
He truly fled.
Then how can we find him now?
Handle your own duty yourself.
He has the Glazed Pagoda.
It hides the evil spirit's aura.
Do spirits
have nothing
that can restrain him?
If spirits had a way,
he wouldn't have been able
to hide for 300 years.
Starhaven's magical artifacts
are most formidable.
Yet you can't counter the Pagoda.
Great Ancestor,
why not come to Nandu?
We can work out
how to catch Song Xingyu.
It has been so long since I saw you.
You finally have official leave.
Come to Nandu, okay?
Your spell bearer, Duan Xu,
is also returning to Nandu.
A mortal life is brief.
Perhaps,
by your next official leave,
he…
He may already be gone.
You should come to Nandu
and truly enjoy yourself
by changing your five senses.
That sounds like a fair idea.
I will think it over.
I...
(East Sea, Fusang Tree)
What is going on?
Why did the Fusang Tree wither?
Wars in the Mortal World rage on.
The Fusang Tree bore it long.
Perhaps the strain finally took hold.
You're responsible
for its yearly upkeep.
How did things worsen so suddenly?
Question me
after pointing out
where I was at fault.
If a spirit was meddling within,
you oversee the access
of the Spirit Officials.
Maybe you're responsible for this.
Oh, no.
The Fusang Tree has split.
We're not powerful enough to repair it.
We must ask Her Grace to come.
Her Grace must have sensed it.
I'll go to receive her.
Rare for you to ask me out.
On my way here,
I saw these rare wildflowers.
Smell them.
Once the exchange of senses is over,
I will return to the Void.
Your Grace,
you truly don't mean
to return to Nandu with me?
Nandu is merely
a city of mortals.
During my next official leave,
I can go and see it.
♪Joys and sorrows of the mortal world♪
♪Swept along by the daylight♪
Next time you come,
I may no longer be here.
♪Lingering for a fleeting moment♪
♪Was once touched by laughing tears♪
Then do your best
to stay alive.
♪I'd be a guest in a sweet dream♪
♪Dawn and dusk rise and set♪
♪Longing to meet, yet parted by destiny♪
♪Let me wander through♪
♪Light and dark, without turning back♪
♪Wander to the other shore
with the lantern♪
♪Accompanied by eternity♪
♪As all things turn and flow♪
♪Whether I stay or go, I'm all alone♪
♪Dawn and dusk rise and set♪
♪Longing to meet, yet parted by destiny♪
♪Let me wander through♪
♪Light and dark, without turning back♪
The time has come.
♪Wander to the other shore
with the lantern♪
I didn't expect ten days
to pass by so quickly.
♪Whether I stay or go, I'm all alone♪
♪As stars shift and change places♪
♪A century is like a dream♪
♪Let me journey across them all♪
♪Without reincarnations♪
Your eyes
can still see spirits.
Consider it a gift
for letting me know
what scent is
and what touch feels like.
This is where we part.
Remember to stay alive.
Your Grace.
Simu.
The game is over.
Go back.
Return to your Nandu.
What about you?
You're rushing back.
Why?
None of your concern.
If you take me with you,
it'll concern me.
Why should I?
You'll leave for years.
Next time you come,
I may have died.
Wouldn't that waste
our spell bond?
I was reckless before.
I offended you more than once.
Will you truly let me off so easily?
Don't you want to settle
the score with me
and make me pay?
In this bargain,
you still owe me one wish.
This time, my wish
is to return to the Void with you.
Do you know the price
to enter the Void
as a mortal?
A true gambler
does not gamble
before knowing the result.
Entering the Void
is more dreadful
than death to mortals.
So what?
So, this is the famed
Fusang Tree of the Cyan Sea.
Mortals can never reach
the Cyan Sea's depths.
If you rush in carelessly,
you will lose your life.
The Fusang Tree
has withered more.
For now, I can only restore its surface.
To fully heal it,
it will take more time.
If you want to enter the Void,
jump down from here.
Think it through first.
The upward force
of the countless Spirit Auras below
is enough to tear apart
your mortal flesh.
You can regret it now.
This kind of makeshift shortcut
can let a mortal pass through,
but it's extremely dangerous.
Young man,
I advise you not to try it.
Just go back to the Mortal World.
It does look frightening,
but I've come this far.
I have no reason to turn back.
To read the moment
and adapt is
the right thing to do
for a mortal.
You're right.
But you refused to go to Nandu.
So, I have to come to the Void.
♪Touched memories linger like shadows♪
♪Scattered reflections
sink into my heart♪
♪If I could softly call you like this♪
♪As gentle as a fleeting embrace♪
♪Though apart, my thoughts still swirl♪
♪A lifetime is given
for a name to be remembered♪
♪There are passions and pains♪
♪Hope we'll experience them together♪
♪Before we forget or grow apart♪
♪Even if the day gives way to night♪
♪Grows dim and fades away♪
♪What would come of it?♪
♪I care for no one but you♪
♪I'll come near and run to you♪
Your Grace, if you can't help him,
I can go and save him.
♪Miracles, eternity, and radiance♪
♪Worth more than any barren land♪
♪I might as well
spend the rest of my life♪
♪Walking with you through eternity♪
That mortal can actually descend?
I wonder if it's because
of the weakened Fusang Tree
or his sword.
He actually passed.
Your Grace, let us enter the Void.
(Sovereign's Hall)
♪Spirits are intoxicated♪
♪With obsessions♪
Your Grace, welcome back.
♪Today, a home is granted♪
♪Joy without grief♪
♪Lanterns light the empty delusions♪
♪All are ferried across♪
♪Spirits are intoxicated♪
♪With obsessions♪
♪Forget the form to achieve♪
♪Yet I can't♪
♪Today, a home is granted♪
(Sovereign's Hall)
♪Joy without grief♪
♪Lanterns light the empty delusions♪
♪All are ferried across♪
(It's him.)
Seize this mortal and drag him away.
Hang him for three days.
Yes, Your Grace.
You've come for me at last.
Up.
What is that mortal
hanging there to Her Grace?
He must've enraged her
by committing the gravest sin.
He looks so tender.
I wonder whom
Her Grace will grant him to.
Tender and delicious.
I really want a bite.
Higher. A little higher.
The Sovereign's Hall of the Void.
Your Grace,
the Fusang Tree has split,
and many evil spirits fled at once.
(Lei Qi,)
Lords have sent
(Lord of Zhuangling Temple)
Spirit Officials to arrest them,
but there are too many.
Your Grace, please send more,
lest evil spirits
plague the Mortal World.
Indeed.
Every temple is deeply unsettled,
for fear that chaos may break out.
What trouble could there be?
Since the evil spirits reached
the Mortal World,
let Starhaven Sect deal with them.
They've had it easy for centuries;
it's time they toughened up a bit.
Send more?
That would waste many spirit stones.
Matters of our Spirit World
should not be left to outsiders.
I've ordered Lords to sort out
the list of escaped evil spirits.
The Spirit Officials we sent out
have brought back over 60%.
Given some time,
we can surely bring them all back.
But right now, in the Void,
there are too many spirits.
If they are not settled properly,
there could be
chaos from evil spirits clashing.
If only we could make them
vanish in a proper manner.
We have the Ascension Pool,
right?
It's lain unused
(Dong Yong,)
because spirits
(Lord of Yuling Temple)
are bound by obsessions
too deep to ascend.
- Indeed.
- Exactly.
Your Grace,
to the northwest lies North Abyss.
The land there is vast,
with hidden spirit stones.
If we can open that region,
it would house
the spirits
and also expand the Void's domain.
We risked our lives
to build the Void.
The 24 Temples
spent a thousand years
regaining their strength.
Peace has only just returned,
and now, we must risk all again?
North Abyss often has seabed storms.
For ordinary spirits to go near it
is nearly certain death.
Rather than waste wealth
and spirit power,
I believe
we should expand the dwellings nearby
to ease the urgent need.
Indeed.
That is a fine plan.
Starting today,
all spirits entering the Void
shall be registered by the Right Hand.
The other Lords
shall help expand the dwellings
to house them.
As for opening the North Abyss,
the Left and Right Hands
shall draft the rules for me first.
In the 24 Temples,
if any can persuade spirits to ascend,
for each spirit that ascends,
the reward is 30,000 spirit stones.
How much? 30,000?
30,000 spirit stones.
- That many?
- 30,000.
No upper limit.
Your Grace,
Fang Chang colluded with Song Xingyu.
Though Fang Chang is now in custody,
Song Xingyu is still at large.
Your Grace, please,
(Yan Zhang,)
deal with this first.
(Vice Lord of Xuling Temple)
Song Xingyu's crimes merit no pardon.
I have sent men to hunt him down.
Fang Chang has been seized by me.
Your Grace, I await your judgment.
The Right Hand did well
in capturing Fang Chang.
Fang Chang deserves to be annihilated
before the Golden-wall Decrees
in three days.
Guan Huai failed in oversight.
Shave his head.
Imprison him for ten years.
During that time,
the Left Hand is
in charge of the Shanling Temple.
Your Grace, you must not.
Your Grace, you must not!
A spirit's hair,
once cut, will never grow back.
If you cut my hair,
you're taking my life.
Then cut only half.
Not even half will do.
Your Grace, you must not.
Your Grace.
Your Grace, you must not!
Your Grace!
Fang Chang kept saying
he would avenge Shao Yinyin,
but in truth, for his career,
he killed her with his own hands.
A heartless man like that
toyed with a woman's feelings.
That is sheer hypocrisy.
Why not
send him to my hall
before his execution?
The ladies in my hall
are fond of tending
to such heartless men.
In these three days,
I will make sure
he begs for death.
Yan Zhang, Vice Lord of Xuling Temple,
has served me well in this plan.
Reward her 10,000 spirit stones.
Thank you, Your Grace.
Farewell, Your Grace.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪