(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Perfect, Hiro.
Let's get out once the actress
ahead of us is past the main photo line.
Who is that?
You don't know her?
That's Do Ra-mi.
The one who's blowing up globally.
Do Ra-mi.
No, I don't know her.
You really don't?
You haven't seen the Do Ra-mi movie?
He has.
It was in your Netflix viewing history,
both this month and last.
Right, that killer zombie?
What was the actress's name again?
Cha Mu-hee.
Her name was in your search history,
yet you don't remember?
Why do you even have my tablet?
You said to always stand by
with it in hand.
Don't snoop without permission.
- Mirror.
- Here.
Okay.
What's up with her?
Why's she standing there like a zombie?
You're right, she is.
She's been standing there long enough.
What is she doing?
She should go so you can have your moment.
Something seems off with her.
She doesn't look well.
If she faints, this red-carpet event
will come to a screeching halt.
But I waited three months.
I waited three months
for this custom-made suit from Italy.
I can't let that happen.
- Hiro!
No way. Is he going to walk past her?
He wouldn't do something so insane,
even if he wants to show off
that custom-made suit.
Hiro is attending
the Tokyo International Film Festival
for the second year in a row.
This year, his performance as Hideo
in Can I Love You? earned him acclaim.
Wake up.
I'll help you.
Let's walk together.
These two are a no-go.
They just confirmed
that they can't make the dates work.
And last time we spoke,
these three were interested.
But they're asking for more time
before making a decision.
As for these girls,
they're really excited,
but I don't think
that Hiro will like either of the two.
Casting this show has been a pain.
But who can we find for the female lead
by the end of the week?
Cha Mu-hee would be great!
Cha Mu-hee?
Do Ra-mi?
Do Ra-mi is a zombie.
Oh, please. The genre's completely wrong.
A zombie on a show called Romantic Trip?
I have a feeling
they'd be a good match though.
Mostly because of this footage I saw.
The clip is going mad viral right now.
Hasn't the Do Ra-mi trend
died down though?
Even that one drama she was gonna be in,
it, uh, fell through, right?
This could actually work.
Oh my God!
Do Ra-mi? Do Ra-mi. Who reps her?
- Get her schedule right away!
- Okay. Got it.
Here's Japan's number one prince charming.
And here's South Korea's
number one scream queen.
Nice to meet you.
Hey there.
But their branding is different,
don't you think?
It is, which is why
they have to learn to communicate.
That's basically
the theme and the concept, right?
Two strangers, meeting for the first time,
falling in love despite it all.
Overcoming different languages.
Black and pink will be a great match.
Blackpink?
Our show needs to be a hit
like the girl band!
Blackpink!
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
Great, thank you.
You need to meet
with a specialist when it gets this late
if you wanna buy any sleeping pills.
Fortunately, for you, I just so happen
to know one who works late.
So talk to him first.
Why can't I pick up some pills
and just go?
I'm in a rush, and there's a party
I need to be at later tonight.
Then tell the doctor.
Also, how did you figure out
I was at that hotel? Tell me, Mu-hee.
Because I've got a room there too.
My manager, Yong-u,
he said he spotted you before,
back in the lobby.
Ah.
Do you happen to have any other problems?
Why? You don't believe me?
I feel dizzy, shaky,
nauseous, and feverish too.
Like I wanna collapse all the time.
Give me your forehead to check.
No.
Cha Mu-hee, don't play around.
You'll be forced
to go to a hospital immediately
if I translate all of these symptoms.
- So no games, okay?
- Hey! You think I'm pretending?
I had those symptoms earlier.
I'd never dream of asking for your help
'cause you turned me down.
Ho-jin, sorry to keep you waiting.
Not at all.
Come in. This way.
Let's go in. Here.
Tell him I'm just here
to, um, get a prescription.
And mention
that my heartbeat was too fast.
Anxiety pills would be great.
He's asking you
to try and describe the anxiety.
As well as any symptoms.
Does he need to know?
Yeah, he kinda does.
All I need is to buy medicine
without providing all these details.
Then buy whatever you need from the store.
You can't buy anxiety drugs
without a prescription.
Exactly.
You came here 'cause you're in pain,
so let the doctor know
because he can help with your symptoms.
He's a doctor,
so I hope he won't tell anyone, right?
But you're translating,
so you'll hear everything
and know exactly what's wrong.
Well, you need to talk so I can translate.
If that's a problem, then just fly home.
I'll look for a flight back to Seoul.
No way! I have an event tonight!
These actors and a big director
wanna meet up,
so I can't just leave and blow them off.
What about the doctor?
Ah…
Well, basically…
what I'm anxious about is…
that I've had visions of
Do Ra-mi lately.
She just shows up randomly.
She laughs.
Like she wants to taunt me.
At first, I thought it was just fatigue
making me see things.
But I was wrong.
Because I kept seeing her
even after I got some rest.
So Director Peter Jason is gonna make
an appearance at the after-party.
You think that's true?
Oh, and apparently there's gonna be
a bunch of famous actors.
Would it be rude to ask for pictures?
I just wanna ignore it
because it's only a hallucination.
But I see her so clearly, so I can't.
I'm always on edge,
worried about where she'll appear next.
And today,
I think I just fell apart.
Am I crazy?
What would you like?
Whatever. You choose.
When I was just a kid,
I was in this really bad accident.
But it's a giant blank.
I don't remember anything about it,
even how my parents died.
Is there any history
of mental illness in your family?
I was raised in my uncle's house.
There was no one with mental issues
as far as I can recall.
Not on Mom's side.
The accident was probably her fault.
'Cause nobody ever mentions
her in my family.
Any more questions?
As you can see,
Mu-hee is not in good shape.
Once she graduated from high school,
she informed us via letter
that she was cutting ties
with our side of the family.
So don't contact us,
no matter what happens to her.
Excuse me?
That's pretty cold.
The medicine's only a temporary solution.
So when you go back home,
try to get proper care.
I know what to do, all right?
This isn't a lecture. I'm interpreting
what the doctor said earlier.
He said your condition
could be stress-induced,
like you presumed it was.
But it…
it could just as likely be brain damage.
That's something you've
already translated, so please stop.
Your manager will arrive soon.
He said he'd come by and pick you up.
You talked to Yong-u?
He called to say he was looking for you,
so I told him earlier you were here.
And the hospital stuff?
I said you gave me a call,
and you needed help
because of a bad stomachache,
so I ended up taking you to the hospital.
Oh.
A stomachache, huh?
It's funny.
I never said anything,
but Yong-u figured out
that I asked you out and got rejected.
Then how stupid is it
that a painful stomachache
was all it took in the end
for me to come see you?
He must think I'm desperate or something.
Is the new medicine making me giggle?
Maybe I really did lose my mind.
Thanks for your help, Joo Ho-jin.
But I just can't repay a favor like this.
'Cause I know we'll never meet again.
You were only an interpreter, but…
but you know too much about my life now.
So sometimes
I don't know how my face looks
or how to react when I see you.
Today, you ended up making me laugh.
I'll probably cry
next time I see you though.
Yong-u should be here soon.
I really appreciate your help,
and I apologize.
The doctor said to try and take it easy,
but I guess
you're going to the event, right?
Yeah, of course. This is my festival.
Yeah. I'm so in love with my new life.
And I never wanna stop loving my life.
Okay, you can enjoy the night,
but no drinking, all right?
Don't mix it with the medicine.
The doctor recommended that too?
It's not a translation.
It's me, worrying about you, Mu-hee.
Nice to meet you. You look so amazing.
Thank you.
I'm a big fan. Can we take a picture?
Okay.
It might just be the medicine.
I'm tired.
It's the zombie.
Hello there.
So we meet again.
Ah, Japanese.
He's cute.
An actor?
Hmm. What's she saying?
Wow.
What is he staring at?
Does he wanna talk to me or what?
What's with this woman?
Aren't you going to thank me at all?
A simple thank-you can't be that hard.
Hmm?
Photo? I'm okay.
- Selfie? Camera?
- "Camera"?
Take a Picture? Picture?
- "Camera."
- Ah… right.
Okay. One, two, smile!
Uh, a heart?
Okay, one, two, three, hearts!
Thank you very much.
Thank you. Have a nice day.
Does she think
she did me a favor by taking a selfie?
Huh?
That zombie doesn't realize who I am.
He seems kinda familiar.
Or maybe he was in a movie I saw?
I took a look
at the request you sent over.
My experience with TV is a little limited,
so I don't know if I can help.
Oh, no, no. Don't worry about that.
- Don't worry. It doesn't matter at all.
- Ah.
We're gonna see Europe.
Parts of North America as well.
And when we heard
that there was a man like you
who knew all of those languages,
I thought, "Oh, my! That's it!"
- "You are the chosen one, Mr. Joo."
- Exactly.
So please, you've gotta help us out,
just this once.
Well, how long
is the shoot expected to be?
It'll be a slightly longer trip.
Three to four months, probably.
It's not as long as you think.
Uh, that sounds like quite a long time.
We are moving between countries,
but you can be sure we'll come back
to Seoul too. Isn't that right, Ms. Cho?
Yeah, sure.
The show is called Romantic Trip.
It's like a fairy tale.
So I want you to picture
these truly magical,
scenic, gorgeous places we'll be visiting.
It won't be exhausting
or anything like that. Right, Mr. Kim?
Yep.
Also, did you happen to watch
our previous season?
Oh, you'll love it!
Well, Shin Ji-sun,
our producer, recommended you.
We worked on that first season together.
This is because
Shin Ji-sun mentioned my name to you?
Yeah.
On that note,
Producer Shin said she'd come by.
She wanted to see you, Mr. Joo Ho-jin.
Oh, hey.
Where's Ho-jin?
He's, uh… Well, had somewhere else to go.
Is that so?
I was hoping we'd grab lunch together.
Me too.
Maybe I could have persuaded him
over lunch, but he didn't fall for it.
Shin Ji-sun, I heard that
you're dating his brother, right?
Tell him to put in a good word for us.
We're getting really desperate.
His brother doesn't pay attention either.
I'll try my best.
Hey, isn't that the writer, Na Jin-suk?
- He came to our store for a signing event.
- Yeah, that does look like him.
Still dresses as flashy as ever.
Oh, hey. I was going to…
So you're not taking the job?
I don't really see the need to.
Mostly because I have other opportunities.
Yeah, you better pass.
I heard a gig would take you
out of the country for way too long.
If you take it, you'll miss the wedding.
What wedding?
Matrimony? Next month.
Finally doing it.
Just gotta tell Ji-sun first.
So you haven't even gotten around
to telling the bride
about the wedding next month?
Ji-sun has wanted to get hitched
for a while, but I kept getting cold feet.
We've been arguing
and bickering constantly,
and I'm just done fighting over it.
So I made up my mind, and it's happening.
Aren't you proud?
How on earth could I be proud
when she doesn't even know
what you're doing?
Please be proud, Ho-jin.
Hmm? You're the only sane person
in our family after all.
I mean it.
You're the only one I'm not embarrassed
to introduce Ji-sun to.
Please, Ho-jin. Do your big bro a solid.
You are embarrassing, Jin-suk.
I mean, which thrift store
did you get that from?
My scarf?
Doesn't it look nice?
Not at all.
It clashes with the rest of your clothes.
Really? It does?
- It'll match yours, maybe.
- Not interested.
And by the way, the little robot vacuum
you took from me? Give it back.
No, no, no, not him!
We already bonded,
and I even named him "Alberto the Third."
What are you talking about?
And all I have to do is tell him "sock,"
and he zooms off to bring the sock!
Are you okay? You need a cab?
I'm good, I'm good.
She's gonna pick me up.
Oh, she's here already.
Now, now. You, sh! Hey!
You're such a pain. Take a cab next time.
- Ho-jin, good to see you.
- Thanks for coming.
A gift?
Rose for my rose.
Um, thanks. You're the only one
who got drunk again?
You always seem to have a fun time,
but nobody else is.
Well, today's 'cause you begged me
to try and convince my little bro here.
Oh, really?
Well, did it pay off?
They probably were hoping
you'd agree to join by now.
Nah. He doesn't want to.
Doesn't wanna play.
Hey, here.
Ah!
- Peace out.
- Come on!
Hey, take it back! Hey!
It looks great on you, little bro!
Rock it!
- It looks…
- Give it.
It's my scarf.
It was a birthday present from him,
but he wears it more than I do.
I'm sorry. Your present's nice.
I didn't take it personally.
He's the one who's inconsiderate.
I think he forgot
he gave it to me in the first place.
You should get angry
when he's acting like that.
Don't just dismiss it.
'Cause Jin-suk,
he has to be told
that things aren't all right.
Everything's great
as long as he's happy, and then…
Good point.
I can't just keep
indulging his character like this.
Should I punch him?
I could… whip him
or smack him just like this.
Do it. You have my blessing.
Okay.
Na Jin-suk's dead.
Getting whipped with that
won't hurt though.
I shouldn't actually smack him like that.
Hurting him isn't the point.
I just wanna try to scare him
into treating me better.
The team told me you turned down the show.
Sure you don't wanna be part of it?
They probably need you
since they begin shooting next month.
Matrimony? Next month. Finally doing it.
Please reconsider it.
I'm begging you. It'd be so great.
All right. I'll join the project.
Really?
Now I got a reason to say yes.
So count me in. I'll do it.
Mr. Joo Ho-jin!
- Good night, little brother of mine.
- See you later! Careful!
Good night!
Ah.
I'm excited to be working with you.
Welcome aboard, sir.
Thanks a lot. It's my pleasure.
We were worried, and we thought
we might have to find another solution
because you didn't wanna be
gone that long.
The production schedule said
the following month
would be in Canada, right?
Yes.
Well, you mentioned
you need to get back to Seoul.
- Does that worry you?
- Oh, no.
I'd prefer being overseas
working and staying busy.
I'm thrilled to be working with you!
The chosen one!
Oh, I believe she's here.
That's great. Perfect timing.
Our lead has just arrived
for her audition.
Since you might translate for her,
swing by and say hello, okay?
So are you still looking
for the female lead?
Because I saw a couple people
on that form you sent over.
Oh, it's someone else. She's brand-new.
We found her yesterday. Last minute.
She's, uh…
She's in this movie The Quiet Woman.
- No one remembers the name, Jeong-su.
- Really?
Do Ra-mi. You know Do Ra-mi, right?
Do Ra-mi… You mean…
Ms. Cha Mu-hee is here!
- Hello there.
- Thanks for coming.
Welcome.
This is Mr. Joo Ho-jin, the interpreter
who'll be handling our translation needs.
But, Mr. Joo, you know Cha Mu-hee, right?
Uh, yes.
Mr. Joo.
You know each other?
Yes, we do.
He interpreted her interview
for a foreign magazine.
Really? Well, that's great!
You'll be traveling together
for a long time,
so it'll be a lot easier
if you already know each other.
Wonderful!
I couldn't imagine I would end up running
into you again, Ho-jin.
It is just as surprising to me
as it is to you.
Nice to see you, Cha Mu-hee.
I didn't think you'd want to work
on a TV show again.
Yet here you are.
Are you doing better?
Did you start seeing a therapist?
Please.
This isn't the right place for that.
We can catch up
on this subject later, all right?
Ms. Cha Mu-hee,
we're about to start shooting.
Okay.
The writer will be asking questions.
Maybe about five or six at most.
Got it.
Okay, let's get ready!
Mu-hee, just talk at your natural pace,
and be comfortable.
It's like talking to a friend.
Look into the camera.
I'll ask a few questions from back here.
Okay.
I'm ready to start.
Cha Mu-hee, do you like to travel?
Oh, yeah. You bet.
I haven't had a lot of opportunities yet.
Still, I like visiting new places.
Quiet on set!
Sorry about that, Mu-hee.
Let's start from the top.
Do you like to travel?
Uh…
Tra… Travel?
Travel? Travel.
Oh, yeah. Uh…
I have been looking for opportunities to…
Mu-hee.
Mu-hee!
Uh, my apologies.
Please look into the camera.
And relax. Lighten up a bit.
Yeah, I'm sorry. Sorry, I'm fine.
Let me start again.
Uh…
My bad. My bad. Once again, please?
I haven't had many opportunities
to travel, but…
Uh…
Let me do one more.
I'm sorry.
Let's take a break.
She's terrible.
She's not funny at all.
She can't talk and can't focus.
Do Ra-mi is a lot more interesting
'cause the actress
isn't charming at all whatsoever.
I guess she wasn't that bad
in Junprecedented, right?
That's just because
the host did really good.
Let's end the shoot.
Let's explore other options.
Cha Mu-hee's not gonna work.
You believed in her though.
Blackpink levels of popularity.
Well, I was wrong, okay?
How do I send her out now?
She probably believed this was in the bag.
I messed it all up, didn't I?
She hates me. I can tell she does.
Nah, this is nothing more
than first-time nerves.
You'll do great once you get used to it.
By the way, Mu-hee,
did you really not know
he was working this show?
You saw how shocked I was earlier.
I'm not that good of an actress.
Why was Joo Ho-jin even on set anyway?
I asked the assistant director
about that earlier,
and it seems it's a favor to Shin Ji-sun.
Shin Ji-sun the producer?
Yeah, that lady we found
in the comments of his Instagram posts.
I know.
So he's here because of her.
She was the coproducer
of the previous season.
I heard he really didn't want to do it,
but he said yes after they talked it over.
Guess he still likes her that much.
I get it already, so just stop saying it.
Come on.
Should be safe here.
- What did you wanna know?
- Did you get a follow-up?
I can take care of myself.
You already told me
you weren't taking any TV gigs.
Guess that wasn't true.
Did your doctor say
it's okay to take on the show?
You'll be out of the country for a while.
You sure that's not an issue?
Of course not.
It's not an issue if I'm okay with it.
But what about you? Do you think
you can handle us working together?
You're not facing your issue.
Admit it. Did you see a doctor?
I feel like I make you uncomfortable,
don't I?
I get why.
So, well, can't you just
quit the project altogether?
I feel uncomfortable when I'm with you.
I shouldn't have translated
your therapy session.
I heard things about you
I didn't want to know.
I feel bad, and I'm worried,
so if you want,
I'm going to quit this show.
But I did…
I saw a doctor.
So, is something wrong with me?
Did my brain get damaged in the accident?
Upon checking your MRI,
it seems there's nothing wrong
with your brain.
However, you're still clearly suffering
from hallucinations.
Something is happening inside your mind
that cannot be diagnosed
by modern medicine.
Then what am I supposed to do, Doctor?
Memory issues would be alarming,
or paralysis,
but these are just visions, right?
You should see a psychiatrist
on a regular basis.
I did, but they said to see a neurologist
because it was caused by the accident.
And I don't have any problems
other than the Do Ra-mi visions.
Can we please just find
a way to get rid of her?
Well, given that we don't know why
those particular visions are presenting,
there's nothing we can do for now.
He said that Do Ra-mi can't be removed
with medicine.
I even tried going to a shaman healer
because I was so frustrated.
But since it's not a ghost,
she couldn't help me either.
Are you happy?
Are you still feeling uncomfortable?
Now please quit this project.
We're done here.
But me quitting
won't solve any of your issues.
You seemed to be struggling on set.
It's almost like you're totally different
all of a sudden.
You're not the Cha Mu-hee I know.
Well, I've changed ever since
Do Ra-mi has taken over in here.
But this isn't going to work.
Then what?
Are you gonna tell the crew on me?
Tell them she's crazy,
and she's haunted by Do Ra-mi.
I'll be kicked off of the shoot
in an instant.
I don't have to do anything.
That's what's gonna happen anyway.
Happy trips and exciting romance
is the very essence of the whole show.
People won't watch it or feel good
with that sad look in your eyes.
I feel uneasy
when you are looking at me this way.
You finally admit you're crazy,
but… you don't seem like
you wanna improve your situation.
I guess there's no point
in talking you out of this.
Goodbye, Cha Mu-hee.
I'm gonna quit the project.
I owe you my thanks, Mr. Joo Ho-jin.
But are you sure about that?
If you pull out, you'll ultimately
let down the person you love.
This job's the only way to show off
to your beloved Shin Ji-sun.
You really hope
she won't find out how you feel?
I assume you changed your mind?
I mean, you must've already agreed to it,
which would put you in a tough spot.
You're right.
This is a real issue.
I'm gonna have to confront it now.
She's getting hitched soon.
And that's it.
I didn't wanna see her get married to him
or plan the wedding.
I tried to find the best way out of this,
but that plan was ruined
when I met a psycho.
Fuck.
Mr. Joo!
Hey, sorry. Do you know Ms. Cho?
She's the head writer.
I think they're gonna
kick Mu-hee off the show.
They stopped filming, and they're even
refusing to give us the contract
'cause they didn't like her interview.
Doesn't look good.
So could you put in a good word?
I was about to tell them I'm done.
That's great!
Threaten to drop the project
if they get rid of Mu-hee.
It really seems like they like you.
That's not why I'm leaving.
So don't bother.
But… but…
- Um--
- Mr. Joo!
Why don't we all have lunch together?
Let's talk about the show.
There's something
I have to inform you about.
If you'd like,
we can grab a quick Japanese lunch.
Do you drink?
The company is gonna pay for it, huh?
Let's head out. Let's go.
If Mu-hee's off the project,
so are you. Go team!
- I don't wanna get myself involved.
- Come on already!
Hey.
You getting in?
Now you're talking to me?
Fine. I'm ready for this.
You're finally talking to me.
Such a shame.
You made a total fool of yourself
in front of him.
- Bitch, you crazy.
- Shut up! Oh, shut up!
I said shut up! Enough! Enough!
Oh, fucking hell.
Oh.
I scared ya, huh?
This thing happened.
Almost made me lose it.
And you know, for a sec, I did.
Ms. Cho.
You look kind of shocked right now.
Sorry I scared you.
Mm…
You despise me, right?
During the shoot, I noticed
you were all giving me very bizarre looks.
And you!
You were asking yourself,
"Should we get rid of her?"
Do it. Do what you gotta do!
I might be bitter about it, but, you know,
I'm not actually Do Ra-mi, right?
Mu-hee.
Yong-u.
Let's go.
Ho-jin.
Can you help me out here?
- Ah, sure.
- I need an extra hand.
Can you reach for a book
on the top shelf over there?
It's on the right.
Top shelf. It's a beige cover.
That's it.
Huh?
Uh, what's this?
It's your family photo.
You all may be living
in different countries now,
but back then,
you all seemed to get along.
I was only a kid back then.
- The tall one is Na Jin-suk?
- Yeah.
What's he doing in your family picture?
He's still my father's son.
My goodness.
I don't get how your mom raised
a kid that's not hers.
And your dad,
smiling so innocently like that.
Or Na Jin-suk,
who joined this family photo.
Your family's really strange.
What's even more strange…
This photo?
It's Jin-suk's mother
who actually took it.
What?
Uh, oh, for the love of God.
This is way too much.
Sounds like an American soap opera.
Amazing.
So does that mean you'll be getting
together for Jin-suk's wedding?
He just asked me to officiate it.
It's happening next month.
But I said no.
But you'd be a good fit.
No.
I decided a while ago
that yours will be
the first I'll officiate.
So, uh… any progress with that actress?
I told you. There's nothing going on.
You can't fool this old man here, Ho-jin.
You just keep trying too hard
to be distant.
Make sure you're more gentle with her.
Wait.
Do I come off mean?
To be honest, you usually
come across as mean and blunt.
You sound like "Mr. Always Right."
Since you know it all,
do you know how many different languages
there are in this world?
I believe over 7,100.
Nope. Wrong answer.
It's the same number
as people on this planet.
Everybody speaks their
own personal language.
And that's why misinterpretations happen,
and we end up offending one another.
Listen, I know you very well, Ho-jin.
You always sound so clever and eloquent.
But you're too harsh.
People won't watch it or feel happy
with that desperate look in your eyes.
I feel uneasy
when you are looking at me this way.
My words are harsh, huh?
They must be painful to hear.
You've been summoned.
A customer at the restaurant
asked for you.
Could you come over?
Please sit.
It would be a little stalker-y
to go to your house.
I asked to meet here instead.
You saw me freaking out.
Did that surprise you?
The crew hasn't reached out to me since.
That's that. I lost that gig.
Sorry. I'm sorry for what I said.
Don't worry.
I totally crossed the line that day.
I'm really sorry.
It wasn't fair of me
to bring up Shin Ji-sun.
I wanted to address your weaknesses
because I…
I felt like you knew
all about my darkest secrets.
Are you still seeing her? Your demon?
Do Ra-mi?
After I flipped out like that,
she just vanished.
She's gone now.
Looks like, sometimes,
it's better to let it all out
than to get sedated with pills.
Still, it's probably not helpful
for mental health.
I should be careful.
And what about your situation?
They decided on the wedding date.
I just don't wanna be dragged
into any wedding events
or get involved in all the family drama.
It might be a good idea to be a part
of that show if you still can.
I hear they're still looking.
And they're getting real desperate now.
I know.
They're still reaching out
to see if I wanna join.
Is that so?
Good for you.
They dropped me.
You managed to freak everybody out.
Are you surprised?
I'm not.
That was such a good gig.
It would've improved my brand.
Do Ra-mi changed my career so much.
I got lots of offers,
but they all wanted me to play
a serial killer, a psychopath, and so on…
If I played all those parts,
my body count would be in the thousands.
Mu-hee the serial killer.
That was precisely my reason to do it.
Because the whole point of the show is
happy trips, exciting dates.
Hmm.
Oh, and we get to see
the aurora borealis during the trip.
It was always a pipe dream, I guess.
Yeah, it's been one of my dreams too.
It's not an easy sight to see though.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Getting there is kinda difficult.
Oh, that's so disappointing.
- Sorry, I'll be back.
- Sure.
Yes, Yong-u?
The aurora…
What?
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, I'll call you back.
Okay.
Yong-u called you?
You should probably go.
Um, I… I just booked the gig
we were talking about.
Romantic Trip called Yong-u just in.
It confirmed that I am cast
and sent over a contract.
That's…
That's really good.
You wanted that.
But
booking it and actually going
kinda frightens me though.
I hope you'll have an… interesting
and exciting trip, Mu-hee.
It'll be hard.
I'm worried.
You know that Do Ra-mi is still an issue.
She keeps haunting me, and I need help.
I won't be able to make it alone.
In a foreign country
where I don't speak the language?
And no one will help me
with all my issues!
Mu-hee, I'm making an effort to be polite
and keep boundaries with you.
This is what you wanted.
Why are you making me say
things like that?
Because you're mean but honest.
I'm aware that you say all that stuff
'cause you're worried about me.
Mu-hee, you are a…
a very adventurous person
who can also be pretty fickle.
You might say one thing,
then you change your mind again.
Then you take it back and go in circles.
And you also have Do Ra-mi
giving you major anxiety.
I can picture you freaking out again,
and I'm worried.
You're right.
What if…
I can find a guy to join?
Someone who keeps cool
and always goes by the book
to make sure everything works out.
And if maybe he just so happens
to be fluent in many languages,
I should be okay, right?
I can probably get by
if I had a guy like that.
What do you think?
Mu-hee.
Just say what you wanna say.
You're beating around the bush,
and you're still getting worked up
and upset about everything.
And I'm not able to understand…
what you really want from me.
Please help!
I'd like you to come with me.
Are you uncomfortable around me?
Do you think I'm gonna try
to make you go out with me?
I'm confident that won't be an issue.
Then, let's go!
We might see
the aurora borealis, remember?
Aurora!
Aurora borealis. Green and blue.
You can take nice photos.
The coolest photo of your life!
Aurora!
Okay. I'll join you.
I need a place to hide from everyone.
All right, I'm in.
Aurora borealis, here we come.
Yay! Let's go see
the Northern Lights together.
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?