(Wooju / Barcode Tinnasit)
(Raon / Jeff Satur)
(Woo-hyuk / DION)
(Q / Q)
(Hachi / Jason) (Air / Alpha)
(Jirong / Kim Namsu, Mr. Kim / Song Wonsu, Chairman Lee /
Choi Sanghak) (Officer Sin / Im Changseop, Mina / Heo Yeseul)
"Wooju Bakery"
(Episode 4)
(Hachi has run away from home)
Is that all?
Hey! Hurry up!
Hurry! Come on!
The quicker you finish
the quicker you get paid.
This feels weird.
What kind of weird?
It feels like when my parents
used to bathe me when I was a kid.
You have memories like that?
No, it's just a feeling.
My memories of my
parents are already so blurry.
I can barely recall them.
The doctor said it was
because of that trauma.
A part of my memory is gone.
I see...
I don't have memories of my mother either.
Why?
I hatched from an egg.
So the first thing I saw
when I was born was my dad.
Wow... your amnesia is on another level.
You're not even scrubbing properly.
Turn around.
Seriously, that's not how
we do it on my planet...
Shut up.
This feeling... it's so nice.
That bakery owner right now...
Is he the son of that
guy from 15 years ago?
I don't know, I don't know anything.
You say you don't know.
But you've been living here for 100 years.
There was indeed a
bakery here 15 years ago.
Their bread was really
popular around here back then.
Business was booming before the incident.
I didn't know you were
such a jerk back then.
Hey, you were part of it too, okay?
We built that building together.
I just wanted to go back home.
Yeah, exactly.
You guys go back to your home.
And I'll go make money and become
the richest person in the universe.
That was our deal from the start.
The blueprint you brought
was completely wrong, wasn't it?
That wasn't my fault!
Fine, even if there was
a mistake back then.
Let's just review the
issues from that time.
This is the revised blueprint.
Come on, take another look at this.
You better show me what
you're really capable of this time.
Is my baby hungry?
Do you want something to eat?
You scared me! What are you doing?
That looks delicious, can I have some?
I'm kidding! This is dog food, you know?
(Basic Dog Food)
I like this one!
You look so seductive wearing that.
Where did you buy this?
There's a convenience store
nearby, they sell them there.
Seeing you even wearing dog clothes...
You must really like dogs, right?
Do you have a dog?
- Officer Shin.
- Yes.
That's enough.
Let her go.
I wanted to stay here myself.
Please, leave me alone.
Ugh, whatever. Suit yourself.
I'm off the clock.
Okay.
Alright, let's go over this again.
So why did you go to that bakery?
Because I'm an influencer.
I visit every new shop that opens.
It's my responsibility to
inform my subscribers.
So you were there to promote it?
Oh, right... yeah, promotion.
But I didn't expect...
To get bitten by that dog-thing.
That's how I ended up like this.
Are there vicious dogs there?
No, it's not a dog.
It's this... this pervert
wearing a dog mask.
And did he say anything else?
Just stuff like it's a
bakery run by aliens.
I just posted a thumbnail for now.
That's the one.
That perverted jerk in the dog mask.
No, that person...
Must be an alien.
Is... is that so?
But the person who kidnapped
me was someone else.
He bit your finger, that's assault, right?
Let's arrest him and investigate.
When?
Now.
Are we arresting him directly?
Of course not.
We wait until he meets with other aliens
and catch him red-handed.
Follow him.
Look over there.
I told you that dog-thing was suspicious.
Hi, little doggy!
Are you doing fine here? I'll see you... later...
Customer.
Is there something you're looking for?
This one! I'm looking for this one!
Oh, so you're a foreigner.
You need to pay first.
Here, take it!
Boss, that's dog food!
You'll get sick if you eat that.
I told you, you can't eat that!
You can't eat this!
You'll really get into trouble.
Gotcha!
What are you guys doing?
Got this one too!
Oh yeah, jackpot!
What is this!?
(Wooju Bakery)
Um...
Raon, are you asleep?
No, I'm not.
There's something I want to ask you...
Yeah, go ahead.
Woo-hyuk and... that princess... uh...
Do they really get along?
We get along pretty well too, don't we?
I'm such a fool for asking you!
Boss, come in quickly!
What?
Hachi has dissapeared.
Hachi really dissapeared!
For real?
Hachi is really missing?
Yeah.
Answer me, what is your relationship?
How many times do I have to say it?
We met for the first time today.
He's just a customer who came to
our convenience store to buy something.
You bit this person, didn't you?
That constitutes assault.
You dare look at me? You bit
my finger and made it look like this!
Looks like we'll be
investigating all night.
Can a police officer just drag innocent
people in for questioning like this?
Aliens must follow Earth's
laws when they come here.
Stop talking so much.
W-what, aliens?
Officer, what are you doing?
Let me go!
We don't even have a part-timer now,
the store is a mess.
Wait a second. We're going
to do an alien identification test.
Aliens who have been on Earth for a long
time are hard to distinguish from humans.
The easiest way is a blood test.
Let's start with a blood test.
Right, let's check your
body temperature first.
Are you really a police officer?
Are you going to draw blood
from innocent people now?
Hachi!
Come out!
Come here.
Hachi!
Come out!
Come out.
Please, no blood please.
I'm scared of blood please, no blood...
There should be a thermometer
in the warehouse over there.
There should be a
breathalyzer or thermometer.
Wait, this person looks like a foreigner.
Is this really okay?
Which country are you from?
I came from a country far away from here.
See, see!
He said he's from very far away.
No way, the South Korean police
are treating a foreign tourist like this?
Isn't this illegal?
Watch them for me for a second.
I'm going to get the thermometer.
Okay.
Do you think the handcuffs
will just open like that?
You bit my finger, so
you have to pay the price.
What on earth are you doing?
So you're a magician.
Wait... Officer! This guy is getting away!
Hey! How are we supposed to find him?
Officer! Hey!
Catch him! Hurry up and catch him!
Catch him!
It's so late, where could
that dog have gone?
This has never happened before...
Hey, when was the last time you saw Hachi?
I don't know, he was just DJing all night.
Searching aimlessly
like this is so inefficient.
Think about what that dog might like.
Not a dog, it's Hachi!
He's not a dog.
But...
He seems to like what dogs like.
Should we split up to look for him?
What? You aren't thinking of...
Colluding with that dog to
make a run for it, are you?
Absolutely not!
You stay right by my side, got it?
I mean what I say.
A prince should follow the rules.
A prince? Stop talking nonsense.
Don't you dare leave my side!
OK OK.
I'm going this way, you
guys go that way. OK?
I am a noble prince, after all.
I won't run away until I find Hachi.
Let's go together!
Officer Shin.
What about the suspect?
I'm heading back to
the station, wait for me.
Got it.
What kind of suspect is it?
The guy in the dog suit.
The one from Wooju Bakery.
I've got the other one tied up
tight, he's not going anywhere.
Understood.
Sorry, let me untie you right away.
You catch them and then just let them go?
One escaped, and you let the other one loose.
The South Korean police
are truly something else.
What were the blood test results?
It's B positive.
So, is he an alien?
No.
If you dare mention the word
'alien' in front of me again...
But, senior, however...
You're still...!
They didn't just handcuff
me, they taped my mouth shut!
Isn't that a human rights
violation and torture?
Sir, we are truly sorry. We
don't even know what to say.
Enough! I'm going to report everything
you've done to the news stations.
Do the South Korean police
have nothing better to do?
Playing some kind of alien game?
It was truly our mistake,
we are very sorry.
But sir, that companion
who came with you...
Do you know him?
No. He was just a foreign customer who came
to our convenience store to buy something.
But he did look a bit like a magician.
That guy isn't a magician, he's indeed an alien.
An alien from a planet far, far away.
An alien?
Alright, everyone go home.
Just pretend today never happened.
Bye.
Wait...
No, seriously, what exactly is that gun?
This?
It's probably hard to understand
using Earth's scientific knowledge.
Earth's scientific knowledge?
Don't worry.
I won't shoot you.
Is he still at the police station?
He was there a moment ago, but he escaped.
We're looking for him now, too.
No.
We have to find him quickly.
Because... he's a foreigner.
He doesn't speak the language well.
Don't worry too much.
We'll find him soon.
I'll help look for him too.
Oh, okay...
Thanksz.
We have to find him first.
Otherwise, if he gets caught
again, they'll dissect him.
Hey, why would the police dissect you?
You're not frogs.
That's been a rumor where
we're from for a long time.
You're actually buying into that?
Were you raised in a bamboo forest?
No wonder you believe such nonsense!
A bamboo forest? What's that...
Let's go!
What is that?
What?
That's a playground, right?
A playground? What's that for?
It's a place for kids to play.
What? What backwater place were you raised in
that you don't even know what a playground is?
Want to play here for a bit before we go?
This is my first time seeing a playground.
When I was little,
I always wanted to play with friends.
That was my wish.
I'm sorry.
But, you and I aren't friends, are we?
Do you want to play with me?
I'm your employer, your boss!
I know, I know.
Can't a boss be friends with me?
Your eyes... they look like
the Earth I saw from space.
W-what?
They're beautiful.
Stop that!
You're a weirdo.
Fine, I'll play with you for a bit.
Since it's your first time at a playground,
and you don't have any friends,
I'll keep you company, okay?
Have you ever been on a slide?
Wait for me!
You really can't read the room, can you?
The mood is perfect,
why go and interrupt them?
We still have to tell him.
He looks like he's having a great time.
Our Wooju,
he's actually really worried, isn't he?
Does that look like he's worried?
He looks like he's having a blast to me.
How long are you going to
keep worrying about him?
Woo-hoo!
Oh, merciful and great gods,
I am your loyal follower.
Oh, for heaven's sake...
Vice President Oh!
God bless us.
Are you praying for us?
It seems the gods of
Earth are truly powerful.
Look, they both got released, didn't they?
That was Chairman Lee who let them go.
Chairman Lee isn't a god.
Alright, enough of that.
But do we really have to
do what Chairman Lee said?
We'll be punished by the gods
of Earth if we do bad things.
Vice President Oh,
this is the only way we can get back home.
You're right.
These two...
they don't understand anything.
It's not like there's no other way.