=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 4=
Stay alert.
Xiaoxiao,
how's it going?
It's all right.
We're safe now.
Ancestors bless us.
Xiaoxiao,
what on earth is going on?
Maybe our ancestors wouldn't
want their descendants
to be bullied.
This place is creepy.
Let's leave now.
Yes. Let's move.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
(Shuozhou)
Why are there more people coming?
It's Tabai Army.
I wonder how long they'll stay.
How about we flee the town?
Don't say that.
If the Chong Army returns, we'll suffer.
Xiaoxiao,
I think we're in Shuozhou.
Stop looking. Come back in.
As you expected,
some Chong soldiers ambushed Miss He.
Captain Han was there,
so Miss He survived.
In that case,
is Captain Han
cleared of suspicion?
In an ambush,
they must have had
more soldiers than us.
How did Han Lingqiu
manage to repel them?
It was pretty strange.
We were lurking around there.
- Stay alert!
- I saw them
become outnumbered
and it looked real.
I had intended to help them.
But many blue fireballs
appeared out of nowhere
and only attacked our enemies.
General,
Miss He has arrived.
Captain Han,
are you all right?
We got ambushed.
But we're fine now.
(Lin Mansion)
Mission completed.
Miss He has been delivered.
I heard you had been ambushed.
Thanks to your desperate fight,
Miss He has survived.
Actually,
I take no credit for that.
Things were a little bit weird.
Weird?
Not at all.
Our ancestors showed their power.
General Duan,
since Shuozhou Campaign,
how have you been?
(Lin Mansion)
You got ambushed.
I was really worried.
I came here on your orders.
But on my way,
I nearly lost my life.
How could that be?
You've always been blessed.
Captain Meng once told me
she met something wicked.
But when you appeared,
it was gone.
During the ambush,
you were there with my men.
And thanks to the blessing,
you arrived safely.
What a coincidence.
Isn't it?
Yes.
Maybe you're right, General.
I am
blessed.
(This body)
(won't last much longer.)
Miss He.
I think
you have a fever.
General Duan,
are you testing me again?
Can you really not feel it?
Oh, I'm really sick.
Xiaoxiao,
you're finally awake.
Are you feeling better?
(This body is so weak.)
Where are we?
According to the General,
we are in Mr. Lin's mansion,
the richest man in Shuozhou.
Miss He, since you're awake,
let the physician
give you a checkup.
Have you been
feeling fatigued
with weak limbs and abdominal pain?
A little bit, I think.
Sensitive to wind and cold,
with a dull appetite?
A little bit.
A weak chest?
A little bit, too.
Do you feel sick or upset?
A little bit.
Physician,
since she's so seriously ill,
please prescribe properly
and make sure she recovers.
Miss He,
it's medicine time.
Um...
Xiaoxiao,
I'll go buy you some preserves.
General, you don't need to bother
bringing me medicine yourself.
You contributed to my army.
So, your illness
isn't a minor thing.
Is it a rule of your army?
If Commandant Xia falls ill,
will you also send him medicine?
No, actually.
Meng Wan told me you like me.
So, bringing you medicine
can make you happier.
Sorry, sorry.
Hey, if you keep wiping,
you'll rub my skin raw.
I don't think you like me.
I think you like my skull.
I've been wandering about for years
and I just have some quirks.
Let's both drop the act,
Miss He.
Or I should call you
"a miraculous lady lacking five senses".
I can't compare to you,
General.
You've never trained.
But when you were 19,
you escaped from bandits
and went home alone from afar.
Commandant Wu has fought wars for years.
But within just a few moves,
you took him down.
Over seven years in Daizhou,
all who knew you are now dead
and dead men tell no tales.
Besides...
Red birds are to...
Red birds are to burn
all living beings.
You know Aphorisms of Cangshen.
Are you really the one
from before you turned twelve?
You checked up on me.
Right back at you.
You did the same.
So,
what's your conclusion?
Then, do you have
any conclusion about me?
We are both
puppets in disguise.
Let's not break the ice.
There may be more ice.
If we break some,
there will be more.
You used me as bait.
What if I helped your enemies instead?
From what I've seen,
they don't have pretty skulls.
They can't attract you
like I do.
Are you so sure?
I'm not sure.
But I'm a born gambler
and I'm always lucky.
I always land on my feet.
So, you believe you won't lose?
If I don't gamble, I won't.
But in that case,
I'll never win, either.
Since you're a wagering man,
let's make a wager.
On what?
On whether you are
the real Duan Xu.
(Real Duan Xu.)
Stop running!
How dare you steal from me?
I'm going to kill you!
Don't you dare.
(Liang)
Xu sent you to shadow Captain Han.
I don't know if you're injured.
Here, take this.
I'm fine.
Take it.
I'm really fine.
You keep it.
Use it next time you get hurt.
Come on.
Are you cursing me?
No, no. I don't mean that.
Miss He...
How is she now?
The physician checked,
saying she was fine.
She's in Lin Mansion.
What?
She stays with the General?
Yes. What's wrong?
Hey, think about it.
Why does Xu care so much
about her?
Because she helps us
with weather observations.
Do you think she's pretty?
Yes.
You're pretty!
I didn't ask that!
You don't judge me.
I do think
you look very good.
(Enjoy the Beauty)
(In the face of enemies,)
(how can you still laugh?)
(Well disguised.)
(No clues have been left)
(about his identity.)
(That's a good physique.)
(How does he have)
(so many old and new scars?)
(He's quite vigilant.)
(Well, he remains chaste.)
(Yan Ke, Right Hand of the Void)
No more hiding.
Come out.
Chang.
You let her go?
Your Lordship,
Yinyin and I didn't mean to escape.
By the Golden-wall Decrees,
spirits shall not
enter the Mortal World.
How dare you defy the decrees
issued by the Sovereign?
I can make you
continue as the Vice Lord.
Or
you can turn to ashes with her.
Make your choice.
Chang.
Yinyin.
When you first became a spirit,
I saved you.
Yinyin,
I'm sorry.
Remember.
This is your own choice.
(Liang)
We were kept in ignorance.
How could he be so childish
about military operations?
What if...?
Commandant Wu, you're back.
Let me introduce the one
who contributed to our army.
You lied about us attacking Yuzhou.
Actually, we attacked Shuozhou.
Why? Try to trick me?
Now you get me back.
You tell me.
What about Yuzhou?
Commandant Wu!
The General doesn't need
your approval to deploy troops!
Commandant Wu, calm down.
The tea is very hot.
Any complaints?
I don't have complaints.
Indeed.
We won this battle.
But you...
You were never honest
with any of us.
Soldiers can risk their lives,
but no one wants a senseless death.
You have a special way
of conducting military operations
and playing tricks on enemies.
But with people,
you're pretty flaky
and quite evasive.
I don't accept that!
Commandant Wu,
you always show your emotions
and you've guarded the border.
Enemies know you very well.
If I had told you about the feint,
they might have known.
Besides,
there was a huge gap in strength
between both sides.
Cornered soldiers fight best!
If they hadn't fought
with the resolve to die,
a backup plan wouldn't help at all.
So what?
We couldn't have won
without the red birds
that happened to fly by.
Those birds didn't happen to fly by.
They were part of the General's plan.
Those were pigeons
the General had painted
with the flame pattern.
What?
Before the war, I asked Meng Wan
to search nearby pigeon farms.
(Liang)
Chong people believe in Cangshen.
In Aphorisms of Cangshen,
red birds with the flame pattern
will be sent down from the heavens.
Chong people firmly believe red birds
will bring disasters.
So,
I had those pigeons prepared.
When the wind blew at sunrise,
I had them released.
(You're so familiar with their belief.)
(Is it because you're knowledgeable)
(or is it because you're a Chong man?)
General, you're quite knowledgeable
while I'm merely uneducated.
I'm no match for you.
Now,
Awo'erqi of the Chong Army
and reinforcements
will arrive in days.
I believe
you've had a surefire plan.
Will you share it with us, please?
Yeah.
Miss He, what do you suggest?
This is Miss He
who offers us weather predictions.
During Shuozhou Campaign,
she predicted the weather conditions.
General, do you have to
stop their reinforcements?
Of course.
Then how about
you blow up the Guanhe River?
Blow up the Guanhe River?
What?
How can we do that?
It's still very cold.
What's the use of blowing it up?
In a few days,
the river will freeze again.
That area has a pleasant climate.
The river doesn't freeze in winter.
But this year,
the rare freezing weather
has led to the frozen river.
But in my opinion,
the freezing weather
won't last much longer.
In ten days, the temperature will soar,
the cold will recede,
and it will get warm.
If you blow up the river
before that,
I don't think
it will freeze again
anytime soon.
I think it's a good idea.
Blow up the Guanhe River?
And then?
Go back to Liangzhou?
Commander Qin ordered.
We'll defend Shuozhou at all costs
and defeat their reinforcements.
We must not retreat.
Defend Shuozhou at all costs?
We must not retreat?
This is no joke.
If we blow up the river
without going back to Liangzhou,
every single person here
will end up dead!
Is it really Commander Qin's order?
Or did you fake it
for military merit?
Ambition is never satisfied!
The city under our feet
belongs to Great Liang.
Thirty years ago, Great Liang troops
were utterly defeated right here.
North Chong troops
occupied the 17 Prefectures
without scruples.
They even marched south,
massacring Liangzhou.
After tough wars
and bloody battles,
we finally made it back here.
Are we just going to give in?
Since it's our duty,
don't be so worried.
We will win.
Can we win just because
you think we will?
Commandant Wu,
I'm indeed dictatorial.
But so far,
I have never lost.
Have I?
Fine.
I'll trust you one more time.
No one here is afraid to die.
But we shouldn't die in vain!
If we fail to repel our enemies,
I will haunt your family
even if I die!
Don't worry, Commandant Wu.
If you die, so will I.
I'm counting on you all.
Wu Shengliu hates you so much
possibly because
you're too good-looking.
You flatter me.
It's my honor.
Actually,
Commandant Wu trusts you.
How do you know that?
From Liangzhou to Shuozhou,
the battles were hard.
But after winning these battles,
Wu Shengliu trusts you.
Even captains in the camp
and all the soldiers in your army
genuinely trust you, too.
Are you saying
you have
full confidence in me?
Now that you know
I like you,
I certainly have confidence...
Full confidence in you.
Your feelings are too strong
for ordinary guys.
Blowing up the river
is very dangerous.
One misstep will lead to the destruction
and everyone will die like a dog.
You're really merciless to the man
you have feelings for.
But you accepted that with pleasure.
Are you really sure
you can win this battle?
If I were 100% sure,
I wouldn't be a good gambler.
You're a mad gambler, indeed.
♪Wander to the other shore
with the lantern♪
♪Accompanied by eternity♪
(Well, he's also a gambler,)
(cheerful and kind-hearted.)
♪Love and hate will fade away♪
(Liang)
General.
What's up?
Have you met me before?
About five or six years ago.
Why do you ask?
If we have met before,
why can't you remember?
At that time, I was badly injured.
That's how I got this scar on my face.
After I recovered,
I forgot everything
about my past.
I didn't know
you suffered that.
But at that time, I was in Daizhou
and I didn't see you.
Simu.
Take a seat.
I brought you a human gadget.
You'll love it.
This is tea-whisking.
I once saw some mortals
make tea like this.
It's nice to do it myself.
The first pour
shouldn't exceed 40% of the cup.
Yan, you must be busy lately.
Jiang Ai doesn't like to take charge.
You have to handle
all the affairs in the Void.
You work too hard.
War has raged in the Mortal World.
Fusang Tree was unusual.
But I've taken care of it.
When I supervise in the Spirit World,
you can enjoy your vacation
and have fun.
The tea tastes good.
You always pick up quickly
these human gadgets.
It's a nice present.
I'll take it.
I knew you'd like it.
A mortal easily gets tired.
You need to eat and sleep regularly.
Yeah.
This body
is especially hard to tend.
I've been out too long.
I still have work to do.
I should go.
When you're here,
I can spend
more days in the Mortal World.
If it makes you happy.
Foxy
blew up the river one day earlier.
Quite a lot of people died.
Much more spirit aura will appear
on Fusang Tree.
Troops from Yuzhou would cross the river
to attack Shuozhou.
You set up an ambush here
and completed the plan
to blow up the river.
Foxy,
did you anticipate
they would launch a sneak attack?
What does death look like
in mortals' eyes?
He Xiaoxiao.
You can see me?
So, you associate me
with the crows.
He Xiaoxiao,
are you here?
Ever since then,
you've noticed me.
The time is right.
Soldiers, follow my orders.
Yes.
How brave!
A wise man avoids danger.
But you get close to danger.
You're just betting that I'll help.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
Kill!
Simu,
Aunt has got you
a present.
Maybe one day,
you will meet a spell bearer
who can connect with your five senses.
When that person appears,
the Pearl will let you know.
(I'm alive and dead.)
(For 400 years,)
(I've never had five senses.)
(I thought I'd never)
(know how it felt to be alive.)
(But surprisingly,)
(the man who can)
(give me five senses)
(has appeared.)
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪