(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
[Chunxiao Theater]
[Nanxi Tribe, 15 years ago]
Wait for me!
Hurry up!
It's the village!
Brother!
What happened?
Someone's here! Hide!
Father.
Mother.
Mother!
Father!
-Mother!
Mother, where are you?
Mother! Father!
Brother,
where are Father and Mother?
Mother!
They are all dead.
Father!
Father, where are you?
[Young Zhan Ziming]
Brother, you eat it.
[Young Zhan Ziyu]
I'm not hungry. You eat it.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 13]
No need for formalities, Director Zhang.
Take a seat.
I dare not.
Sit.
Yes.
And this is?
You don't need to ask, Director Zhang.
I understand.
My late-night visit this time
is somewhat presumptuous.
Not at all.
Your Highness, may I ask why
you're visiting at this time?
I've long heard you compiled a book
named Compendium of Creation.
It consists of five volumes:
Metal, Wood, Water, Fire, and Earth.
Metal
is metallurgy.
Wood
is formations and fortifications.
Water covers meteorology
and water conservancy.
Earth
is topography.
It is a grand and invaluable work,
a classified archive of Biantang
kept within the Manufacturing Bureau.
I've come today
to borrow it.
Will you do me this favor?
Your Highness, you are the ruler
and I am your subject.
This compendium I compiled
belongs to Biantang.
If you wish to use it,
I will certainly help.
However,
it falls under the Manufacturing Bureau,
a highly confidential office.
You would need an imperial decree
from His Majesty,
and with that I will certainly help.
Lord Zhang, you've served
as an official for years,
so you are naturally no stranger
to the affairs of the imperial court.
You should know that
some matters are appropriate
for requesting a decree,
and some are not.
Since I am the Crown Prince,
I'm the future ruler of Biantang.
Helping me would not be considered
overstepping.
And I will certainly
reward you handsomely.
What do you say?
I-If that's the case, Your Highness,
I understand.
But I have one question to ask.
If you answer truthfully,
I will certainly help.
Feel free to ask.
Your Highness, what do you intend to use
the Compendium of Creation for?
I...
I need... the Metal volume.
Your Highness,
since Lord Zhang has his difficulties,
we shouldn't force him.
Why don't we...
take our leave now?
Alright. Alright.
Let's go.
Farewell,
Your Highness.
This person is not Director Zhang.
We fell into Mother's trap.
What do we do now?
How do we get out?
Cover up.
Why?
Cover up your face with it.
What's the point of this?
Be quiet.
Just follow me from here.
Let's go.
Stop!
Catch them!
I want them alive!
Arrest them!
Yes!
Can you slow down?
I can't keep up.
If you say one more word,
you're on your own!
I don't know martial arts!
Stop!
Over there!
This way!
Hurry up! Stop!
Stop!
-Stop!
-Let's go!
Stop!
After them!
Wait! I'm exhausted!
This way!
Zhuge Yue,
I'm just a frail scholar.
Do you have to be so inhumane?
I haven't seen any literary talent
from you.
How dare you call yourself a scholar?
You...
Qiao?
Come with me.
Stay close.
Qiao,
why are you here?
I guessed you'd fall into
the Empress's trap.
I had Wang Shi'er bring me here.
We're here.
This leads outside
the Manufacturing Bureau.
We'll go out from here.
Wang Shi'er is waiting for us outside.
Follow me.
It's so deep...
Zhuge...
Li Ce, hurry up and come down.
Don't be afraid. I'll catch you.
I-I...
I'm not afraid, Qiao.
Catch me, will you?
I'll catch you!
Come down now!
Why did you, a grown man, catch me?
I told you I didn't need to be caught.
Zhuge Yue...
You...
Wait for me!
Qiao,
where are we?
This canal used to be for flood discharge.
It's abandoned now.
Keep walking, and we'll reach
Tianyuan Bridge in Rong District.
Wang Shi'er found it.
You guys go first.
I'll meet you at Tianyuan Bridge later.
Hurry!
Search over there!
Go! Search over there!
Search every spot!
Don't let those two get away!
It is a grand and invaluable work,
a classified archive of Biantang
kept within the Manufacturing Bureau.
"Tianji" means...
Tianji Pavilion.
"The river originates from Kunlun."
[Tianji Pavilion]
Who's there? Who's in there?
Search!
Did you find what you wanted?
Here.
Xing.
Let's talk outside.
Li Ce.
Qiao,
are you alright?
Where did you go?
There have been several waves of troops
searching the area.
Let's find a place to hide first.
There's a hiding spot up ahead.
I'll take you there.
Okay.
-Let's go.
Once we get there,
I'll draw the pursuers away,
and you wait for an opportunity to escape.
Qiao,
I'm injured.
Look.
Injured?
It's just a scrape.
No.
It hurts a lot.
Look carefully.
What's going on?
Let me see.
Look closely.
Why does it hurt so much?
I feel dizzy, my vision is blurry,
my legs are weak,
and my hands are shaking.
I think I have internal injuries.
Oh, no.
I can't even stand anymore.
I can't stand.
Feeling better?
It's getting worse.
Let me lean on you a little longer.
Qiao,
where did Zhuge Yue go?
Are you saying that the Crown Prince
was wearing a veil
when he fled,
and none of you saw his face?
It was too dark at the time.
We could only judge from his figure.
It should have been His Highness.
Not only did you fail to catch him,
but you also didn't see his face clearly.
What's the use of keeping you?
Guards!
Drag them out.
Kill them.
Spare us, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, have mercy!
Spare us!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty, spare us!
Please calm your anger, Your Majesty!
Get out! Get out, all of you!
Get out!
Your Majesty.
I failed you.
If you're really too angry, punish me.
What's the use of beating you to death?
Will that get me the evidence
that the Crown Prince colluded
with a foreign power
and stole the archives?
Your life isn't worth that much!
My life is worth nothing,
but it belongs to you.
What I need is to get rid of him.
If you can't do that,
you're useless to me!
I can testify!
I did see the Crown Prince.
It was him who broke into
the Manufacturing Bureau at night.
You can testify?
Who do you think you are?
Without me,
would His Majesty
listen to a word you say?
Who do you think you are
to accuse the Crown Prince of Biantang?
I'm telling you,
you didn't bring back any witnesses
or material evidence today.
Even if your subordinates swear
that the Crown Prince broke into
the Manufacturing Bureau at night,
His Majesty won't believe it.
He will only turn a blind eye
and brush me off.
For him,
bloodline and the throne
are the most important.
I am just a woman.
Your Majesty.
We haven't lost.
We still have Ziming.
And the child in her womb.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
May Your Majesty enjoy good health.
Look up.
Are you really pregnant with Ce's child?
I dare not deceive you, Your Majesty.
It is indeed the Crown Prince's kid.
Since that's the case,
you should move out
of the Crown Prince's Mansion.
[Boque Palace]
Yes.
We uncovered everything.
Lady Ziming's original surname was Zhan.
She is Zhan Ziyu's biological sister,
and also the Empress's
deepest planted spy
in the Crown Prince's Mansion.
After her identity was exposed,
she left on her own.
I was born as the Crown Prince.
Living in the palace, I've always known
danger is everywhere.
I never dared to easily reveal
my true feelings to anyone.
But Ziming…
I thought she was different.
Stop! Don't run!
Stop!
How dare you run!
Keep running!
Stop!
Go back and tell your master
that I bought
this slave.
Li Ce,
I promised you
that once we rescue He Xiao,
I would regroup
and help you reclaim your rightful power
as Crown Prince of Biantang.
Burn all of Lady Ziming's belongings.
Your Highness.
These are battle reports
from various regions
of Great Yong and Great Yan.
It seems they are preparing
to exchange prisoners of war.
There's nothing important.
Since the Compendium of Creation
has been found,
take some rest first.
We will enter the palace today
to bid farewell
and depart for Ximeng tomorrow.
[Great Yong and Great Yan are set to
exchange prisoners of war in a border valley]
[at the end of the month. There may be
further actions to follow.]
Let's make a deal.
I need 20 days.
After 20 days,
I will leave with you.
Why should I make a deal with you?
If you bring back the Compendium of Creation
with missing pages,
do you think King Ximeng will let you off?
Zhuge Yue.
You think you're threatening me?
Your poisoning relapsed yesterday
because we have already passed
the agreed time.
If you go another 10 days
without the Blood on Snow,
you will die.
There are some things
I must do.
I'll give you one last chance.
Give me the compendium
and go back to Ximeng with me.
You know
you can't kill me.
It's for that Chu Qiao again, isn't it?
I want you to help me do two things.
First,
find out
if there is a man named He Xiao
among the prisoners
handed over to Great Yan by Great Yong.
Second,
if there is,
I need 20 days
to save this man.
You don't have to go with me.
Just stay in Tangjing
and buy me some time.
As long as you help me
complete these 2 things,
I will also help you
accomplish the 2 things
King Ximeng assigned you.
Hurry up!
Get in line!
Keep up!
Hurry!
What's all the noise?
Elder.
I have been ordered
to dispatch an elite unit
to escort prisoners of war.
We are pressed for time,
I apologize
for disturbing your rest.
Making a fuss over nothing.
They're just a few dying men.
Why do you need a whole unit for that?
Yes.
We've also been ordered
to assign 2 fast horses each
and rush to the main camp first.
We've been instructed
to reach Lincheng within 5 days.
Reach Lincheng in 5 days?
Are they trying to run the men and horses
to death?
Who the hell gave this order?
Mind your words, Elder.
This is His Majesty's order.
Then I'd like to ask him myself
whether the lives
of our Lanchuan soldiers are worthless!
Prepare my horse!
Your Majesty,
the scent of Platycladi seeds can
calm your mind and nourish your energy.
It can also soothe your nerves.
Your Majesty,
Elder Lanchuan requests an audience.
I won't see him.
Your Majesty,
is it because you feel guilty
that you dare not see me?
Lincheng is far from the Capital.
Why are we taking the risk of losing
our elite soldiers and fine horses
just to escort a few death-row prisoners
of Great Yong?
Are the lives of Great Yan warriors
worth less than a few dying men?
Do I need to explain my thoughts
to you one by one?
Your Majesty, ever since your recovery,
you've become like a different person.
Not only do you want a truce
with Great Yong,
but now you also want to exchange
prisoners of war with them.
Everything you've done
goes against your previous nature.
Do you think
we elders are so blind
that we can't see your intentions?
You simply want to exchange
for He Xiao, the Xiuli Army general,
so you can lure a woman here.
Cheng Yuan!
Drag this outspoken Elder Lanchuan
out of here.
Your Majesty,
General Cheng is no longer here.
See Elder Lanchuan out.
Guards!
Who dares to touch me!
No need for it!
I will leave on my own!
Your Majesty, you're in a bad mood.
How about going for
a horseback ride with me to cheer up?
You lost again.
I just learned how to ride.
Your Majesty, you're bullying me.
Then I will let you win.
Let's go!
Stop.
Turn around.
Cheng Yuan?
Why are you here?
Your Majesty, you don't want to see me,
so I will leave.
I'm asking you!
Your Majesty,
I have joined the army
since I was a child.
The military camp of Great Yan is my home.
The Black Eagle Army and you
are my family.
Great Yan is so large,
but I don't know where to go.
The racecourse is the closest place
to the military camp.
I found a job here
to make a living.
I never thought I would meet you here.
Your Majesty,
just pretend you didn't see me today.
I will leave now...
and never come back.
Guards!
Prepare a horse for General Cheng!
My Lady,
let me do it.
Or just let the maids and servants do it.
If you get too tired,
the Prince of Luo will blame us.
I stay here all day
and have nothing to do anyway.
I might as well help out with some chores.
Miss, you look different
these past few days.
How so?
You smile more,
and you've become more beautiful.
But it makes sense.
I've never seen His Highness
care so much about anyone before.
[Portrait of Zhao Chun'er,
Princess of Great Yong]
Let me go!
Chun'er, let me explain.
You've known who I am for a long time.
How long were you planning
to hide it from me?
What's your real purpose in treating me
so well, always attending to me,
and caring toward me?
Chun'er!
I got that portrait by chance
a few days ago.
I didn't tell you
because I knew
you didn't want to talk about your past,
and I didn't want to remind you of that.
I didn't mean to hide it.
Stop talking!
I will never believe you again!
Someone's robbing me!
Help!
Someone is robbing me!
I was robbed!
Help!
In broad daylight,
how dare you rob someone in the street!
Get lost!
Miss,
this jade pendant is yours, right?
This area is often frequented by merchants
from beyond the borders,
and there's all kinds of people around.
A young lady like you
should be more careful
when you're out alone.
Miss?
Your jade pendant.
What's wrong with you?
You didn't even thank our Princess.
Princess.
This girl...
looks a bit like someone I know.
It's alright.
Let's go.
Yes.
How is it?
Is there any news?
For the past half month,
I've asked many friends to gather
information in Zhenhuangcheng,
but there's been no news.
What about you?
Me too.
I think it's very strange.
When I was a wandering physician,
I got to know quite a few people.
Not just people from the martial world,
but also nobles and aristocrats.
But for some reason,
none of them have heard of He Xiao
in the prisoner of war camps
they've inquired about.
He Xiao is now a prisoner of war
under Zhao Che's command.
Zhao Che has always been strict
with his army.
If you're not in his army,
it's very hard to get any information.
Who are you?
What do you want?
I'm here to see your princess.
Great Yong and Great Yan
have agreed to exchange
a batch of prisoners of war in Lincheng,
which is near Baichuan, in ten days.
I've already had people inquire about
the list of these prisoners of war.
He Xiao is indeed on it.
Yan Xun has called a truce
with Great Yong for months,
and he's been continuously sending
the Black Eagle Army to search for you.
The real purpose
of this prisoner exchange
should be He Xiao.
Thank you for the information.
How will you save him?
How do you know I'm going to save him?
You've been secretly training troops
in this restaurant for Li Ce,
and you disguised yourself
as Princess Fu in Tangjing.
Is it because you're fond of
the luxurious life
in the Crown Prince's Mansion,
or because you want to get involved
in Biantang's palace intrigues?
Aren't you doing all this
just so that when you finally get news
of He Xiao,
you can go save him?
Yes.
You're right.
But this is my business.
It has nothing to do with you.
Lincheng is at least
15 days' journey from Tangjing.
Even if you set off immediately,
you won't make it in time before Great Yan
takes He Xiao away.
You can only
take the Biantang official road,
switch to the waterway halfway,
and go through Qingluan Pass
to arrive exactly within 10 days.
But the official road
requires an imperial pass.
How can I take it?
Under the name of the Ximeng envoy team,
as an attendant to Crown Prince Li Ce.
Your Highness!
We found Miss Chun'er.
Where did you find her?
Did you have people bring her back?
She came back on her own.
She's in her room now.
Chunxing.
Come here.
Is this Princess Fu?
Princess Fu?
Yes.
She was close to our prince
when they were young.
But...
But later, she met with misfortune
along with Prince of Pingnan
and was gone for many years.
After returning,
she became distant from us.
Is she in Tangjing now?
Yes.
I heard that since she came back,
she has been staying
at the Crown Prince's Mansion.
The Crown Prince likes her
and wants to marry her.
Chun'er!
Chun'er,
where have you been these past two days?
I was so worried about you.
Chun'er.
Chun'er, what's wrong?
Did something happen?
You like me, right?
Then marry me as your consort.
I want to be Princess Consort of Luo.
Your Majesty.
General Shiyan.
Here!
Great Yan and Great Yong
have been at war for years,
and the people are exhausted.
This journey of yours
is to bring back Great Yan's lost generals
and soldiers for me,
end the war with Great Yong,
and bring even a brief moment of peace
to the countless people of Great Yan!
Yes, Your Majesty!
We will not fail our mission!
Lord Cheng.
This is the list for the prisoners of war
exchange between Great Yan and Great Yong,
along with the compensation
for the wounded.
Please review it.
[He Xiao]
Since your presence here
is Her Majesty's goodwill,
we will travel
with you.
Lord Zhan!
Wait!
Zhao Chun'er.
Why are you claiming to be
the Princess Consort of Luo
personally appointed by me?
Chu Qiao,
rest in peace.