(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
Ji Ling!
Hide!
Where are the prayer beads?
I've moved them to a place
where you'll never ever find them.
Tie them up with the Demon-Binding Rope!
- Yes, sir.
- Bravo!
Let me do it.
‪-Bravo!
- Bravo!
Bravo!
- Had a bad dream?
- No.
I was just recalling a lot of the past.
So long ago, feels like a past life.
Yeah.
Over a thousand years.
That's many ordinary lifetimes.
Wangyan,
do we really
have to kill Ji Ling?
Didn't you say
Ji Ling isn't the Dragon Deity?
TOKEN OF SCALES
You haven't changed.
Every time you can't sleep,
you come to my place.
Hui. You did good in every mission.
This is your reward.
Thank you, Master.
I already have so many colorful stones.
The other sisters don't have any!
What's wrong?
Master,
has the Dragon Deity
truly been corrupted by evil thoughts?
Nothing in this world
is purely good or evil.
Be it human, demon,
deity, or even devil,
all have a hidden side.
The brighter the light,
the darker the shadow it casts.
Demons can wear painted skin,
humans can wear masks.
Even deities have their obsessions.
Wangyan.
BY WANGYUE
Over a hundred years,
I've done many things with you
that we had no choice in.
Though we meant to stay pure,
our hands are stained with blood,
and our hearts are full of guilt.
Wangyan, let's go.
This mission is dangerous.
I know you've developed
feelings for Ji Ling.
Whether he is the Dragon Deity or not,
it's a hard choice for you.
I don't want to see you
torn between duty to the world
and drawing blood against your beloved.
Take care of yourself. I'll be back.
I've been waiting for you.
The Oracle Stone has a new prophecy.
It says…
the Dragon Deity will fall.
I'm not that easy to kill.
"Won't die"
and "not easy to kill"
are two different things.
What are you trying to say?
You wanted to take back
your power from Xiaowei,
so you sent Li Jie to the Wei mansion.
But you wouldn't risk your life,
so you sent a puppet instead, Ji Ling,
to go with Li Jie in your place. Right?
When I saw Ji Ling at the Wei mansion,
I was surprised.
I thought you were just pretending
to be some innocent, lively young man,
acting like you didn't know me.
You're the hunter commander
of the Shilin Sect. And you?
What exactly are you?
Me?
Just an ordinary hunter, no flower
on my forehead. What's wrong?
Were you joking,
or were you serious?
Not until Xiaowei gravely wounded Ji Ling
and the wound's edge showed wood chips.
I figured Ji Ling and Li Jie
might run into
a Formless Moon member there.
I just didn't expect it to be you,
of all people.
When things are too coincidental,
someone's usually pulling the strings.
The Fox Queen
specifically sent Wuyi and me.
She knows about Ji Ling.
She said Ji Ling and Wuyi are fated ones.
What does that mean?
Fated ones?
Now, your power has passed to Wu Shiguang.
Only one piece, for now,
not enough to seal your fate.
But the Oracle Stone never errs.
The Dragon Deity's fall
will come, sooner or later.
That's why I need your help.
What do you want me to do?
Get close to Wu Shiguang.
Find a way to take the prayer beads
and bring them to me.
Those beads know their owner.
Taking them won't be easy.
Foxes from the Formless Moon
are masters at seduction.
A mere Wu Shiguang
shouldn't be too hard for you.
Right.
For a thousand years,
I've played countless roles,
had countless family,
lovers,
and dearest friends.
But truth and lies blur,
this life is but a dream.
I can barely remember who I am anymore.
You're tired?
What about you?
Wearing a skin
for too long,
you'll forget the heart beneath.
But the heart
always remembers who it truly is.
I hope this is the last time.
Trust me,
this is the last time.
After this, you and everyone
in the Formless Moon
will be truly free.
Wu Shiguang, do something!
Wu Shiguang? Wu Shiguang?
I rubbed it off!
I rubbed the rope loose!
My spell did that.
Why… Why didn't you use that sooner?
My bones are stiff!
You're a weasel.
Your bones are the softest in the world.
Stop playing the victim.
You just make up rumors out of thin air!
What now?
Indeed,
a weasel's fart really does work best.
Can you stop with the rumors?
That's black smoke from my blade, alright?
So? Praise me!
Hello?
Be careful!
I don't want to vanish into thin air.
What are you doing? I'm here.
Commander Li, as you instructed,
I let them escape.
What now?
Follow them.
He'll definitely go get the prayer beads.
Didn't you go back to the Formless Moon?
The moment we parted, I couldn't sleep.
I told myself I shouldn't think of you,
and I can't think of you.
But when feelings arise,
the heart follows.
So I had to come find you.
Formless Moon foxes are truly something.
You make tracking someone
- sound so seductive.
- Seductive?
You've misunderstood me, sir.
The one tracking you isn't me.
It's Li Jie.
He meant to let us go.
Ye Changsheng doesn't need a token on him.
Exactly.
I trapped him in my maze formation
or else Li Jie would've caught you by now.
Instead of thanking me,
you nearly deflowered me.
Nearly cut you. Don't talk nonsense,
and that's what your name implies.
So why are you here?
To help you.
I'm used to going solo.
I don't need your help.
Killing the Dragon Deity
is no easy task.
You sure you don't need help?
I'm killing him
to avenge my entire clan.
What about you?
The Oracle Stone gave a prophecy.
I have no choice.
You're a cunning fox,
always deceiving and running off.
Why should I trust you?
Have I ever deceived you?
Back at the Wei mansion,
who claimed to be after Xiaowei
but ended up wounded by me?
That was to help you.
Lu Wuyi's not easy to fool.
Wangyan, are you okay?
You wanted to buy time
for those Shilin Sect hunters.
So I pretended you wounded me,
to hold my sister back.
That hit of yours was pretty hard.
And now you blame me?
You even deceive your own sister.
I didn't want to deceive her either.
But that move isn't just for Xiaowei,
it's for you.
You're in my heart.
And I know you have feelings for me too.
Your heart's racing.
Want to work together?
Show your cards.
What do you have?
That depends
on what you want.
I want to know
where the next piece
of Dragon Deity's Power is.
I've been dreading telling you this,
but Wangyue has also turned.
I know you two are like sisters.
So, go find her, uncover the truth,
or perhaps help her find her way back.
Master, I will find out the truth
and prove she hasn't betrayed us.
Wangyan.
You blame me for liking Ji Ling.
But you're into someone too.
Helping him gather
the Dragon Deity's Power
was a mission from our master.
Really?
Of course.
Ji Ling is innocent and kind.
I do like him.
But right now,
the greater good comes first.
I understand that.
Besides, he's not the Dragon Deity.
It's the Dragon Deity turning evil,
destined to fall.
Ji Ling was just deceived.
He'll understand me.
Wangyan, don't leave me behind again.
I won't.
No matter where,
we'll be together.
Wangyan, why are you so fragrant today?
Do I?
Maybe just the grass damp with night dew.
I'm real.
I don't understand love, nor hate.
I don't think I've ever loved anyone
or hated anyone either.
I guess
- I'm just…
- A woodenhead.
Fine, I'm a woodenhead then.
No, you're not.
Master Dragon Deity.
I…
Master Chi Wen.
Wu Shiguang said
I'm a puppet.
But I'm clearly a fox from South Mountain.
There must be some mistake,
right?
So you found out.
You are indeed a puppet I made.
Not a fox.
No… No way.
It's not true.
I was born on South Mountain,
in a cave by Yumian Lake.
I was a blind fox.
Outside the cave,
there were lots of raspberries
and wood sorrel.
Then, I was hit by falling rocks
and was about to die.
You saved me and healed my eyes.
You even gave me power
and sent me to save people.
I remember all of this.
How could I possibly be…
a puppet?
If I can give you power,
I can also give you memories.
Give me…
memories?
So,
all of it is fake?
You made it all up?
In this world, there never was
a blind fox like me?
No Ji Ling?
Is that true?
Master…
why did you create someone like me…
a puppet?
Are you blaming me?
I granted you life
to experience the human world.
Isn't that a gift?
Being a puppet, controlled,
deceived by my most trusted,
my dearest one…
- You call that a gift?
- Don't be insolent.
Master,
did you create me
just to have a puppet
you could manipulate at will?
Or did you need someone
who could die in your place anytime?
- Does it matter?
- Yes, it matters!
To me, it matters a lot!
Even if I'm a puppet,
I want to know why I exist!
Even as a puppet,
if I can protect you,
then my existence has meaning!
Then I'm not just a piece of wood!
I'm my own unique self!
I am Ji Ling!
I am Ji Ling…
I… I am Ji Ling…
Follow me.
How will I find you?
Don't worry. I will find you.
Still think you're unique?
I always hoped
you could stay innocent forever,
living a carefree life.
You're the piece of my youth, my past,
that I most wanted to keep.
What a pity.