♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my playful charm♪
♪Just to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for you♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 10=
=Love Elope=
=Save the Lis=
(That person sent over Xiaodi's photo,)
(saying Xiaodi is safe.)
(Are they waiting for me to hurt Ye Lang?)
(If I still can't find any clues,)
(could it be...)
We're here.
Where are we?
(This was our home)
(in the previous life.)
What do you think?
Do you like it?
Mm.
This place
has everything I love.
(Because every single thing here)
(was picked by us in our previous life.)
Thank you
for making a home for me,
a home I truly love.
Don't worry.
This is a home just for us.
(Xiaodi.)
(Forgive my selfishness.)
(Wait a bit longer.)
(I promise.)
Ye Lang,
come down for breakfast.
Niannian.
I...
I need a morning kiss.
Otherwise,
I won't have any appetite all day.
Niannian.
Being with you
really makes me happy.
If you want to stay with me forever,
then win over my stomach.
That's perfect.
Then your personal chef
will make my best dish for you.
Give me a hand.
Okay.
Pass me an onion.
Do you want a red onion,
or
a white one?
(1 Notification)
(Li Group's stock
has been falling for three days.)
(It hit the down limit at open.)
(No way out for retail investors.)
Ye Lang.
What was I about to say?
Do you want to go back?
No need.
Nothing matters
more than cooking for you.
(Stay close to Ye Lang.)
(Don't do anything rash.)
(What is he really after?)
(Ye Lang.)
(What should I do?)
Brother.
Come home with me.
Which home?
I know you're still at odds with Father
because of Ms. Jiang.
You've seen the news.
Father was even hospitalized.
Only you can save tomorrow's
shareholders' meeting.
Finished?
Brother. I'll be waiting for you tomorrow.
Ye Lang.
Tomorrow's big show
won't start without you.
Wait here for me.
Mr. Li, let me be blunt.
The stock hit limit-down at open.
Who's going to
cover our losses?
Yeah. Last week, you said
the new smart prosthetics tech was your ace.
So how did it end up
a material at a rival's launch?
Mr. Li always prized the study.
All confidential files
kept in the main residence.
Turns out
you got hit
by our own people.
Everyone,
please stay calm.
The board
will fully investigate
the tech leak.
Give me another three days.
Three days?
Till the stock becomes worthless?
Young Master
was all glory at the engagement party.
What, did love cloud your judgment?
Calm down please.
This has nothing to do with my brother.
There must be a mole.
Nonsense.
Brother,
just tell the truth.
The fingerprint access log only shows you.
Don't forsake family business for that woman.
Our family can't be ruined by you.
Master, please stop.
Young Master was fooled by that woman.
I saw it clearly
Jiang Niannian was sneaking by the study.
Master, please see the truth.
Ye Lang.
How could you
let the wolf into the house!
Father.
Don't get so worked up.
Brother,
I know you're protecting her.
What if she really did that?
I know you clearly draw the line.
You won't cover for her.
Right?
You unfilial son!
Stop!
Why are you here?
Master Li.
It was me who entered
the study.
Ye Lang.
You heard her?
She's a spy
sent by the Ming family!
Dad.
She's not a spy.
I told her to go to the study.
What?
Brother, you're saying
she's not a spy,
then she is the insider?
Ye Lang.
Even if you're my own son,
if you ruin the Li family,
I won't go easy on you.
Mr. Li.
I know what I should do
and what I shouldn't.
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪