How impressive.
They look incredibly sturdy.
That's Lord Van for you.
Thanks to your help,
we finished the ramparts in two weeks.
In so little time?
I know we helped out,
but I'm still shocked at what you can do.
Panamera's "ramparts"
are jutting out the most,
but I'm not foolish enough
to say that out loud.
We'll build more houses as more people
like merchants and adventurers move here.
I'm positively envious of you.
It's been my dream to have my own land.
In the next battle, I'll just have to earn
more glory than money can reward,
and ask for my own patch.
By the way...
What are those things?
Ballistae.
I tried crafting larger versions of
the simple ballistae I'd made before.
You made those, too, Lord Van?
Yes. Top and bottom can fire separately,
so they can loose two bolts in a row.
Khamsin, could you test-fire one for us?
Sure.
Here I go.
Yup, they came out quite well.
EASYGOING TERRITORY DEFENSE
BY THE OPTIMISTIC LORD
EPISODE 6: SLAYING A DANGEROUS
FOREST DRAGON WITH LARGE BALLISTAE
You have ballistae that powerful
atop your ramparts?
Yes, over a hundred of them.
A hundred?!
Name your price. I'll buy one.
I'm sorry, but these aren't for sale.
Then, I'll owe you a favor, Lord Van.
In return, please let me
have one of these ballistae.
I see.
Very well. I'll give you one.
I'll call in that favor later.
You have my gratitude.
How will you transport it?
And what about the bolts to load into it?
It does look rather heavy.
I'll arrange a carriage.
The bolts are made from iron,
so I can craft those on my end.
Lady Panamera.
I think you should take at least
one or two of Lord Van's bolts.
Why?
Take a look at this.
I've never seen a sword that shape before.
Seems like it'd make heavy work
of foes with armor and shields.
Got a sword you don't mind breaking?
This is my spare sword.
If it breaks, so be it,
but this beauty has seen me
through several battles.
I'd be impressed if you
even managed to chip it.
Then, if I may...
There was hardly an impact.
Did he just graze it?
Very impressive.
It has an incredible edge, doesn't it?
Lord Van made it, after all.
What material is that sword made of?
Ordinary iron.
That's impossible.
Wait, you mean those bolts are also...
I made them the same way
I did that sword.
They pierce right through
two or three armored lizards.
Pierce
through
armored lizards?
Lord Van, could I have some bolts
in addition to the ballista?
Of course. Pleasure doing business.
Khamsin, you have my gratitude. Thanks
to you, I'll also have powerful bolts.
I'm happy for you.
Everyone!
Run for your lives!
Ortho?
I'm sorry! We couldn't outrun it!
- A dragon!
- It's huge!
We'll distract it to buy you some time!
Use that to get everyone
back to the village!
They plan to be decoys for us?
But that puts Ortho's party in danger.
Should we fight back here?
But that could endanger the villagers.
I'll aid you.
It's only a matter of time
before it heads this way.
Ortho, this way!
We'll shoot it down with the ballistae!
Got it!
Today, we'll be fighting a forest dragon,
a mid-class dragon with no breath weapon.
Someone escort Lady Arte
back to the village.
The rest of you hurry up onto
the ramparts. I'm right behind you.
Yes, ma'am.
Lady Arte.
I'm sorry for exposing you
to such terrifying danger.
I believe forest dragons
are very powerful foes.
But this time, we have
our enhanced ballistae.
- We have Panamera as well.
- There's no time! Hurry!
We might not be able to slay it,
but we won't be beaten.
R-Right. Good luck.
Till, escort Lady Arte.
Could you also summon Dee
and his men from the village?
Right.
This is
too
scary!
D-Don't close the gate!
We'll be right there!
Flying foes are trouble.
It won't be good
if it reaches the village.
Ready the ballistae!
Be sure not to hit Ortho's party!
Yes, sir!
First, we'll ground it.
Aim for its wings!
Don't worry about me! Just go!
Come on. This way!
Damn it. It's not working!
Tsk. I don't have a choice!
I-It's coming!
Sorry! Thank you!
Damn it! This is desperate now!
Forget about me! All of you, run!
All right! Everyone,
head for the ramparts!
Huh?! Seriously, boss?!
You're the fastest member of our party!
I have faith you'll make it back alive!
Do you
really
mean that?!
Everyone, let's never
forget Kusala's sacrifice!
I'll get you back for this, boss!
Ballistae, once it is within range, fire!
Before it can get a taste of Kusala!
Hey! Are you sure you're not
trying
to be mean, lord?!
We can't hit it. What do we do?
I'm best suited to stopping its advance!
Panamera!
Here comes my first strike!
I figured as much. Being valued
by the count at such a young age
and being made viscountess for
her exploits can only mean one thing.
She's undoubtedly
a top-class elemental mage,
and her aptitude will soon
become very obvious.
Fire Javelin!
Incredible.
It's not down yet.
I grew arrogant after
slaying those armored lizards.
But this...
is on a different level.
Fire all ballistae!
Good. We shot through its wings.
Second volley! Fire all bolts!
It read our second volley?
W-We're saved.
W-We made it back alive somehow.
I-I won't forget how I was treated.
I'm glad to see everyone's safe for now.
But if we stay here, we'll be in danger.
I'd love to retreat to the village, but...
I'll buy you time.
Fire Javelin!
Not good enough?
So that's the true pinnacle of fire magic.
If she wasn't facing a dragon,
that power and versatility
would've been devastating.
Lord Van!
I'll head back first
and prepare to intercept it.
Right. We'll be right behind you.
Everyone! Let's take this chance
to flee to the village!
Yes, sir.
It should've been seriously wounded.
Esparda?
What are you doing? Hurry up and run.
I won't run unless you're with me, too!
That would be troublesome.
Just this once, let me buy some time,
and then I'll head back.
Good.
That should buy us
a fair amount of time.
He just casually dropped
one hell of a line.
That said...
That's
way
too casual.
Don't
walk
away! Run!
Put some effort into it and
I'll get you that red wine you like!
Running is harsh on these old bones,
but I'll do my best.
Lord Van, I'll stay by Sir Esparda's side.
Go on ahead and take charge
of the village's defenses.
Right. Keep Esparda safe.
But the village is quite a distance.
I'm running for all I'm worth,
but it's still so far away.
Ortho's party is almost fit to drop, too.
I need to buy more time
or the forest dragon will be on us again.
Hey, boy!
We're in position!
Panamera!
Mind if I call in that favor right now?
Not at all. So? What am I doing?
When the forest dragon
reaches the ramparts,
use that magic you did earlier
to pin it down!
Then, we'll hit it with a barrage
from the ballistae!
Good plan.
Still, who would've thought my magic
would be used to merely pin down a foe?
Sorry about this! I'll share the dragon
meat with you, so please forgive me!
Very well!
Okay, the meat is on the move.
Ballistae, prepare to fire.
I know it's scary, but be sure
to draw back far enough before firing.
Right.
If I could just buy a little more time...
Leave it to me!
Dee?
Sorry we're late.
Deputy Commander, we can't keep up.
Uh, will you three be okay?
It won't be a problem!
We have the weapons you made, after all!
Esparda! Khamsin! Hurry!
- Retreat!
- Yes, sir!
We've drawn it in close enough.
Panamera!
Right!
Flare Blast!
- Now!
- Fire all ballistae!
We did it.
We won! Let's raise our voices in victory!
Are you all right, Lord Van?
You aren't hurt, are you?
No, I'm fine, thanks to everyone.
Lady Arte. So this is where you were.
Lady Panamera.
Don't worry. I'm unharmed, too.
Thank goodness.
You gave good commands, boy.
Congratulations on slaying a dragon.
We cut it very close, though.
Regular villages would've
been wiped off the map.
Heroes like your butler, Esparda,
and Dee, the man who beheaded that dragon
in one stroke, aren't very common.
I'm proud to call them my friends.
Not to mention, you had those ballistae
with their ridiculous force.
I can't believe they were able
to pierce a dragon's scales.
Still, I'll need to
upgrade them even more.
They need to be capable of
firing ten successive bolts at least.
I feel like you just said
something terrifying.
Well, anyway...
For now, we need to host
a dragon-slaying ceremony.
A ceremony?
The most distinguished in battle
receives the title of "Dragonslayer."
That's Sir Dee.
Huh?
Dee's being made a Dragonslayer?
Today, we have slain the lord
of the forest: a forest dragon.
We are here to honor the deeds
of those who contributed the most.
Now, over to the head of House Cayenne,
Viscountess Panamera Carrera Cayenne.
The forest dragon you slew today would've
wiped most villages and towns off the map,
and most fortress cities
wouldn't have fared much better.
Yet this small village not only survived,
but suffered absolutely no casualties.
Even the total damage was a small portion
of the ramparts and two ballistae.
I will now call out the names
of those who contributed most.
First up is Dee, deputy commander
of House Fertio's Chivalric Order.
He beheaded the forest dragon
in one fell stroke,
dealing the decisive blow in the battle.
Next is the exceptional
elemental mage, Esparda.
Words cannot describe his talent for magic
that let him pin the dragon down.
Last up is House Fertio's fourth son,
Van Nei Fertio.
Yeah!
W-Wow.
His knowledge, decisiveness, and genius
are rare in a boy of eight,
and he has made
unprecedented use of his magic
to greatly strengthen
this village's defenses in a short time.
In the battle with the forest dragon,
he took charge and led our men
to victory as lord of this land.
Lord Van!
I've met people of every status
on my rise from lowly knight.
Yet has there ever been a man like him?
I was born into a long line
of knights in the royal capital.
But when my aptitude
for magic was known,
I was quickly handed to the county
that offered me the best conditions.
My grueling training
made me wish for death,
and I sacrificed sleep to study
in my quest to become a squad commander.
My feats were recognized,
and I was made commander of
the county's chivalric order at 16.
After that, I fought in several battles,
earning enough glory to be made a noble.
His Majesty was delighted
with my success,
so six very short years later,
I was given the title of viscountess.
Then one day, I was summoned
by Count Ferdinatto.
He told me he wished to wed his youngest
daughter to the lord of some remote land.
I-It's been a long time, Father.
This is her.
I see.
Still, wouldn't a letter of introduction
suffice to someone with no title?
In most circumstances, yes.
Well, even if anything happens,
you're only dealing with a young boy.
It won't be an issue.
Understood.
Well, depending on what he's like,
I can just bring her back.
Hey, Lady Arte On Ferdinatto.
I'm Viscountess Panamera
Carrera Cayenne.
Did you hear? If he's talented,
he'll become your fiancé.
But if he's incompetent, I'll reject him
for you, so you don't need to worry.
I-I'm unwanted?
That's why they're forcing me
out of my home, isn't it?
That's not why at all.
I don't know if you know this, but all
of your siblings have fiancés already.
You're the last one.
I hope he's a nice boy.
When I left my parents long ago,
I was filled with anxiety.
So perhaps I projected myself
onto Lady Arte.
But my fears were all for nothing.
After meeting this boy,
the timid Lady Arte began taking
the initiative to push things forward.
This boy is a breath of fresh air
in a way I've never experienced before.
I, Viscountess Panamera Carrera Cayenne,
hereby vow to forge an equal alliance
with Van Nei Ferdinatto.
An alliance?
Up until now, you haven't had any support
from the marquis, correct?
But if you ally yourselves with me,
I can promise you support.
You won't have to worry about Count
Ferdinatto's knights invading, either.
True, if I forge an alliance,
I'll replace enemies with allies.
It'll also help us financially,
so it's a win-win.
You managed to develop this village
in such a short time.
Don't you think you should set
your sights even higher?
Forge an equal alliance with me,
and the nobles of this kingdom will soon
learn that Lord Van is my sworn friend.
So? Will you accept?
With my father cutting me off and
few connections among the nobility,
this is a great opportunity
I may never get again.
Thank you for the offer.
May our friendship hold strong.
NEXT EPISODE: EARNEST MERCHANTS
AND RECEIVING A PROUD TITLE