[Bloom Life]
[2015]
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Uncle Elishir.
Why are you playing Tobok again?
Mom, can't you do something?
What are you holding?
Knucklebones.
They made a pact.
No matter when and where,
whoever fails to take out
his own knucklebone
has to give the other person a sheep.
This game is called Tobok.
Three, two, one.
Both of them keep their knucklebones
with them at all times,
so it's always a tie.
[Episode 5: The Beginning of
a Great Friendship]
Happy Eid al-Adha.
Come celebrate at our house later.
How is it?
Not bad, right?
Let me tell you something.
I deleted
the dating application.
You'd delete
yours too.
It's okay that you've deleted yours.
But don't interfere with me.
Just delete it.
Why?
Young man,
look at the clothes you're wearing.
It looks terrible.
It's a festival.
You need to dress for the occasion.
Adalanti,
bring a Kanawayi shirt.
You're back.
Dad.
Why is Mulading sharpening the knife?
We are distributing mutton
for the festival today.
I asked Mulading to handle it.
How could you let him do it?
Isn't it you and Uncle's work?
Mulading
will become my son-in-law soon.
Of course, he should handle it.
I'm here to return your bag.
I'll transfer the money to you.
No need.
I already ate the pomegranate.
The pomegranate isn't worth much.
I broke your jar,
so I should pay you back.
No need, really.
But
could you do me a favor?
A favor?
What is it?
Do you have a girlfriend?
Can you pretend to be my boyfriend?
Is that okay?
If it's too much trouble,
just forget it.
I...
I can ask someone else.
It's really fine.
I guess I could.
So you agreed?
Okay.
I'm Parhat.
I'm Laili.
Laili.
And this is Ying.
Ying.
How did you do that?
No, I can't.
Uncle.
Hello, Uncle.
Hello.
I brought some stuff.
Happy Eid al-Adha.
Wait.
Adalanti.
Get one more shirt.
Got it.
Shirt?
Hello.
Go, Grandma wants to give
you a red envelope.
Say thank you to Grandma.
Happy Eid al-Adha. Thank you.
Thank you, grandma.
Happy Eid al-Adha!
You have to dance
after receiving money.
How? I don't know how to dance.
Just like this. Come on.
I can't dance.
Follow the rhythm.
Come on.
Yes.
Dance like this.
Follow the rhythm.
You are quite good at it.
I learned it just now.
Quite talented.
The mutton is cooked so well.
Auntie,
let Mulading distribute
the mutton this year.
What do you think?
Let me introduce
my boyfriend, Parhatin.
Hello everyone.
Hello.
Take a seat first.
Hello, grandma.
I picked him up on the road.
Picked him up on the road?
You picked up a boyfriend?
You are quite bold, Little girl.
Parhat.
Adijiang's grandson?
Yes, grandma.
Adijiang is my grandfather.
Good boy. Drink tea and eat some snacks.
Asimjan.
Grandma.
You distribute the mutton
to everyone today.
Okay.
What did grandma say?
Grandma mistook you for Asimjan.
She asked you to distribute the mutton.
Grandma, I'm
Zhou.
Wearing this clothes, you look
exactly like
my Asimjan.
Who is Asimjan?
Laili's elder brother.
He passed away many years ago.
Come, the mutton is ready.
Eat it while it's warm.
Eat it while it's warm, everyone.
Grandma, I will be responsible for
distributing the mutton this year.
Who are you?
Grandma.
How can you touch our family's mutton?
Don't misunderstand.
My mother is old.
Her eyesight is bad.
She mistook him for someone else.
All right.
Come on.
Come on, everyone, eat up.
Have some food.
Happy Eid al-Adha, everyone.
What's up?
I finally got a chance to come back.
Why are you so unhappy?
Am I not welcome?
No.
Minawar.
Why didn't Sadiq come?
I asked him to go to his own home.
And I came to mine.
It doesn't conflict.
I didn't let him follow me.
Nonsense.
Dad.
Everyone is here for the holiday.
Don't scold me.
I'm hungry. Give me something to eat.
Minawar.
Did your mother-in-law not feed you?
How did you get so thin?
Really?
Yes. You're slim now.
That's great.
Then, I won't hide it from everyone.
I have good news for everyone.
I'm going to play Sänäm in the troupe.
Sänäm!
Good!
Laili.
Is this your friend?
He's not my friend.
He's my future husband and my family.
A lady shouldn't say that.
Shame on you!
How am I shameless?
You force me to marry every day.
Now that I've found a boyfriend.
Why are you upset?
Master.
Please don't be angry.
It's fine,
as long as Laili is happy.
Bro.
Sit for a while.
I'll go pour you some more tea.
Mulading.
Sit down.
Laili.
Mulading has been
in our family for ten years.
I raised him like a son.
He is your future husband.
He's not!
And he is not your son.
My brother is long gone.
Batur.
Uncle.
Dad.
Don't go back today.
Just stay here.
No, I still have to go back.
Or my dad won't be able to sleep.
Don't worry.
I'm not really mad at my dad.
I'm just mad at myself.
I often think that,
back then,
if I hadn't
asked my brother to feed the dog,
he wouldn't have been crushed
under the house.
Then,
our family wouldn't have lost hope.
Maybe things wouldn't be like this now.
You think too much.
It's not your fault.
It's not your problem.
I think it is my fault.
No.
Coming.
[Ten years ago]
My Asimjan has grown up too.
Let him distribute
this year's mutton to us.
Laili,
your favorite sheep tail fat
dipped in chili.
My brother loves me the most.
Laili, I gave it a name,
Meat-buns.
Okay, it's chubby.
Let me hold it.
No.
Let me hold it for a while.
Come on, let me hold it for a bit.
Let me hold it.
Fine, here you go.
So cute.
Look, brother.
I made a small bowl for it.
Do you think Dad will
let it into the kiln?
Yes, I believe in you.
Then, you tell Dad to do it.
Slow down.
Goodbye.
Bye.
I'm leaving.
We'll walk you in.
No need.
We'll watch you go in before we leave.
It's fine, I can go by myself.
Let's go.
We're leaving.
Are you
okay?
Actually,
I'm really sorry
for letting you
see this scene.
I don't even know how to face you.
It's fine.
I just came to see how you are.
I'm happy to see you're okay.
Well,
I'll leave first.
Thank you.
No problem.
If this happens again, just call me.
No,
that's not what I meant.
I mean,
if you ever need help,
you can always come to me.
-Bye.
Go inside.
I'm back.
Why are you back so late?
I'm starving to death.
Sadiq, let me tell you,
the troupe leader finally
praised me today.
-She said I…
-Good.
Can you pour me some water?
Sure.
Eat up.
Can we eat less meat?
The calories are too high.
I want some vegetables.
I packed naan with mutton for you.
How is it not nutritious?
Isn't this mutton good?
It has fat and lean.
This onion can be seen as a vegetable too.
Eat up.
I was too tired after work yesterday.
And
there was a pile of unwashed dishes.
You told me to leave them alone for now.
I thought you would wash them.
But those dishes are still
in the kitchen.
Let me ask you a question.
Last month,
I wanted to get a new interior for my car.
Did I ask you to do it for me?
No.
Why?
Because
that's your business.
And I don't know anything about that.
Exactly.
I'm the one who couldn't
stand the old interior,
not you.
So I had to change it myself.
But think about it,
I don't mind leaving dirty dishes
there for two days,
or even piling them up for a week.
When Auntie comes on the weekend,
just let her wash them.
This mutton is pretty good. Have a taste.
What's up now?
Nothing.
What are you doing?
You've been in there for ages.
Wait a minute. I'm not done yet.
Hurry up.
What did you want to tell me?
Come here.
I'm pregnant.
Really?
Laili, come here.
What's wrong?
She's pregnant.
Really?
Would I joke about this?
What are you going to do?
Have the baby.
I didn't know you liked kids so much.
It's not that I like kids.
I just think
getting married is for having kids.
I'd like to have them sooner
rather than later.
Are you ready to be a mother?
Here is what I think.
Nanny, check.
Money, check.
Big house,
check.
No, I didn't mean money.
I mean,
what about Sänäm?
You hit the nail on the head.
About this,
only
you two
and I know.
Do not let anyone else know it.
Sadiq and my mother-in-law
still don't know I'm pregnant.
If she finds out,
she'll react.
Did your mother-in-law
make things difficult for you?
Who could make things
difficult for me?
Let me tell you something.
Last week, I got up at 8 a.m.,
and she hinted that I was lazy
and not diligent.
Then, this week,
I got up at 6 a.m.
and bought breakfast for the whole family,
and she still complained
that food from outside isn't clean.
She advised me to cook myself.
How could she be so harsh?
Guess what time I woke up today?
What time?
4 o'clock? That early?
Before dawn,
I got up for the whole family
to make dough and bake naan.
As expected, she had nothing to say.
Isn't it just playing the role of
a good daughter-in-law?
What's so hard about it?
As long as I want to do it,
there's nothing I can't do.
I have a performance in a month.
Once I put on that baggy costume,
who will be able to tell I'm pregnant?
Cheer up. Have some pistachios.
I'll go clean up first.
She has morning sickness.
Get this.
Come on.
Watch your hair.
Nothing came out.
Why do I feel sick eating this?
-Do you want something sour?
-I'll remove it.
Congratulations.
You're going to be a mother.
Thank you guys.
I'll be the godmother.
We will both be godmothers.
Accompanying Minawar
as she becomes a mother,
I share her fears,
scares,
and nervousness.
I can't imagine
that in the process of becoming a mother,
a woman's body
can house a brand new life.
At the same time,
we are also excited,
joyful,
and looking forward to this new life.
This is truly an adventure
and a journey full of surprises.
I brought some food.
Have a few bites before you go.
What delicious food did you make for me?
Eat some.
Thin-skinned buns.
I made them myself.
You made them?
Try them.
Good for you.
I'll save some
to give to your dad
and trick him into thinking I made them.
I can just make some more for him.
Look at your little tricks.
Mom.
I'm not planning to go back to Shanghai.
You're grown-up now.
Just bear the consequences
of your choice.
I think
I should retire.
When I first came here,
this hospital didn't even have a decent
traditional Chinese medicine doctor.
I built this department from scratch.
Now, it has over a dozen
local doctors.
They can all stand on their own now.
I think I can leave with peace of mind.
Can you bear to leave it?
I also have to consider
how to spend the rest of my life.
That's great.
I'm happy for you.
Mom.
How did you feel
when you were pregnant with me?
What's wrong?
When I was pregnant with you,
it was the busiest time
setting up this department.
I threw up every day
for the first three months.
Really, every single day.
I threw up like crazy.
When it came to the sixth month,
I remember it clearly,
you
finally made peace with me.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Coming to aid Xinjiang while pregnant
gave me a lot of pressure.
At that time, all your grandparents
were against it.
I was thinking
maybe I'd stay for three or four years
to set up this department
and go back once it was on track.
But once I stayed here,
I fell in love with this place.
I couldn't bear to leave.
Besides, seeing you so happy here,
so free,
and so carefree
I strengthened my determination
to stay here.
I should thank you.
Because of you,
I became who I am today.
I should thank you even more.
Let's thank each other.
Is this your cat?
Yes.
How have you been lately?
How could I be?
Pretty good.
Come on, kids.
Eat some apricots.
I just picked them from the orchard.
I was just craving apricots.
Ah, our cat
is usually afraid of strangers.
Come here.
This is my grandpa.
Hello, grandpa.
Hello, child.
Laili, my friend.
Okay.
Let's go.
Go home.
Be a good boy.
This is what I want to mail.
I was going to charge you five yuan,
but I won't charge your family anymore
since you helped me.
Thanks.
By the way, there's something
I came here to tell you.
You don't need to
pretend to be my boyfriend anymore.
Sorry for the trouble last time.
Parhat.
I was just thinking,
if your dad knows you
don't have a boyfriend,
wouldn't he still force you
to marry Mulading?
Then, all the things we did before...
Then...
Then, how about
I trouble you for a bit longer?
It's okay.
What did you...
Have one.
♪ Miss. My lady ♪
♪ Follow me ♪
♪ Play the fiddle and dance ♪
♪ I'll send you home ♪
♪ Since I met you that day ♪
♪ You are always in my mind ♪
♪ Don't throw away ♪
♪ The roses I gave you in a hurry ♪
♪ The roses I gave you ♪
♪ Come on, darling ♪
Three, two, one.
Alright, take a look. How is it?
It looks so beautiful.
It's because you are pretty.
These figs'
cultivation
depends on the saplings.
The older the sapling,
the tastier the figs.
The small ones'
figs aren't sweet.
That young man
knows nothing.
Figs from small saplings
aren't sweet.
I think it's quite sweet.
You're making insinuations.
In recent years,
businessmen
came to Kashgar's old town and left
as they pleased.
A few of them have actually stayed.
Just like the figs
growing on this tree, which fell,
those men left without any hesitation.
Am I right?
Xia Zi.
Look at me.
Smash it.
Smash it into pieces.
Is this edible?
It is. Eat it.
I think Uncle
won't agree so easily.
Don't be so impatient.
I'm not impatient.
I really want to run this homestay well.
I'm doing business on my own.
No one shares the risk with me.
Don't worry.
I will protect this century-old shop well.
It's a win-win situation.
No one loses.
Just like this fig,
we hit it off instantly.
That's not how you smash it.
I will
try to convince my uncle.
But I have one condition.
Within five years,
this homestay cannot be
transferred to anyone else.
This must be written into the contract.
Alright, I agree.
Then I think our new homestay
can keep the carved wooden doors,
and make it a folk culture photo spot.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Let me think about how to tell my uncle.
Come down quickly.
Be careful.
Uncle.
Tell me.
At this moment,
if someone suddenly jumped out
to play Tobok with you,
what would you do?
It's been a long time
since I played this Tobok game.
Besides,
the person who played Tobok with me
is no longer here.
No one knows
that my knucklebone is
in my pocket right now.
But I know that
I,
Xia Hui's daughter,
Xia Zi,
the homestay's goddaughter,
will officially take over
for my dad, Xia Hui,
to play the game of Tobok with you.
Please take out your knucklebone.
My clothes are...
I
have been led astray
by you little kids.
You guys are really something.
Open your hand
and let me see your knucklebone.
If I open my hand,
and you do not have yours,
you will lose to me.
Uncle,
if you lose,
I don't want sheep
or money.
I want you to give me a chance.
Give our homestay a chance.
I know you are experienced at Tobok.
If I let you lose to me so easily,
it would be unfair to you.
Let's do it another day.
Arzugul.
Uncle.
I can't take it anymore.
I need water.
Water.
You've only been buried for a short while.
Can't you take it?
Uncle.
What are you holding?
This is the Tobok game we play.
See this knucklebone?
Arzugul's dad has one,
and I have one.
If I go to him and ask,
"Where is your knucklebone?"
and he can't take it out,
he has to compensate me with a sheep.
If he asks me for them,
and I can't take one out,
I have to give him a sheep.
But nowadays,
these young guys
don't
play this game anymore.
Alright.
I see you can't take it anymore.
After a few more sand therapies,
all your illnesses will be gone.
Come on.
Let's go.
Uncle, what's up?
Slowly.
Let's hurry back.
Come on, take it easy.
It burns.
Uncle, slow down.
I'm fine.
-What did the doctor say?
-So serious?
Why are you in a wheelchair?
The bones are fine.
Just a slight sprain.
Come on, son.
Look how dirty your clothes are.
Let me wash them for you.
Uncle.
Since the bones are fine,
please take out your knucklebone.
Naughty girl.
I'm already in a wheelchair.
Are you still trying
to take advantage of my misfortune?
When you played this game with my Dad,
didn't you always take advantage of him?
I remember one year, there was a flood,
and my mom and I hid in a tree.
You waded across the river to tell him,
"Take out your knucklebone".
Forgot it?
That's how the game is played.
Right.
That's exactly how the game is played.
You knew I changed
clothes in the hospital.
Here.
Zhou.
I'm helping you.
Uncle gave it to me.
You cheated.
I was prepared for this.
Before I went into the hospital,
I gave the knucklebone to Zhou.
Girl.
Now that your Dad is gone,
the game we played
should also come to an end.
I know why
you wanted to play this game with me.
Opportunities
can't be obtained by winning or losing.
Time shows
a person's true colors.
It can just be won by sincerity.
Do you understand?
Do you two
dare to play Tobok one more time?
The only condition is
to keep our inn
and make it
prosperous again.
To the beginning of our great friendship.
Do you need an airport pickup?
Okay, please send me the flight number.
I'll arrange it later.
[Lobby manager]
[Already placed an order]
Look, our family
also has a space like this.
We can dance like this
in that space too.
Right.
This shop is the one I mentioned before.
A room costs 1,500 yuan a night.
There are not many rooms,
but they are almost always fully booked.
Just like ours, it has three floors.
Uncle, look how booming the business is.
Just a little bit of food
costs 89 yuan?
Uncle.
Keep your voice down.
People are mainly paying
for the atmosphere
and the environment.
These few shops
are hard to book during the peak season.
Prices are probably
several or even over ten times ours.
That's normal.
Over ten times?
Yes.
So expensive.
Exactly.
Uncle.
I think if we
renovate our shop too,
it could be this popular as well.
We are living in the new Kashgar now.
That means having both heritage
and innovation.
I'll redesign and renovate
our home.
You don't plan to return to Shanghai?
Yes.
I plan to stay in Kashgar.
No, Xia Zi.
You have to go back to Shanghai.
Maybe it's because
I'm used to constantly chasing after you.
You got into a school in Shanghai,
and I joined the song and dance troupe.
You bought a house,
and I wanted to be the principal dancer.
And now you're telling me
you want to go back to Kashgar?
Are you kidding me?
What can you do here?
Just be Manager Xia forever?
That's a good idea.
Right now,
I think I'm starting to like this feeling.
The grain
and the weeds
grew together.
Grain and weeds?
All right.
Minawar,
you did a good job keeping it secret.
If your mother-in-law hadn't
come to ask for a leave for you today,
how long
were you planning to hide it from us?
I...
Having a baby is a good thing.
What are you afraid of?
I wanted to tell you
after the performance.
That won't work.
Your mother-in-law specially
came to tell us.
We can't be careless.
How about this?
From tomorrow onwards,
work in the dressing room.
The work there is lighter,
which is good for both you and the baby.
Let Gulistan be the leading actress
for the time being.
How did they know you were pregnant?
That's so disrespectful.
Then,
what about
Sänäm?
Gulistan is playing the role.
Why?
They don't know that lately,
I practiced Sänäm
until my feet cramped.
Every day, I longed to be Sänäm on stage.
I am Sänäm.
I have already
embodied Sänäm.
No one is more like Sänäm than me.
Do you want to see me dance?
Yes.