No, no.
To meet the Gold Boys,
who are too busy with their world tour,
I've flown all the way to New York.
Gold Boys, it's great to see you!
- Two, three.
- Hello, we're Gold Boys.
First of all, congratulations.
I heard every show on your world tour
has completely sold out,
and thanks to the overwhelming response,
the tour has even been extended.
Before we dive in, could you say
a few words to your Korean fans, Goldy,
who've been eagerly waiting for Gold Boys?
Everyone.
I hope you're all doing well.
Even when we're not there, I believe
you'll take good care of yourselves.
We're working hard so we can come back
to you as soon as possible.
So until then, make sure you eat well,
don't get sick,
and stay healthy.
- I really miss you guys, Goldys.
- Chicken delivery!
Shall we talk about your new album now?
I heard all the members took part
in writing and composing this time.
- Cheers!
I still have a bit to pack,
and I wanted to grab
some chicken with you.
Anyway, congrats
on deciding to retry the appeal.
What about you?
How's everything? Getting ready?
I'm opening my office soon.
I even printed business cards.
Oh! Let me see.
Ta-da!
Wow.
Drop by the opening.
Maybe help promote it a bit.
You're giving me the drumstick?
That's new.
You've got your own place now,
starting your own business.
- I'm so proud of you.
- Hey!
Your hands are oily.
Stop, enough.
Come on. I'm an adult too.
I can't live off you forever.
Did you know
I've lived here for over five years?
Already?
It was fun.
We bickered all the time,
like friends, like family.
Me too.
Spending time with you,
like friends and family…
I felt really reassured.
You stayed by my side
when things were hard
and took care of me without a word.
That's how I got through it.
And now that you're gone,
I have no one to boss around.
It feels strangely empty.
Right? You must be super bored without me.
Call me anytime.
If you need anything for the retrial,
just call me.
My worth has gone way up, by the way.
Oh, yeah?
I'm a proper detective now.
Ugh, it's warm.
You still drink it warm?
These are all the records
from your father's case.
And these are the contacts
of the people who testified back then.
You kept all this until now?
It's a case that's always weighed on me.
And I knew
you would take it on someday.
I'm just getting started.
You'll do well.
Come on. I know what you're capable of.
Even the Do La-ik case,
everyone said it was impossible,
but you kept pushing
and proved him innocent.
You'll do the same for your father's case.
If you need anything, just tell me.
Sir.
Thank you.
I wouldn't have made it
this far without you.
Come on.
You know,
though I graduated top of my class,
I turned down all those great jobs
and came to your firm. Because--
I know.
Of course I know.
I took care of you
when you were a student,
fed you all the time,
bought you books for the bar exam…
I'm basically your second father,
aren't I?
You really had to spill everything?
I was going to say my part.
Oh, yeah? Did I make it too obvious?
Anyway,
don't act like you're gone for good.
I'm not sending you away.
Finish your father's case
and come right back.
- Okay?
- Yes.
All right.
She became a high-profile lawyer
thanks to the Do La-ik case,
- and now she's taking leave?
- Exactly. When her value is at its peak.
If it were me, I'd open my own office
with my name on the door
and really cash in.
No, no, no.
Absolutely not.
This isn't about money.
A retrial, of all things, a family case!
Bringing hidden truth to light,
restoring justice…
That is the sacred duty of a lawyer!
You seem really happy
about snagging the partner spot
while she's gone.
What? Happy?
No, I meant…
- As a colleague…
- Yeah, sure.
- No, Ye-sol, as a colleague…
Whatever…
Ye-sol, I organized the documents.
Could you stop by my office later?
Yes!
And…
I know I've caused you
some trouble and worry.
Thank you
for understanding.
Did she just thank us?
Never thought I'd live
to hear her say thank you.
THANK YOU FOR PROTECTING LA-IK
I'm here to pick up the documents.
Yes. Here you go.
Do you want some help?
No, I'm finished.
But, Ye-sol.
Thank you for everything.
I would've had
a really hard time without you.
I didn't do anything.
Actually…
there's something
I've been meaning to tell you.
Remember when I once said
I'd explain everything later?
Thank you, Ye-sol.
I'll explain everything to you later.
Yes.
I kept thinking about
how I wasn't honest back then.
And…
The truth is…
I'm also…
- Goldy.
- Sorry?
I'm Goldy, a hardcore Gold Boys fan.
And my favorite is La-ik.
- What?
- I'm really sorry I hid it.
It's not like I meant to…
I thought it'd be a problem
if people knew the lawyer
was a fan of her client.
And I have this rule about keeping
my fangirling secret.
Actually…
I knew.
Well, I couldn't be sure, but…
I had a pretty good idea.
No way.
You may think you hid it perfectly, but…
Here you go.
Even before the Do La-ik case…
Attorney Maeng, you got mail.
Every time La-ik posted a story on SNS,
your alert went off whenever mine did.
GOLDYS - HAVE A GREAT DAY!
And all over your office,
there were purple items,
his signature color.
They say you can't hide
a cough and fangirling.
I just thought,
"Yep, fans are everywhere."
I tried so hard to hide it.
I only knew because I'm Goldy too.
So I was always grateful.
You let me help La-ik from afar,
and because of you,
Gold Boys could come back together.
You know…
For fans,
if our favorite is happy, that's enough.
That's all we ever want.
Is for them to be happy,
wherever they are.
La-ik,
how have you been?
FROM THE FIRST TRIAL
THE PRIME SUSPECT - MR. MAENG
My days have been so hectic lately.
Did their conflict seem serious enough
to become a motive for murder?
Sometimes time flies by so fast,
and other times it moves so slowly
that I can't even see the end of it.
A behind-the-scenes video
of Gold Boys' overseas tour just dropped!
Whenever that happens,
I look at you.
And…
even from far away,
it feels like you're right beside me.
Like your voice
is telling me,
"It's okay. You can do this."
CRIMINAL CASE FILING
PETITION FOR RETRIAL
PETITIONER - MAENG SE-NA
That's what gives me
the strength to get through today…
and the courage to face tomorrow.
I miss you,
La-ik.
WITNESS STATEMENT - HONG HYE-JOO
This case is finally over.
She really held out until the very end.
She didn't say a single word
during the final appeal.
She must've known it too
that a lie can't beat the truth.
Sorry?
- Is this everything related to the case?
- Yes.
Anyway, thanks to you,
her conviction was finalized.
That's worth celebrating, right?
I'm not so sure. It feels a bit lacking.
She was put in a psych facility
because of her mental evaluation.
I think she should've gone to prison.
Well, a win is a win.
How about we go out for a drink?
Should I make a reservation?
Let's do it next time.
I have something important today.
Okay.
Counsel,
please summarize the grounds
for your retrial petition.
Your Honor,
this is a petition for retrial
in the case of the late Maeng Ji-yong,
who received a life sentence
for murder 15 years ago.
The original ruling found him guilty.
However, it has now been revealed
that the key witness,
whose testimony
was central to that conviction,
gave false statements
under the prosecutor's coercion.
And major discrepancies have been found
among the primary pieces of evidence.
These issues undermine the basis
on which the guilty verdict was reached.
Your Honor,
before he passed away,
Mr. Maeng Ji-yong maintained
his innocence
to the very end.
Today, as the petitioner
and as his surviving family,
I stand here to prove
his innocence and to restore his name.
I respectfully ask
the Court to open retrial proceedings,
so that the truth may be established
and the values of justice
and the law may be upheld.
Prosecutor Kwak!
I…
have been reviewing
Attorney Maeng's case for her.
Since it's a murder case,
I need to go through everything carefully.
And, well, I owe her a bit too.
If you look it over properly,
it will really help the case.
But are you okay with this, Prosecutor?
Once the retrial starts,
your father's name
will definitely come up.
Well…
That's something my father has to face.
I mean,
you seem more relaxed these days.
Ever since you caught her
and became a big-name prosecutor
what, did you get
a big promotion or something?
No.
I'm transferring to a regional office.
What?
My mother is in
a nursing facility out there.
Work kept me from visiting her often,
so now I want to stay by her
and live my life a bit.
About back then, I'm sorry.
I thought that was the only way to win.
But in the face of truth,
winning or losing means nothing.
Back then,
I just didn't see it.
In this war-like world,
I thought the only way to survive
was never backing down.
I feel the same.
But…
in the end, we did win.
We caught the real culprit.
Cheers!
So good.
Chug it!
Please look at the camera!
Attorney Maeng, the court
has officially approved the retrial today.
Could you share how you feel?
I'm grateful to have the chance
to set my father's case right
before it's too late.
As an attorney
- and as Mr. Maeng's daughter…
- Let's go.
…I will uncover the truth,
and I intend to prove
that even if justice comes late,
it always returns in the end.
Oh? It's Do La-ik.
- It's Do La-ik!
- Where?
Congratulations.
You can't just show up without calling!
My heart nearly jumped out of my chest!
I wanted to surprise you.
If I'd gotten here a little earlier,
I could've watched the hearing.
But the flight was delayed. Sorry.
But don't you still have tour dates left?
They were canceled
because of local circumstances.
In a way, it worked out.
I got to come here.
Today was such an important day for you.
There were many people and reporters.
You can't just appear like that!
The internet's gonna go crazy.
- Please be careful…
- I missed you.
I missed you so much.
How about you? Didn't you miss me?
Well… I…
Of course, I missed you.
What?
What was that? I couldn't hear you.
I said I missed you!
Get in.
But where are we going?
To say hello.
- Hey!
You!
- Who are you?
- Hands off…
La-ik's private life!
Don't film him.
How dare you point a camera at him?
THE LATE MAENG JI-YONG,
THE LATE PARK SU-HEE
I figured you'd want to see
your parents most right now.
But how did you know about this place?
I asked your old tenant a while back.
Oh, Chung-jae…
It's an honor to finally meet you.
Father, Mother.
I'm sorry for coming so late.
My name is Do La-ik.
Today, Attorney Maeng achieved
something truly remarkable.
I'm sure you saw it.
Please keep watching over her
so she can see this through to the end.
And please don't worry
about your daughter.
I'll stay by her side
and make her happier than anyone.
I'm sorry
for not being there
when things were hardest.
From now on, I'll always be with you.
Let's…
be happy together.
While I was on tour,
everything was nonstop.
But whenever I was alone in my hotel room,
all those old memories
would come back to me one by one.
Do you remember
what you told me back then?
After I was cleared and everyone
started calling, asking me to return,
I told you I was scared
to stand in front of fans again,
and you said that to me.
I like Do La-ik.
See?
I like you, La-ik.
The way you worry
about going back onstage
might hurt your fans,
I like that about you.
And…
I like the La-ik on stage, too.
Because up there,
you look truly free.
So…
for now,
just listen to your heart.
The answer's already in there anyway.
If you hadn't said that back then,
I don't think I could've performed again.
Thank you
for giving me courage.
I should be thanking you.
For finding the courage to sing again.
While preparing for the retrial,
whenever things got too hard
I watched your performances.
Seeing you sing with your whole heart
helped me keep going.
Really?
Sometimes a single line from a song
can comfort you more than anything else.
That's why I'm so glad
that you're singing again.
We're already here.
Yeah, we got here fast.
Go on in first.
I'll go in after you leave, La-ik.
Yeah.
All right.
Sleep well, I'll go.
Good night!
Now I can't leave.
- Let's take a picture.
- Me too!
Wait, Han-gu.
Come on.
One, two, three.
What is this?
I knew it. I knew this would happen.
Ever since I took you guys back,
I haven't had a single break. Look.
LA-IK HEADS STRAIGHT TO SE-NA
Who cares. Everyone already knows.
La-ik is totally in love mode right now.
Right.
Fans love her too.
They call her La-ik's lifesaver.
It's not the fans I'm worried about.
It's the reporters grilling him nonstop.
Don't worry. If they cross the line,
the fans will handle it in the comments.
Seriously, our Goldys are no joke lately.
They even have a privacy protection squad.
If it's not official, they won't show up.
Even if they run into him,
they pretend not to know him.
See?
I just posted on Babble
that I finally had Korean food again
and uploaded a photo of the restaurant.
Look.
No one showed up.
Maybe you're just not as popular anymore.
Anyway,
where the hell is La-ik?
Why hasn't he shown his face?
- What?
- He's probably…
very busy right now.
Oh, no!
- What? What is it?
- Don't talk to me right now, I'm busy!
Wait.
You shoved me aside
and ran out here for this thing?
This thing?
It's a rare chance
to buy the Japan-only merch.
How is that "this thing"?
I can just give you one.
Fans work their butts off to get merch.
Using a personal connection to snag it
without any effort? Unthinkable.
Go stand over there. I need to focus.
Wait a minute.
"Random photocard and limited bonuses may
be omitted for international shipping"?
And they still charge per-item fees?
What kind of nonsense…
PURCHASE PROZY SERVICE
SHIPPING FORWARDING REQUEST
After everything we did last night,
you just… no afterglow? Nothing?
I'll feel the afterglow in a minute.
So you're going to keep acting like this?
Add another.
Ta-da!
INVITATION TICKET
Now you're looking at me.
What is that?
Is it…
We locked in our domestic concert dates.
We wanted to thank the fans.
I set aside some seats
where you can watch comfortably.
Here. You'll come, right?
INVITATION TICKET
Isn't it hilarious?
I offered her merch, an invitation ticket,
but she refused them all.
She said it only feels good
if she earns fan goods on her own.
She's unusual. Right?
Not unusual, special.
See? She likes kimbap so much
that you came all the way here
at dawn to learn how to make it.
I'm going to make it for her from now on.
Because you make the best kimbap in Korea.
And you think
you can just toss this ticket at me
and wipe your hands clean, huh?
No! That one's set aside just for you.
It's a festival, you can sit back
on the grass and enjoy. You have to come.
I don't know. I'm so busy these days.
Maybe I should sell it on Pumpkin Market?
Hey!
Hey, you're hurting my ears.
Fine, I'll go.
I'll see for myself how good
that big voice of yours really is.
If you hit one wrong note,
I'll make you eat goat soup.
Am I doing right?
Just make it roughly.
Come on. It's falling apart
because I made it roughly.
She'll eat it with love.
I'M IN FRONT OF YOUR PLACE
CAN YOU COME OUT FOR A MINUTE?
La-ik!
Se-na!
- What?
- It's insane.
So handsome.
What is this? Why do you look so good?
Anyway,
how did you come out so fast?
I just texted you.
Were you already getting ready?
Did you know I was coming?
No, it's not like that.
- Why did you suddenly come?
- Get in. We're going on a picnic.
I have plans today.
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR GRAND OPENING
It's been a long time.
Yeah.
A very long time.
So I heard you became a detective?
PARK CHUNG-JAE
Can't you tell by looking?
If you have anything you want to dig up,
call me. I'll give you a discount.
I heard you moved out of Se-na's place.
Best news I've heard in a while.
I didn't completely move out.
As you can see,
if there aren't any visitors,
I can always go back.
Stop eating that.
I woke up at dawn to make those
for our picnic today.
So that's why
the sides are all burst open.
But I'm glad that you came back.
Making kimbap at dawn for Se-na,
caring for her,
it's a relief.
I really thought you'd never come back.
You're such a big star now.
Why would I not come back?
That only benefits you.
And for the record,
I was always a big star.
Even so, thank you
for looking after Se-na
when I wasn't here.
And for helping
with my case until the very end.
I didn't do it for you.
It just felt like the last thing
I could do for her.
Do you remember
when I told you she didn't like you?
That she only liked you as a fan,
so don't get the wrong idea?
I remember.
That wasn't true.
I just didn't want to admit it.
I thought I should be the one by her side.
But I was wrong.
It's been you for her
the whole time.
Whether I liked it or not.
- You're here.
- What?
What were you two talking about?
Nothing much.
- Have some kimbap.
- How is it? Is it good?
Of course it is. I made it.
Chung-jae,
you eat too.
Eat up.
Thank you. I'll enjoy it.
How is it?
Come on, we're Gold Boys.
Of course it should be gold. Yellow.
Hey, we still have to consider the TPO.
Let's go with white.
You two never agree.
Just do half and half.
Gold.
White.
Please make it a nice half-and-half.
KANG WOO-SEONG
Sorry it took us so long to come.
We're doing well.
We were terrified
to go onstage without you,
but we finished the whole world tour.
Woo-seong, we put all the songs
you left in the cloud onto the album.
We did good, right?
It's a good thing you found the cloud.
If you hadn't, we might never have heard
Woo-seong's last song.
He should've let us hear it earlier.
It's such a good track.
You know how secretive he was.
Even when he was struggling,
he never said a word.
He was the kind of guy
who let everything out onstage.
Pain or misery,
the moment he stepped onto the stage,
he forgot it all.
Remember our first concert?
Right before going up, he kept saying
he felt like throwing up.
But once he was onstage,
he jumped around the most.
Yeah.
And the moment he got offstage,
he threw up right away.
He really was such an idiot.
It would've been so nice,
if he were still with us.
He is.
When we worked on the album
with his songs,
I kept asking myself,
"What would he have done?"
And it felt like
we were making it with him.
YOUR TIME LIVES ON IN YOUR SONG
As long as we don't forget him,
he will always be with us.
So you remembered
that today is Woo-seong's Memorial Day.
How could I forget?
You look better. It's good to see.
So your concert's coming up?
How's the preparation going?
Well…
- thanks to you.
- Don't say that.
When we left the company,
you handed over the trademark
without asking for anything.
We could come back together.
What could I have done
with that name without you guys?
But…
seeing how well things are going now,
I almost regret letting you go. Maybe
I should've held on tighter back then.
I watched all your tour performances.
You looked free.
It reminded me of when I first met you.
I don't know when it started,
but seeing you become someone
who holds in the pain and forces a smile,
it felt like it was my fault.
It bothered me.
It's all in the past.
And back then, I didn't understand
why things had to be that way.
Now I do.
Running a company…
it's not easy.
Now you get it?
Thank you…
for being the first to acknowledge me
when I was a nobody.
No.
I wasn't the first.
Your mother was.
The moment she saw you singing,
she told me that she's a singer too,
but you were going to become a real one.
She said I should take you
and train you as a singer.
I don't know if it was
about money or something else,
but thanks to your mother,
a guy like me, singing at local clubs,
got to meet someone like you.
Go visit her.
She's probably waiting for you.
Ms. Do Mi-gyeong?
It's you, right?
Please take this.
What is it?
You'll know once you open it.
What,
is it another fine or something?
I'm not taking it.
No! It's not that.
I'm not taking it!
My first case won't be complete
unless you accept it!
What?
Anyway,
how did you even know I was here?
This is what I do for a living.
Anyway! Delivery completed!
What the…
INVITATION TICKET
Gift card charged, done!
Pop-up blocker off.
Server time synced. Perfect.
Please let me succeed!
All right.
LET'S GO TO THE GOLD BOYS' CONCERT!
Now!
YOUR QUEUE NUMBER - 486
486?
486!
Sorry.
Hey, my phone and laptop both kicked out.
Why is the universe doing this to me?
It's okay, Like.
I got in around the 400s.
I'll try to grab two seats.
Would you want to go with me?
YOU'RE IN THE QUEUE DUE TO HIGH TRAFFIC
TWO SEATS
PAYMENT COMPLETED
It's here!
I mean,
they said the item just got to Korea.
How did it arrive already?
The delivery was lightning fast.
Let me see.
Wow!
These look amazing in person.
Good thing they arrived without a scratch!
I walk a path
That's neither warm nor cold
After walking alone for so long
I start to mistake the creeping unease
Sometimes it feels like
It'll never end
And even the broken moments of rest
Were never truly mine
I can't live mindlessly
The way the world wants me to
I'm in front of the ticket booth.
I'm holding a lilac umbrella.
Where are you?
Me too!
I'm carrying the Japan-only Gold Boys bag!
Excuse me,
are you Like?
Ye-sol?
Attorney Maeng?
I knew you were a fan,
but I never imagined you were Like.
And I never dreamed it was you.
I should've guessed when you said
you were going to collect evidence
and sue every single hater.
Come to think of it,
we've never met offline, have we?
Thank you for the ticket.
Wait, back then…
Like,
can I ask you one thing?
Hey! Why'd you disappear?
You even deleted your account!
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
Sorry to bother you out of nowhere,
but about that hidden message you said
was in Woo-seong's song,
can you tell me more about it?
Oh, that?
The one who told me
about the secret in Woo-seong's song!
It wasn't really me.
It was all thanks to you.
Gold Boys were able to come back together
thanks to you.
Looks like the wait time is up.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
When we move into the second song,
smooth the chord transition.
Got it. Just give me the cue
and I'll go right in.
And for the tempo lift in the last chorus,
you take the lead, Jae-hee.
Okay. But if I get too hyped,
I might throw my sticks.
Throw them after playing.
Today, for Woo-seong's share too,
let's fill that stage completely.
All right?
Of course.
Let's make sure no one
feels the empty spot he left.
You ready? Let's go!
Let's go!
Hello, we're Gold Boys!
- I love you, Gold Boys!
No name, fading streets
And something I can't erase
Rises in my mind
World's best Do La-ik!
The ticking hand keeps pressing on me
As if the doors are about to close
I love you, Do La-ik!
A melody I thought I forgot
Circles in my ears again
I'll run to you, even out of breath
Before this night comes to an end
The memories left somewhere behind
Are calling out to me
In the cracks of time
I'll sing the last song
We left behind
- I love you, Gold Boys!
I'll close the torn page now
And let everything rewind to the start
You're still the same
Just like that very first day
Even if you burn bright
Like a flame and disappear
Being you was more than enough
Even out of breath, I'll run to you
Before this night ends
There are days like that.
The memories left somewhere
Days when I dreamed about you.
Are calling out to me
I'll sing the last song
We left behind
And on those days,
I can't help falling
into foolish little fantasies.
In twisted time
When I look at you,
and you look back at me,
even that thought alone
is enough to make me happy.
And then I realize…
none of this is a dream
or a fleeting fantasy.
It's the day we shaped together,
and the tomorrow
we'll keep creating, together.
Idol I.
Subtitle translation by: Soyeon Kim