ظآزJust To Meet You, you fell for meظآز
ظآزJust to meet me, into my trap you fellظآز
ظآزWanna try a breathless love?ظآز
ظآزEvery move hits the heart, close and sureظآز
ظآزJust To Meet You, you love my playful charmظآز
ظآزJust to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for youظآز
ظآزWanna play another brand-new game?ظآز
ظآزLayer by layer, we close the gapظآز
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 12=
=Lang Vanishes &amp; Xiaodi in Peril=
(The same thing happened
in the previous life.)
(You helped me through it.)
(We fought side by side back then.)
(This time,
I planned ahead and fixed it all.)
(I even helped you out of danger.)
(But I still can't tell you the truth.)
You won't even tell me the truth.
How can I trust you?
I did look into you.
I just wanted to know you better.
Know me better?
Niannian.
I know you entered the study
using my print.
No matter what you do,
I'll be with you.
I'll protect you.
If you're hiding something,
you can tell me.
You must feel good,
watching me enter the study.
So you knew everything that night.
You knew I took your print,
and you still played along.
Young Master,
that must've been exhausting.
So everything that night was fake.
The promises you made to me
were all lies too.
Everything I told you was true.
I can wait.
Until you finally trust me.
Okay?
Can I really trust you?
I swear.
Everything I did was to protect you.
Can I treat your wound now?
Alright.
To get your body,
I will make Jiang Xiaodi's surgery
a complete success.
By the way,
tomorrow,
check in advance
the stock of O-type RH-negative blood.
Xiaodi is only fifteen.
I have to keep him alive and well.
Only then
will Niannian trust me.
Contact me in advance.
I won't accept any accidents.
I won't repeat that mistake.
This time
I will change how it ends.
(Behave and Jiang Xiaodi will be fine.)
As long as you behave,
Jiang Xiaodi will be fine.
Nothing comes up.
Still nothing.
I can't trace it!
The sender's IP,
the location in the photo,
I can't find anything at all!
Xiaodi.
I'm such a useless sister.
Who is the one
messing with me?
Come out with me
after breakfast.
Okay?
Any work plans today?
You forgot it?
Today, we're going to
try on wedding dresses.
I already told the media
I'd give you a real wedding.
You forgot it?
Niannian.
You look stunning.
I'll try another.
Niannian.
Mr. Ye, this is the ring
you ordered 3 months ago.
Please sign here.
(3 months earlier.)
(That was when we first met.)
Niannian.
From the moment I first saw you,
I swore
I'd give you a perfect wedding.
I'll never forget
your ring size.
(Previous Life)
Sleeping that soundly?
ظآزWhen I come back once againظآز
ظآزI'd still walk toward youظآز
ظآزLetting go of all calculationsظآز
ظآزJust to melt your frozen heartظآز
ظآزI can see hesitation in your eyesظآز
ظآزI pretend I cannot seeظآز
ظآزYet somehow we meet againظآز
ظآزAnd somehow it's still youظآز
ظآزDon't let me goظآز
ظآزLet me look into your eyesظآز
ظآزEven if it takes all my courage and luckظآز
(Proposal Plan Ring Size)
ظآزIt's the meaning of my rebirthظآز
ظآزTurn past pain into proof I love youظآز
Once the ring is done,
I'll make sure you say yes.
(Jiang Niannian.)
(I still remember)
(you held a knife at our wedding.)
(I should hate you,)
(but my heart still beats for you.)
(This life,)
(I dodged every scheme)
(and bet everything I had.)
(Could you...)
Niannian.
Will you marry me?
(Ye Lang.)
(What are you hiding from me?)
(Right now, are you)
(being sincere?)
(Will we really be happy?)
ظآزI'll take you to see more viewsظآز
ظآزAnd leave the mark of my loveظآز
ظآزThe only answerظآز
ظآزIs your nameظآز
ظآزDon't let me goظآز
ظآزLet me look into your eyesظآز
(This time, even if)
(it costs me everything...)
Trust me.
We'll be happy, I promise.
ظآزIt's the meaning of my rebirthظآز
(I'll find who kidnapped Xiaodi.)
(Ye Lang.)
(I want to protect you too.)
(I don't want either of you hurt.)
ظآزLet me look into your eyesظآز
ظآزShape unknown roads into your journeyظآز
Mr. Ye,
we've received
a new batch of couture gowns.
They'll fit Ms. Jiang even better.
Would you like to try them?
Try them all.
My bride
deserves the finest wedding dress.
I wasn't honest from the start.
I approached Ye Lang
at first for money.
Later,
I wanted to use the Li family's ties
to find Xiaodi.
But Ye Lang not only protected me,
he kept telling me he loved me.
That was when
I realized true love can melt it all.
I've been married so many times.
This is the one I want most.
I originally thought
once I found Xiaodi,
I'd take him back to China,
mom's hometown.
But this time,
I actually wanted to stay for Ye Lang.
I hated that he kept it from me,
but,
I love him too.
If I forget all
and follow my heart
selfishly for once,
I'd choose him.
I want to marry him.
I only want this moment.
Ye Lang.
I got close to you
for a reason.
My brother, Jiang Xiaodi
was kidnapped, and now he's missing.
At first,
I wanted to use the Li family's ties
to find Xiaodi.
So I approached you.
But later, I realized
someone in the Li family threatened me.
He told me to hurt you.
I didn't want to hurt you.
So,
I want to tell you the truth.
I want us to face this together.
Once I find Xiaodi,
I won't leave again.
I'll go with you
back to the seaside villa,
and live
a simple
happy life together.
Ye Lang!
I wanna tell you something.
Ye Lang.
Ye Lang?
Ms. Jiang,
Mr. Ye had an urgent matter
and has already left.
Please wait for his call.
(Zheng Lu)
Hello?
Speak.
Xiaodi's in danger. Come now.
Okay.
I'm on my way.
Pack up everything she tried on
and all the sample dresses in storage.
Okay.
One more thing.
Tell her I had to leave.
Ask her to wait for my call.
Mm.
I'll wait for him.
Please have some water.
Thank you.
Hey, I'll be there in ten minutes.
I've unlocked access
to all blood banks in Li's hospitals.
Check if any
can be transferred.
Jiang Xiaodi's surgery
must succeed.
(Is this fate)
(really impossible to change?)
ظآزStitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red duskظآز
ظآزYou return reborn,
seeing through all my cracksظآز
ظآزThis tenderness, a trap or a gift?ظآز
ظآزStill, I'd wager my next life on itظآز
ظآزJust for a moment to recognize you againظآز
ظآزYou are the blazing light in my despairظآز
ظآزLighting the edges of my frozen wingsظآز
ظآزI burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fireظآز
ظآزBreaking free
from dead vines in the ashesظآز
ظآزYou are the brightest star in the nightظآز
ظآزAwakening my dormant fateظآز
ظآزFreeing me from this half-life prisonظآز
ظآزAs the bells shatter the pastظآز
ظآزLife finds its way againظآز