MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
YOON SONG-JEONG PSYCHIATRIC CLINIC
Oh, you're from the States.
I studied in the States.
I can never get used
to psychiatric clinics.
You must've been to quite a few.
Right? But don't worry.
I'll be nice and gentle.
Okay, then. Shall we begin?
What's your occupation?
If you don't mind my asking,
what do you do for a living?
I had this superior at work.
He was competent and sociable.
But then...
What are you going to do now?
Please give me a little more time.
Listen.
Does time appear out of nowhere
just because you ask for it?
Must be nice having it so easy.
Listen carefully.
It's all about the results.
Yes, sir. I apologize.
ANGELA SENT YOU A MESSAGE
YOU GUYS READY FOR TONIGHT'S PARTY?
YES, I'M TOO READY
You can go.
I'll excuse myself.
Yes, it's considered a blessing
to meet a good superior.
You must've been very lucky, right?
But he looked down on me.
- So...
- Yes, so?
Freaking bastard.
He doesn't even work hard.
I killed him.
What?
I keep imagining myself killing him.
Yes, that happens.
You could imagine such things.
You must've been
under extreme pressure.
That's not quite it.
That superior...
He's a bit on the disgusting side.
Now I work for someone else.
It's a bit boring, but not bad.
You can make a killing.
Let me pour you a drink.
Hang on. That's too weak.
You need a splash of this.
Drink it up.
- Let me pour you some.
- No, I'm taking Chinese medicine.
Now, link arms and drink together.
Drink it all, and you'll become rich.
Okay, bottoms up.
It's a long-standing drinking custom.
That's it. Good for you.
Now let's go make money.
Are you all right?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- Have a bite.
Your new superior at work.
You like him, then?
Can I assume so?
He's an idiot.
But forget about that.
Something has been on my mind lately.
Something's on your mind?
- There's this client of mine.
- Okay.
He's just some middle-aged guy.
Do you remember my brother-in-law?
A man named Kim Gyun.
If anything,
I need 30 billion won for his sake.
What do you say?
Let's sign the deal quietly
for 30 billion won.
Doctor.
How would you feel
if a friend betrayed you?
Well...
Don't you think I can just kill them?
Well, killing them would be a bit...
That's a bit too...
The friend slept with his wife.
And kidnapped his daughter.
That was a bit too much.
It was.
Sometimes I get it,
but other times I don't.
How will you escape this time?
Keep talking nonsense, you idiot.
Is that why he's on your mind?
My dad died when I was young.
When I look at that man
- I'm reminded of him.
- "Him?"
My dad.
I see.
You seem to have a father complex.
I think that's what it is.
If you don't mind explaining
can you tell me
about your relationship
with your father?
I killed him.
In front of my mom.
Like this, with a knife.
I cut his throat.
You imagined doing that?
Yes, that happens.
That's the truth.
It was self-defense.
He was a violent abuser.
That's why.
He did this.
He strangled me.
It hurt so bad
and I couldn't breathe.
I thought I'd die.
Does that
still make me the bad person?
Why are you taking it so seriously?
I was just saying it.
LICENSED PSYCHIATRIST YOON SONG-JEONG
You own this building, don't you?
Let's end the session for today.
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
EPISODE 11
SENIOR ATTORNEY
I hope we get along.
Let's begin.
Why were you at Se-yoon Building?
At the time, my client...
The building was on fire,
as you know.
I wanted to save lives.
That's why I went inside.
Wasn't it to take lives?
That comment is a bit out of line.
Why would I kill anyone?
I risked my life to go in there.
To me, it looks like
you killed Jang Dong-chul.
No, no way.
Who, me?
How do you know Gi Su-jong?
Did he hire you?
A text he sent around that time
said "save us."
Mr. Gi and I met through business.
We grew close in the process.
"Save us."
So I went to help.
We should save others.
She's barking up
the wrong tree again.
What's her problem?
Do you remember
the man you were with?
The man you shot with your gun?
Yes.
How do you know him?
He's a coworker.
We went in together to help people.
But...
You...
You shot your gun and...
My coworker...
My coworker almost died.
You two threatened an officer.
I've had enough of this.
Not only did you shoot
an innocent man
but you're trying to blame my client?
I assure you that I will sue you.
I'm the one who was at the scene.
Excuse me.
Let's all calm down.
You, come with me.
Come on. Right now.
Detective.
Were you hurt in any way?
It's normal to panic in a fire.
I'll let you off this time.
That's enough. We're out of here.
Come with me.
Leave.
What if they actually sue you?
She's a US citizen.
Must you make things worse?
- Sergeant.
- And?
Who told you to fire your weapon?
How many times is this now?
I don't care anymore.
I can't defend you this time.
Ju-ran.
Gi Su-jong's wife
and daughter are here.
Da-rae.
I just need your witness statement,
so don't worry.
Be honest.
Just tell me what you know.
Can you tell me
how you got kidnapped?
Da-rae.
Can you manage?
It's not too hard.
You just have to tell the truth.
That's you, isn't it?
Yi-gyeong admitted to kidnapping you.
She also said
you know everything.
Can you write down
everything you know?
PERSONAL DETAILS
NAME: GI DA-RAE
VCU TEAM 1
"It's not true that Yi-gyeong
kidnapped me."
Ju-ran.
We got Jeon Yi-gyeong's
bank transactions.
TRANSFER TO LOAN HEAVEN
She sent a lot over time.
It was likely a hit request.
Did you find her phone?
No.
Oh, and that Real Capital woman.
We let her go.
Her lawyer threatened to sue us.
What the heck?
That brat.
She has such a temper.
Bo-ram.
Calm her down
and go check the redevelopment site.
The site where they found ruins.
Why should we go there?
They found a dead body.
- Cause of death yet unknown.
- What?
Okay.
How's your ear?
It's fine.
Tteokbokki asked for you.
To clean up Jang Hee-ju's mess.
The body.
- Did they find it?
- Yes.
I took care
of the surveillance footage.
And the thing I asked for?
It wasn't as hard to get
as I thought.
It's an improvised gun,
so it should be used at close range.
I like that.
Why do you like that?
There's no way I can miss
at point-blank range.
Yes, right.
One more thing.
Jonah.
The head office
is putting pressure on us.
We should start wrapping things up.
- Are you worried?
- Well...
I don't mind where and when I die.
But you...
Thanks a lot.
Hello, thank you for your work.
Do murders always crop up
this many at a time?
I've seen enough bodies
to last me a lifetime.
She didn't die here.
Someone brought her here.
For us to find.
What?
And the realtor's office footage?
We have it. Will you take a look?
It's Gi Su-jong.
What is he doing here?
Isn't this Kim Seon?
The seaweed soup is delicious.
Is it someone's birthday?
Why did you cook seaweed soup?
It's not only for birthdays.
You were discharged just yesterday.
I made abalone seaweed soup
so you'd recover quicker.
It's so good.
Da-rae, do you want another abalone?
This one?
You don't want it?
(What will happen to Yi-gyeong now?)
Mom and Dad will make sure
nothing happens to her.
We'll take responsibility.
(I haven't forgiven you.)
(I have my eyes on you,
so keep your word.)
(I thought you were good people.)
(Don't disappoint me again.)
We won't disappoint you.
Da-rae.
You too.
From now on, if you have any concerns
could you talk
to Mom and Dad first?
Okay?
Da-rae, let's eat.
Isn't the soup just amazing?
Oh, right. After this
I'll drop by Se-yoon Building.
There's a lot to deal with
after the fire.
Are you going to look for
Yi-gyeong's phone?
Yes, we'll both get arrested
the moment someone finds it.
I don't think the police have it.
I don't mean anything else.
We need to avoid arrest
if we're to look after Yi-gyeong.
I'll come with you.
No, I'll go on my own.
We can't get you involved.
You care about that now?
See you later.
Are you all right?
No.
I'm not okay.
Let's go downstairs.
It seems like the phone isn't here.
We searched everywhere,
but it's nowhere to be found.
Do you think the police found it?
Let's hope not.
Darn it.
I actually had divorce counseling.
To leave you.
Out of the blue?
Were you serious?
I was serious.
Ever since you bought this property,
it felt like...
As Da-rae got older,
there was more and more to do
and I had to do it all alone.
You were busy being a landlord
and didn't care about Da-rae or me.
I guess
I told myself I'd hang on only until
Da-rae was admitted to college.
Why would you say
something like that?
Come on.
That's how most people live.
You're just saying that, aren't you?
No, I'm not just saying it.
No way.
You were both down here.
I'm glad the damage isn't severe.
Yes, we're lucky it wasn't any worse.
What brings you here?
I wanted to ask you something.
If it's about the fire,
we have nothing else to say.
It's not about that.
You know Jang Hee-ju, don't you?
Yes.
You were with her at her office
all through the night.
Yes, that's right.
What did you two do?
We talked about the redevelopment
and had a couple of drinks.
And then?
And then I fell asleep
because I drank too much.
You came by the next day
to get me, didn't you?
Yes, I did. I...
We left together and went back home.
Yes.
You left in Jang Hee-ju's car.
That's right.
She dropped us off at our place.
We tracked her movements
on the traffic cameras.
You were carried inside.
Yes, that's right.
I have narcolepsy.
- Narcolepsy?
- Well...
My wife has that kind of condition.
Yes, I do.
It usually happens
when I'm under a lot of stress.
With the redevelopment
and Da-rae's university admission
- she has been overworked.
- Yes.
If you fell asleep
how do you know you were driven home?
You told me what happened later.
Yes.
We owe Hee-ju a lot.
Yes, right, Hee-ju.
- We owe her.
- She did us a favor.
Did she say she was going anywhere?
She probably went
to the construction site.
That project is the only thing
on her mind these days.
VCU YOON BO-RAM
We tracked the car's movements.
Jang Hee-ju drove to
Gi Su-jong's home
then went straight
to the redevelopment site.
We're still looking into why.
Okay, thanks.
Is there anything else to note?
No, that's it. But...
May I ask what this is about?
Jang Hee-ju was found dead.
I can't say more
since it's an open case
but it's likely she was murdered.
What?
Why... How come...
How did something like that happen?
I told you before.
I don't think Gyun died
in a simple hit-and-run.
Give me a call
if anything comes to mind.
Darn it.
Seon, wasn't narcolepsy
a bit too much?
What else should I have said?
Lots of people suffer from it now.
Since she mentioned Gyun...
Hang on. Who's this?
Why is Deputy Nam calling?
Sorry. Hello, Deputy Nam?
Hello, partner.
We need to meet pretty urgently.
What would this be about?
You know Jang Hee-ju, don't you?
We need to talk about her.
You seem to be in trouble.
What do you mean by that?
That's enough talk from you.
Come to where I am.
I'll text you the address.
And don't tell anyone
where you're going.
I'm doing what I can to protect you.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
Okay, see you.
Why? What's going on?
Deputy Nam wants to see me.
I won't be long, Seon.
Six, four, five, eight...
- Did you find the car?
- Not yet.
Did you get anything from Gi Su-jong?
I think he's lying,
but I'm not sure yet.
Six, four, five, eight.
Ju-ran.
- I think I found it.
- What?
Six, four, five...
Six, four, five, eight.
Yoon Bo-ram.
- Thanks.
- Get the memory card first.
Got it.
IEUM BUILDING
YOON SONG-JEONG PSYCHIATRIC CLINIC
DEPUTY NAM SANG-HO
YONGDAEMUN-GU SEJEONG-RO 338
IEUM BUILDING
YOON SONG-JEONG PSYCHIATRIC CLINIC
You made it.
Isn't it a bit creepy
even in broad daylight?
I travel a lot on government business
and most redevelopment sites
look like this.
There is a brief moment
in that gloomy, damp, desolate state.
You need to overcome those times
to welcome brighter days.
Come and sit down.
Read this.
What is this?
Something interesting.
I wrote it myself.
Go on. Read it.
"I confess my crime.
I argued with Jang Hee-ju
over a business disagreement
and unintentionally killed her,
then got rid of her body.
I apologize for causing unrest.
I'm too ashamed to face my family.
I have nowhere to run or hide,
so I'll end it all here and now.
I take full responsibility
for my actions."
What is this?
That's it.
Your suicide note.
Isn't it clean and concise?
Void of emotion.
Stamp your thumbprint at the bottom.
It's Jang Hee-ju.
She turned off the dashcam?
Why is that?
Play a file from the day before.
It's Hee-ju and Su-jong.
Wait.
This guy...
It's Deputy Nam Sang-ho.
She's ignoring my calls?
M&amp;A REALTORS
COUNSELING OFFICE
You crazy...
I caught you red-handed.
Were you trying to steal the deal
from under my nose?
Is that it?
Be quiet. Let's talk outside.
Let's go. Let's take it outside.
What's going on?
Did you ignore my calls
to hook up with that punk?
Hook up? What are you saying?
Come on.
You don't get to call me out,
Mr. Married Man.
You once said
you liked your men married.
What did you say again?
You said they were more chill
and never clingy.
That's just something I say.
I had to scrape together
something nice to say about you.
Don't you have any shame?
I'm a mess, but you're no better.
Why do you care
if I see another man or not?
You're not doing this
because you like that punk.
You're trying to take his shares.
No?
It's because you didn't give me
what you promised, Mr. Nam Sang-ho.
I did my portion of work
so I need to take
what's rightfully mine.
I said I'd give it to you
in good time.
Why won't you believe what I say?
We're almost done,
so give me a little more time.
I promise you.
No, forget it.
You've broken promises before.
I don't need it.
I'll take care of my share.
You know
I could take you down in one go
if I set my mind to it, right?
Corruption and infidelity.
Should I spill it to someone?
A congressman?
Your wife?
Before I decide to rat you out
go home already.
Do you seriously mean that?
Do you?
I... I even got
some tteokbokki to eat with you.
What is this?
What the heck? We aren't kids.
This is why you've been nothing
but a lackey to those at the top.
Do you think you're somebody?
Know yourself.
Hey, Sang-ho.
Let me give you some pocket money.
Take this and go play with your wife.
Oh, right.
Didn't you say your wife
was never satisfied with you?
To be honest
I felt the same way.
What a pity, Sang-ho.
Hee-ju.
Hey, Jang Hee-ju. Wake up.
Hey, it's me.
I need you to come here right now.
So you killed Hee-ju, Mr. Nam.
Is that so?
So why did she get greedy
and try to take a share?
She should've taken
whatever I offered her.
But you know what?
She had a nice ending.
She reflected on her sins
and took her own life
at the redevelopment site.
What are you doing?
How do you feel right now?
What?
Any words you wish
to relay to your family?
Nothing?
I guess not.
I was really going to pass it on.
Are you really going to shoot that?
Darn it!
Are you crazy?
Why are you doing this to me?
What now?
What?
What should I do
with this tteokbokki punk?
Kill him or not?
Wait, Mr. Gi.
Su-jong. My brother.
I really... We were good partners.
We can make a fortune very soon.
Why are you doing this?
Let's work it out.
Su-jong.
I'm really sorry. I beg you.
Just let me live.
If you let me live
I'll admit to killing Hee-ju.
And if you kill me now
you won't have any evidence!
That means our business
is going to fall through!
Right?
What do you mean there's no evidence?
There is.
You said you deleted the footage.
I kept the parts that I could use.
DELETE 1 FILE?
DELETING
What?
It looks like
Nam Sang-ho is the culprit.
Put out an APB on him
and track him down.
Okay.
If you kill me like this
do you really think
your headquarters will stay quiet?
Get this away from me.
If you stop now
I'll put in a good word for you
at Real Capital.
But I didn't kill you.
You took your own life.
Why are you doing this to me?
I don't know.
If I had to label it,
it's a power trip.
Wait, what?
You're now the one in power.
So?
Have you decided?
Get your revenge.
Su-jong.
Let him live.
- What?
- You know.
Let the law take its course.
In that course, you're going to die.
I'll take care of that myself
so let the law handle him.
You're so boring.
You really are such an odd man.
My mistake.
I don't think Gyun died
in a simple hit-and-run.
I bet you didn't know this.
Su-jong has something to do
with Gyun's death.
KIM GYUN
Gyun's birthday.
Zero, three, one, four.
ENTER PASSWORD TO UNLOCK DRIVE
WRONG PASSWORD
Mom's death anniversary.
Zero, six, three, zero.
WRONG PASSWORD
Da-rae's birthday.
It worked.
SEJEONG-RO REDEVELOPMENT
YONGDAEMUN POLICE STATION VCU TEAM 2
SLUSH FUND
REAL CAPITAL
DEPUTY NAM'S SLUSH FUND HISTORY
DEPUTY NAM SANG-HO'S
SLUSH FUND RECORDS
SEJEONG-RO REDEVELOPMENT
SLUSH FUND HISTORY
CONSULTATION FEE
FOR YONGDAEMUN POLICE STATION
NOUVEAU CITY CORPORATION
STOCKHOLDERS' LIST
SEJEONG-RO REDEVELOPMENT ZONE
BUILDING OWNER LIST
COMMERCIAL PROPERTY SALES AGREEMENT
SE-YOON BUILDING
GI SU-JONG'S FAMILY INFORMATION
POLICE OFFICER PERSONNEL INFORMATION
NAME: KIM GYUN
Da-rae.
(Where have you been?)
(Did you and Dad
do something wrong again?)
No.
I told you, didn't I?
If there are any wrongdoings
I'll set things right.
(Remember what I said last time?)
Yes.
(I didn't mean that.)
(What I said was too harsh.)
Da-rae.
(I need to go out for a moment.)
Okay.
KIM GYUN
LAST WILL
Hey.
Are you going to kill me, too?
I'm not a serial killer.
After all I did to help,
you're treating me like a psychopath.
That hurts.
Do you call this helping?
All we have to do now
is continue doing our business.
We should make 30 billion won.
So?
What's your plan?
What do you think?
We have to handle it.
Handle what now?
You know.
Who's that at Pyeongbukgwan?
- Jeon Yi-gyeong.
- Yes.
Ms. Jeon Yi-gyeong.
We can easily obtain Pyeongbukgwan
without that woman.
Is your idea of handling a situation
killing someone off?
Let's not do that.
I'll handle Jeon Yi-gyeong
in my own way.
Don't lay a hand on her.
What are you saying?
You asked for help, and I helped.
Mister.
Just sit still.
And do as I say.
Let things take their course.
Okay?
- All done cleaning up?
- Yes.
Should we go?
See you around.
We've met every now and then,
haven't we?
We never had a proper conversation.
You must feel distressed right now.
Why did you come here?
HAVE YOU MET WITH YI-GYEONG?
HOW'S SHE DOING?
Yes, and she's recovering.
But the problem is what's inside,
not the outside.
Even the hospital can't heal
the wounds of her heart.
She wants to see you.
And she's sorry
for what she did to you.
That won't bring peace to your heart.
It'll end up hurting more people.
Yi-gyeong should
overcome this by herself.
She can't hurt others
just because she's hurt.
THEN WHAT ABOUT YI-GYEONG?
HOW CAN I MAKE HER FEEL BETTER?
In good time.
There will come a time
when you can share
everything with her.
WHEN? WHAT IF IT'S TOO LATE?
We should do our best
not to let that happen.
SO WHY DID YOU COME HERE, SIR?
I came to find something.
But I don't think that's necessary.
Did you find my phone?
That's where all the evidence is.
Why can't the police find it?
Why can't anyone?
Did someone take it?
You're good at handling these things.
You were in this line of work
with my mom long ago, right?
Yi-gyeong.
You won't be freed
just by finding your phone.
At the very least
I can bring Su-jong and Seon down.
Is that what you want?
Do you have to ask?
Why do you think
I ended up in this mess?
And whose side are you on?
Your visit is over.
All right.
I'll do my best to find out.
You should.
If you had gone with my mom
she wouldn't have suffered like that.
THE LATE KIM GYUN
Hello?
Where are you?
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
I had to do something. What's up?
Mr. Nam was the culprit.
That man, Nam Sang-ho?
Yes, he killed Hee-ju
and tried to frame me.
Do you remember
what Hwal-sung said back then?
So where's Nam Sang-ho?
Are you with anybody?
No one's around.
He's dead.
- What?
- The Real Capital jerks are no joke.
They've gone completely insane.
It looks like they're controlling
everything from the back.
I'm here to meet Yi-gyeong
and it looks like those jerks
will do something to her as well.
Call Da-rae and go home early.
Make sure you lock the door.
Wait, what about Gyun?
Did she kill him?
Yes, it looks like it.
And you knew that?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm sorry.
I thought it'd be bad
for you to know.
You're always like this.
You should've told me
from the very beginning!
I'm sorry.
I'm hanging up.
MY LOVING DAUGHTER
Where are you?
It's late, so come home quickly.
I'M ALMOST HOME
I'll be there soon, so stay home.
And lock the door.
THE LATE KIM GYUN
So what happened here?
A report came in,
and the officer arrived to find this.
He died while we were checking
the dashcam footage.
Everything is laid out.
An improvised gun used
to kill himself and his last will.
Wait a second.
If he killed Jang Hee-ju that night
then who is the woman
seen in the footage the next day?
She walked out
with the landlord couple.
Who do you think?
What?
The lady of Se-yoon Building?
But why would she do that?
KIM SEON
Hello, this is Koh Ju-ran
from Yongdaemun Police Station.
I'd like to see you right now.
That sounds great.
I've got a lot of questions as well.
Excuse me.
You're not allowed in.
Let me check if she's okay.
It won't take long.
Visiting hours are over.
Is Yi-gyeong really okay in there?
Who are you?
Her family.
What's your relationship with her?
Well, we're like family.
Just a moment.
Visiting hours are over,
so come again tomorrow.
She was sedated and fell asleep.
Are you saying
someone is after her life?
Yes.
Those guys are monsters.
But the police are guarding her.
That's true.
But I have a bad feeling
about this place.
Yi-gyeong claims you abducted her.
If you're that worried
you can guard her yourself.
I'm exhausted
after staying here for a few days.
I need to get some rest tonight.
Okay.
MORGUE
I didn't think I'd miss Gyun so much.
He was a rather curt man.
I guess he was different
with his sister.
No.
He only hung out with Su-jong.
All we ever did was bicker.
I should've been good
while he was here.
I hate this cliché kind of regret.
We caught the culprit
who killed Jang Hee-ju.
But we're still left
with a suspicious situation.
I know we've been
putting you through a lot.
The police often work in vain.
But the culprit is eventually caught.
That's always the case with crime.
Gyun was the one who told me this.
DEBT TRANSFER AGREEMENT
ASSIGNEE
REAL CAPITAL &amp; GLOBAL PARTNERS
How did you find this?
I found his flash drive
at Real Capital's office.
It was locked,
so I didn't know what was inside.
But I found out that the password
was Da-rae's birthday.
Those are ledgers
of Real Capital's corruption
and evidence of their crimes.
DEPUTY NAM SANG-HO'S
SLUSH FUND RECORDS
Where's the flash drive?
And I don't know who it is
but the ledger includes
a police officer.
Someone in Yongdaemun Police Station.
One of my colleagues?
I'm handing it over because it's you.
Gyun always had
a keen sense of people.
I'll hold onto the flash drive
until you find out
the colluders on the inside.
Also, I'm not completely sure
but the staff members of Real Capital
are also involved
in murders and blackmail.
It seems Gyun was one of the victims.
I'll use these files
to reinvestigate.
But this isn't enough.
They'll do whatever it takes
to evade responsibility.
And you may face danger
in the process.
So just in case, be careful.
I will.
You too.
SLUSH FUND HISTORY
CONSULTATION FEE
FOR YONGDAEMUN POLICE STATION
Hello? Can you look something up?
Nara Bank,
account number 3659-453151.
CONSULTATION FEE
FOR YONGDAEMUN POLICE STATION
Call me as soon as you find out
who the account holder is.
You should go home and sleep.
You're right on time.
- Great work.
- Yes, have a good one.
How may I help you?
What's going on?
Is that you, Su-jong?
Yes.
EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER
Hang in there, Yi-gyeong.
Please get in.
- Wait!
- What are you doing?
ENTERTAINMENT EXPENSES
FOR YONGDAEMUN POLICE STATION
EXPENSES RELATED
TO YONGDAEMUN POLICE STATION
Hey.
What?
Yi-gyeong is gone?
This is driving me insane.
Okay, I'm on my way.
Hey.
What are you doing here so late?
Sergeant.
You haven't left?
Yes, and I heard from Detective Yoon
that you met Gyun's older sister.
She had something to report.
Oh, is that it?
Right.
It's not a big deal.
What is it? Is it something good?
I told you. It's not a big deal.
I'll tell you once I'm sure of it.
All right.
THIS ACCOUNT BELONGS
TO SERGEANT GEUM AT YONGDAEMUN VCU
I told you to stop snooping around.
KIM GYUN
Kim Seon.
Da-rae's asleep.
Oh, right.
She's unable to hear.
I heard you met a police officer.
So?
Did you get your justice?
I'm here to take what is mine.
Where is it?
I can take it today, right?
GI SU-JONG
SEON
Hey, Seon. What's up?
Hand it over. Hand over your phone.
- Why...
- Give it to me.
Goodness, Gi Su-jong.
What's going on?
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
- Da-rae!
- Can you give up on the property?
For our family
can you give up everything
and choose us?
In the event of divorce,
your wife gets part of your share.
The problem was Kim Seon,
not Jeon Yi-gyeong.
I told you to stop snooping around.
You're beyond help.
You have everything now, right?
You got rid of everyone in your way.
- You scare me now.
- Seon.
I can't do this anymore.
Let's get a divorce.
Talk to me. What's the problem?
Can you kill my wife?
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Jennifer Lim