(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
ONE DAY 5 YEARS AGO
Isn't this fun?
This is great.
Oh, my. Yi-gyeong!
Help!
Someone, help!
Yi-gyeong, are you okay?
Hold on, Yi-gyeong.
What's going on?
Help!
What's wrong?
Seon!
What's the matter?
Why that punk...
- You're insane.
- You scared me!
You can't do that
in places like this.
What's wrong with you?
Pulling a prank like that here.
You're way too childish.
Min Hwal-sung, what's your problem?
Tell me.
Don't pull such pranks out here.
Oh, goodness.
Would you save Seon
if she were drowning?
Didn't you see me
jump into the water?
- It's such a nice day.
- Yes.
What are they talking about?
I won't save her.
Why not?
Yi-gyeong's worth a fortune.
You sound pretty serious.
I'm kidding, idiot.
Join us!
Jump in!
I will.
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
- Get him.
- Stop right there.
EPISODE 3
- Get him!
- Stop!
Don't let him get away!
- Hey!
- Open the door.
- Open it.
Stop that car! Get him!
Hey.
- Hello.
- You're here.
How did it go?
Where's the culprit?
You lost him?
You...
Shoot.
- Get down there and check!
- Yes, sir!
Hwal-sung.
- He's still breathing.
- It's Bugwang Sky Road parking lot.
Help me.
Can someone save me?
Leave me alone!
Is something wrong?
Are you all right?
My car's out of gas.
Did you call your insurance provider?
My phone's dead.
Hang on.
There's a gas station nearby.
I'll go and get you some gas.
No, it's fine.
- No, we should help each other.
- You don't have to.
It's raining hard. Wait in the car.
I shouldn't take long.
My gosh.
What's going on?
Where did he go?
Did he leave this behind?
Help!
Help me!
Can't we go home to sleep?
The sergeant told us
to be on standby.
I'm going to the sauna to shower.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Oh, dear.
Hello, sir.
Sit up. Are you praying or something?
Listen. Madam Jeon
met with our commissioner.
We're all done for if we don't find
her money and daughter.
We just have to catch the culprit.
That's rich coming from the fool
who lost him from under her nose.
This is Yongdaemun Police
VCU Team Two.
What?
- They found her daughter.
- What?
Where at?
Munyang, Gyeonggi Province.
Hey, guys.
Get over there, all of you.
Thank you. We'll be right there.
- Bye.
- Get to it!
Darn it.
He had something on his face.
REDEVELOPMENT
WITHOUT A PROCESS IS VIOLENCE!
SE-YOON BUILDING
KIDNAPPING
MULTIPLE CASES OF MINORS
LURED ON SOCIAL MEDIA
ABDUCTION
KINDERGARTNER FOUND IN SUSPICIOUS CAR
DELETE ALL VIDEOS FROM SCREEN?
CONFIRM
How long will you live like this?
570 million won.
580 million won.
590 million won.
I said I'd pay you back, punks.
1 BILLION WON
What are you doing at this hour?
(I couldn't sleep.)
(Dad didn't come home last night,
did he?)
(Is something wrong?)
He had a business to take care of.
(What business?)
Did you take your vitamins yesterday?
You didn't.
How many times must I tell you
to take them?
Must I put them in your mouth?
You won't be strong enough
to survive in the States.
(Must you nag
first thing in the morning?)
I don't nag for my sake.
- It's all for your...
- (Really?)
(I think you want me to go abroad
for your sake.)
What?
What got into you?
JEON YI-GYEONG
Hello?
Am I speaking to Kim Seon?
Yes, who is this?
This is Yi-gyeong's number.
I'm calling from a hospital.
I'm Koh Ju-ran, a detective
at Yongdaemun's Violent Crimes Unit.
Ms. Jeon said you're the only person
she can ask for a favor.
Oh, I see.
Who's there?
It's me.
Open up.
Hey, what on earth happened?
You're going to keep all the cash?
What are you talking about?
Do you think
you can get away with it?
Gi Su-jong.
Do you think you can pull it off?
What?
Gi Su-jong.
You're under arrest for robbery,
assault, and threatening to kidnap.
Go on your knees.
No way.
Darn it.
Just a moment.
Let me pay off my debt.
Just let me pay off
my building loan, please.
Please.
Honey.
Let me go. Don't touch me!
Let me go!
No!
TO MY DEAR WIFE
To my dear wife, Seon.
If you receive this letter
it means I'm in
the worst situation I thought of.
Hello?
Is your phone not working?
It's broken.
The touchscreen is smashed and...
Hurry over
to Hanguk University Hospital.
Why?
A detective just called.
Hwal-sung and Yi-gyeong
are both there.
Hwal-sung is unconscious.
I'll get some of Yi-gyeong's things
before heading to the hospital.
You should get there quickly, too.
Are you listening?
Seon, the thing is...
I have to go somewhere
as soon as day breaks.
Can't I go to the hospital
in the afternoon?
What?
Have you lost your mind?
Your best friend is
in a vegetative state
and you'll go somewhere else?
Get yourself together
and do as I say.
Go to the hospital
and check on them first.
Do you understand?
Okay, bye.
Mr. Gi.
Someone smashed the flower pot
and left such a mess.
Let's see the surveillance footage.
I'll report it to the police.
I'm in a rush right now.
- See you later.
- Wait.
It looks like you're going hiking.
It won't take long to see
the surveillance footage.
I'm really sorry.
But it'll only take...
What a punk.
FROM MORGAN LEE, NO TITLE
JEON'S DAUGHTER KIDNAPPED THEN FOUND,
3 BILLION AND CULPRIT UNKNOWN
I'm here to pay you back.
Did you make an appointment?
What appointment?
We're not yet open for business.
Who cares about that?
I'm here with your money.
You know me. I own Se-yoon Building.
Yes, you're Gi Su-jong.
Mr. Gi.
We open at 10 a.m.
I don't care about that.
You should've texted me
your business hours.
- Count it out after 10 a.m.
- The thing is...
This isn't between two individuals.
We must follow the protocol.
Protocol is all good.
I have something to take care of.
I have to go.
Wait.
Hold on.
My brother-in-law.
You killed him, didn't you?
What?
How do Koreans say it?
What is it?
I pray
- For the soul of the departed.
- for the soul of the departed.
Is that it?
How dare you...
- Hey, you.
- No.
Get out of my way.
Come back after 10 a.m.
What a nice place.
She said her underwear
and socks are in here.
6 WEEKS
THE DAY WE FIRST MET
I CAN HEAR YOUR HEARTBEAT NEXT TIME,
THANKS FOR COMING TO US
8 WEEKS
I HEARD YOUR STRONG HEARTBEAT!
I WAS MOVED TO TEARS,
YOUR DAD CRIED HIS EYES OUT
You have her, Seon.
That's what I'm most envious about.
TEXT MESSAGES
SU-JONG, MARCH 18, 2026
ARE YOU SURE IT'S SAFE?
ARE YOU GOING TO STAY
UNTIL THE END OF THE FUNERAL?
OF COURSE... WHY DO YOU ASK?
HAVE YOU MADE UP YOUR MIND?
ARE YOU SURE IT'S SAFE?
Ju-ran, I investigated the car
involved in the incident.
It's hard to follow
because it's not registered.
What's the point?
The previous owner
comes up as Jung Chang-su.
Jung Chang-su?
The construction company owner
who went missing?
Yes.
Okay, text me the address.
Got it. Bye.
CHANGSU CONSTRUCTION &amp; DEVELOPMENT
CEO JUNG CHANG-SU
SENDER
MIN HWAL-SUNG
"Min Hwal-sung"?
SEJEONG-RO AREA 3 REDEVELOPMENT PLAN
AREA SELECTION &amp; PLANNING
FLOOR AREA RATIO INCENTIVE
CHANGSHIM, SE-YOON BUILDING
PYEONGBUKGWAN
LIABILITY REPORT OF SE-YOON BUILDING
PROMISSORY NOTE
SIGNED BY GI SU-JONG
The person in debt.
Gi Su-jong?
SEOUL YONGDAEMUN POLICE STATION
I have something to tell you.
We need to look into Min Hwal-sung.
I need a warrant.
I burned my tongue.
You, punk.
Have you lost your mind?
Pardon?
I told you to catch the culprit
and you want to look into
a victim who's comatose?
There's circumstantial evidence.
The kidnapper used a car registered
to Chang-su's company.
Min Hwal-sung and Jung Chang-su
had some sort of business connection.
Jung Chang-su?
The builder and developer?
Yes, hear me out.
This is what's really weird.
Before Gyun died
he was looking into
Jung Chang-su's disappearance...
If we keep digging
we might find a connection
with Real Capital or...
Hey.
I told you to drop that case.
Don't you know you can't let
your emotions control your work?
Ju-ran.
You get too emotional.
Look at the objective evidence.
I am following the evidence.
What evidence?
As I just told you
the car was registered
to Jung Chang-su's company.
What? In that case
you should go after the culprit,
not grill the victim.
Not to mention
there are other leads.
What was that?
The coffee grounds.
They found coffee grounds
on Yi-gyeong's body.
Yes.
You can search all the cafés
in the metropolitan area.
There are over 30,000 cafés
in Seoul alone.
Have the coffee grounds analyzed.
Can't you figure out
how to find a match?
We can't compare that
with every single café's beans.
It's a detective's job
to do just that.
POLICE COMMISSIONER
Keep quiet.
Hello, Commissioner.
Yes.
No, we have nothing yet.
Pardon?
Yes.
What, right now? Oh, sure.
I understand, sir. Bye.
Hey, guys.
Madam Jeon is at the hospital.
Let's go.
We must explain the situation.
I'll finish something up here first.
Will you? If you wish.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
Go.
PERSONAL BELONGINGS
PHONE, MIN HWAL-SUNG
HANGUK UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Let me take your fingerprint.
ENERGY DRINK
I'm a friend.
Your blood pressure is low
and you're quite poorly nourished.
It's nothing fatal
but you'll need a good rest
to recover from dehydration.
How do you feel?
I'm okay.
I'm fine, Mom.
- Hey, Su-jong.
- I got something to drink.
You're here.
I hope you aren't badly hurt,
Yi-gyeong.
Did you see the kidnapper's face?
Think carefully.
Think of anything, like his voice.
It was a man.
Not something that obvious.
I think she should get some rest.
We'll investigate.
It's three billion won.
What?
He took three billion won for ransom.
Three billion won.
I want to see Hwal-sung.
You should do that
once your condition is better...
I want to see him now.
Yes, right.
ALBUMS
RECENTS
This guy.
SU-JONG
ARE YOU GOING TO STAY
UNTIL THE END OF THE FUNERAL?
OF COURSE... WHY DO YOU ASK?
What's going on with everyone,
including Gyun and all?
Tell me about it.
ARE YOU SURE IT'S SAFE?
HAVE YOU MADE UP YOUR MIND?
DELETE
But still, stay strong.
I will.
Wait.
This backpack...
What is it?
That's a good brand.
You're now about to enter the ICU.
Please be careful.
The patient needs absolute rest.
He may have had damage to his brain
so there's a possibility
of a major surgery in the afternoon.
Let us enter.
Are you his friend?
Yes.
You know what happened, right?
His wife was abducted.
Is that so?
You didn't know?
Lately
we haven't been in touch.
How did you hurt your finger?
This? While working out.
What is this?
A backpack for hiking.
I know that.
What's inside?
It seems heavy.
Just my things
I use while hiking.
I feel so bad for Hwal-sung.
They often went hiking together.
- Let's go inside.
- Okay.
In this state,
he may not recover enough
to enjoy his everyday life,
even if he wakes up again.
There seems to be a problem
near the frontal lobe
but we'll have to open him up
to be sure.
For now
he's expected to suffer
from a mobility disorder
and he may also have difficulty
when he tries to speak or eat.
Hwal-sung.
He's likely to have
severe mood swings
along with memory problems
or impaired judgment.
Here.
Goodbye, ma'am.
It's all right.
Accept it gladly
when an elder offers you something.
My foolish daughter said
only you two can be trusted.
Think of it
as a token of my gratitude.
Don't worry about Yi-gyeong.
She'll get well soon.
I'm someone who has never worried.
Worrying does nothing.
When a problem arises,
you either handle it
or accept the matter. Isn't that so?
Madam.
The commissioner is looking for you.
All right.
Take good care of my girl.
- Yes, ma'am.
My phone is completely out.
What happened to your hand?
People will suspect you of something.
I got hurt.
I have to go, Seon.
Go where?
I'll tell you when I return.
What?
I'll tell you when I get back.
How may I help you?
I came to pay back my debt.
- May I have your name?
- Gi Su-jong.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Are there
any other staff members available?
There was someone
who took charge of my account.
Who was it?
Someone who's wearing a gray hoodie.
A hoodie?
I'm not sure.
You can talk to me.
You must be Mr. Gi Su-jong.
Yes.
Yes, I confirmed your account.
There's a mortgage on your building.
How do you wish
to make your repayment?
Cash. I got it here.
It's a billion won.
One moment.
Let me go ahead and check.
- Please give me a moment.
- Sure.
Thank you for waiting.
Everything has been confirmed
and the account has been paid off.
Really?
Your debt has been repaid.
Does this mean everything is settled?
Yes, sir.
You'll also receive a text message
with the confirmation.
- Thank you.
- Wait.
Does this mean
the building is now mine?
I'm the owner now, right?
Yes, sir.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Yes, Vice President.
Did you get your hands
on Se-yoon Building?
HANMAEUM BADUK CLUBHOUSE,
SE-YOON STUDY ROOM, FOR RENT
There's a bit of a problem, sir.
What?
Yes, thank you.
Hello, we're Captain Toast.
Thank you.
Su-jong.
Mr. Kang.
CAPTAIN TOAST
I can't believe I ran into you here.
- It's been so long.
- Yes.
I just opened this business.
Come by for a bite.
Yes, sure.
Quitting your job back then
was such a good call.
After you left, they couldn't pay us
and I'm now in a lawsuit
to get my severance pay.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
How's your family doing?
I got divorced.
It wasn't easy to hold out.
Are you doing okay?
I've been fighting every day
to make ends meet too.
Yes, of course.
We should do our best.
Stop by sometime.
- Yes, of course, I should.
- Sounds good.
I love the idea of this business.
SEOUL YONGDAEMUN POLICE STATION
- I'm sorry for having you come here.
- It's okay.
I just need you to answer
a few questions.
It's not a big deal.
It's my duty as a democratic citizen.
Anyway, is that woman all right?
Yes, she's in recovery.
May I have a chance to meet her?
- Pardon?
- I was just worried.
Since we crossed paths
I feel somewhat responsible.
- This is just routine questioning.
- Yes.
Please take a look at the photos
and let me know
if anyone looks like the culprit.
All right.
It's not him.
NAME: WI SEO-HUN
AGE: 45
It wasn't someone
who looked like a criminal.
By any chance
- was it him?
- Sorry?
Is he the culprit you saw last night?
The man who abandoned the car.
Was it him?
I only saw him with a face mask on.
CAPTAIN TOAST
Yes?
(We're eating beef for dinner.
Why did you get toast?)
This?
It's a good place.
You can have it later.
Da-rae, you can eat some beef first.
Oh, right.
Here.
COCHLEAR IMPLANT OPERATION GUIDE
A DEVICE FOR THE HEARING IMPAIRED
Da-rae.
Let's go to the States
and do the operation.
I'll make the reservation.
(Dad, it's not covered by insurance,
and it's really expensive.)
Don't worry about it.
I'm a guy who owns a building.
(I really don't have to do it.)
What are you talking about?
You have to do it.
Eat up, Da-rae.
Please go to his home, Mr. Kang.
Let's move it.
- Bo-ram.
- Yes.
We don't have to tell
the sergeant, right?
I'll handle him.
(Once I get the implant,
I can listen to music too, right?)
Yes, of course.
What do you want to listen to?
(I don't know.)
BTS?
BLACKPINK?
- Panic.
- That's a band
that people our age listen to.
Is that so?
(Everything sounds good.)
(But I want to listen
to the song that you two sing.)
(Something like
the sound of you two whistling.)
(And the sound of you snoring.)
You're having a family gathering.
Is there something to celebrate?
How may I help you?
- You're not asking.
- Asking what?
You are not asking
why we're taking you.
Yes, why are you taking me?
You'll find out once you're there.
Goodness, I knew this would happen.
I always knew
something wasn't right with that man.
RECEIVE PREMIUM SERVICE
AT SOUND RESEARCH LAB
HEARING IMPAIRMENT,
EXAMINATION, SURGICAL INFORMATION
HOW DOES THE TEST
FOR HEARING-IMPAIRED PEOPLE WORK?
IS SURGERY NECESSARY?
I've been odd lately, haven't I?
And you must've resented me a lot.
Even if the entire world denounced me
I hope you and Da-rae, the two of you
will still have faith in me.
I heard your building
is heavily mortgaged.
Nobody in Korea pays for a building
in full with cash.
Everyone goes into debt.
I heard you were trying hard
to find money quickly.
Where did you get that from?
The informant isn't important.
I just need you
to share the facts with me.
Sure, I'm not in debt.
- You aren't?
- No.
How?
Well, to be exact
I'm in the process
of repaying my debt.
Exactly.
How are you repaying your debt?
We aren't talking
about a penny or two.
I've been doing part-time jobs.
Do I have to share
these personal information with you?
Where were you on the night
of Min Hwal-sung
and Jeon Yi-gyeong's abduction?
Home.
Do you have a witness?
Before I went home,
I was at my building.
At Se-yoon Building.
So where were you last night?
Home.
Any witness?
My daughter and wife.
Wait.
Do we need a witness for this?
Mr. Gi.
If you confess everything
your sentence could be reduced.
Detective, I do not understand
what's happening here.
- Sit here for a moment.
- Okay.
Do you think it's him?
I'm not so sure.
As I mentioned before,
he was wearing a face mask.
What about his voice?
It sounds similar, I guess.
Are you sure?
Yes, it's him.
Well, it does seem like him...
I'll put a face mask on him
- so take a good look.
- Okay.
Put this on.
Put this on and look in the mirror.
Now.
Do you have to take things this far?
Just put it on.
Koh Ju-ran!
Come out now!
Dang it.
Hey.
You're doing this
based on pure premonition, right?
We have a witness here.
You little punk...
RESTRICTED AREA
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Are you sure it was that man?
Is he the one who kidnapped me?
He was wearing a face mask,
so I didn't get a good look.
No.
You don't need to ask, Yi-gyeong.
This is nonsense.
Mr. Gi's wife confirmed his alibi.
There's nothing else.
Or what?
Are you saying Mr. Gi and his wife
are accomplices in this crime?
I was half-asleep,
but I clearly remember him coming in.
And I remember holding his hand.
I'm not exactly sure of the time
but it was around midnight.
When did you say you saw him?
It was well over 1 a.m.
You need to drop this
before it snowballs.
Let me put the mask on him once.
You punk.
Look at him with the mask on
and tell me if it was him.
The life of a family depends on this.
Mr. Gi.
Put the mask on.
Yes, fine.
Stand in front of the mirror.
I'm not so sure.
By any chance, is my wife here?
Seon.
Are you here?
It can't be him.
His wife said she was with him.
I doubt it.
It's not him.
I don't think he's that man.
Wait.
What now?
You were at the scene
of Gyun's accident
weren't you?
Let's go, Su-jong.
Okay.
I'm sorry, Su-jong.
They gave you trouble
because of Hwal-sung and me.
No, don't say that.
What would've happened
if I hadn't seen you come in?
You would've been locked up by now.
You saved him.
You married
such a wonderful woman, Su-jong.
Thank you for everything, Yi-gyeong.
I mean, you're still unwell.
Don't mention it.
Let me take a quick nap, Seon.
Yes, you must be tired.
I thought you were having an affair,
but that wasn't it.
That's nonsense.
You need to disinfect this
and get a new bandage.
It might get infected.
I'll do it for you at home.
What about your phone?
It's like this now.
Get a new one. It's frustrating
when I can't reach you.
Okay.
Your hair looks messy,
so get a haircut too.
You abducted her, right?
You'll explain, right?
Yes.
Okay, let's eat for now.
Okay.
Hello?
Ms. Kim Seon.
Yes?
Will everything continue as planned?
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
- Let's sell this building.
- All of a sudden? Why?
Let's just sell it
to that Real Capital or whatever.
Three billion won. How's that?
I'll give you some time to consider.
They're going to build
the biggest building in Asia here.
Hwal-sung knew about Se-yoon Building
being included
in the redevelopment project?
You call us friends?
What do you take me for?
There seems to be a problem.
Please give me a little more time.
Hee-ju, how do you do that?
Do what?
Finding the right connections?
It's not just up to you!
I'll need 30 billion won.
How intriguing.
I thought I had made myself clear.
This was your last chance
to let matters go quietly.
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Jennifer Lim