INTERROGATION IN PROGRESS
Your handbag was found in the sewer.
Even the tattoo on her ankle
matches yours.
You disguised the body as Sarah Kim.
No, I mean,
you perfectly disguised it as you
and slipped off the suspect list.
All the evidence points toward you.
People think what they want to believe
is the truth.
Just because the evidence points to me
doesn't mean I killed anyone.
And yet, you believe I'm the killer.
I know nothing about this.
If you're not the perpetrator,
you must feel this situation is unfair.
How would you feel if it were you?
I'd want to prove myself.
How about it?
Can you prove yourself?
I would've already if I could.
What if you could?
What if there's a way to prove who you are
and whether you're the killer or not?
Do you consent to providing a DNA sample?
THE ART OF SARAH
UNREGISTERED PERSON
Apparently, no DNA from the crime scene
matches hers.
That goes for prints too.
How is this even possible?
- She was smiling.
- What?
Do you consent to providing a DNA sample?
She knew we wouldn't be able
to prove anything,
as she had no identity to begin with.
How can we have a victim and a suspect
and not know who they are?
Can unregistered people even exist?
There are always blind spots.
That means there are no existing records.
That means we might have to track down
a person who exists but doesn't exist
within 34 hours.
- But that means--
- It's impossible.
Only the suspect's statement
will provide the missing pieces.
The suspect was certain
we wouldn't find any evidence.
She'll never cooperate.
What if we use that certainty?
She can get rid of evidence,
but she can't erase
the tracks she left doing it.
Yes, sir.
What's going on here?
Lee is in charge now. You're off the case.
Sir!
The warrant is likely to be denied
if we can't find evidence by tomorrow.
And you know what's next.
You'll have a disciplinary hearing
for making an unlawful arrest.
Take responsibility.
No, but I'm not done yet.
I can solve this in time.
It's the incompetent ones
who think they can actually do something.
Get inside.
If you do this,
you'll single-handedly ruin
the entire case!
I know you pushed ahead with that arrest
out of blind ambition.
Get out of my way.
Instead of holding your men back
to save your ass.
Go inside.
Sir!
There you are.
Sarah Kim is refusing to talk.
She says she'll only talk to you.
You're back.
Let's take a break.
Why do you look trapped
when I'm the one who's locked up?
I know what you're going through,
trying to hang on. I've been there.
Doors that open easily for others
have often seemed like walls to me.
I'd feel robbed in those moments
when things were never even mine.
It's the world that's messed up,
not you, Detective.
Wow.
I thought you were being sincere.
Is this how you've been fooling
all those people until now?
By exploiting their vulnerabilities?
Do you know what kinds of people
con artists usually target?
Stupid people?
Incredibly vain people?
No. If anything, they're intellectuals
with expert knowledge.
The more expert they are,
the more adamantly they believe
they can't be fooled.
Be careful. I'm talking about you.
Let's get started.
- Start recording.
- Yes, sir.
You were last seen at the Boudoir party.
You cut off all contact
and disappeared after that.
Where were you?
I went to Samwol right after the party.
I had to get the shop ready
for the February opening.
Are you sure?
I finished at 10:00 a.m.
and went straight to the hotel.
You can check my dashcam footage.
Wasn't it a bit early to check in?
I'm an extended-stay guest.
And after that?
I wanted some quiet time alone,
so I stayed in with my phone off
until I met you yesterday.
They'll have a record
of my room service orders.
What a perfect alibi.
Is it?
If I had told you sooner,
I could've saved us both a lot of trouble.
She's just trifling with us, isn't she?
Sarah Kim's statement conflicts
with someone else's.
Who do you mean?
Choi Chae-u!
The lease agreement in question
was reviewed and deemed invalid
by our MD Team.
We've already addressed the issue
by disciplining the employee responsible,
per our internal regulations.
So I was told.
It means one of them is lying.
See if the store construction has started,
then come right over.
Yes, sir.
2024 KEF NEW YEAR'S PARTY
Distinguished members
and esteemed guests
who have honored us with your presence,
the 2024 Korean Enterprises Federation…
- Excuse--
- It won't be long. Please cooperate.
Entry is not permitted
unless you've been preapproved.
Either get the organizer's approval
or wait here until the event ends.
Even through the immense waves of change,
you have protected South Korea's economic…
Sir!
- Why haven't you gone in yet?
- What did you find out?
Sarah Kim was telling the truth.
Construction was underway
until a few days ago, apparently.
But everything has been torn down now.
Both the build-out and the tear-down
are impossible without Choi's approval.
But I don't understand.
Why would Choi do that?
She must have a reason for it.
What brings you here?
Oh, hello.
Is my father inside?
Are you meeting the assemblyman?
I guess I am.
I have something important
to discuss with my father.
Do you think I can get inside?
Just a moment.
We will now begin the 2024…
Please, come in.
Sir, we got in. Come on.
To victory!
The assemblyman is over there.
Sir, I'll just speak to my father.
I'm counting on you this year, Chairwoman.
- Likewise.
- Yes.
I look forward to everything, Chairman.
- Lovely ambiance today.
- I appreciate your support.
How did you get in?
This might take a while,
so let's talk elsewhere.
This is no place--
It's no place to discuss
the allegations of evidence tampering
against the head of a major corporation.
Shall I go on?
Say hello to Mr. Lee here.
This is my son.
This way, Chairman.
- It's a pleasure.
- Come this way.
This is my son.
- Is it?
- Yes.
- Good job!
- He joined the National Police Agency.
Did Sarah Kim give you that?
This is the only one in the country,
here on my special order.
No one can have this but me.
You had even signed a contract.
So why did you lie?
Were you the one
who had the security footage erased?
What in the world did Sarah Kim do
for you to go this far?
You think this is because of Sarah Kim?
You did this!
I didn't even know she'd conned me
until you came to see me!
I never thought
she would dare drag a corpse
through my department store!
I was protecting my store, not her!
Because that is my position and my duty.
"Drag a corpse"?
So you've seen the footage?
Replace the entire security system.
And tear down the Boudoir shop at once.
Erasing it unknowingly is negligent.
Doing it after watching it is intentional.
But how will you prove that?
The footage is long gone.
How would you prove that?
I will help you
if you want to protect your store,
not Sarah Kim.
Look at you, making threats.
Inspector Park Mu-gyeong,
you're much scarier than I thought.
I'm just saying we should make a deal.
Now this is a deal.
If a word of this is leaked to the press,
you're finished, Detective.
Were you the final target
of Sarah Kim's con?
"Final"?
You really don't know anything, do you?
Sarah Kim targeted me from the very start.
She made everything happen
just to get to me.
Excuse me.
I want to propose a brand
for your luxury brand section.
Would it be possible to speak
with the highest-ranking person here?
Please come this way.
Would you have a seat?
Hello.
"Bu-du-i-ir"?
It's Boudoir.
I'll pass this on for you.
Chief Director Park Sun-bok
will be with you shortly.
- Please bring this lady a drink.
- Yes, ma'am.
THE AUTOBIOGRAPHY OF CHOI CHAE-U
JOURNEY
LIFE IS A SERIES OF MISTAKES AND LESSONS
TO THOSE STARTING A GREAT JOURNEY
- I'm heading out. Take care.
- Good night.
Excuse me, but will it be much longer
for Chief Director Park Sun-bok?
There's no one by that name.
PARK SUN-BOK GUKBAP
I was too hasty.
KANG JI-HWON
I NEED YOUR HELP
I'm going to get Boudoir
into Samwol Department Store.
I want to take it slow,
even if it takes time.
For now, I need an ally to get close
to Choi Chae-u and help me get intel.
Wait a minute.
Are you suggesting I do that?
You said she came by the host bar.
Yes, she did. But that was only once.
And in person,
she's someone on a whole different level.
Eun-jae, no. I can't do it.
One of my regular clingy clients
is a Samwol executive.
She's even a chief director.
I'll connect you with her instead.
No, it has to be you.
The one thing she could never have
is youth.
She said the one thing
she could never be is a man.
To her, I bet a young man
is the most desirable thing in the world.
Notable details?
You must like it.
Cognac, I mean.
I've never tried it.
Blowing money!
She collects Richard Hennessy
even though she doesn't drink it.
You must be in the middle
of a VIP gathering.
- Hello, Chairwoman.
- Who were you again?
Choi Chae-u doesn't trust anyone.
She always leaves her phone behind
when she steps away.
Did you all hear?
Apparently, Sarah Kim got completely drunk
at the club lounge and broke an Opale.
I heard she went to Chanel
and pulled the "I'll take it all."
Like some nouveau riche.
But honestly,
Chanel isn't really our style.
Chairwoman Choi was in Chanel again today.
- She does like her Chanel.
- I know.
It's Chanel that likes me.
The pop culture scene now
is split into those who have a Boudoir bag
and those who don't.
Chairwoman Choi is slowly on her way down.
Oh, here comes the "Human Chanel."
Smile, everyone.
Where is this Boudoir? Take me there.
Yes, ma'am.
You're Sarah Kim?
You're not like what I've heard.
Pardon?
Don't worry about it.
Where's the restroom?
- Let me escort you.
- Don't. I'm not some frail old lady.
This way, please.
Chaebols aren't all that special.
Drinking in broad daylight
and throwing up like that.
I wouldn't want to end up like that,
no matter how much money I had.
You could never end up like that.
You can't become a chaebol
just because you want to.
So watch your mouth.
Selling high-class goods
doesn't make you high-class.
I'm sorry.
The first and last person
to pass that test
was MD Chief Director Kim Hong-mi.
That fast-tracked her from division head
to managing director.
Excuse me, ma'am.
May I check your queue number?
I'm here for your regional head.
She is currently in a meeting.
Would you mind waiting in the store?
Ms. Kim is still in a meeting.
- Good work, everyone.
- Thank you.
She's over there.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
It wasn't too bad.
That's a relief, then.
Why did you want to see me?
We'd like to invite you to open
at the Samwol Gangnam branch.
How interesting.
There are many terms.
Exclusive rights
and a hefty 15% commission.
I was at London Fashion Week
a few days ago.
It was odd,
but no one there seemed to know
anything about Boudoir.
Perhaps those you met were unqualified.
Perhaps.
We request that you submit
company review documents, just in case.
Working out the details
can proceed after that.
Boudoir is considering Samwol.
Not the other way around.
We can't sign on these terms,
so come back with a revised contract.
We've asked Boudoir to provide
company review documents,
but they keep delaying
and refuse to submit them.
There's also that client data leak,
and Sarah Kim's reputation
hasn't been great lately either.
I heard about that too.
A trusting relationship
doesn't seem sustainable.
She seems to have many faces.
I don't know how she is with you, ma'am,
but with me…
She's right to have many faces.
She obviously can't treat you
the same way she treats me.
No, she can't.
Then what's the problem?
Propose a 10% commission to Boudoir.
Yes, ma'am.
Sarah Kim?
Fancy seeing you here. Are you here alone?
Yes.
I'm spending today with Richard Hennessy.
Beats any human company.
I guess you don't trust people.
With two people, you end up crying.
With three, you end up fighting.
With any more than that,
you end up feeling lonely.
You appeared lonely
even when you were alone.
I lost an employee I cared about.
She secretly sold client information
to an insurance company.
I heard.
That you covered up their mistake
and protected the employee.
But be stern when necessary.
I'm not that nice a person.
I had to give up on the employee
to protect the brand.
We really do have a lot in common.
The problem is…
that one thing made me doubt everything.
I can't trust anyone anymore.
It's not people we can't trust.
It's their promises.
As a token of their promise,
the two of them each took a key,
since you need two keys turned at once
to open a Richard Hennessy.
They promised to return
and share the bottle together.
But
the promise was never kept.
I'm sorry.
I must decline your offer to join Samwol.
Please understand I never broke a promise,
as I never made one.
Your reason?
The Mirae has offered
to take a lower commission.
Personally, my relationship with you
comes first.
But professionally, profits come first.
I understand.
That's what a businesswoman does.
Chairwoman Choi.
May I say something
as your drinking friend
and not as a businesswoman?
It may be an unfounded concern,
but something feels amiss.
As soon as Samwol offered
a 10% commission rate,
The Mirae came to me with 9%.
It may be wise to check
for internal information leaks.
The only one who would even know
the details of the contract…
is Chief Director Kim Hong-mi.
Am I right?
You ought to be stern when necessary.
Why did you get off work so late?
Kim Hong-mi
was forced to resign.
And Choi Chae-u is reacting hysterically
because of it.
Not a disciplinary dismissal?
She's surprisingly soft-hearted.
Do you know you've changed?
Why are you this obsessed with Samwol?
For me, it has to be that space.
How do you like it?
October 14th. Who closed up that day?
It's just as I had imagined.
If you agree,
we'll begin the interior work right away.
We will handle all the expenses.
Do you still have concerns?
I'm thinking of ways
to persuade headquarters.
Headquarters…
They've had a complete change of heart
due to Samwol's attitude.
We've had countless offers in the past,
but we've never been asked to submit
to a company review.
Even so, we can't ignore procedure.
Yes. Please think it over and let me know.
But I'm afraid we can't wait too long.
We need to finish our talks
with The Mirae.
Do you mind if I look around?
Ma'am. Apparently,
there was a disturbance in the VIP lounge.
But why did I need to be informed?
Is it someone I know?
Well…
They say it was Sarah Kim.
Dear,
did you ever break an Opale
at the hotel lounge before?
No.
Just as I thought.
It's all that woman's doing.
Sorry?
I had something like this before.
That you were going around
acting like some obnoxious nouveau riche.
That means this has happened
many times before.
Imitating someone like that
is a form of mental illness.
How pathetic and miserable
do you have to be
to steal someone else's life?
All you'll ever be is an imitation.
Your profile isn't even
on the web portals, is it?
People put their faces up there
for a good reason.
This sort of thing happens all too often.
I'll tell them to do it right away.
No, it's all right.
Please don't worry.
Security has the impostor in custody.
We'll hand them to the police,
so don't worry.
Honestly, it's really fine.
I'm sorry. I guess I'm quite shocked.
I'll deal with this myself.
Don't worry about it.
How could I not,
especially when it happened in my store?
If I end up owing you
before signing the contract,
it'll be awkward for both of us.
That is true, but…
You'd be helping me
by not helping me.
It's not that she didn't report it,
but that she couldn't.
Her identity would have been revealed
if she had.
I never doubted her,
even in obviously suspicious moments.
She appeared to have a life
desirable enough for someone
to want to impersonate her.
I had no idea
she had covered my eyes and ears
and pushed out my people.
An excellent con is never discovered
because you don't even realize
you've been conned.
Yes, you're right.
Seeing as how she fooled me until the end.
That bitch really is something else.
I was convinced
the moment I set foot in that party.
A company review didn't matter.
That's right!
She was there too.
That impersonator.
She was wearing
exactly the same hairstyle and dress.
Chairwoman Choi.
We meet again.
Indeed.
She was caught
on the store's security footage.
That woman killed Sarah Kim.
Sarah Kim is alive.
Which Sarah Kim are you talking about?
- The dead woman impersonated Sarah Kim.
- What?
There were two Sarah Kims.
And Choi was the last person
to see the two together.
Call in CSI.
The security cameras are cut clean.
God.
They made a total mess in here.
Just how far
does the blood on the floor go?
So after being hit there, they fell and…
It's a mark made by a weapon.
VICTIM'S DRESS MADE BY MORPHÉ
Both women wore the same dress
on the day of the murder.
She had two identical dresses made before
and disabled the security cameras.
This murder was planned.
We can prove she was preparing
for the crime
if we can confirm she was the buyer.
It's too sloppy.
Do you think someone that meticulous
would just leave behind
such important evidence?
What do you think?
Just a moment.
This dress is from here, right?
Yes, I made that dress.
Do you remember who bought it?
Yes.
She's our boutique regular.
Sarah Kim.
How does the waist feel?
It was an unusual order.
She wanted me to make
two of the same dress.
- No security cameras in the store?
- No.
Clients usually have several fittings,
and tailoring takes a long time too.
Do you still have
the pins you used for tailoring?
FORENSIC REPORT
DNA ANALYSIS INDICATES A 99.99998% MATCH
What's taking so long?
Oh, that scared me.
It's here.
The DNA matches.
Let's get the warrant now.
- Okay!
- It's not Sarah Kim.
Neither the prints nor the blood matches.
What are you saying? Then what's this?
We compared it to the victim's.
What?
Be careful, would you?
Do you know what kinds of people
con artists usually target?
Stupid people?
Incredibly vain people?
No. If anything, they're intellectuals
with expert knowledge.
The more expert they are,
the more adamantly they believe
they can't be fooled.
Be careful.
I'm talking about you.
The perfect con.
Sarah Kim chose me for the perfect con.
Subtitle Translation by: Yung Un Choi