Don't say a word in there.
I'll handle all the talking.
I'm practically family.
Careful there.
He's with me.
Let him through, bro.
Let him go.
Hey, bro, where's Uncle?
Next time the money comes up short…
- Over there.
- Alright.
Get lost now.
Hey, Uncle, how are you?
I seek your blessings.
I'm Lakhbir Munga's son.
Dad wants some stuff.
Oh.
You should've said
you were Crackhead's son.
Brother!
Atif bhai, look who's here!
Crackhead's son.
You came alone?
Where's your dad?
He wanted to come,
but he got too high
on smack last night.
Couldn't even get out
of bed this morning.
Tell him if he keeps smoking
so much of his own stuff,
what's he gonna sell,
my family jewels?
- Shall we?
- Go upstairs.
Okay.
What's the holdup?
Your legs gone numb?
Move your butt.
We're coming.
Uncle ji!
How are you doing?
I seek your blessings.
Your knees better now?
Dad sent a list.
That's quite a list.
"Hash, 3.75 kilos."
"Mandakini, 2.5 kilos."
"Opium, Lollipop, hashish,
Saajan, Kharghosh."
Yes, the army's tightened security
at the border big-time.
Nothing's getting into Punjab anymore.
We're short on two items right now.
They'll come in on the 9th next month
through the Nepal border.
- Come pick them up then.
- Alright.
Take the rest of the stuff.
Give it to him.
You got the money?
Yes, we brought the cash. Look.
Go on, take it.
Go already!
- What's this?
- Well, he's asked for a few more things.
Dad wants them.
"AK-47."
Why do you need it?
Junkies have been
harassing us nonstop.
They take kilos at a time
and don't pay up.
Dad said we should keep weapons
to scare the money out of them.
Who's he?
This is my childhood friend, Jaskirat.
He was home on leave,
so I brought him along.
What does he do?
He's training for the military.
- Military?
- Yeah.
Look at this fool's face,
hasn't even grown peach fuzz yet,
and wants to join the military.
- Go on, take it.
- Okay.
Get going now.
Settle the payment downstairs.
- Okay.
- Next time, send your dad
to pick up the goods,
or I'll shove your head up
your friend's butt.
- Let me keep the bag.
- Don't…
Why are you scared?
We risk our hearts
We risk our very lives
Our only crime is…
Pull over here.
That we love them
Think it through again.
You sure this is the only option left?
Jaskirat, my buddy…
I always dreamed of seeing you
in an army uniform.
In this life, my family comes first.
If Waheguru ji gives me another,
I'll give it to the country.
You'll marry Jasleen, right?
Come on, bro.
Think it through again.
Get going.
Move it.
Go!
Leave!
Drums are playing, everybody's celebrating
Drums are beating, everyone's celebrating
Young men with twisted
Mustaches are dancing
Those with twisted mustaches roar
As they pass the GT road
I got to say…
I really love this song.
Bunty's wedding is finally over.
We have many memories tied
to this room, too, right?
Don't get me started.
- Where's my sister?
- Jassi!
- Where is my sister?
- Have you completely lost it?
Tell me where she is,
or I swear I'll kill you.
- Drop it right now, you dimwit.
- What are you doing?
- Where is my sister?
- Put it down!
- Last warning.
- Drop it.
Who do you think you are,
pointing a gun at me?
- Where is my sister?
- You're going to die, kid.
- You got into the house…
- Tell me, where is my sister, you dimwit?!
Hey! Who's up there?
Who is it?
Now the skies will rain
When two paths meet again
You better watch your head
Now the skies will rain
The winds have turned again
You better watch your head
Now it's the question
Of my pride once again
Listen, listen, listen!
- Listen, we are one
- Who is it?
One look at you and my heart was gone
Compared to the gamble of my heart
No pain feels…
No pain feels big or grand
All the world's tricks
- And ties fall apart
- Where's my sister?
- I'd give my life for your hand
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Listen, listen, listen!
Listen, we are one
One look at you and my heart was gone
Listen, listen, listen!
My father raised me a winner
If I kill for my people
It don't make me a sinner
- From the coast to the plains
- Where's Bunty?
- Everybody know the name
- I asked you, where's Bunty?
- Coming for 'em, we got bills to maintain
- He stepped outside.
Bitch you got an ego
Shouldn't mess with me though
I make all this money like
I'm running a casino
G code, now I got that power
In my genome
Cut the bluff
Can you stand up what's between yo?
Pop up heads to the paper like
They were crossing on each other
I'll make a deputy bet to me
I'll make a couple other
Craziest turn the laziest
Problem to a product
Hustler probably profit 'cause
I was profitable
Profit words of mother, words of mother
Two hands on they neck like
I was turning butter
So hot-headed, if I go to sleep
I'll probably burn the covers
Burn the covers, if the covers burn
I gotta turn the mattress
Hoping the first pick you wanted
A pic like a wordy caption
Many years I spent working
And I returned
With a piece of sugar candy
Many years I spent working
And I returned
With a piece of sugar candy
Where's my sister, Bunty?
Where's my sister, Bunty?!
Tell me, you dimwit!
Tell me, Bunty!
Speak up!
- I'll come to check on you, my dear
- Show yourself, you…
- The world tests your love
- I won't spare you.
It turned against me here
Only you truly know
The love I carry for you, my dear
Listen, listen, listen!
Listen, we are one
One look at you and my heart was gone
Listen, listen, listen!
Compared to the gamble of my heart
No pain feels…
No pain feels big or grand
All the world's tricks and ties fall apart
I'd give my life for your hand
Listen, listen, listen!
Many years I spent working
And I returned with a piece of sugar candy
But what truly finished me off
Was your laughter, baby
Listen, listen, listen!
Listen, we are one
One look at you and my heart was gone
Listen, listen, listen!
Ladies and gentlemen
You're still not ready for this!
Jassi, you fool!
You dimwit!
This is my house, you fool!
How dare you use AK-47 at us,
you dimwit!
If I don't make you my slave,
I'm not Tittu!
Come to daddy, stupid!
Son of a gun!
You idiot!
You fool!
Oh no! He killed Gonu!
That idiot!
Where are you, Jassi?
Where did that fool go?
Where are you hiding?
Dimwit!
Get lost, you idiot!
- Where is your sister, Tittu?
- Get lost!
I'll do to your younger sister exactly
what I did to the elder one!
Don't worry, Jassi, you fool…
Where is my sister?
- Let me go!
- You moron!
- Where is my sister, you smug-bag?
- You…
Speak up!
Where is my sister, Tittu?
Tell me!
Speak up, you dimwit!
- You…
- Where's my sister, Tittu?
Where's my sister, Tittu?
Tillu pump…
She's inside the pump room,
you fool.
Forgive me, brother.
Jassi, please, forgive me.
We used to play together as kids.
You remember, don't you?
Jassi, please, bro.
Jassi… Jassi, no…
this is not fair.
I'm your brother, Jassi.
Jassi! Jassi, just hear me out!
Jassi!
That rascal killed my brother!
Sir, over a petty land dispute,
ex-gangster turned MLA Sukhwinder
beat Jaskirat's father,
retired Subedar Arjun Singh,
till he was barely alive.
Drag the fool!
Put the noose around his neck.
Then he hung him from a tree
- in his own fields, sir.
- Pull!
Pull!
No!
Jaskirat's two sisters,
Harleen and Jasleen,
were brutally gang-raped by Sukhwinder
along with 12 men from his family, sir.
- Let me go!
- Hold her down!
Hold her still!
Hold her!
Hold her down!
Let go of the hand!
- No!
- Let it go!
- After that, they murdered Harleen…
- Let go!
in the most savage way.
They kidnapped Jasleen
and held her captive
in the pump house on their fields.
And while all this was happening,
21-year-old Jaskirat,
a true patriot,
was preparing to join the army
at Ramgarh Cantonment.
Jaskirat's mother,
Mrs. Prabhneet Kaur,
tried everything possible
just to get a police complaint
registered against MLA Sukhwinder.
But under political pressure,
not a single police officer
was willing to touch the case.
Now tell me, sir,
when the authorities whose job is
to deliver justice to innocent citizens
shut their doors on us like this,
where do we go?
- What are we supposed to do, sir?
- What are you saying, Veena ji?
What are you even talking about?
He deserves to be hanged.
Murdering 12 members
of MLA Sukhwinder's family,
almost wiping out his bloodline.
And the subordinate court hands him
just seven years?
Sir, this is a mockery
of the Indian justice system.
Your Honor, if Jaskirat is not given
the death penalty in this case,
the people will lose faith
in the Indian justice system forever.
Jaskirat…
I believe Judge Maheshwari's verdict…
will go in the appellant's favor.
And you could face the death sentence.
But don't worry.
We'll appeal in the Supreme Court.
If needed, we'll even approach
the President.
If I'd died serving the army,
my mother would've been provided for.
No matter what happens,
you'll finish your studies.
If he doesn't get his act together
till you're old enough to marry,
then you stay unmarried, alright?
If a junkie's son grows up
to be a junkie,
there's no need to marry him.
Stay strong, buddy.
Take care of my mother.
I'll take care of her.
Stop bringing her to court.
She gets depressed.
Grief will make her sick.
Mummy…
I'll keep writing to you.
My brave soldier boy.
BURAIL JAIL
JAILER'S OFFICE
I'm coming in to get my shit
Somebody tell me how I got so shameless
I'm on the way to take my things
Goddamn it, I'm so audacious
We are in love
We don't fear the world
I'm coming in to get my shit
Somebody tell me how I got so shameless
I never miss when I blow kisses
My love's gonna be contagious
We are in love
We don't fear the world
What happened?
Get down!
What is happening?
Sir, we're under attack.
We are in love
- We are in love
- You fool!
Get him…
Stop! I said stop!
Where are you taking him?
- We are in love
- Dimwit!
Stay put…
We don't fear the world
Stop it, you fools, he's gone!
Your case is rather interesting.
You were a good student,
training to join the army.
How terrible it must feel,
having your entire life wrecked so young.
I empathize with you.
If I were in your place,
I'd probably have done the same.
Taking revenge isn't easy.
Pain needs courage as fuel…
to turn into revenge.
And not everyone has that fuel in them.
Do you know me?
Ajay Sanyal, sir.
Good.
He is Sushant Bansal,
and he works with me.
What do you want from me, sir?
We can save you from the gallows.
The Government of India can provide
everything your mother and sister
need to live comfortably.
In return, your life belongs to us.
You will do exactly what we tell you.
The Government of India
will take care of that mother…
whom every government officer
refused to help?
And you're asking me
to protect that system…
which did everything possible
to destroy my life?
Sir, my father was in the army.
My grandfather as well.
I was about to enlist myself.
Patriotism runs in our blood.
But what did we get
for loving this country?
The love I had…
for this nation, sir.
It's gone now.
I'm finished, sir.
I've got nothing left to give you.
All I want now is
to go to my Waheguru.
I want to weep in His presence.
"A true warrior is one
who fights for a cause."
"Even if he's cut to pieces,
he never abandons the battlefield."
We are men, Jaskirat.
From the moment we're born
till the day we die,
we are meant to fight.
For our cause.
For our dreams.
For our rights.
For our family.
This is our duty.
And we get no appreciation
or medals for it.
And I'm not saying that…
joining us will make
your life easier.
In fact, I have to be straightforward
and frank with you.
This ocean is deep.
Dark beyond sight.
But if you manage to cross it,
and Jaskirat, I believe you can,
then trust me…
your purpose will become crystal clear.
Death comes for all of us, Jaskirat.
So, isn't it better to die raising hell
than to fade away in shame?
Jaskirat, before you answer,
understand one thing.
The fuel inside you…
can only be lit by me.
A wounded lion doesn't fear death…
It just makes him more lethal.
- Hello.
- Yes, is this Mrs. Prabhneet?
No, this is her daughter, Jasleen.
Ma'am, this is Joshi,
the branch manager from the SBI Bank.
Our system is down,
so I just need to confirm
whether this month's Government PPF
amount of 30,000 rupees
has been withdrawn.
Yes, yes, it was done the day
before yesterday.
You've already withdrawn it.
Alright, thank you.
You were kidnapped while
under police protection.
Using that as the cover,
the Indian Government is depositing
30,000 rupees every month as compensation
into your mother's SBI account.
This compensation will continue
as PPF for the next 36 years.
Any doubts or questions?
In Karachi, your handlers
will be supervised by a coordinator.
He'll have information
on all handlers and assets.
You may never even come
face-to-face with him.
But if you're ever in a soup,
he'll take care of you.
Sir, it's time.
He needs to catch
a flight to Kabul.
Our profession's most
lethal weapons
are vigilance and patience.
Keep them razor-sharp at all times.
Do you know what this name means?
Lion.
The king of beasts.
Your goal is to dominate
the whole jungle.
Jai Hind.
I met a boy out the place I knock steady
Like my vibe when I left that as a wife
Said wandering back
But we doubled it twice
Next thing you know
We outside in the night
Windows down wanna race the light
City blur past when you
Cut through the sight
Sun fall down but I'm smiling ahead
Adrenaline all the way up to my head
What a wild ride
One look and I'm by your side
I'm down going way past five
Boy I couldn't even change my mind
What a wild ride
Thought it'd just be a kiss goodbye
Now the sun's coming through the blinds
DARLING, DARLING
WHY DID YOU BREAK MY HEART?
DRINK AALAM MILK SODA
AND GET A FRESH START!
What a wild ride
That day, Jaskirat died.
After killing Rehman, it feels like…
the real Hamza finally came alive.
When I left India,
I thought I'd put in a few years here
and somehow find
my way back home.
But that part of me is gone now.
Dead.
What's left is obsession.
An obsession to keep
my country safe.
And if I have to spend
my entire life in a wolf's skin,
living among wolves to make that happen,
then so be it.
Where are you from, Aalam bhai?
Who all do I blame?
Today belonged to you.
I'll tell you someday,
when my heart's heavy.
Everyone played their part
I hold no grudge against death
It was life that tore me apart
Tears fall down from the clouds above
Yet these eyes refuse to weep
Such a bond I made, O Lord divine
Never has a love so deep
Since the day you left my side
Sleep has evaded me
This whole city feels strange
No one here belongs to me
Never again will love feel the same
Though the world is cruel
I didn't cry in vain
I've seen every color
Now there's no more fear left in me
This love will live forever in me
Even if I wander
No road ahead will lead me home
There is no one left to bare their soul
Every path I knew now stands forgotten
Tell me, beloved, where do I turn then?
The clouds
Every path I knew now stands forgotten
Tell me, beloved, where do I turn then?
- The king of Lyari, the pride of Lyari…
- Arshad Pappu! Arshad Pathan!
Though the world is cruel
I didn't cry in vain
I've seen every color
Now there's no more fear left in me
This love will live forever in me
Even if I wander
No road ahead will lead me home
There is no one left to bare their soul
Every path I knew now stands forgotten
Tell me, beloved, where do I turn then?
For insulting the Prophet,
there's only one fate.
You lose your head!
For insulting the Prophet,
there's only one fate.
You lose your head!
We were planning a major strike
in Amritsar.
Something on the scale of 26/11.
The Baloch were about to supply
the weapons and explosives, but…
Anyway, SP…
why did you kill Rehman?
Revenge.
For who?
For Bade sahab.
Rehman's brother-in-law, Bilal,
owned commercial land in Lyari
worth 400-500 crore.
Bade sahab's brother, Noora,
usurped it by force.
And refused to give it back.
Really?
And then?
- The slogan of greatness…
- Allah is the Greatest!
Then Rehman called Bade sahab.
He told him to get Noora
to vacate the land.
Bade sahab laughed it off
and said it's between Noora and Bilal.
Why are you sticking your nose in it?
He was joking.
But that "sticking your nose in" line
didn't sit well with Rehman.
After that…
the Baloch snatched Noora
in broad daylight from Gul Plaza.
Then they called Bade sahab.
Bade sahab panicked.
He begged and apologized.
But that idiot Rehman
wasn't the forgiving type.
He said,
"Bade sahab, you're too late."
And over the phone,
he put nine bullets into Noora's face.
They say the Baloch buried him
in the same land he'd grabbed.
But after Rehman,
Uzair will sit on Lyari's throne.
And he'll come after you, SP,
with all of Lyari behind him.
Don't worry, Major sahab.
SP Aslam is that jinn
who'll still be puffing away
in an LTF car
even after the Judgment Day.
For insulting the Prophet,
there's only one fate…
there's only one fate.
You lose your head!
SP, you know ISI takes very good care
of the mujahideen
who wreak havoc in India.
You remember Zahoor Mistry, right?
The IC 814 one?
He wanted to open a shop
in Karachi.
And he liked the one
owned by that guy.
We asked nicely.
Even offered more than market value.
- Hit him!
- But saying it's an ancestral property,
he refused the deal outright.
Don't hit him, please…
So we looked into him.
Our luck…
turns out he was a Sikh.
Don't hurt him!
Let him go!
Within hours, we spread the rumor
that this infidel
had burned the Quran.
Stamped him with blasphemy.
You lose your head!
For insulting the Prophet,
there's only one fate.
You lose your head!
For insulting the Prophet,
there's only one fate.
You lose your head!
For insulting the Prophet,
there's only one fate.
You lose your head!
Iqbal bhai…
you put out a cigarette with real style.
SP, one more thing.
A jinn only walks in daylight
as long as Allah lets him.
What's done with Rehman is done.
But no more random, reckless stunts.
Nothing like that happens again
without my clearance.
- Good.
- Calm down.
You blindsided my brother!
Uzair, don't be stupid.
Let's go inside.
Now you show up here
with your pack of dogs!
- You've started a war!
- Get lost!
- I won't spare you all!
- Come with me.
You came at my brother from the back!
Sit down and listen, Uzair.
Just listen to me!
After Rehman bhai's death,
everyone thinks
the Baloch reign is finished, right?
But we won't let that happen.
Not just you, Uzair,
all of Lyari wants the heads
of the men who killed Sher-e-Baloch.
And all eyes are on you.
Show everyone who you are.
I want SP's head.
At any cost.
You can't even touch him.
He's got a bunch of Rangers
protecting him.
And do you really think SP did
this on his own?
SP was just a pawn.
He had inside information.
Who gave it to him?
Rizwan!
Salaam, bhai.
I overheard Arshad Pappu on the phone.
He's the one who gave
SP Aslam the exact time
and place to hit Rehman bhai.
He wants to be
the undisputed king of Lyari.
After Rehman bhai's death,
he thinks there's no one left
in Lyari who can challenge him.
Beloved, the day you walked away
You tore my heart right out that day
I gave my love to a heartless fool…
Why isn't SP taking my call?
Go, go, go…
Oh no. Missed it.
SP said he was going
to run an operation in Lyari.
Come on out, you fools!
Your daddy's here!
What the…
Bullets are flying everywhere.
It's a full-blown crossfire.
Pappu Gang on one side.
Lyari Task Force, on the other hand.
It's quite intense.
It's chaos out here.
Get out of there, you fool.
You'll get yourself killed.
Your love, my dear
Made me dance in such a way
Yes, Jameel sahab?
Your love, my dear
SP, what's that noise
in the background?
Are you watching a movie?
What do you need, Jameel sahab?
Hamza says now
that the attack's underway,
that idiot Arshad Pappu
is trying to sneak out.
Keep Lyari sealed tight.
Not one Pathan
should make it out alive.
I know you're Pathan.
Don't take it personally.
Remember Pakistan's ride…
Clip-clop, clip-clop, clip-clop.
Hamza's taking Arshad too lightly.
Petty gunfire won't bring him out.
You!
Won't even let me have tea in peace!
Arshad, my child, where are you?
Those Baloch haven't got their hands
on you, have they?
I'll wipe out the entire bloodline
of these Baloch.
And the first neck I'll cut will be
your son-in-law's, Hamza's.
What are you doing, you fool!
No, not you.
Don't take his name!
My innocent girl's marriage was
all neatly fixed with her cousin.
God knows where this birdbrain came from,
ran off with her,
and now, with Uzair,
he's turned all of Lyari into
a killing field.
I'm just waiting for the day
I get the chance
to send both those fools
straight to the netherworld.
Take my advice.
Do one thing…
Get out of Lyari right now.
I'll arrange everything.
Where are you anyway?
Baloch or Pathan?
Pathan.
Where's Arshad Pappu?
Don't know, sir.
If I speak in terms of personal politics,
I hate the Baloch.
My loyalty belongs to the Pathans.
But a pig once told me,
you can't put loyalty and politics
in the same sentence.
And this is politics, kid.
Hey, hey, hey…
Why are you crying, kid?
Haven't you heard?
Pain makes the man.
We'll wipe out his boys, bhai.
But that rascal Arshad
is nowhere to be found.
Rizwan's got his eyes locked
on his den.
Feels like he's hiding
in one of these places.
Set Lyari on fire.
When the flames reach him,
he'll come crawling out
of his hole on his own.
Dimwit!
Speak up!
Where'd all that
big mouth of yours go?
Who Pathan?
The king of Lyari?
If someone like you walks into my life
Everything would just fall into place
Oh no.
- Arshad, you alright, kid?
- Jameel bhai…
They've burned every single
one of my shops.
They can reach me anytime.
Get me out of Karachi
any way you can.
I tried to tell you,
but you wouldn't listen.
Look, getting you out
of Karachi will take time.
First, you need to get out of Lyari.
SP has blocked every road.
So here's what I'll do.
I'll send my official
siren-equipped vehicles.
No one's got the guts
to stop those cars.
Till things cool down,
you and Yasir go hide
in my milk factory in Mirza Khan.
Alright, son?
Don't worry.
Your Jameel mamu has
got your back.
Come on.
Move it.
Hurry up.
Hey!
- Where are you going, you idiot?!
- Stop right there!
- You…
- Wait!
Rizwan, you dimwit!
Come on.
Come on, you idiot.
Come on!
Come on, you fool.
Look!
Look over there!
We've just received reports
that Uzair Baloch has announced
the curfew in Lyari
will be lifted from noon today.
Residents can step out of their homes.
Shops will be allowed to reopen.
There will be no restrictions.
No one moves from their place.
Got that?
Everyone stays right
where they are.
He thought taking out Rehman bhai
would crown him king of Lyari.
That's what you believed, right?
Tell me.
Speak up.
Speak up, you blockhead!
Go on, let's see you take Lyari now.
From today onward,
in Lyari…
the Pathan gang is wiped out!
Move, you meathead.
How dare you kill my brother?!
You thought you could take over Lyari?
Take it over now, you blockhead.
Do it!
You attacked from behind, you fool!
The king of Lyari,
the pride of Lyari…
Arshad Pappu!
Arshad Pathan!
You idiot!
How dare you kill my brother?!
Move, you moron.
The king of Lyari,
- the pride of Lyari…
- Zarwari sahab,
you've got some very white ducks
at your farmhouse.
Your "buttocks" are really white.
I'll shove those ducks up your butt.
They're demanding
my resignation!
They're hanging people
from electric poles.
They're chopping heads off
and playing football with them
in the middle of the market.
What in the world, Jameel?
Do you have any control
over Lyari or not?
And SP,
what is your
Lyari Task Force doing?
I openly announced the alliance between
PAP and the People's Aman Committee
to the whole world.
And this PAC left no stone unturned
in railroadng me
in front of all of Pakistan.
Major,
what do we do now?
We'll have to divert public attention.
We'll pick up a couple of Baloch boys
from the Gulshan-e-Iqbal
Medical Coaching Center.
We'll label them as BUF terrorists
and finish them in an encounter.
That'll keep the media
busy for a week.
And we'll get time to plan properly.
Not a bad idea.
SP, get on it.
Anyway, we'll have to break
our alliance with PAC.
The Baloch have too much clout
in Lyari, Zarwari sahab.
And in this country, Lyari decides
which way elections turn.
If we don't get PAC's votes,
winning the next general election
will be almost impossible.
What kind of clout?
Rehman's gone.
Arshad Pappu's gone.
Lyari can rot for all I care.
I still have to answer
the people of Pakistan.
Do one thing…
First, declare PAC
a terrorist organization
and ban it permanently.
Throw those idiots out of politics.
He's right.
Absolutely right.
What about Uzair?
Have him killed.
But Zarwari sahab,
after Rehman's killing,
Lyari's already…
Lyari's already on edge.
If Uzair dies too,
Karachi will go up in flames.
So what do we do?
I've got an idea.
Let's get him arrested under the ATA.
Let's send the fool to jail.
Whether he slips on a
bar of soap and dies in prison,
or gets killed in a gang war inside,
what do we care?
The blame won't come on us.
Good.
Do it.
Major?
Uzair, an ATA warrant
has been issued against you.
My child…
Uzair, this isn't a small matter.
An ATA warrant has been
issued against you.
Pack your things and run.
Where's your bag?
I'll look for it.
Hey, Jamali!
I don't care about any ATA warrant.
Got that?
They issued a warrant against
Uzair Baloch.
Those fools…
What?
Let them try crossing into Lyari.
- I'll build a mountain of their corpses.
- It's the ATA! Why don't you get it?!
This time it won't be
the LTF or the police.
The Rangers are coming.
And they're not coming to arrest you,
they're coming to tear you apart.
They'll kill you outright!
I've booked your ticket.
You leave right now.
Until I hang SP Aslam's head
outside the Lyari graveyard,
I'm not leaving!
Don't be stupid, Uzair!
Understand how serious this is.
You can only take revenge
on SP if you stay alive!
As long as you're alive,
you'll get more chances.
Don't act on emotion.
Use your head.
You owe a debt to Rehman Baloch.
And you'll have to repay
that debt, all by yourself.
You will repay it,
of course, you will.
You leave for Dubai.
I'll handle everything here.
Sir, please let us go!
Sir, we haven't done anything wrong!
You handle things over here.
You take care of yourself.
Goodbye.
Uzair's on his way.
He's using an Iranian passport.
He'll land in Dubai in two
and a half hours.
No!
No, no, no!
You Baloch fools have been begging
Pakistan for freedom for years.
Today, I free your black souls
with my bullets.
- No, sir!
Give my regards to the devil.
No!
No…
Excuse me, sir.
Can I have your passport?
- Boarding ticket. Coming from Karachi.
- Yeah, I can see that.
Sir, sir, sir…
What's wrong?
What happened?
Officer! Officer!
It's a mistake!
In a dramatic encounter
earlier this week,
SP Chaudhary Aslam risked his life
to eliminate four militants of the
Baloch United Force in the Phasani jungle.
An LTF soldier, too,
was injured in the attack.
In recognition of his gallantry,
President Aquib Ali Zarwari
today conferred
the Tamgha-e-Imtiaz
on SP Chaudhary Aslam.
He shouldn't have killed the kids.
You knew about this?
Why didn't you inform me?
If I'd told you,
do you really think
you could've stopped SP?
Zarwari?
PAP?
These people rule Pakistan.
Pakistan is ruled by whoever
holds Karachi's leash.
And Karachi's leash belongs
to the one sitting on Lyari's throne.
In this election,
who's giving PAP its toughest fight?
Nawab…
Nawab Shafiq.
Muslim Movement Party.
MMP.
So from today,
Lyari will back MMP.
Set up a meeting
with Nawab Shafiq.
You know that bald
man's shamelessness
starts where all shame ends.
Are you joining hands
with the Muslim Movement Party now?
Not just me.
You too.
If you want to stay in power.
At my age,
you expect me to go sniffing the
Muslim Movement Party's butts?
Hamza…
Have some patience.
I'll speak to Zarwari sahab.
PAP is sinking anyway.
Zarwari's ten percent obsession
has turned all of Pakistan into beggars.
The people won't spare him now.
If you want to drown too,
stay tied to them.
The political throne is about to flip.
Keep election funding ready.
I'll handle the rest.
Nothing, nothing, nothing
Like the man that you are
Come give me something, give me
Something like the man that you are
You're such a wild thing
He's the chief of 25 towns
My beloved's well known
Today I won his heart
Yet lost my own
Crazy in love I wear
A crown high on my head
Whenever he calls
I run where I'm led
I'd…
I'd give my life away
For my handsome love
I'd give it all away
My heart he has won
I'd give my life away
For my beautiful weapon
I'd give it all away…
After losing Rehman and Uzair,
I thought I had ally left in Lyari.
Shirani sahab, I might not be
the Sher-e-Baloch like Rehman bhai,
but I am a Baloch from this soil.
Whatever you need,
anytime,
just say the word.
By right, Uzair may
be the Sher-e-Baloch.
But by intent,
you are the Sher-e-Baloch.
You'll be a good father, Hamza.
Nothing, nothing, nothing
Like the man that you are
Come give me something, give me
Something like the man that you are
You're such a wild thing
He's so sweet can't feel my face
When I'm with him it feels like sin
Young magic till the end of the day
I'm losing all my control and soul
I'd…
I'd give my life away
For my handsome love
I'd give it all away
My heart he has won
I'd give my life away
For my beautiful weapon
I'd give it all away
I'd give it all…
See how this gangsters
Legend travels afar
Even his enemies stand
Helpless before the star
I wear my warrior's bullets like
Jewels on my head
Whenever he calls
I run where I'm led
I'd…
- Hamza! Hamza! Hamza!
- I'd…
KING OF KARACHI
I'd give my life away
For my handsome love
I'd give it all away
My heart he has won
I'd give my life away
For my beautiful weapon
I'd give it all away
I'd give it all away…
My beloved brothers of Karachi,
after this election,
our Muslim Movement Party
has emerged as the largest
political force in this country.
Now it is our duty
to free this sacred nation
from corrupt men
like Mr. Ten Percent Zarwari.
And as long as we stand united
with people like Jameel Jamali
and Hamza Ali Mazari,
we will succeed in this mission.
THE ERA OF MUSLIM MOVEMENT
THE ERA OF NAWAB SHAFIQ
Nawab Shafiq's victory
is being widely credited
to an aggressive ground campaign.
A central role in that campaign
was played by Hamza Ali Mazari.
Pakistani politics has long witnessed
the opportunistic instincts
of Jameel Jamali.
Abandoning the sinking PAP,
he seized the moment
and aligned himself with the MMP.
With this victory
in the national elections,
Nawab Shafiq has been appointed
Prime Minister of Pakistan.
Local sources claim
this sweeping win was secured
- My king of beasts.
- with the backing of Karachi's underworld.
Pakistani politics has long witnessed
the opportunistic instincts
of Jameel Jamali.
Abandoning the sinking PAP,
he seized the moment
and aligned himself with the MMP.
IN THE NAME OF BRIGADIER JAHANGIR
CRESCENT OF COURAGE
I…
Narendra Damodardas Modi
do swear in the name of God that
I will bear
true faith and allegiance
to the Constitution of India
as by law established,
that I will uphold the sovereignty
and integrity of India,
and that I will…
Well done, my princess.
What have you drawn today?
That's me, Dad, and Grandpa.
I will faithfully…
Very nice.
Wonderful.
What should I draw?
Anything you like.
You said your people would win
again this time, didn't you?
Sofia.
Go with Sofia.
I'll join you in a bit.
You poured American dollars
into India's NGOs,
media, socialists, and universities.
You were stacking piles of cash for them.
You even set up a fake currency factory.
And they still won.
You useless, penny-ante hustler!
I asked you for one
legitimate male heir.
What did you give me instead?
Well, it's good this way.
Your clueless daughter will never know
her impotent father was so weak
he couldn't even father a son.
You're a toothless tiger!
Eyes down, Major Iqbal.
I'm your father.
Your father.
- Bashir!
- Yes, sir?
Turn the water off, you fool.
How long has it been overflowing?
Who do you think's going
to shut it off, your father?
Go do it!
Idiot!
In the 1971 war,
Brigadier Jahangir molested
a thousand Bangladeshi women.
Even today, his kids are probably
roaming all over Bangladesh.
If I'd brought back even one
of those whelps and raised him,
he'd have turned out
a better son than you.
Worthless tool!
Put it down, Iqbal.
I need to talk to you.
Iqbal!
I need to speak to you.
Come back!
Turn it around. Take me back.
Leave me.
Take me back!
Bashir, open the door.
I want to talk to him!
I want to talk…
Yes, Bade sahab.
Yes, everything's fine.
Tell me.
Alright.
Yes, he's most likely
in Balochistan right now.
I'll check and get back.
Inshallah.
I burn in the fires of your love
And you do not in mine
I'll not push you away
So that I won't cry over you
I have no luck
No bliss, no good fortune
Take the beautiful girl away
Look who's back like they never left
They see a gangster and a gentleman
Kicking the door, break down the wall
Revenge is in the hands of Allah
This is so magical, you better know
What you want, what you asking for
I burn in the fires of your love
And you do not in mine
I'll not push you away
So that I won't cry over you
I have no luck
No bliss, no good fortune
Take the beautiful girl away
I burn in the fires of your love
And you do not in mine
I'll not push you away
So that I won't cry over you
I have no luck
No bliss, no good fortune
Take the beautiful girl away
The King, the Maharaja
There is nothing in his head
Money like Mansa Musa
Travel like Ibn Battuta
I burn in the fires of your love
And you do not in mine
I'll not push you away
So that I won't cry over you
I have no luck
No bliss, no good fortune
Take the beautiful girl away
LION OF BALOCH
Assalamu alaikum.
- Hamza, my brother!
- You summoned me in a rush.
Everything okay?
Do we have a problem?
We do have a problem, my friend.
The tremors you've set off
have drawn the attention
of the top brass, Bade sahab himself.
Who can possibly outrank you?
You're practically the godfather of ISI.
But even godfathers have a father,
the one ISI keeps on a pedestal.
Come with me.
This will be fun.
Let's go.
Yeah, from the sunrise to the get-go
Where the sun sets, it's lit though
This is big biz, you need big dough
It's a man's world with a chick though
You should stop running
It's gon' get cold
You can't hide now, it's official
They got one eye in the sky
You can't win though
Just look out the window
Oh beautiful
What have you done to me
You left me alone
Oh my mother, what a beauty
Check, one two, we bless you
- Salaam.
- Have a seat. We'll call for you.
- Good afternoon, sir.
Yes, the truth can be painful
But they're trying to kill you
Your queen is your angel
Sir, would you like to have anything?
This is what it's all about
We got a business to run
Putting it all on the line
That's where the legend becomes
Wiser than the tranquilizer…
Excuse me, sir, you've been called.
A man on fire, built like a gladiator
There is nothing greater
Moving to the top without an escalator
How you sip diamond
With a respirator
Come get this gold
Not the scraping paper
When is it enough?
You will be king
This is your time
You gotta rise
Ever since that tea-seller
took over in India,
fear among our people
there has only grown.
If we loosen the grip any further,
the entire system we've built
over decades will collapse.
The path to the throne of Delhi
runs through Uttar Pradesh.
Our mission in Kashmir continues.
For now, prepare for the UP elections.
11,000 crore in counterfeit currency
is ready to be pushed into UP.
I've spoken to Atif Ahmed.
He'll coordinate directly
with Yaqub Ansari in Nepal.
Another 60,000 crore
will be needed.
60,000 crore?
How much money have you
already taken from me?
Send another 60,000 crore into India.
After that, we're even.
Dawood bhai…
He's Hamza.
He's calling you.
He's my boy.
He controls every inch of Lyari.
He's my son-in-law.
Come here, son.
Dawood bhai…
Dawood Ibrahim.
From Bombay.
Salaam, Dawood bhai.
Whenever someone new takes
the throne of Pakistan's underworld,
he has to prove his loyalty
to the Muslim community first…
no matter whether it's
in Pakistan or India.
Kala Nag,
Hafiz Saeed, Laalu,
and Rehman Baloch
have all fought for this very purpose.
Now it's your turn.
For a long time now,
we've wanted to fan the flames
in Punjab again.
How does bloodshed in Punjab
prove loyalty to the Muslim community?
A burning India
keeps our community alive
and our business profitable.
And for that,
from rebels in Punjab
to mujahideen in Kashmir,
from PFI in Kerala to the Naxals,
ISI has tasked us with
mobilizing all of them.
Amarjit.
Our men from across the Punjab
border will be arriving soon
to collect a large drug consignment.
Why? They are available there too.
Yes, but expensive.
We plan to buy cheap drugs
from Karachi,
sell them in India at premium rates,
and use the profits
to buy American
and Russian weapons in bulk.
Beautiful.
So we fund jihad against India
with India's own money.
And at the same time,
turn their kids into addicts.
That's a double win.
Right?
I don't deal in drugs.
Becoming king is easy.
Staying king is the hard part.
Men like us don't get
to choose our business.
So should I take that as done?
Consider it done, Dawood bhai.
No problem at all.
He'll handle it.
Everyone's here.
Iqbal bhai, Javed…
Oh, I forgot myself.
I want the boy to answer me.
He's got the same stare as me.
He'll go far.
Tell SP Aslam
to stay with him until the drugs
safely cross the border.
When's the next meeting
with Dawood?
Maybe after the deal's done.
I need dimethylmercury.
Alright.
I'll arrange it.
In the Uri sector of
India-occupied Kashmir,
an attack has taken place
on an Indian Army headquarters,
where 17 soldiers have been killed.
Indian sources are attempting to link
the incident to Pakistan.
However, Pakistan has rejected
the allegations as baseless,
saying that blaming our country
without evidence
is a deeply irresponsible act.
He is my childhood friend, Jaskirat.
Come on, bro.
Stay strong, buddy.
Hamza paaji,
this is Balwinder Sandhu.
Hello.
And this is Sunpreet Singh.
Everyone calls him Sunny DVD.
And this is Gurbaz Singh.
People call him Pinda.
Paaji.
- Works?
- Absolutely.
How much longer will it take?
About half an hour.
Drive a little faster, bro.
Where are you from, Pinda sahab?
You know Pathankot?
When Punjab becomes free,
I'll take you there myself.
The list?
The list.
Must be here somewhere.
Paaji, make sure the stuff is top-notch.
This is quite a list.
You planning to turn the whole country
into junkies or what?
Paaji, this won't last beyond four
or five districts of Punjab.
- Iqbal bhai.
- Come on in.
- Assalamu alaikum.
- Wa-alaykumu s-salam.
Hamza!
How are you?
- All good?
- Iqbal bhai, this is Pinda.
So you are Pinda.
They are our guests from Punjab.
Salaam, this way, please.
Have a seat.
Look, our old friend
Zahid Akhund is here too.
A true Pakistani.
He's made many sacrifices
for the country.
This shop is his as well.
Don't joke, Iqbal bhai.
It's your shop.
I'm just your employee.
He's the one who set everything up.
He's very close to me.
He was once known as Zahoor Mistry.
We live just across
the border, you know.
If you think you've got the guts,
go ahead. Do your worst.
Shall we get down to business?
Hand it over.
Here you go.
Please.
Let's do this.
"Hash, 200 kilos."
"Kharghosh, 70 kilos."
"Lollipop, 120 kilos."
"Mandakini, 100 kilos."
"Cham Cham, 110 kilos."
"Dubai Dashing, 90 kilos."
"Chika powder, 90 kilos."
That's a lot of stuff.
In bulk quantities.
How's it all going
to cross the border?
That's where my expertize lies, paaji.
Border Force must be
running tight checks.
This is an old family business.
We've run it long before
you came into the picture.
No one's ever managed
to seize even a single packet of hash.
Paaji, there are underground tunnels.
Nepal and Bangladesh boys handle it.
These days, we've got drones too.
We've also got UP's slaughterhouses,
Kashmir's sympathizers.
We've got an awesome
network going, paaji.
Iqbal bhai,
let's lock the deal at 12 crore.
In India, this will sell for at least
150 crore.
Done, paaji?
Seal it.
Finalize it.
Congratulations.
Excellent.
SP Aslam will deliver
the entire consignment
to Hamza's house tonight itself.
And the agreed amount
will also reach you by tonight.
Thank you.
Come on then,
congratulations all around.
Everything's done.
Shah ji, it's not every day
we come to Pakistan.
How about showing us some good time?
Sorry, my friend,
I have to rush to Islamabad, Aabpara.
But Hamza's here.
He'll take very good care of you.
- Really?
- Hamza, throw them a party.
There are great clubs around.
Paaji, we're not tourists from Canada
who you'll drag to clubs.
We prefer a "desi" celebration.
That too with my brothers.
- Nice shawl, SP.
- Jameel sahab.
Looks like you're feeling cold today.
- Hamza…
- SP sahab.
What will you have?
Whiskey?
Okay, I'll get it.
Long time no see.
It's a pleasant surprise.
You sure he didn't recognize you?
He's been high since he got here.
I'll keep an eye…
On whom, Aalam miyan?
- On the guests.
- Oh.
Jameel sahab, shall I make you
a special pomegranate delight?
No, I'm laying off sweets these days.
Good move.
Make me a chikoo shake instead.
- My blood sugar levels are high.
- Perfect.
Grandpa!
- Wear your jacket first.
- My little troublemaker!
My Zayan… naughty boy.
You look great, cutie pie.
Hamza…
Watch it, alright?
There's a kid in the house.
Jameel sahab,
I forgot to mention,
Uzair's being extradited
from Dubai to Pakistan on the 18th.
The Foreign Affairs Department
finally got the order.
SP, you're digging
your own grave here.
Word is, Uzair's sworn
to slice your head off
and hang it at Lyari graveyard's gate.
He won't make it to jail.
On the way from the airport, we'll…
I've already spoken to Shafiq sahab.
He told me to inform both of you
so Karachi doesn't blow up that day.
Take every possible precaution.
Listen carefully.
There are still plenty of Uzair
loyalists inside your gang.
Your boys better not create trouble
when the convoy leaves the airport.
Find a way
so I can send Uzair off peacefully.
Paaji, where's the bathroom?
Go in from here, first right.
- Jameel sahab?
- SP, I have to say…
Paaji, walk with me, please?
I'm so wasted, I'll lose my way.
Idiot me.
They sit in the assembly
and fart such filthy crap
that the place empties
in two minutes.
I swear.
What's up with Zarwari?
No idea.
Probably busy protecting
his white "buttocks".
I'm telling you, all political
parties should be like MMP.
With a clean gut, clean intentions,
and a clean tongue.
You've built a fine house, paaji.
Thank you.
How long have you been living here?
Two, maybe two and a half years.
Don't you miss home, Jassi?
How long you been here for?
Speak up, you dimwit.
I even held a freaking prayer meet
for your death, you know.
Didn't you miss your
mother even once?
How is she?
Fine.
Jasleen's happy too.
We've got two kids.
You turned into a terrorist, dipshit.
Look at what you've done to yourself.
How'd you land up here?
I managed to escape
Sukhwinder's men.
Had a death sentence hanging over me,
so I slipped across the border.
My brave soldier, Jaskirat.
A fake soldier, Jaskirat.
Every month, 30,000 rupees
is deposited
into your mother's account
as compensation.
What kind of compensation runs
for this many years?
That's how I got suspicious.
Seeing you here today…
now I know I was right.
Hey…
What's your game, Jassi?
Keep your voice down.
Who are you working for?
Bhai… calm down.
Hey…
Are you an Indian agent?
Listen to me.
Just hear me out.
Pinda, listen.
Pinda, calm down
and listen to me.
Just hear me out.
Walk away from this deal.
I'm begging you, bhai.
Thousands will die.
Think about your country for once.
Which country?
What country?
That country…
That never once
truly accepted us as its own?
I'm loyal to one thing.
My mission.
And you?
You traitor…
You ran off, leaving your mother
and sister behind.
Who are you loyal to?
You spineless traitor!
Pinda, just hear me out.
Let go of me!
- No! Let go of me!
- Pinda, listen…
- Pinda!
- Stay back!
Listen to me. Stop, Pinda!
- No! Let me go!
- Stop!
Pinda…
I never quit goin' hard enough
Never quit showin' everyone
- Never quit killin' what I touch
- Stop, Pinda!
Never quit winnin' got too much
It got too much often
It got too much quickly
It got me, but it never got in me
I thought that it'd get me back
When they would never
Quit makin' fun of me
- Stop!
- Never quit sayin' wannabe
Never quit those comparisons
Never quit…
Don't you remember when school
Suspension made mom leave work early
Don't you remember me hidin'
Myself just so you don't hurt me
Never quit when I shoulda quit
Never quit what's a bully
- When I can duck under fists
- You…
And laugh at the joke he's pushin' with
I never quit stayin' versatile
But I quit takin' personal
Then I quit carin' who's winning
Cause I quit takin' opinion
Never quit tryin' to be better
Never quit, never surrender
Never quit stackin' these letters
Never quit puttin' in pressure
However, whoever, whenever
Never quit bein' me
Who better, you better know better
I never see defeat
I never quit runnin'
Runnin' when the gun go off
I never quit gunnin'
Gun to my head still none of y'all
Would ever see me slow my roll
- Pinda, stop it! Just hear me out.
- Highest on the totem pole
- Hear me out.
- Destiny my only goal
- Just relax.
- Anything else gotta go
Destiny, you know what I want to be
Destiny, so please don't you lie to me
Who am I supposed to be?
Should I change who's close to me?
Or is it all destiny?
So destiny don't lie to me
I'm tryna listen to the pain
Umbrella the rain and weather the shame
- When is shame gon' come
- What are you doing, Pinda?
Then my brain go numb
I'm tryna listen to the pain
Umbrella the rain and weather the shame
When is shame gon' come
Then my brain go numb
When you feel the shame
What does it do to you, I mean
You gonna let it kill you
Or you gonna let it breathe
Don't take me as a joke
Just take me how I is
A kid who don't know how to stop it
And don't know how to quit
No I never quit runnin'
Runnin' when the gun go off
I never quit gunnin'
Gun to my head still none of y'all
Would ever see me slow my roll
Highest on the totem pole
Destiny my only goal
Anything else gotta go
Don't you remember me
Diggin' through crates
- Don't you remember me tryna be great
- Pinda!
Pinda… Pinda…
My heart was so alone
You played such a clever game with it
Now I spend my nights awake
Thinking only of you
Gambler, O gambler
You're a true magician
I traded my heart for yours
A fair deal in the name of love
I won this game of hearts
By losing my own
I'm a gambler
The finest among all lovers
Hit it!
Come on, beat that drum!
Secretly, through my eyes
You entered my heart
You dipshit!
Get talking!
Why did you kill him?
Who else is working with you?
Tell me!
Who's in this with you?
Speak up, you dimwit!
Speak up!
Why did you kill him, you idiot?
He's an Indian agent!
Who else is with you?
Speak up!
What in the world, Hamza?
He walks into my house…
and kills my guest?
How dare he!
This is Hamza Ali Mazari's house!
Their bodies…
Burn them.
Baloch.
That was fun.
Drummers, hit it!
Two cups of tea.
Who is it?
Aalam.
He recognized me.
He said he'd go outside
and tell everyone.
I asked him to walk away from the deal.
Then he grabbed the injection…
- Then he hit his head.
- Get out of here.
Get out of here.
He's not breathing, Aalam bhai.
I'll handle this.
You should leave.
Aalam bhai, we can say
it was an accident and that he--
Get out of here, Hamza.
What are you doing, Aalam bhai?
Have you lost your mind?
It's important
that you stay alive, Hamza.
You've gone too deep.
Whoever gets caught today
won't die easily.
I've fought my part of the war.
- Yours is still ahead.
- Aalam bhai, no…
Today, a Bareilly pickpocket
gives his life for his country.
Don't take that right away
from me, my brother.
Let the world forget me,
just you remember me.
- That's enough for me.
- Aalam bhai…
Come on now,
go back outside.
- Aalam bhai, no…
- Leave.
Aalam bhai, no…
Just go, Hamza.
Hamza, just go.
Come on, just go.
What can I say
I'm undone by the way you forget me…
O Krishna
Do you remember us at all?
Hamza doesn't kill
without a reason.
Didn't he run a juice stall
with Aalam once?
He's the one
who introduced him to Rehman.
Sir, Hamza never felt right to me.
You suspect him?
Why didn't you say
something earlier?
Sir, I…
Don't worry.
When in doubt, investigate.
It helps you sleep better.
Keeps the gut settled, too.
Hamza's reach goes
all the way to the top.
We'll never get a warrant against him.
Which means we can't search his house.
Do one thing…
Look into Aalam Juice Center.
Don't go yourself.
Hamza's men are watching Lyari.
Send Sajjad instead.
Alright, sir.
You're an Indian?
Hamza…
I told you, you can't ask questions
if you choose to stay with me.
As long as it was about
your business, I stayed quiet.
Now it's about my country.
Are you an Indian agent?!
Answer me!
Are you an Indian agent?
Why?
Why did you ruin my life?
What did I ever do to you?
I can't live with a man
who wants to destroy my country.
Kill me.
Go on…
All you have to do
is pull the trigger.
Do it!
It should be easy for you.
I was the only one
who loved, right?
Hamza probably isn't even
your real name, right?
Muhammad Riyaz.
Ahmedabad blast, 54 dead.
Jaipur blast, 80 dead.
Iqbal Bhatkal…
Mumbai train blasts,
209 dead.
Major Iqbal, Sajid Mir,
Abdul Bhuttovi, Azam Cheema.
26/11 Mumbai attack,
150 dead.
Tell me one name on this list
who was innocent.
They call themselves "Ghazis."
Shame on such Ghazis
who build dreams of their people's
glory on piles of innocent bodies.
Our war isn't against
your country.
It's against the terrorists inside it.
You think they are your people?
What have they been doing
in Pakistan all these years?
520 from the Hazara community
have been killed in the past five years.
630 injured in Quetta.
Do you know
what they do to the Baloch?
Every year,
300 boys are picked up
in the name of interrogation and killed.
Recently, they poisoned
their water supply…
63 children died.
These people…
As dangerous as they are to India,
they're even more dangerous to Pakistan.
I swear on Zayan, Yalina.
Everything I've done
is for my country's safety.
When this is over,
you can tell the world who I am.
You can take Zayan and walk away.
I won't stop you.
But Yalina…
I won't stop either.
To reach this point,
I walked through fire,
and that fire won't die
until it burns them all.
If you can…
forgive me.
Whatever you're planning,
you need to move fast.
SP already suspects you.
And remember…
nothing happens to my child.
First, Rehman bhai,
then your grandson Shehzad.
And who knows
how many innocent Baloch kids
he's stamped as terrorists
and slaughtered without mercy.
A man like that doesn't stop,
Shirani sahab. Not in this lifetime.
Today, he's hunting Uzair.
Tomorrow, it could be us.
What time does Uzair's flight land?
Sir, 3:30 p.m.
Anything from the juice center?
No, sir. It was clean.
Sir, fresh intel just came in.
Hamza went to BUF
to meet Shirani.
Both of them will try everything
today to save Uzair.
A Baloch will always be a Baloch.
First, he sat on Rehman's throne.
Now he wants to sit on our heads.
Let's do one thing.
Today, we pick up
Hamza along with Uzair.
First, we make them talk…
then we crack open both
Baloch heads together.
Those idiots!
Getting to SP is near impossible.
Leave that to me.
I'll give you the where
and the when.
How you finish him…
that's your call.
- SP sahab,
- Yes?
Baloch boys are waiting
on Nishtar Road with weapons.
I suggest you don't take
Uzair that way.
Go through Johar Road behind
the airport. It's safer.
Where are you?
At home.
Jameel sahab's here too.
Goodbye.
Omar…
to become a great man,
you need to take responsibility.
I've collected enough medals
in my time.
Now it's your turn.
Today, you lead Uzair's arrest.
Go.
Make your mark, kid.
And listen…
Yes, sir.
Don't use the Nishtar Road.
Take the Johar Road instead.
Yes, sir.
And you?
Today, I'm in the mood to pull Hamza
down from the heavens to the dust.
Understood, sir.
Hamza bhai, SP sahab is
on his way to your place.
He's coming to take you in.
Omar's heading out to grab Uzair.
Be careful. Goodbye.
Jameel sahab, every man
in this world has a price.
A loyal one just costs more.
Sir, why's Omar's convoy
taking the Johar route?
Hamza's a sly rogue.
He met Shirani.
Told me Johar Road was safe.
The son of a gun must've
lined it up to get me killed.
And listen…
send a bouquet
to Omar's house.
A big one.
Poor kid was a nice boy.
- You love me
- Yes
- I love you
- You're ready
- Yes
- I'm ready
So why should we care
About what our parents say?
Keep your eyes on the road.
Things are about to get interesting.
You need a beloved like me
I need a beloved like you
Let the envious
Turn even greener with envy
Let's celebrate our joy right
In front of them
SP sahab,
I'll always regret you never got
to castrate Jameel sahab
or pimp me out.
Your hatred for us Baloch…
It's justifiable.
Anyway…
we'll settle the score
when we meet again in the netherworld.
That kind of overconfidence
will get you killed, Baloch.
SP Aslam is a jinn, who--
Take a bouquet for SP sahab.
A big one.
In Karachi today,
LTF's senior officer,
SSP Chaudhary Aslam,
was killed in a bomb blast.
According to reports,
a BUF suicide bomber rammed
an RDX-laden vehicle
into SSP Aslam's car.
Sources say the attack
was carried out in retaliation
for the killing of four BUF militants
in a recent encounter.
You need a beloved like me
I need a beloved like you
SP used to speak highly of you.
If you ever need anything,
just say the word.
Yes, sir.
In connection with the Lyari gang war,
this court finds Uzair Jan Baloch
guilty in all 36 cases
of kidnapping, terrorism, and murder.
For these crimes,
the court sentences Uzair Baloch
to 12 years of solitary confinement.
KARACHI JAIL
Talks are underway with the jailer.
TV, AC, sofa, home-cooked food, mattress,
and furniture.
You'll get everything you need.
Be patient.
You won't be inside for long.
You're my brother.
I'll move mountains to get you out.
Jailer sahab,
make sure my brother
faces no discomfort.
No matter what happens.
From today,
his safety is your responsibility.
Thank you, sir.
On September 28th,
the Indian Army launches a surgical strike
against the terrorists camp in PoK.
This strike was in response to
an attack by Pakistani terrorists.
PM Modi said that they wanted justice
for the soldiers killed in the Uri attack.
And the Government gave
the army a free hand
to plan and execute
the surgical strike.
Sir.
I heard about Aalam.
It's been a while,
so I thought I should come see you.
How are Yalina and Zayan?
I saw the news.
Surgical strike.
The winds are shifting in India.
Javed Khanani's brother,
Altaf Khanani, was picked up in the US.
I heard.
Before your last intel reached us,
11,000 crore in fake currency
had already entered India through Nepal.
Another 60,000 crore
is ready to be shipped.
Yaqub Ansari in Nepal…
He's close to Dawood.
He's moving the money
from Kathmandu to Atif Ahmed.
From there, through the butcheries,
it'll fund the UP elections
and terrorist operations.
They'll never let an honest
man take power in UP.
Not after flooding the country
with that much fake currency.
After Uri, the government
gave clear orders.
Dismantle the entire
terror finance network.
We're ready to do
whatever it takes.
That's why we've strengthened ties
with Middle Eastern countries and the US.
The goal is to financially
isolate Pakistan.
To cut off every funding artery.
It's time to expose
Pakistan to the world.
Hamza, the real reason
we asked you to come here is this…
Years ago, someone told me,
"We live just across the border.
If you've the guts,
go ahead. Do your worst."
Well… it's time to do our worst.
From here on,
you have a free hand, Hamza.
Courage. Fuel. Revenge.
Now India will decide Pakistan's fate.
Sir…
Hamza's intel checks out.
The first consignment of 60,000 crore
in fake Indian currency
will move from Karachi
to Nepal by the 15th of November.
Here, sir.
Yaqub Ansari is in Nepal.
He'll make sure the money crosses
into India by the 16th.
Bansal, all the intel and evidence
we've collected over the years…
Keep that ready.
I'm briefing the Prime Minister
and the Home Minister.
Bansal,
we may have to go
for Operation Green Leaf right away.
We'll have to figure out something.
We don't have another option.
You carry on.
From November 8, 2016,
midnight onward,
the 500 and 1000-rupee currency notes
will cease to be legal tender.
We're toast.
Those dipshits have ruined us.
Tell Dawood bhai
that impossible to stop them.
We'll need to pull off something
massive to stop them.
We've run countless jobs for him.
Can't he return the favor just once?
Idiots!
Shut up, dimwits!
Can't you see? That tea-seller has ripped
our guts open and left us bleeding?
Look at you chattering
like a schoolgirl.
Can't you see I'm on the phone?
Bring me my sandal.
Understand this…
UP is out of our hands now.
We'll lose the election.
The rest is in God's hands.
The old 500 and 1000 rupee notes
held by anti-national and
anti-social elements
will now be nothing more
than scraps of paper.
Honest citizens
who have earned their wealth
through hard work and integrity
will have their rights and interests
fully protected.
Major sahab,
how did we not see this coming?
I'm sitting on 60,000 crore
of Dawood bhai's money,
all in 500 and 1000 rupee notes.
I'm finished.
Help me.
Talk to Dawood bhai on
my behalf, would you?
Hello?
Hello?!
We are waging a battle against corruption,
black money, and counterfeit currency.
This will empower the honest citizen
struggling through his daily battles
and us.
Javed bhai, everything okay?
Hamza…
this Modi has ruined me.
I'm sitting on Dawood's 60,000 crore.
Do something, anything, bhai.
You always find a way out,
don't you?
Javed bhai, Javed bhai…
Don't worry. I'll handle it.
- You at the factory?
- Yes.
- Alone?
Do one thing…
Hamza…
Is everything set?
Yes, but what are you going to do
with all these 500 and 1000 rupee notes?
Don't worry.
I'll get you full value.
Is this everything,
or is there more?
This isn't even half.
The rest is upstairs,
in the terrace room.
Come along.
I heard your brother Altaf got
25 years from the Americans?
It's bad luck from every side, Hamza.
Hamza, once we get past
this demonetization mess,
we'll make those Indians pay--
Make them pay how?
That's your last cigarette.
Take your time with it.
Let me go, Hamza.
Let me go, you fool!
I spent 15 years suffocating
just like this
while you all ripped
my country to shreds.
I lost count of the times
I wanted to kill every last one of you.
But looking back,
I know it wasn't the right time.
This is…
the right time.
Now it's… for you to think
what will happen,
if that much fake currency floods
that state and the country.
What implications will it have
on law and order?
I'm sure you'll appreciate
that the only way out is
what we're suggesting, Mr. Kumar.
Police in Allahabad
have arrested Atif Ahmed.
Pertaining to nearly 200 bank accounts
as well as 50 shell companies,
all of the cash transactions
worth more than
50 crore has also been unearthed
as a result of these searches.
What is this?
You told the doctor
you're in a lot of pain.
So… I'm giving you a medicine.
It'll ease the discomfort
and help you sleep long and deep.
Accused of terror financing
in Jammu and Kashmir,
Abdul Rehman Makki
died under suspicious circumstances
after reportedly suffering
a sudden heart attack in Lahore on Friday.
Karachi's Principal,
the former commander of Al-Badr,
Syed Khalid Raza,
who had carried out numerous
terror attacks in Kupwara, India,
has been shot dead in broad daylight
by unidentified assailants.
Come on, dance
Drug trafficker Amarjit Singh,
a close associate of Dawood Ibrahim,
was shot dead today
by two unidentified assailants
in a park in Lahore.
News coming in from Pakistan. Absconding
Indian Mujahideen chief Muhammad Riyaz,
the planner of the Jaipur blasts,
was shot this morning in Karachi.
A shocking report coming in
from Rawalkot in PoK.
Lashkar-e-Taiba commander
Abu Qasim has been brutally murdered.
Onlookers watched in shock
as Lashkar-e-Jabbar founder
was shot dead today
during a celebration in North Waziristan.
Notorious terrorist Syed Noor Shalobar
was gunned down inside an elevator
by two unidentified assailants today.
Come on, dance
Can't you catch a glimpse
Of my love, baby
I want so much more of your touch lately
Give me sweet romance
Throw a glance at me
Come close, we'll hold hands
Come on dance with me
Can't you catch a glimpse
Of my love, baby
I want so much more
Of your touch lately
Another attack by Unknown Men in PoK.
Lashkar-e-Taiba's Khwaja Shahid
has been eliminated.
Come close, we'll hold hands
Come on, dance
Who is behind the killings
of these revered mujahideen
living in Pakistan?
And the question now is,
as this list keeps growing by the day…
whose name will be next?
- Bhuttovi sahab.
- Hamza.
Did you manage to find out
who's behind all this?
No, Bhuttovi sahab.
I can't trace these dogs.
I don't even know
what game they're playing.
What should I do?
They'll connect the dots soon
enough and come for me, too.
Bhuttovi sahab,
if you ask me,
it's best you keep your distance
from your Lashkar-e-Taiba brothers.
Think it over.
It's the smartest move right now.
Anyway, I have a place in mind
where you'd be safe.
A key conspirator
of the Mumbai train blasts,
Iqbal Bhatkal of the Indian Mujahideen
was found shot dead today
in Multan, Pakistan.
Yet another attack by Unknown Men
in Pakistan.
Come on, dance
LET's Khwaja Shahid
was eliminated inside a washroom.
Come on, dance
How long am I supposed
to rot in here?
The stress has wrecked my diabetes.
My sugar levels are all over the place.
Me and you
How is it possible that
no one knows anything
about these murderers?
Me and you
In the same way, no one knew
about you people all these years.
This isn't stopping, Bhuttovi sahab.
What was it you said
during the 26/11 attack?
"Ghazwa-e-Hind would begin from Mumbai."
We now take you
to a sensational development.
An accused in the 26/11 attacks,
Abdul Salam Bhuttovi,
has died in Sheikhupura Jail
after suddenly suffering
a heart attack.
Pandit ji, please,
forgive me, I have to leave.
Sorry, sorry.
Son, would you take over for me?
I'll be right back.
Sit, sit, I'll be right back.
Oh…
Zahoor Mistry.
Remember me?
What was it you said?
"You Hindus are a bunch of cowards."
- Remember me now?
- It was a mistake.
- Good.
- I made a mistake. Please forgive me.
It didn't take much, right?
Forgive me. It was a mistake.
Forgive me.
- Please… forgive me.
- Listen…
Do me one favor, will you?
23 years ago,
I left a sentence unfinished.
Help me complete it.
Glory to…
To…
Glory to Mother India!
Me and you
Come on, dance
Across the country, the list of killings
carried out by Unknown Men
has claimed another name.
Reports say that in Karachi,
Zayed Akhund was shot in the head
inside his own furniture store.
Sources indicate possible involvement
of the Indian government in this.
Iqbal bhai, assalamu alaikum.
Wa-alaykumu s-salam, Hamza.
What can I do for you?
Dawood bhai wants to meet us.
What is it?
Everything alright?
Be there at 9:00 p.m.
We'll talk then.
Okay.
This is dimethylmercury.
Extremely poisonous.
DRDO has developed
its attenuated formulation
that seeps in through your skin
and slowly begins destroying
your kidneys,
your lungs, and your liver.
Early symptoms are similar
to food poisoning,
so the victim never suspects
that they are being slowly poisoned.
What's ISI saying?
We know R&AW is behind it, for sure.
But we're still investigating
who's running their operations
inside Pakistan.
Where the call of Takbir once echoed,
devotional bhajans will now be sung.
In its verdict on
the Babri Masjid-Ram Janmabhoomi case,
the Supreme Court of India
has awarded the disputed land
for the construction of a temple.
The government has also been directed
to establish a trust to oversee
the temple's construction.
Pakistan's Foreign Office has stated
that every country bears a responsibility…
They killed Khanani.
They killed Khalid Raza.
They killed Bhuttovi.
And now they've ripped open
a 30-year-old wound
and declared war.
India has struck us again
and again.
This time, we hit back.
- Sajid.
- Yes.
Azam.
Assemble a lethal unit
from the Lashkar-e-Taiba camp in Muridke.
We will send them across the border.
Iqbal.
Keep an eye on everything.
Inform Atif Ahmed in UP.
Not four or five,
this time, 40-50 mujahideen
will enter India.
But Atif is in jail.
As long as Atif is breathing,
our operation continues.
Jail or free.
Okay.
Hamza.
Yes, bhai.
Stockpile rifles,
rocket launchers,
and top-grade weapons.
Spill so much blood
that even a river of tears
can't wash it away.
You should rest now.
I'll take your leave.
Goodbye.
Next week, deliver a shipment
of arms and ammunition
to our madrasa in Muridke.
We'll also show you how
our mujahideen train.
- Rizwan…
- Yes, Hamza?
Prepare for the next target.
We're running out of time.
Okay.
Bhai, I've spoken to the doctor.
Hello?
Atif bhai, assalamu alaikum.
Wa-alaykumu s-salam.
Good news.
The weapons will be
in place by tomorrow.
Our boys, too, are ready
to cross the border.
Start setting things up on your end.
Yes. I have a medical
checkup this evening.
Ashfaq has spoken to the doctor.
He'll issue a fake certificate.
Two, three days, and I'm out on bail.
Excellent.
Alright then, I'll hang up now.
Goodbye.
Serve the curry.
You can't just eat rice and curry.
- You need eggs, too.
- Yes.
- You want to grow strong like Dad, right?
Then eat eggs.
- Will you eat them?
- Yes.
Yes.
Will you eat eggs?
Will you drink milk?
Good. Go.
After what I'm about
to do tomorrow,
we can't stay in Pakistan for long.
These are tickets to Vancouver.
The moment I'm back
tomorrow night, we leave.
Umar.
In the name of Allah.
Seeing all of you here
brings me great peace.
Blessed is this brother
who has been chosen
to carry forward God's grace
and the next chapter of our fight.
If God wills it,
next time,
the chosen one will be you.
Will you make yourselves worthy of it?
Inshallah.
Will you stand by your brothers?
Will you sacrifice your lives?
Inshallah.
Ma'am, there's someone
downstairs to see you.
- You go ahead. I'll be right there.
- Alright.
Zayan!
Give me.
Zayan…
Go to your room.
No, wait.
Yalina, I'm going
to ask you one question.
Your answer will decide
what kind of life Zayan gets
from here on.
Hamza's death is certain.
If not today, then tomorrow.
And if you lie to me…
you'll never see your son again.
It hurts.
But tell me the truth,
and I give you my word…
Zayan stays safe.
Your name never comes up.
You and Zayan can live in peace.
Yalina…
is Hamza an Indian agent?
Iqbal sahab,
if you haven't tasted bong paya
in Muridke, you haven't lived.
Care for some?
Move back.
Please tell us!
- Mr. Atif! Mr. Atif!
- Move back! Move back!
- What would you like to say?
- Any comments, sir?
Mr. Atif! Mr. Atif!
- He's gained a lot of weight.
- Mr. Atif, did you make it to the funeral?
Mr. Atif, did you make it
to the funeral?
Mr. Atif, did you attend the funeral?
They didn't let me go.
I couldn't attend it.
The main issue is--
Assalamu alaikum, Iqbal sahab.
Thought you should hear this.
Your loyalist, your favorite,
Hamza Ali Mazari,
turned out to be an Indian asset.
Hamza was behind every single
one of our men's deaths.
I've confirmed it with his wife, Yalina.
There's no room for doubt.
Goodbye.
Atif Ahmed and Ashfaq
have been shot dead here.
There is no confirmation yet
on who opened fire.
But we are bringing you this
breaking news live from the scene.
Atif Ahmed and Ashfaq…
You're back, dipshit?
Bravo, Major Iqbal. Bravo!
This is exactly what I expected
from my spineless heir.
Our men are getting gunned down
in broad daylight here.
And in India, even our own allies
are dropping dead.
Shame on you!
After '71, we bled,
we broke our backs
to rebuild this country.
And you wretched curs bent it over
and handed it back to the masses.
Bashir!
Where do you disappear to, you fool?
Take it. Get me out of here.
Listen, Major.
You and your lot
can strain every muscle you've got.
You still won't match them.
And one day will come, Major,
when those Indians drag you
to the border
and make you dance like a kept woman.
Take me away, dipshit.
Be careful.
Bashir, shut the water off!
Turn it off!
Turn it off, Major.
Turn it off, you--
Major.
Brigadier Jahangir,
for 50 years, I've listened
to your fake war stories.
- You kept deceiving Pakistan.
- Let go of me!
You roamed around with the Hilal-e-Jurat
pinned to your chest.
But Mother told me the truth
a long time ago.
Bashir!
Where are you?
Shut up!
This poisonous tongue of yours.
You molested Bangladeshi women, right?
And you lashed at my mother,
my wife, and my child,
with this acid tongue of yours.
What happened in '71?
What really happened in '71?
In '71, to save your own skin,
you sold out your own
army like a cheap loser.
You split Pakistan into two.
Hindus came and stripped
your soldiers of their pants.
You idiot,
the humiliation our country
endured because of you…
I have spent my whole life trying
to restore its lost honor.
You don't deserve an heir, Jahangir.
Your bloodline ends with you.
And mine begins with me.
Major Iqbal once laid
an Indian infidel's severed head
on Musharraf's table.
I swear to God,
tomorrow I'll cut down another Indian
and hang his head
from the minaret of Muridke.
Many years I spent working
And I returned with a piece of sugar candy
But what truly finished me off
Was your laughter, baby
Welcome.
Saeed, Faizan, get the goods.
Wonderful.
Come, have a seat.
The full and final payment.
Feel free to verify.
Don't embarrass me.
Rizwan bhai.
You faced no trouble during
the journey, I hope.
- Call for some tea.
- Of course.
Also get Nizami biscuits.
They are delicious.
What's on your mind, Iqbal bhai?
Hamza…
Do you know…
why I stay on the satellite phone
with the mujahideen during every attack?
To guide them?
To hear the infidels scream.
It soothes me.
It gives me peace.
And still…
the thought of destroying that country
never leaves my mind.
Do you know why?
Because it isn't just a thought.
It's my dream.
For years, we agonized that country,
made it bleed.
And yet my heart
was never fully satisfied.
But… this time,
I can see the dream taking shape.
I can see India burning to the ground.
I can see their country collapsing.
I can see your country fall.
Hamza, servant of God,
tell me, how does it feel
when someone backstabs you?
Thousands of Baloch died
fighting for freedom.
All the people we lost…
do you want to avenge them?
If I bring them all together
under one roof…
what would you do?
I'd unleash the wrath of the depths.
That's exactly how I feel right now,
you dipshit!
The executioner of infidels,
Major Iqbal!
The executioner, my foot!
I won't give you an easy death.
I'll keep you breathing.
First, you'll watch the body
count of 26/11 double.
Then…
I'll personally drag you into the netherworld.
No matter what happens,
press the trigger at the right time.
But you will be in there…
how do you plan to escape?
I'll manage.
If you all are done playing
with your firecrackers…
It's my turn to blow this place up.
Bomb?!
Bomb!
All of you stay in Rangers uniforms.
So the locals think
there's a clash underway
between the Rangers and Lashkar-e-Taiba.
That way, no one will interfere.
We're under attack by the Rangers.
Send the mujahideen immediately.
Come out, you moron!
Come out here!
You thought you'd destroy
the system we built for years?
We won't spare you!
DRIVE SLOW
NEAR SCHOOL
Reduce all of Muridke to cinders.
Rizwan!
Cover!
Cover fire!
Iqbal!
Stop, you jihadi!
You infidel Indian agent!
You walked into my country,
handing out sweets?
You remember how
your country trembled
when Islamabad came down
on Mumbai, don't you?
Now, all of Pakistan will come
down on India.
I'll make every one of you infidels
recite the kalma.
I'll have every last one of you
circumcised.
You toothless tiger!
And your women?
They'll be spoils of war.
I'll peddle them at the den of vice
for pocket change!
Now you die.
Meet your end, you wretched cur!
From the afterlife,
you'll watch your country torn to pieces.
Here you go.
Now it's your turn to die.
You've spilled enough Indian blood.
It stops… now.
Because this is the new India!
We barge into your homes,
and terminate you.
Deceiver…
kill me, and a thousand more will rise!
When the armies of mujahideen
rise from Khorasan,
the star and crescent
will fly over the Red Fort!
When the armies of mujahideen
rise from Khorasan,
you will see,
they will not stop
until they reach India.
Infidel,
listen carefully.
We are not going to stop.
We will keep infiltrating.
Again and again.
We will turn Delhi
into the new Islamabad.
What do you think?
You won't pay for this?
You will see,
on Judgment Day,
you will answer for this.
Long live Paki--
Yalina…
When I am gone, after me
No love like this will ever be
The love that exists between
These two worlds
Omar was here.
Such love will never come to be
I am your shadow
I am your breath
I'll walk beside you
Wherever you may be
So what if I'm gone?
My love will still live on in thee
I want to hear you say
my name one last time.
So what if I'm gone?
I am the last…
Hamza.
Your final love to be
When I am gone, after me
No love like this will ever be
Do you want to know
my real name?
The love that exists
Between these two worlds
Such love will never come to be
Jaskirat.
Jaskirat…
Hamza…
When I am gone, after me
No love like this will ever be
Get talking, you dimwit! Speak up!
You gave Aalam an easy death.
I won't be that kind to you, Hamza.
Start talking, you son of a gun!
Speak up!
Who is in this with you?
I'll keep lashing
you until you start talking.
Speak up, you dipshit!
Who else is in this with you?
Speak up!
Hello?
Hassan sahab.
Ajay…
Sanyal.
Assalamu alaikum.
Oh…
Wa-alaykumu s-salam, Sanyal sahab.
I was just thinking about you.
It's been a long time.
Everything alright at home?
One of my boys is with you.
Word hasn't spread yet.
So here's what I suggest.
Drop him safely near the Margalla Hills.
No tag.
No tail.
Come on, Sanyal.
We've done this a thousand times.
Just sit back and watch this
boy turn into an example.
India's going to be shredded
in front of the global media.
And what my boys do to him…
after that, I doubt he'll ever stand
on his feet again.
Come on!
You're wasting your time.
And most importantly… mine.
- Here.
- Let me have him.
Sure.
- Good night.
You have no idea
how tough that boy is.
He won't crack.
Stay on the line, Sanyal sahab.
In a few minutes,
your asset will start
singing like a canary.
Release him immediately.
Or we'll rain so many shells
on your forward post
that Islamabad will feel the tremors.
We're jihadis.
Infidel threats don't scare us.
Hassan,
are you still fond of stories?
Want to hear one?
Three months ago,
a top-ranking,
highly decorated Pakistani ISI officer
flew to London on a personal trip.
Ready to sell highly sensitive
details of Pakistan's nuclear
program for millions.
To?
The Israelis.
The Jews.
The infidels.
Pakistan's enemies.
General sahab,
I'm sending over some
photos and videos.
I'm sure after you see them,
your knees will buckle
just like your voice.
There lived a certain man
In Russia long ago
He was big and strong
In his eyes a flaming glow
Most people look at him
With terror and with fear
But to Moscow chicks
He was such a lovely dear
He could preach
The Bible like a preacher
Full of ecstasy and fire
But he also was the kind of teacher
Women would desire
Out!
I said out!
All of you out!
Out, all of you.
Out! Out! Out!
Ra-Ra-Rasputin
Lover of the Russian Queen
There was a cat that really was gone--
You really thought Israel
wouldn't inform us?
You understand
what happens if this gets out.
Your own people will hunt you down
and tear you apart
in the streets like a rabid dog.
And they'll burn your innocent wife
and daughter alive.
I want the boy
at Margalla Hills within the hour.
Safe and sound.
No one will tail him.
Soon, an unregistered private jet
will land at the Rawalpindi
Flying Club.
Make sure ATC cooperates.
But Sanyal sahab,
word has already spread
that we've caught an Indian agent.
I'll have to put this on someone.
Uzair.
Uzair Baloch.
Had kept him alive
for a day like this.
I won't call again.
Have a good day.
Goodbye.
May God protect you, Hamza.
Jai Hind.
He's a fight to the death
He's a gun to my head
In Karachi, your handlers
will be supervised by a coordinator.
You may never even come
face-to-face with him.
But if you're ever in a soup,
he'll take care of you.
And put it all in one man
Dad, Omar is going to kill Hamza.
Dad, please… save him.
Do something, please!
Please talk to Uncle Nawab Shafiq.
- Good morning, sir.
- Morning.
Check this out
That's a tight suit…
Those some nice boots…
Why you always got light 'tude
Little brother?
Yes?
Sanyal sahab…
ISI is about to grab Hamza.
They're taking him…
to a black site behind Aabpara.
Please,
act fast.
I'll have to speak
to the Home Minister.
Keep me informed.
Am I gay or am I just angry?
Am I impatient? I can't stop dating 'em
And I'm insatiable
I love the taste of 'em
And I have too much tolerance
Shit!
And if I had more common sense
Then I would grab my ride and dip
And I have too much tolerance
You ugly and fine as shit
And if I had--
Since when?
They sent me here 45 years ago…
to join politics.
Forget them, son.
That's what's best for everyone.
Know this… we won this war
because of you.
But there are many
more wars to fight.
Go. Get some rest.
You've done enough.
I'll always carry one regret.
I didn't get to kill Dawood.
Oh the one with a tilted cap
Oh naive, rustic lad
I can't keep you out of my mind
I'm losing this heart of mine
Killing him wouldn't be as satisfying
as keeping him alive
and watching him suffer.
Faith in love grows stronger
When they pass us by
Like strangers walking by
We risk our hearts
We risk our very lives
My king of beasts.
Be ready at 8:00 a.m.
tomorrow for debriefing.
Bansal will pick you up.
Jaskirat,
you did good.
Give them a bouquet from me, simple.
No, no,
I want you to be with me.
- Bansal?
- Morning, sir.
Hey, Sushant. Come, have a seat.
- Ma'am.
- Have some breakfast.
Thank you.
The asset is on the loose, sir.
What happened?
It's all fine, ma'am.
When you were gone
I used to
Speak to
Your memories
Fragrant
Became all
My paths
With your memories
I don't know how
My eyes well up again
I thought
The grief had reached its end
But my heart won't comprehend
My eyes well up again
I thought
The grief had reached its end
But my heart won't comprehend
My eyes well up again
I thought
The grief had reached its end
But my heart won't comprehend
My eyes well up again
I thought
The grief had reached its end
But my heart won't comprehend
Then…
In lonely nights the one who made
My heart ache endlessly
Was nothing else but only
The shadow of your memory
There was no one else but you
To walk beside me, strong and true
When you were gone, loneliness came
And in my arms, it softly stayed
I never thought
Your memories
Would come this way
That standing here
Before you
My first words
Lose their way
I don't know how
My eyes well up again
I thought
The grief had reached its end
But my heart won't comprehend
My eyes well up again
I thought
The grief had reached its end
But my heart won't comprehend
My eyes well up again
I thought
The grief had reached its end
But my heart won't comprehend
My eyes well up again
I thought
The grief had reached its end
But my heart won't comprehend
Then…
SACRIFICE IS THE HIGHEST DUTY
Destiny, you know what I want to be
Everyone will fall in line,
collect their kit, sign off,
and move out.
Who am I supposed to be?
Should I change who's close to me…
There is no act greater than sacrifice.
No duty higher than sacrificing
for the nation.
The deeper you bind yourself
to these words,
the more pain and suffering
you will be able to endure.
Always remember,
sacrifice is the highest duty.
SACRIFICE
Never quit sayin' wannabe
Never quit those comparisons
Never quit…
This drill isn't just physical.
It's psychological as well.
Your ability to endure pain
will never be allowed
to fall below the enemy's.
Your tolerance, morale,
and patience
will be systematically broken.
Never quit tryin' to be better
Never quit, never surrender
Never quit stackin' these letters
Never quit puttin' in pressure
However, whoever, whenever
Never quit bein' me
Who better, you better know better
I never see defeat
I never quit runnin'
Runnin' when the gun go off
I never quit gunnin'
Gun to my head still none of y'all
Would ever see me slow my roll
Urdu. The Quran. Religious doctrine.
Namaz.
Your command over all of it
must be absolute.
My heart got held by the carefree one
You'll be trained in Pashto, Punjabi,
Sindhi, and Balochi.
Any questions?
No, sir!
By the king of faith, the holy one
You'll break the enemy in the mind first.
And you'll have only milliseconds
to gauge how much pain he can endure.
My heart got held by the carefree one
Today, we'll study steganographic ink,
aka invisible ink compounds.
Specialized ink.
Specialized paper.
- By the king of faith, the holy one
- And…
The false-friend technique,
where you deliberately befriend someone
who's central to your target environment,
the gang you're infiltrating.
Someone who runs on emotion, not logic.
Rehman Baloch, aka Rehman Dakait.
ISI relies heavily on gangs
like his to spread terror in India.
At a recent tribal ceremony,
he was given the title Sher-e-Baloch.
Meaning no Baloch will ever refuse him,
even if it costs them their lives.
I never quit runnin'
Runnin' when the gun go off
I never quit gunnin'
You will learn to stay silent.
It will be mandatory.
Because silence improves
your odds of survival.
Control your breathing.
Control your breath.
This is dimethylmercury.
Extremely poisonous.
DRDO has developed
an attenuated formulation
that seeps in through your skin
and slowly begins destroying your kidneys,
your lungs, and your liver.
Early symptoms are similar
to food poisoning,
so the victim never suspects
they have been slowly poisoned.
The more control you
have over your breath,
the slower you burn it,
the tighter your control
over stress and emotion.
My heart got held by the carefree one
You go full throttle
only when life is on the brink.
Give it your all!
By the king of faith, the holy one
- My heart got held by…
- Destiny, you know what I want to be
- Destiny, so please don't you lie to me
- My heart got held by…
Who am I supposed to be?
Should I change who's close to me?
Or is it all destiny?
Destiny don't lie to me
He has nothing to do with India.
He works for Nawab Shafiq.
What are you saying?
Watch your tone, Omar.
This is above your pay grade.
Stick your neck in again,
and you'll lose it.
He's an Indian agent.
He's slaughtered hundreds of our people.
And you're saying this isn't a big deal?
Just forget the case.
Just go home, Omar.
I won't stay quiet.
I'll go to the National Assembly.
I'll tell them you're involved too.
Dipshit!
You're threatening me?!
Take him away!
- You can't just arrest me like that.
- Declare him insane.
- Ship him to a mental asylum.
- I'll expose you!
I'll go to the National Assembly!
- Take him away!
- I'll expose you!
- You're with them!
- What are you all staring at?
Get back to work!