(Uilhan Brewery)
(1. Malting, 2. Malt milling, 3. Mash tun, 4. Hopping)
(Kim Se Jeong)
(Highly passionate, highly sensitive)
(Lee Jong Won)
(Shin Do Hyun)
(Baek Sung Chul)
(Uilhan Brewery)
(Naro Beer)
(Brewing Love)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Scenes with child actors and animals were filmed...)
(under production guidelines along with experts.)
Hold on.
Didn't you say you'd wait?
I was doing just that.
Who waits for a meeting right in front of someone's nose?
What's going on? Is this a romance flick?
Should we give you some privacy?
If you stand around like that, who will trim the weed...
that keeps growing despite being cut down daily?
You're bothering the ladies.
Come on.
Hold on a second.
Why are you picking up a sickle?
How can I sit around...
and let the ladies work alone in this heat under the blazing sun?
- I should help. - Hold on.
Don't do this. To be honest,
you blatantly trying to kiss up to me won't work.
Who's trying to kiss up to whom?
It's true that I'm lurking around your property...
hoping to strike a deal with you,
but this isn't me trying to score points.
One should help those in need.
But... Weeds are no joke.
It isn't easy to work with a sickle.
You can get hurt. Hold on!
The two of them are like water and oil.
Tell me about it.
However, opposites attract.
- What on earth? - What?
- Come on. - What about it?
(Episode 3)
Goodness.
I'm good with sickle and shovels.
If I think about all that shoveling I did in Mount Baekma...
That'll be all.
Boss. Hire Chae Yong Ju as a part-time worker.
She used to be in the special task force.
No. No way.
I'll call the part-timer I already have.
Goodness.
Chan Hwi, it's me. Can you work a shift today?
You can't?
No, it's all right.
It seems as though I should stay, right?
Sure.
Oh Chan Hwi, cleared.
(Brewing Love)
(Hwi's Toast)
Chae Yong Ju.
I had to turn down that part-time gig for her,
but she's not even at the office.
What is she even up to?
I should just head back.
(Hwi's Toast)
I'll be back.
Wait.
What was her name again?
Ye Ppeum?
Yi Ppeum?
I got it. Ah Reum as in beautiful.
What the...
- What was that? - Did you hear that?
- No way. - That was weird.
Why...
Why did I turn away?
Since I'm here, maybe I should stay the day.
Clinging onto Yoon Min Ju in the hope of striking a deal...
is hopeless.
What I need the most right now is...
intel.
Yoon Min Ju.
Tell me who you are.
That's just how it is.
- Is that so? - I mean it.
It's driving me crazy. You see, the other day...
Loud noises often trigger headaches for him.
Unbelievable.
What happened there?
It's nothing.
Physical contact makes him uneasy.
He can't stand anything rubbing against his skin...
and cuts off the tags on his clothes.
That's why most of his shirts have holes in them.
Yoon Min Ju...
is highly sensitive.
Goodness, thank you.
- Good work, everyone. - Good work.
- You all did well. - How about a drink?
Sure.
Goodness me. Look at her working hard.
Even the weeds will stay away at the sight of her.
Sure.
That's it.
Pace yourself. You don't want a heatstroke.
It's fine. My working more means more time for the ladies to rest.
I should work hard while I'm at it.
Why bother working so hard when it'll go unnoticed?
That's not why I'm doing this.
Is that perhaps for me?
- Yes. - Nice.
- What... - Wait!
Darn. Seriously?
Did you see my core strength?
There's no falling for me. Nice!
How can I send her packing?
Are you okay?
Goodness.
He's fine!
Kicking his knees against something is a pastime of his.
He's one to often leave his wits at home.
I usually have a lot on my mind.
Let's grab some lunch.
Yoon Min Ju often walks into things.
What? But it's not lunch hour.
Sorry?
Goodness.
Since it's a hot day, let's call it a wrap early.
I'm sure you'll be EAT like always...
as in "eating alone today."
How come you're still asking that after all this time?
- You sure are persistent. - I know.
I'll eat alone.
- What about you, Ms. Chae... - Goodness.
Don't mind me. I'll grab lunch where I can.
Sure. Enjoy your lunch, then.
Isn't this unreasonable?
You have to eat outside in the sun,
but he's heading home to eat indoors in a cooler space.
No one said anything about eating out in the sun.
I'm exhausted, oh, wild bee
Come with us if you want.
We'll take you to a place that will surprise you.
Here.
Open sesame!
Gosh, it's so cool in here.
No way.
You could even live in here!
Are you seriously surprised by this?
This is what we're entitled to.
Said by our boss.
So go ahead and relax.
Yoon Min Ju takes good care of his employees.
I hardly expected this from him.
Gosh, my head.
I'm all out of sorts.
One should help those in need.
That's not why I'm doing this.
Photo, there are such kinds of people.
Those who give their all to help others...
but fail to look after themselves.
People who don't know how to take care...
of themselves.
It makes me uncomfortable...
to see her.
This won't do. I'll send her home this afternoon.
I should put an end to this. Right?
Hey, why won't you believe me?
I can be cold-hearted when I need to be.
(Jisang Liquor)
She went to see him once again.
She really isn't the average person.
Highly ambitious is what she is.
I just hope her actions don't backfire on me in any way.
(Planning Team's Director Yeom)
My office.
- Did you call for me? - Bang Ah Reum.
Why are you at the office?
Ms. Chae of the Marketing Team...
is out there trying to sign a deal with Yoon Min Ju.
In my opinion,
there's no chance of him working with us.
So instead, I put together...
a list of breweries we can merge with...
- that are similar to his... - Bang Ah Reum.
Who are you to make that judgment call?
Do you know why we're putting everything on the line...
for a nobody like Yoon Min Ju?
Because the chairman...
of Jisang Liquor wants him on board!
That's why we must lay down our lives for this.
Or we'll get the boot.
Don't make me compare you to Chae Yong Ju.
Yoon Min Ju.
- I'll meet with him again. - Bring him here.
We're running out of time.
Yes, sir.
He didn't even read what I put together all night.
How am I supposed to persuade Yoon Min Ju?
Strike that. I must get it done.
I only have one year left.
That darn little twerp.
Ah Reum.
- Yes? - Did you get an earful?
Of course not. It wasn't enough to faze me.
We never doubted you.
Would you like to join us for lunch?
Go ahead without me.
I'm having a salad anyway.
I'm watching my weight.
(Jisang Liquor)
What's this delicious smell?
- Thanks. - Thanks.
- Please enjoy. - One cheese toastie.
- A cheese toastie? Got it. - Yes.
Thank you.
- Thanks. - Thanks.
Enjoy!
(At Hwi's Toast, we cook to order.)
Wait, it's Ms. Beautiful Bang.
You're really here.
Don't you work at CEO Yoon's brewery?
That's right.
You got it right, the name is Oh Chan Hwi
What brings you here?
Who exactly are you?
(Hwi's Toast)
Yummy!
Isn't it good?
You'll be coming back for more.
All over the country,
there are customers of mine who are hooked on my toasties.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- I won. - No way.
I can't believe you.
I mean it.
Do you want another?
Hey, Grandma.
I'm working.
Have you eaten?
And your medicine?
You still have a lot left. Are you sure you're taking them?
Grandma, I can't be there to manage everything.
You have to...
Hello?
You always hang up when you know you're in the wrong.
Unbelievable.
It's really hot in here.
Thanks for that.
Why are you here alone?
Where are the ladies?
It's hot outside, so I told them to rest longer in the den.
Right. I knew it.
It must be just you and your grandmother.
How did you know that?
You said you always couldn't manage her medicine intake...
which means you're the only one she has.
How perceptive of you.
When it's hot outside,
nothing beats a cold cup of iced Americano...
That's so sweet of you!
Thank you so much.
This is more acidic...
Acidic, what?
- That brought me back to life. - Forget it.
Now I'm craving a sweet cream bun...
Are you kidding me?
(Cream Bun)
Are you Mary Poppins?
- No way. - How's the injury you suffered?
It's fine now...
That reminds me. How did you know that?
I never told anyone.
You're the first person to ask about it.
Well...
My gosh!
Goodness.
Wait.
Thanks.
- Here. - Thank you!
Tie your hair with this.
Wait. Sorry.
Should I tie it back for you?
- Would that be possible? - Yes.
Thank you.
Wait a second.
How did you know to bring a rubber band?
That was all I had to tie hair.
The yellow rubber band.
It hurts when letting down your hair.
Also, it makes you lose your hair too.
You know a lot of things.
By the way, how did you know about all this stuff?
I'd die for some coffee.
Ma'am, what kind of coffee do you like?
I prefer men like this guy...
No, I meant coffee.
(Checklist: Coffee)
- Gosh. - It's so tiring, isn't it?
It's the right time for sweet things.
You aren't diabetic, are you?
Why are you only asking me?
- So you're not. - I'm not.
I'm not either!
- "I don't either!" - You've got diabetes, no?
(Checklist: Coffee, sweet snacks, hairband)
You're right.
She worked hard. She deserves a cup of coffee.
(Checklist: Coffee)
Cream bread.
(Checklist: Sweet snacks)
Here it is.
What about a hairband?
(Checklist: Hairband)
Do I even have one?
(You poor one, Min Ju)
I feel like I've gotten a little bit closer to you.
Folks!
Look what's happening here!
That's why you told us to come late.
- That's not... - Goodness. What should I do?
That's a misunderstanding. It was...
My hands were dirty, so I needed help...
Didn't you tell us she was prohibited from entering here?
Did you see our boss...
- gently touching her like this? - Sure!
It makes me uncomfortable.
This won't do. I'll send her home this afternoon.
I should put an end to this.
Actually, I was about to tell you something
Ms. Chae,
I would like for you to leave here now.
Suddenly? Why?
I feel uncomfortable.
I feel uncomfortable whenever you see me.
But I told you I wasn't doing this to impress you.
Is it because you just can't stand seeing me?
I can't be that bad.
All I did was help out a bit.
How could you say that?
You're the worst.
You're the worst of the worst.
I'm leaving, then. For now.
This isn't how I wanted to send her away.
I'm the only one who thinks this is unjust?
Is that your way to block all the people around you?
What a twist with rudeness!
(Uilhan Brewery)
(Carbon Dioxide)
I won't have to deal with her now, right?
No, I kept cool.
Yes, I was.
That's the end.
What are you talking about?
(Uilhan Pub)
Did you think I'd just leave and give up?
I haven't even started yet.
When is this place going to open?
Something interesting inside?
Chief, when does the pub open?
That's something a thirsty soul should know.
- Then, can I have one now? - Sure!
It's still daylight.
Chief,
how much Naro draft beer is left inside this keg?
You mean now?
Let's see.
This keg can hold 20 liters of beer.
- I think it's still half full. - Then, there's about ten liters.
Take a seat over there. Will a 500ml glass be enough?
No, give me a ten liters, please.
(10 liters?)
What?
(Uilhan Brewery)
Here. Here you go.
(Uilhan Pub)
I guess she'll really drink all the beer here.
Yoon Min Ju can't stand the sight of me.
Then, I can make him come over to see me!
(17th Village Chief of Baegok-ri, Very Nice Man)
CEO Yoon, you better answer my call now.
Answer the phone.
- Yes, Chief? - CEO Yoon!
She's beyond your imagination!
Sorry?
(Uilhan Brewery)
Darn it, Chae Yong Ju.
It's a never-ending story!
- What was that? - You tell me.
You drank it all.
There's nothing left now.
So, please leave now.
- What did I do wrong? - Chief.
Originally, I used to work as a saleswoman...
in Busan for a long time.
Baekmok Liquor had a dominant power in Busan.
So, it was very hard to sell our products in pubs and bars.
So, whatever we produced, we couldn't sell any of it.
At that moment, I came up with an idea...
It's too much. Are you sure you guys can drink all?
Sure, owner.
We Jisang Liquor are all thirsty souls.
So, please take our beer and just show it to your customers.
If they don't sell, we'll drink it all! Right?
- That's right! - That's right!
Please give me another.
I used to drink a lot back then.
Those were the times.
I'll save our colleagues...
no matter what.
I'll make sure they're fine!
How about you save me first?
Darn it. Why isn't he here yet?
You...
Why are you just standing there?
What took you so long?
- I'm leaving now. - Please, wait.
She and I just don't see eye to eye.
Wait, so you're leaving?
It's even worse for me.
- So what? Deal with it! No! - No, wait.
She's really something. She really is.
My goodness.
Oh, no! I'm so forgetful.
I need to order beer for the festival.
Why that... Darn it.
(Uilhan Pub)
My gosh! We meet again.
You're dragging me into these situations where we meet again.
Whatever.
Let me ask you just one straightforward question.
Why is it that you can't even stand the sight of me?
You see, I'm...
Never mind.
I know you're trying.
But...
you're trying way too hard.
How did you know?
You treat your job like your entire life, don't you?
And you try to help others with everything.
You were in the special forces, so you'll try...
to protect your employer like they're your country,
but don't do that.
It'll only eat away at you,
without you even realizing it.
Are you all right?
I told you. You're not okay.
Feelings don't vanish on their own. They'll keep piling up like this.
They'll fester and eventually explode.
Should I tell you what would happen after that?
Hey.
Are you sleeping?
My gosh, Chae Yong Ju.
She can keep her posture even while dozing off.
She keeps her guard up even when she sleeps.
Why is she trying this hard?
I should take her, right?
(Uilhan Pub)
(2024 Uilhan Hop Beer Festival, Happy Beer Festival)
(2024 Uilhan Hop Beer Festival)
A little more to this side.
- How about now? Is this good? - No, that doesn't look good.
- More? - Yes.
- Like this? - That's right.
- It's good now, right? - But why does it...
look like this?
- Why does it look like this? - Yes.
- It's downhill this way, - Yes.
- and it's uphill this way. - Right.
It's a slope, so it's naturally higher on one side.
Come on. Let's go.
- Go where? - Let's get some work done.
We should finish this. Where are you going?
- We're done here. Come on. - What?
- Come on up. Let's go. - Goodness! He always does this.
He never finishes anything properly.
You know, I'm casting my vote that Chae Yong Ju will come back.
- So, just one vote? - Yes.
I'll use my 2 hands and 2 feet, so she gets 4 votes from me.
I knew it. Great minds think alike!
Yes!
What?
What's that wrapped behind our boss's back?
I see that he's got luggage.
- Boss! - What?
(Uilhan Hop Beer Festival)
Chae Yong Ju is really back!
She's really something.
I'm giving up.
Come over here!
You can set up here! Keep it neat and tidy.
Is it going well?
- You scared me. - Why do you have it on your head?
- Hurry up. - Doesn't this look nice?
- Look. - What are you making?
This hat completely blocks the sun.
Goodness gracious. Look at that clown.
- What? - My gosh, hello!
We're here!
Oh, boy. You must've been very busy.
I had to take off when you were so busy,
so I've been feeling really bad about it.
You bet. We've been busier than ants.
But then again, what would you even know? You've been playing hard.
All we do is work,
and all you do is play, you know?
What's going on, Jjuan?
I thought you went back to Vietnam for good.
You were away for a while, so I thought you were gone for good.
- Yes. - I'm going back to Vietnam.
No!
My goodness. I told you not to say stuff like that.
My sweet bride here will think you're being serious!
Come on. It means they're happy to see you again...
and that they missed you.
- Yes. - That's right.
Thanks for the envelope.
Thank you for coming back safe and sound.
Now, that's a better picture.
Darn, that looks awful. Really awful.
What an eyesore!
(Uilhan Hop Beer Festival)
Nice, a beer festival?
- Oh, boy. Take it easy. - You too.
My gosh!
- My goodness. I'll help you. - Oh, boy.
Oh, boy. You've sobered up already?
Your liver must be very healthy.
You don't need to help me. You look dainty and weak anyway.
Well, everyone here is older,
so I should help out as much as I can since I'm young.
She should compete in a wrestling tournament.
What's she doing here?
She really is something. Oh, my.
My gosh, you're amazing.
Here, have some water.
- Here. - Thank you.
Drink up. Oh, my.
- Well done. - I've been watching you.
You can really get stuff done.
Can't you move here?
Well, shall I just live here, then?
That'd be so amazing!
I'm expensive though.
That woman looks familiar.
Wasn't that the young lady who got drunk, blacked out,
and slept like a log earlier?
Why is she showing up everywhere?
Can she teleport herself?
- That hearty laugh. - Oh, how's it going?
Not well.
- My gosh, Chae Yong Ju... - What is it?
Wait! This beer festival.
I heard you organized this, Mr. Yoon.
I know. It's hard to imagine, knowing his personality.
But he really was the biggest contributor!
Are you pretending you didn't hear us even though you're proud?
Why can't you just say it?
"I organized this festival."
Why can't you say that?
Just say it, sweetheart!
My goodness. That's enough, all right?
Well, I should hurry up and make hop wreath samples.
- Oh, I'll help you! - No, I politely decline.
- Please, let me help. - No, it's really fine.
- Anyway, aren't you hungover? - What?
Who drinks ten liters of beer at once?
- I do! I'm totally fine. - No, wait!
I think she's our only option if we want to make it work in one blow.
Yes. Let's send them to the valley of love...
where they'll enter as two people and exit as a family of three.
Shoot.
Oh, this looks nice.
Well, this is pretty.
Does this look all right?
Oh, okay.
What is this? My gosh!
What are you doing?
Why? What is this about?
My goodness. What is this about? I can walk.
Goodness. You ladies are very strong.
You need to seal the deal with our boss, don't you?
Shall we step in and help you?
- Do you have a good idea? - Yes.
Go into the woods and get some Fischer's ragwort.
- Oh, Fischer's ragwort? - Yes.
Okay, but why do you need Fischer's ragwort all of a sudden?
You can only find them until June. Am I wrong?
How do you know that?
- Attention! - Yes.
Fischer's ragwort is an excuse.
Excuse!
Yes, that's exactly what I wanted to say. All right.
- Okay. - We'll handle the rest.
- Now, off you go! - Okay, I'll go now. All right.
Good. She's gone. Moving on to our next target.
How is this supposed to help me?
My gosh.
Seriously, how many times have I been kicked out?
This really isn't easy.
Fischer's ragwort? What is going on?
Hey, why are you here? Oh, my.
My goodness.
Nice, score!
Where have you been? You were gone for a while.
I made these all by myself.
Boss.
Hurry up and go into that mountain in the back, okay?
- The mountain in the back? - Yes.
We sent Chae Yong Ju there and told her...
to get some Fischer's ragwort.
But the thing is, we can't reach her now.
It'll get dark very soon in the mountains.
And you know, wild boars have been sighted there.
- Yes. - What if something bad happens?
Oh, well. Don't you worry.
She'll beat wild boars too. She's like a human weapon.
Fine. Even if she gets eaten alive by wild boars,
I don't care!
- Yes, let's not worry. - That's right.
- The worst is death anyway. - In that mountain, she will die.
But I heard her grandmother was the only family she had.
- What do we do? - Oh, no. I don't know what to do.
I don't know either. My goodness.
Oh, no. What should we do?
Oh, dear. This is bad.
Her grandmother will be so worried.
- Nice. - Why is it that...
- What? - you ladies suddenly sent...
Chae Yong Ju and Yoon Min Ju to that mountain?
Well...
Don't tell me...
Are you hoping they'd end up together?
Goodness. What is with you?
Can you ladies not see?
At a glance, I can tell they're not compatible.
They're like polar opposites. My goodness.
You ladies are clueless, seriously.
- You really know nothing. Oh, boy. - Sure.
No, that's not going to work. Goodness, these people.
- Hey, can't you... - No wonder he's still single.
- He's a good man though. - Yes, he is.
Where did she go?
Ms. Chae Yong Ju!
I hope she didn't fall or roll down the side.
Darn, they fooled me again.
Those ladies are definitely up to something.
I can't see a thing.
Did something really happen to her?
What's that?
What?
Oh! Hi!
What... My gosh.
Is this "I Am a Natural Person," the TV show?
What are you doing here?
Well, I'm trying to start a fire.
I was so busy picking herbs that I didn't realize it'd gotten so dark.
My phone battery died, so I'm just going to sleep here...
and descend when the sun comes up in the morning.
You're going to sleep here? Wait, you will sleep here?
That's not something you should say so naturally, is it?
Isn't it pretty nice here?
Well, I thought I could manage without a fire,
but I guess it's colder in the mountains.
You want to start a fire?
Well, I'll do it.
- Do you have a lighter? - No.
Then what? Are you going to rub branches together to start a fire?
Do you think that's easy? Your wrists will hurt like crazy.
Everyone carries a fire striker around, you know.
Who does that?
Just kidding.
All right.
- Oh, my. - There.
What?
These days, the sun rises at around 5am,
so let's stay here for a bit and start heading down soon.
If you try to descend now, you'll sprain your ankle as it's so dark.
Okay.
Hold on. I'm just realizing I haven't heard your answer yet.
So? Why is it that you just can't stand me?
Wait.
You didn't hear my answer because you fell asleep.
Fine.
Just go ahead and tell me honestly now.
What is the reason?
I hate feeling uncomfortable like this.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Are you mad at me about something?
If you're mad at me, let it out and yell at me.
I'd much prefer that.
- That way, we can talk it out. - You should...
breathe.
You're too worked up right now.
We can't talk if you're like this.
Now,
can I talk?
Yes.
Telling others to just let out their anger and let it go...
could make some people uncomfortable.
Some people can express their anger and let it go,
but there are also people...
who really struggle to return to their daily life...
when they let themselves get angry.
And for some people, that's more painful.
I'm one of those people.
I should've been more thoughtful.
I'm sorry.
I've never been mad at you.
And I never hated you.
It's just that when I see you...
I'm reminded of my old self. That's all.
If my discomfort made you uncomfortable as well,
I apologize.
No, well...
You don't need to apologize.
I'm surprised that you get flustered too.
What? I'm not flustered.
When I was young,
what I heard the most was...
"Why are you so sensitive? Man up."
I heard that the most.
My dad was a soldier.
What?
Well, he wanted his son to be manly, like most dads would,
but as you can see... He ended up with a son...
who cried at anything and everything.
He wanted me to climb as high as I could no matter what I did,
and he wanted me to be at the center of it all.
But in reality, I was like a solitary island.
I isolated myself because I couldn't even be normal,
like a strange solitary island.
I didn't bring the supplies.
I'll get scolded, right?
I'll help you, so don't be upset.
Thanks.
Hey, can you help me with this?
Hey. You stopped caring about me.
That's hurting my feelings.
Okay.
I'll help you. Don't be so upset.
Thanks.
Why am I...
different from other people?
Everyone is different.
Why would you want to be like everyone else?
How much longer will you keep crying like that?
Stop it.
When I look at you,
you remind me of the son my father wanted me to be.
Your military boots...
keep dragging me back to my past.
I can never anticipate your next move.
May I hold your hand?
I mean, it's just a handshake.
To comfort me?
You're not a weirdo. It just means you're a kind person.
Being kind isn't an easy feat.
Your willingness to help others...
knowing your kindness wouldn't be reciprocated...
Not everyone can do that.
How long...
did it take for him to be able to tell...
his story this calmly?
So are you happy now?
Well,
my life isn't so bad.
Well, someone saved my life six years ago.
Hey!
You're okay.
Everything will be okay.
I can't remember anything about that person...
except for...
what that person said to me.
I should block out everything...
that's harming me...
to protect myself first.
And that's being kind to myself.
I've been trying my best to follow...
what that person advised me to do.
Be kind to myself...
Isn't that for people who don't have to face struggles in life?
Aren't there more people...
who don't have the time or resources to look after themselves?
Did you know?
When you start...
to feel emotional,
you quickly cover your nose first.
If you keep suppressing them,
it will become a habit.
I'm going to get some sleep.
I'll stay by your side.
So...
please rest up tonight.
Hello, ma'am.
Did I get my grade?
Well, you are in Grade A.
But it's an A minus.
It's not just an A.
An A minus?
The occupations of the parents are important these days.
Many of our clients check...
if they have specialized careers or not.
But your parents...
- My dad is in cryptocurrency. - My gosh, don't worry.
- That will be more than enough. - My mom is in real estate.
I can't lie, though.
Okay.
I'm going to work.
How could I get Yoon Min Ju on board?
Is that really the only way?
Don't make me compare you to Chae Yong Ju.
It's better than getting compared to her.
Yes. I can't stand that.
If I put my mind to something, I can get it done too, Chae Yong Ju.
Sergeant First Class Chae Yong Ju.
What? What time is it?
You're up. It seems you had a restful night.
Me?
No way.
I rarely lower my guard.
Look at that.
That's the saliva stain.
My what?
You're lying.
We should go back down.
It's the day of the festival. We have so much work to do.
And the people in the village love me.
I'm certain they've been waiting for me all night.
My gosh. You make it sound like you're hosting the festival.
Even when I get drunk,
I never let myself loosen up like this.
Why did I sleep through the night?
Goodness. I've been slacking off on my discipline.
Why are you beating yourself up for it? Things like this happen.
My self-discipline has been weakening lately.
Goodness. Could you stop with that?
No one's going to criticize you...
for letting yourself loose.
So you shouldn't be so harsh on yourself either.
The day just started too.
Aren't you the enlightened one?
My gosh, wait up for me.
(Baegok-ri Town Hall)
- Hello. - Hey.
I'm Section Chief Bang Ah Reum from Jisang Liquor.
- Where's everyone? - Don't you know who I am?
I'm the village chief.
I got them all in one place. Go inside.
(Many a little makes a mickle.)
Hey.
What is it that you want to talk to us about?
We need to go and get ready for the festival.
Can you get to the point and make it brief?
What a hassle this is. Why did you want us here?
We don't have all day.
Gosh, they are people who are much older than her.
Why are we letting her boss us around like this?
- Right. - Gosh, let's hear her out first.
Everyone.
I'll help you make a fortune.
- A fortune? - What?
- What did she say? - Did she say a fortune?
Everyone, it sounds like this might take a while.
- Let's hear her out. - Sure thing.
Don't you want to sell a lot of Naro Beer?
Sure.
But you're not making much compared to the labor you put in.
I guess our money has feet. It seems to disappear.
Let me tell you why.
The production volume is low because the brewery is small.
Then what's the solution?
Make a super big brewery.
Then we can just produce a lot of beer.
Precisely.
Jisang Liquor has an annual production volume...
of 500,000KL.
What did you say? Five hundred what?
How many bottles is that?
If each bottle contains 500ml,
we would produce one billion bottles.
One billion bottles.
Then how much would we make from all that?
Hold on.
Why is it so quiet here?
It's not usually this quiet.
Maybe, it's because it's still early.
What's the point of making a lot of beer?
- You must sell a lot of it too. - Right.
To do that,
you must have solid distributors all over the country.
Jisang Liquor has 16 direct stores all over the country.
Don't forget about Jisang Supermarket,
Jisang Department Store,
and Jisang Convenience Store.
Naro Beer will be available everywhere.
My gosh.
And the future profits would be incomparable to what you make now.
This sounds amazing!
Hold on.
Then what's Ms. Chae Yong Ju doing here?
Does she have a different agenda?
Ms. Chae Yong Ju from the Marketing Team...
wants to hire Mr. Yoon as a brewer,
so he can launch a new beer product for Jisang Liquor.
She would be taking only Mr. Yoon to Seoul.
What?
That means she wants to steal Yoon Min Ju from us.
Then what about us?
I see. She wants us to starve to death?
Well,
that would be the worst-case scenario.
I can't believe this.
- I can't believe this. - I can't believe this.
- My goodness. - This is awful!
Ma'am!
I got the vegetables!
- Don't come. - No.
That little...
She's back.
- Let's go and talk to her. - Why is she back?
- I can't believe this. - Let's go.
- Goodness. - How could she do this?
What? She seems chirpy this morning.
- How dare she? - What?
- What's her deal? - I can't believe this.
- Unbelievable. - Goodness.
- I can't focus on work now. - Seriously.
- We need to talk to her. - Let's talk to her.
What...
- Let's hear from her. - Let's go.
I heard she disappeared.
What's wrong? What's going on?
- What's this? - Even I would be so angry.
Right.
- Hey, Mr. Yoon. Come here. - What?
What? Go ahead. Just talk to me.
- No, Chief. - No!
- Don't do it. - What are you doing?
- Stop it. - What are you doing?
- Come on. - Let go.
Oh, no.
Come on. My goodness.
Sir.
I...
I wasn't trying to throw that at your face.
I mean, it's your fault!
Because you had such an evil plan,
you were punished by karma!
I wasn't trying to do that on purpose.
- Right. - Exactly.
- Yes. - What are you talking about?
- You can't do that. - Come on.
(Brewing Love)
I want both of you to leave right now.
I can't leave like this.
Me neither.
What did you say to the people in the village?
I only told them the facts.
If we make a deal with Yoon Min Ju,
he could sign with us, right?
You need to judge objectively if Ms. Chae is...
a trustworthy person.
Of all people, at least you can judge me for who I am.
I've been doing that...
from the beginning.