Because we must break up.
Today, everyone might still be hurt.
But just wait. In the days to come,
what will come to them,
what will come to you,
will make them realize that's exactly
what they've been searching for.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you.
That's the choreography.
Got it.
My team and I will brainstorm
the MV concept for them.
Noted. Thank you so much.
- Good luck, kiddos.
- Yes. Please take care of it for us.
Thank you.
Guys, let's continue practicing.
Here you are.
Thank you.
By the way,
have you thought
of any ideas yet, Director?
Come on. I just saw the choreography.
Do you expect me to come up
with an idea right away?
I'd be too smart if I could do that,
don't you think?
Whoa.
You're already smarter than Ming and me.
I can never come up with anything.
You're exaggerating.
Treat me today?
You're not pulling all-nighters
with us anymore.
Even with my promotion,
I still have debts to pay.
Come on.
But sure, I'll pay for you.
- Seriously?
- That's because I must leave
some work for you to do anyway.
- Stop that.
- I'm sorry.
We're sorry to keep you waiting.
What would you like?
I'll have this.
Two Americanos, please.
Two Americanos, right?
It's on me.
1,000 BAHT
1,000 THB received.
Earn?
Are you running an errand nearby?
Uh-huh.
How have you been? Doing well?
Well, I'm good.
Eh? Just "good"?
The MV you directed was amazing.
That's why you got promoted
as the director at Oner.
You've got a bright future ahead.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I wanted to come here
and congratulate you.
You said you were running
an errand, didn't you?
I had to… play it cool a bit, right?
I'm really here to see you.
I want to apologize
for how badly I treated you.
I'm so sorry.
Actually,
I think I've started to understand you.
Back then,
I somehow wondered why you were so mean.
But now,
I get it, really.
Sometimes, people
just aren't meant to be together.
You know what?
I once thought that if we ever met again,
I'd walk all over you.
But now that you're here,
I don't feel like that anymore.
Why?
Is it because I'm as handsome as ever?
Nope.
I guess…
for many things that have come to my life,
I should thank you for leaving me.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have come this far.
Is that supposed to be my credit?
It doesn't sound very nice, though.
You weren't exactly nice to begin with.
Well,
that's true.
We've grown up now.
Yep.
I have to go.
- I'm meeting Uncle Joei.
- Hey.
- I got something for you.
- Eh?
What's this for?
You designed the logo, right?
I never gave these to you,
so here I am, giving them to you.
When people ask who made it,
you now have proof to show them.
Why are you looking at me like that?
This is good for both of us.
My company looks prestigious
with a logo designed by a famous director.
It's also good for your image
since you designed the work
for my company.
I thought
you actually came to apologize.
Eh? I'm here to really say sorry,
but it can't be helped, you know.
Also, you designed it, really.
But I remember that
when you were giving out credits,
you never mentioned me even once.
Well…
Keep this in mind.
I won't take things you never gave me.
And from now on,
you have no right to talk about me.
Hello, Uncle.
Eh? What happened today?
I met Earn.
Oh, it didn't take long for your ex
to come crawling back?
Crawling back? No way.
He just wanted my name credited
on his app,
while before this, he never wanted it.
Nobody even knew who I was.
Whoa. That's hilarious.
And what did you say to him?
I told him he has no right
to talk about me anymore.
Why are you smiling?
Well,
I'm happy for you.
You finally got to put him in his place.
Are you still feeling satisfied
showing him how far you've come?
You even got to crush him underfoot.
It's not like that.
Eh? I thought that
what you've been doing
all this time is for this thing.
I'm surprised at myself too.
Even though I got the job I wanted
and can stand on my own,
don't even have to act awkward
about buying one or two sandwiches,
and received praise for overcoming it all,
I don't feel like
I've won anything at all.
Have you ever sat quietly
and asked yourself why?
Well,
I even sat and looked at you.
You looked at me?
Yes.
Sometimes, I envy you
because you've done your dream job
since you were young
until you're aging now.
You never get tired of it.
You can keep doing it
without caring about anything.
You don't get criticized by anyone,
no matter what kind of life you're living.
Let me tell you something, okay?
Yes.
This is totally not my dream job,
just so you know.
Eh?
I did this because I had no idea
what else to do to earn a living.
Eh?
Then…
What's your dream job then?
I don't know.
I never had a dream.
People always say that
we're supposed to have a dream.
I've been living for 60 years now,
and I've never had a dream,
and see? I'm still alive.
Hey? Here comes my customer.
Hello, Mr. Banjoed.
I already fixed it for you.
You can try it first.
If it doesn't fit properly,
I'll adjust it for you again.
I don't need to try it on, Uncle.
It's just a 5 cm stitch.
What a pity, tailor shops
like this are disappearing.
Off-the-rack suits
never really fit properly.
That's why tailor-made suits exist.
Does it look okay?
Yes.
STUCK IN YOUR HEART PROJECT
It's a bit cold tonight,
and I can't hug you.
If you want to hug me,
put your hands in your pockets, okay?
Po.
I have so much to tell you,
and I'm afraid that
if we talk in person,
I won't be able to get it all out.
So, I'm writing this for you.
While writing this,
we're waiting to check
the last music chart result.
Welcome to Nano's kitchen.
I'm telling you,
the food we're cooking today is…
What are we going to cook?
Pepper is trying not to be sad,
so he keeps himself busy all the time.
Nano and Jun have to accompany him always.
Dylan keeps to himself.
No matter how much we call him,
he pretends he doesn't hear it.
As for me, if I don't do something,
I'd probably lose it just like those four.
That's why I'm writing this for you.
You know what? If we can achieve this,
it will be the second all-kill in my life.
Honestly, I should be less excited
and keep myself together better,
but now, things have all turned
the opposite.
I asked myself why.
Is it because this all-kill carries
everyone's hopes and dreams?
Or is it because we get to be MARS again?
Or is it our first success as a group?
Thame. Thame!
Yeah?
But I think it's more than just that.
All this time, we've been striving
for the top
to prove to the world that we, too,
have value in it.
We all thought it was something
we had to do.
Every member,
myself,
and even you.
How would the world see our worth
if we weren't successful?
But in the end, is that really
the kind of world we live in?
One that measures our value by awards,
rankings, and numbers?
What kind of people do we have to become
to keep pleasing those cruel people?
When, in reality, if we had nothing
and were just trainees,
does that mean
we wouldn't have any worth at all?
I asked myself that,
but I never got an answer
until…
I met you,
the one who makes time slow down,
allows me to learn that
even if we really have nothing,
even if we don't get any praise
from anywhere,
the value of our work is often
the smallest thing that people overlook,
the truth is, we all have worth somewhere,
with someone.
And it's because of you that I realized
this all-kill means more
than just keeping MARS alive.
It's about saving ourselves
from this world.
MARS will conquer the world
that tells us to rush,
that tells us to abandon
each other to be number one.
But we will prove that we are the group
that will walk together,
supporting each other from behind,
being a safe zone when we need comfort,
a cushion to support us
when we fail and rise again,
just like what you've done for me.
And because of you,
MARS is rebuilt with that meaning.
Because of you,
I believe that after this all-kill,
our group will last a long time,
and no one will have to be stuck
in loneliness again.
Po, I've written all of this
to thank you and to beg you.
No matter what happens,
no matter what I have to go through,
and how serious it is,
can you not let go of my hand?
Even if the world doesn't welcome us
or is falling apart right in front of us,
I still want to stand with everyone
and with you.
Please stay and support me as I am.
Stand by my side
and fight together against the world
that keeps placing expectations on us.
What's up?
Where are you?
I need your help.
You haven't found him?
Well, I picked up your call
when we were about to head home.
Eh? You want me
to find Thame's new number?
How would I have that? I'm not Mick.
Why don't you call Mick?
Do this, then.
Go to the rooftop
and check if Thame's there.
Talk to you later.
Let's go to the rooftop.
Go! Run!
But when we got there, he wasn't there.
By the way,
why are you trying to find Thame?
I need to talk to him
about something important.
Well,
Thame's situation now is a real mystery.
We don't even know
where the company's keeping him.
They have everyone practicing separately,
and I don't even know where he's staying.
Working like this is a mess for us.
I'm telling you,
Ming might not be able to help you,
but I can.
- Really?
- Of course.
Don't you see how smart I am?
I asked for Thame's new phone number.
Hold on. Who did you get it from?
Eh?
Here we go.
He's here to give it to you in person.
Why do you need Thame's phone number?
I need to talk to him.
About what?
I have to apologize to him
about something.
Oh.
If it's something small like that,
leave it to me.
I'll tell him.
Mick.
What?
MARS really wants to stay together.
Come on, Po.
That's all in the past.
Miss Pemika has already given them
the best things they need.
No,
that's not what they want at all.
It's true that we used to think
climbing higher
was happiness,
but if we realize along the way
that it's not,
don't we have the right to change things?
You've been with them longer than I have.
You should know better than me
what they truly want.
But this is the best
the company can offer.
Are you saying that
when the company made you a director,
it wasn't what you wanted?
You're right.
It might have been what I wanted before,
but not anymore for now.
Right now, all I want is his number
and a chance to meet him.
Mick,
I want him to be happy, really.
Help him, okay?
Well, then,
come to the company tomorrow.
Meet Thame where you two always used to.
Is this where you two usually meet?
I never knew it was this peaceful.
Mick told me you're not happy
with the company's decisions.
I just want him to get
what he truly wants.
Same here.
But MARS isn't the same anymore.
They're not the ones
who want what you told us.
But I think we're seeing this differently.
So,
I guess you're seeing things
differently from MARS now too.
No matter what, MARS is Oner's asset.
It's a team that has to follow
company policies,
and every member
should know what those are.
If they don't,
they should train elsewhere, not here.
But maybe you joined by accident.
Maybe our visions just don't align.
You don't want to be a director anymore,
so it's better for us to part ways.
We can't keep someone
who harms MARS and Thame.
From today onward,
you're no longer an Oner employee.
I'll be taking back everything
that belongs to the company,
including the contacts
between you and our artists.
Hey. Hello.
I'll have my usual. Just one, please.
Sure.
NO SEARCH RESULTS FOR MARS
Are you worried about something?
Your work?
It's not that much about work.
I just feel guilty.
I feel I should have done something more,
but I just can't figure out what to do.
Have you asked your friends
for any advice?
Who would I even ask?
I can't talk to anyone now.
Here you are. The rest are on the house.
Whoa.
Isn't this too much? I can't eat all this.
I think it's enough for everyone.
Look at you.
You want to reunite the group
but only went to see Thame?
I feel left out.
Why are you all here?
If I tell you,
you'll probably think it's cheesy.
Gags.
Per, explain.
Where do I even start?
Should I begin with how we found out
we should come here,
or why we knew about the whole thing?
Fine. I'll say it.
Hey, if you don't want to talk,
I can do it for you.
But I might throw in a little extra
for flavor,
just to make it more interesting.
Don't. Leave it to me.
There was a time
I scolded Thame about you,
and he brought up the sandwich.
His favorite sandwich
isn't from this store.
After that,
I saved a screenshot
of this sandwich shop.
Then, when I found out about
you bringing the group together,
I looked up this location.
That's how we figured out
that if we wanted to find you,
we'd have to wait here.
By the way,
how did you even know
I'm trying to reunite MARS?
Well, you told someone,
and they ended up telling us.
Are you talking about Ming and Tae?
So…
How will you bring MARS back?
What's your plan?
Before this, I received Thame's schedule.
WORK SCHEDULE
I'm planning to talk to Thame
on the day he's meeting
with the Korean team.
I'm going to ask Thame
to request their contract
for another review to see
what terms are included
and if there are any loopholes
that would allow us to make changes.
But by the time we fully understand
the terms
and figure out a solution,
it'll probably be too late.
Then, what if we find an event
before the concert
where you guys can meet and talk?
No way.
The company won't let us
see Thame before the concert.
Even now, all his contacts
are being erased.
I think if we're doing something,
we can't let her find out.
We'll handle everything at the concert.
But…
If you do it at the concert,
it will cause Oner damage,
and you guys will end up in trouble.
You might get sued and so on.
Bring it on. Just sue us.
At least we'll get to pay off
the debt for Thame,
and we'll be even.
What are you even saying?
He's just talking nonsense, bro.
How could we even find the money to pay?
So, if we're going to take action,
we have to be really sure
that this time, it has to succeed.
Besides,
I don't think anything
could get worse than it is right now.
By the way,
don't you have any other idea, Director?
Actually, I do.
But we'll need help
from someone backstage.
Since I'm no longer an Oner employee,
it's hard to pull strings back there.
Hard? I don't think so.
I think it's way easier for you this way.
Since you're not working for Oner anymore,
if you make little mistakes,
no one's going to call you out on it.
Mick had Miss Pemika fire you
so you could work on this more freely.
Huh?
Mick might seem like
he's sucking up to Pemika
and ignoring us,
but deep down, he's always had our backs.
He probably knew everything
from the moment I called him
and told him you were the traitor.
So, it's Po, right?
No. It's not him.
But he let you keep going,
as long as it didn't affect him.
Everyone, stop.
Go look for Thame now. That way.
Go now. Hurry up.
Hey. Hey, stop.
It's not this way. Head there.
That's right. Go.
Actually, I guess he
wanted to help us all this time,
but he didn't dare to do anything.
Does that mean the group
will debut in Korea?
No, not the whole group, just one person.
Until he found out that
you're planning to help Thame again.
I want him to be happy, really.
Help him, okay?
Hey, Jun.
Mick and I discussed it and agreed that
firing you would make things easier.
I see.
So, you'll go up for this concert,
and the plan is being coordinated by Mick,
and I'm "free" to do whatever I want?
Yes. That's right.
But the real problem is
we can't talk to Thame
because he has to practice
separately from us.
He also has to work separately from us.
And Pemika is monitoring this whole thing.
Being close to the boss
makes this a bit difficult.
Or should we come up with a plan for Mick
to help him separate Thame
so he can come to us?
What kind of plan are you thinking about?
Like,
it's okay if Thame doesn't know about it?
How could that be okay?
- If he's clueless, it's even harder.
- Yeah.
The chance of success drops too.
All this time,
Thame has already managed
to do difficult things,
like bringing the four of us together.
So, can't we really help him come back?
The four of us can't be weaker
than Thame alone, right?
Are you doing all right?
That question keeps repeating in my mind
Hold on, Thame.
You don't sound like you feel this verse.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
Try again, okay?
I need you to really feel it,
or think of anyone who brings
that feeling to you.
- Let's start, okay?
- Yes.
Are you doing all right?
That question keeps repeating in my mind
Just wanna know when you're there
Without me
How have you been?
Have you missed me?
Cuz I keep on missing you in my mind
I can only hope that when you're there
You're happier
Wanna see that smile on your face
Like when
We're in love again
We must control the stage
and make it ours.
We need someone to set up the wires
and someone to cut the signal
from the original control.
I'm all set here.
Then it's all on you now,
whether you can do it or not, Po.
Of course, I can.
No matter what,
I'll bring Thame back to you all.