[If you don't turn yourself in,
your limbs will rot and you'll die]
[All characters and events are fictional,
and any resemblance is coincidental]
[Scenes with children and animals were filmed
safely under professional supervision]
Shall we wrap up the class here today?
- Thank you.
- Thank you, professor.
Officer Lee.
Aren't you a little too old
to take my class?
'Officer Lee.'
Hearing you call me that
makes me feel young again, Detective Kang.
Sorry, shouldn't have called you that.
You've been Chief Inspector for a while.
The Kangseng Serial Murder Case.
The real culprit has been caught.
It's been 30 years.
[Prisoner Info Card
Lee Yong Woo]
He lived in Kangseng County at the time,
and later moved to Cheongju.
He was sentenced to life in 1994
for killing his sister-in-law
and has been serving his sentence ever since.
He was in prison?
That's why...
We happened to visit
right after Lee Yong Woo's
parole hearing had ended.
If we'd been any later, he would've been
released as a model prisoner.
Just thinking about it gives me chills.
The problem is, Lee Yong Woo's DNA was found
in only three cases.
Therefore,
we'll need his confession for the rest cases.
Even though the statute
of limitations passed,
getting his confession won't be easy.
Sir.
Please help us.
You wanted to catch the culprit
more than anyone.
[Lee Yong Woo]
Actually,
Lee Yong Woo requested it himself.
He asked for you specifically.
Me?
[Female body discovered in Kangseng County]
[Public frustration grows
as investigation stalls]
We'll now present the commendations.
[1988 Awards Ceremony
for Outstanding Police Officers]
[Episode 1]
These seats are reserved for the awardees.
Spectators sit in the back.
It's empty anyway, so what's the big deal?
Next, we will present commendations
to Jongno Police officers
for their assistance
in apprehending an organized crime group.
Please step forward upon hearing your name.
Can't you hear me?
That's not your seat.
Aren't we both just sitting
where we shouldn't be?
Then you shouldn't have let it be taken.
The one who can't keep it is the fool.
Right? Now that's more like it.
Otherwise, there'd be
no point in coming here.
I came to flip this whole thing over.
And I might as well make it loud.
Sergeant Choi Jung Mo.
Quit the act and get lost.
I'll buy you drinks someday.
Sergeant Choi Jung Mo.
I'm arresting you on charges of bribery.
Are you out of your mind?
Get these off me now.
You know Kim Dae Pyeong,
Dosan gang's second-in-command, don't you?
The one who gave you the money.
I... I don't know anything about it.
Just take these off first.
Sergeant Choi Jung Mo.
- Hey!
- Is Sergeant Choi Jung Mo here?
Don't you see you're making things
difficult for Chief too?
You really want to stand there that much?
Hurry up and take these off me.
Fine, fine.
There it is, here.
The officer he just awarded
turns out to be corrupt.
Think carefully.
Which will embarrass Chief more?
- Darn it.
- Good call.
That's enough of a scene.
Let's head out peacefully.
Come on, keep your head up.
Let's continue with the awards.
Earlier during the ceremony,
a police officer was unexpectedly arrested.
Is it true there was a corrupt officer
among the award recipients?
Did you know and still turn a blind eye?
Please answer us.
Was this meant as a warning?
You've always said
no amount of achievement
can excuse corruption in public office.
So did you just
demonstrate that belief in action?
That is correct.
Then, was that earlier incident
ordered by you, Chief?
I believed that rather than covering up
wrongdoing within our own ranks,
exposing it and asking for forgiveness
is what makes a police force
worthy of public trust.
I sincerely apologize
to the public for the police's involvement
in this unfortunate incident.
[Auditorium]
[No Mercy for Corruption,
A Bold Move by the Police Chief]
I've come back
home.
Darn it.
[Kangseng]
[If you don't turn yourself in,
your limbs will rot and you'll die]
Is that him?
The most handsome guy in Kangseng?
Yeah, they say he looks like Andy Lau.
No way!
There's an Andy Lau in Kangseng?
I'm telling you!
- Oh, come on!
- Just a middle-aged guy.
What a waste of time.
More like Sammo Hung.
Hey, come on. What is this really?
- Seriously?
- What's going on?
Come on, Andy Lau? Give me a break.
Who started that rumor that he's handsome?
Yes, this is Kangseng Bookstore.
Hey, with a face like that,
I'd pack him lunch every day.
He just made eye contact with me.
Ki Hwan.
- Call for you.
- Okay.
He's so hot!
His eyes are like a deer's.
Hello?
Oh, Ji Won.
What? Tae Joo is back?
Okay, I'll be right there.
[Handcuffed Corrupt Cop at Awards Ceremony]
While others ran Chief with his head down,
[Auntie's Restaurant]
we ran you instead.
Kangseng's own madman, Kang Tae Joo.
Wow, with that cigarette,
you look just like Chow Yun Fat.
It's not... not a cigarette.
Stop right there! You punk!
Hey!
Where do you think you're running off to?
You punk!
[Auntie's Restaurant]
Stop, you!
Aren't those Detective Do and Detective Jang?
- You're not going after him?
- My assignment starts tomorrow.
So you're just letting him go?
He's clearly just a small-time crook.
I've told you, don't hit my head!
Kang Tae Joo!
You are so full of yourself now
after living in Seoul.
Detective, please help me.
- I really didn't do it.
- Who is he?
A guy I put behind bars before.
- Hey, what is it?
- When I got caught by you,
I didn't feel it was unfair!
Why? What? Go away!
You punk!
Detective.
Good grief.
Detective Kang?
How long has it been? Three years?
Oh my.
I heard you got kicked out of Seoul.
You left like you'd never return.
Look at you now.
I'm innocent!
I really didn't do anything!
Alright, let's go.
Detective.
We'll talk tomorrow.
I'm telling you, I didn't do anything!
- You!
- It's not me!
You...
You got kicked out?
Why?
[Handcuffed Corrupt Cop at Awards Ceremony]
Move it. Look, is this what it's about?
Smoking in front of the Chief?
I told you, it wasn't a cigarette!
Then what was it?
I locked up a guy
who took bribes from gangsters.
Turns out he's
the Police Commissioner's nephew.
So I got transferred out of nowhere.
This is ridiculous. Isn't that retaliation?
Hey, Tae Joo, are you really okay?
Why wouldn't I be?
Seriously, it was huge.
We sold so much today.
Oh? Tae Joo.
Hey, it's been a while, guys.
You're a newlywed,
so you should head home early.
I'm out for the first time in a while.
Tae Joo, it's really been ages.
Right, Un Hui,
I heard you're working under Ji Won.
- Yes.
- Hey.
We're not in the mood for greetings now,
so if you're here to eat, then eat.
If you can get inside in three seconds,
I'm paying for your meals.
Come on, move!
Sit down!
What's going on with them?
Something wrong?
When Ms. Seo is acting like that,
it's pretty serious.
Hey, isn't it weird
calling your own sister "Ms. Seo"?
I called her "Ji Won" at the newsroom
and got hit for it.
She still hits people?
Ah, don't even ask.
Ki Beom, did you get caught or something?
Come on, if so, he'd be sitting over there.
Whatever.
What's he gonna do, kill me?
Cheers.
Hey, forget it.
Let's just go all the way tonight.
Just don't pass out before sunrise, alright?
Okay.
It's not that way.
Hold on, we're almost there.
It's Sun Young.
Hey, pull yourself together.
- Sun Young!
- Pull yourself together.
Hey, Sun Young...
Hey, act sober. Pretend you're fine.
Sun Young.
Hold on, you're too heavy.
Should we lay him down here?
Oh, my back.
Sun Young.
Jeez.
Oh, I'm home.
The smell...
It's you, our Sun Young.
Sun Young is mad.
How much did you drink?
My pretty little sister, my...
Jeez, you idiot,
lay off the booze a little.
I'm...
Seriously, what is this?
Is he dead?
Well...
We didn't see anything, Sun Young.
We're leaving.
Ki Hwan, let's go.
Is he dead?
Good night.
- Is he dead?
- Shut up!
Dead or alive?
Alive!
[Period for Reporting and Surrendering Spies]
[Stop]
Excuse me, who are you
to sit in someone else's seat?
It was my seat before.
Hey, what do you mean 'your seat'?
This is where the youngest sits now.
It's not like you were born in that chair.
Just sit over there. It's empty anyway.
Ugh, it's...
It still reeks of your cigarettes.
It stinks there.
You've become a real Seoul snob.
You're the only one who smells it?
This used to be my seat.
Rookie?
Yes, I'm Park Dae Ho.
Okay, rookie.
I've been in Seoul the whole time.
Have you been to Seoul?
- No.
- Oh my.
Then you have no idea
how bad the air is there.
Factories, car exhaust...
I was about to get lung disease,
so I begged to come here.
Just to survive.
Really?
Please stay seated there.
Hey, you believe him?
Look at his complexion.
He looks perfectly fine, oh my.
If you feel wronged,
just take it as saving a life. Okay?
Lee Seong Jin!
Lee Seong Jin, you...
Hey, Lee Seong Jin!
[Security Interview Room]
You...
What kind of world is this nowadays?
Just to get a confession,
you beat him up like that?
If this were in Seoul,
it'd be front-page news.
Hey! You think working in Seoul
makes you special?
So what, you punk?
The prosecutor is demanding
we get a confession today, no matter what.
I've arrested that guy
three times, so I know him.
If you hit him with solid evidence,
he just stammers and spills everything.
It's not like he killed anyone.
Why treat some petty crook like that?
Why? What is it?
Hey.
He did kill someone.
He's a murderer.
What?
With the Olympics just a month away,
things are very unsettled.
Given the situation,
everyone stay careful, understood?
- Yes.
- Everyone here?
Yes.
I heard the suspect in the Im Bok Hee
murder case has been caught.
As expected of Prosecutor Cha.
You really know how to get things done.
I'm flattered.
If we hadn't solved this case,
I would've lost my job.
You know we already have
two unsolved cases at the station, right?
And both are murder cases.
Sorry, I feel ashamed.
This is why the first step matters.
If you're not confident,
why not hand it over to Mr. Cha now?
No need, sir.
It's my case, so I'll see it through.
- Send it to me by tomorrow.
- Yes, sir.
Mr. Cha!
- Oh, yes.
- About the suspect.
How did you find him?
The method of strangling the victim
with stockings was unusual.
So I started with offenders
with stocking-related records.
Turns out one of them lived nearby.
We also got a witness
who saw him near the scene.
Isn't that only natural?
He lives near the crime scene, you said.
So there's still no direct evidence, right?
Make sure you check thoroughly.
Don't end up like me.
He's tougher than I expected.
So please allow me a little more time.
I'll get a confession out of him.
No direct evidence?
He's quite the expert.
Excuse me?
What do you mean by that?
Are you sure Lee Seong Jin is the culprit?
Of course.
I mean, there's a witness too.
But that witness didn't
actually see the crime happen.
He said he just saw him nearby.
He's local, not from Seoul.
Does that really count as evidence?
Well, the blood type at the scene is B,
and Lee Seong Jin is also type B...
I'm type B too!
You're really doing it like amateurs!
Sorry.
Lee Seong Jin...
I need to meet him myself.
In February last year,
he was fined for stealing stockings.
[Criminal Record Certificate]
Served from April to July. What was it for?
Well, indecent assault.
He touched a woman's leg
as she was passing by in stockings.
I told that guy to live a decent life...
Anyway, so it's just theft
and indecent assault, right?
Yes, this would be his first murder.
Who says he killed anyone?
Don't jump to conclusions.
Nothing's been proven yet.
Yes, sir.
Bring me the case files
and crime scene photos
of that Im Bok Hee murder case.
Okay, one moment.
- Jeez.
- I'm...
I'm sorry.
Hey, if you just grab everything like that,
how are you going to sort it out later?
Jeez.
Sorry.
Stop right there.
Huh?
Why? What's wrong?
What is this?
This is...
Why are the bodies all different?
These are the murder cases
that have occurred recently.
Three in total.
Three?
And the killer?
It's still...
What's wrong?
These are
serial murders.
Lee Seong Jin!
Lee Seong... Hey, where's Lee Seong Jin?
Detective Jang and Detective Do...
- There they are.
- Come over.
Lee Seong Jin!
Lee Seong Jin, it wasn't you, right?
What are you talking about?
He's not the real killer!
Hey, you said it yourself
it wasn't you, right?
No. It was me!
I did it!
What's wrong with you?
Seong Jin.
Stop it, you punk.
He already confessed everything.
- Ji Hwan, lock him up.
- Yes, sir.
You beat him again, didn't you?
Is that even a real confession?
It's not like that, you punk.
Don't talk back to me like that.
Don't give me that.
Tell me straight.
The prosecutor in charge got it himself.
The confession.
[Name: Lee Seong Jin, currently unemployed]
[I lost my father in childhood
and live with my mother]
- Mr. Lee Seong Jin.
- Yes.
Why are you shaking?
You're a prosecutor, aren't you?
Prosecutors aren't scary people.
We're only scary to people
who've committed crimes.
Mr. Lee, have you done anything wrong?
So you
really didn't kill Im Bok Hee?
I didn't.
Oh dear, then you were just unlucky.
You happened to live in that neighborhood.
Then,
Mr. Lee,
can you help me out a bit?
I really can't figure it out.
Why did the killer use
stockings to kill someone?
You have a certain expertise with stockings.
That's why you ended up under suspicion too.
Mr. Lee,
why do you like stockings?
Well...
This is...
At first, they feel soft.
But if you keep touching them,
they all become rough.
That feeling is strangely intense.
So it was you.
What?
I wasn't sure until I came here.
But your eyes gave it away.
Those totally fried eyes.
You killed her, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
I didn't kill her.
Listen carefully.
This is the first and last chance
I'm giving you.
Today,
if you confess here,
I'll get you out within five years.
However,
if you don't confess
before I walk out that door?
You'll rot in prison forever.
Got it?
- What?
- One,
two,
three,
- four.
- No, please, Mr. Cha.
Sir!
Please save me.
I'm all my mother has.
She's sick right now.
Oh dear.
Then if you don't confess,
you won't even get out by her 80th birthday.
No, please don't.
- Five,
- Sir!
- six,
- No, sir.
- seven...
- Please spare me.
I'll let you attend your mother's funeral
as the chief mourner.
So don't worry.
No need for a false confession.
Eight.
Sir, please don't.
- Nine.
- Sir!
Sir!
Ten.
I...
I killed her, sir.
I'm sorry. I killed her.
I killed her, sir...
[Kangseng Police Station]
Have him write the statement carefully.
So he won't make mistakes
during the crime scene reenactment.
Sure, don't worry.
Sir!
- I need to talk to you!
- Hey.
Let's talk, okay?
What on earth are you doing?
What do you mean?
What's going on?
Is he talking to me?
Of course not.
You don't need to worry about it.
He was recently kicked out of Seoul.
Apparently he had trouble there too.
Take care on your way home.
Oh, sir.
- Hello.
- Yes, good work.
Please get home safely.
What's wrong with you, you lunatic?
Didn't you say
the prosecutor got the confession himself?
- Hey.
- So I was going to settle things
- with him!
- Hey, hey!
Kang Tae Joo!
- Let's talk in private, okay?
- Kang Tae Joo?
It is you, Kang Tae Joo!
Wow, Tae Joo, you've really changed.
Hey, Tae Joo!
It's been such a long time.
Wow, didn't expect to see you here!
Hey, good to see you.
So you became a cop?
Tae Joo.
Dead or alive?
[Kang Tae Joo]
[Cha Si Young]
Seems you're in a good mood.
I caught a murderer today.
Such a tough case. Wasn't it hard?
Well, I chose this job out of sense of duty.
My father used to say
that you are someone with great capacity.
It's truly an honor that
the Chairman sees me that way.
I'm really in a good mood today.
Meeting someone as beautiful as you,
Hee Jin, makes it even better.
Oh my.
Actually, I also ran into
an old friend today.
Someone I was very close with.
Mr. Heo.
Kang Tae Joo and Cha Si Young
were classmates.
What are you talking about?
Are Prosecutor Cha Si Young
and Kang Tae Joo classmates?
- Really?
- Yes.
We were surprised too.
They seemed pretty close.
Really? What a small world!
So
did Detective Kang say anything about it?
Right, what is that supposed to mean?
Park Dae Ho, do you know anything?
Well...
It's nothing.
I think I misunderstood earlier.
Don't mind what I said.
See?
We've got the suspect's confession,
and Detective Kang is back.
How about we grab a drink together?
Mr. Heo, since we're all here, how about...
a drink tonight?
Sounds good! How about gopchang?
I've got something I need to do.
Please go ahead without me.
Come on, we're doing this for you.
How can you bail on us?
Just pretend I'm there.
Forget it, forget it.
Never mind.
For the first time since you passed,
I've dressed you in hemp mourning clothes.
[After Laying You Before the Cornfield]
I gave the neighbors some clothes you made.
I buried you beside the cornfield
and walked back.
Go now.
Right now!
Now.
I'm sorry.
I'll pay for this.
It's fine. You're just a student.
I'm not some irresponsible kid.
Please let me pay, okay?
That's not your money.
It's your parents'.
You can have this,
so just come to our bookstore
when you buy reference books later.
It's Yu Jeong Rin.
I just wanted to
order the reference books in advance.
Yu Jeong Rin?
I'll write it down.
October 8, 1986, Choi Min Ja, 30 years old.
Found with her hands bound
with a wrapping cloth.
Strangled.
There are signs of manual
strangulation on the neck.
June 11, 1987, Hwang Kang Ae, 21 years old.
Died by strangulation with a scarf.
April 29, 1988.
Im Bok Hee, 29 years old.
Murdered by strangulation with stockings.
If confirmed as serial murders,
the cases will be consolidated.
Choi Min Ja and Hwang Kang Ae cases
were handled by Prosecutor Hwang Jae Hoon.
Im Bok Hee was assigned to Cha Si Young.
So it'll go
to one of those two.
You're still here?
What are you doing here?
- You didn't even call.
- What is this?
- What is it?
- Should've let me know.
- Hey, hold on.
- Stop.
- What's wrong?
- Hold on.
- Let me see.
- Hey.
Let's go out. Let's go.
- Hold on.
- Alright, let's go.
- Seriously.
- Let's go grab a bite.
Alright, alright.
Isn't the guy in the bookstore really sweet?
He'll remember my name, right?
"It's Yu Jeong Rin."
Hey!
That scared me!
What? It's just a scarecrow.
You startled me.
- Min Ji.
- Yes?
Over there...
Do you know Prosecutor Hwang Jae Hoon?
Hwang Jae Hoon?
Of course.
Until recently, he was the ace
at the Kangseng District Prosecutors' Office.
He'd never failed to solve a case.
Especially violent crimes.
- And then?
- A suspect being questioned
in the Hwang Kang Ae case killed himself.
And he wasn't even the real culprit.
So who's the ace now?
Prosecutor Cha Si Young.
Why do you ask?
Trying to get close to prosecutors?
You know,
I'm about to lay out a really great spread.
But I don't like the guy holding the spoon.
It takes all the fun out of it.
Then give it to someone else.
What's with that man?
He creeps me out.
I know, he's weird.
Go home. It's late.
What? Did the lights go out?
Seems like it's broken. I'm scared.
I'll make sure
you get home safe, so hurry up.
Really?
Yeah, go on.
I'm going.
Bye, see you tomorrow!
What? Hmph.
You said you'd wait until I got home.
That's low, Yu Jeong Rin.
What should we eat after this?
Gopchang? Rice soup?
Neither sounds good.
Or should we just eat jjajangmyeon?
I'm not feeling jjajangmyeon.
Let's go have sweet and sour pork.
- No, not that either.
- What do you think?
I don't know.
He's coming out.
[New Era, New Police]
Alright, step aside please.
Get in.
[Public Complaints Service Center]
Let's go eat jokbal.
Aren't you going to
the crime scene reenactment?
I've got somewhere to be.
You stay too, as you have work to do.
Me?
They've just headed to the scene.
Departure was delayed by news reporters.
A lot of reporters showed up?
Yeah, looks like all the local papers
in Kangseng showed up.
Do I look okay today?
You're always at your best, sir.
Officer,
you've got a real eye for detail.
Hey, look who's here.
Came to see me?
We're not exactly happy to see each other.
So, how did you
get Lee Seong Jin's confession?
Come on, that hurts.
So you're more curious about him than me?
Did you beat him?
Or threaten him?
You're good at that.
If that's how you did it,
fix it yourself right now.
Don't pin this on an innocent man.
I've got something to say too.
Yeah? What is it?
Just say you're sorry.
It's just that...
Just one word.
I heard you got kicked out of Seoul.
So stop that and come with me.
It's better to catch one murderer
than ten small-time crooks.
Just come and pretend
to go through the reenactment.
I'll put your name on the report.
Well,
I don't stick my nose
into other people's business.
Especially when there's nothing
worth getting involved in.
What are you even talking about?
I'm telling you Lee Seong Jin
is not the real killer.
Why are you telling me this?
Lee Seong Jin isn't
even a suspect in my case...
It's related to your case too, sir.
Choi Min Ja, Hwang Kang Ae,
and Im Bok Hee were
all killed by the same person.
Do you have any evidence?
No, not yet.
What exactly do you want from me?
The crimes all target women
returning home after sunset,
sexual assault,
binding with victims' clothing,
and then strangulation!
What are the chances there are three killers
with the same method in Kangseng?
Let's say, as you claim,
all of this is committed by a serial killer.
Then,
couldn't Lee Seong Jin still be the killer?
Sir.
Lee Seong Jin was in detention
at the time Hwang Kang Ae was killed.
We'll find evidence soon.
The more they kill,
the more addicted they become.
This punk is going to kill again soon.
Possibly...
Yes, Prosecutor Hwang Jae Hoon's office.
As early as today.
Pardon? Who?
Someone is looking for you,
Detective Kang Tae Joo.
Sir!
A body has been found.
It's a murder case.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Evidence has appeared.
Hold it!
I said hold it.
You touched her? You put your hands
all over the person like that?
That's all you've got?
I don't stick my nose
into other people's business.
Especially when there's nothing
worth getting involved in.
"Nothing worth getting involved in?"
[Police]
Jeez.
What is it?
- Hey! Stop!
- Stop him.
Stop, stop, freeze!
Freeze! Stop it...
What are you doing right now?
The reporters are all here!
Well, another body was found.
What does that have to do with this?
- Another body?
- Another one's been found?
- Don't tell me...
- Yes.
Is it true another body has been found?
What about the reenactment?
Sir, is there really another body?
Sir!
Aren't you going to secure the scene?
Secure the scene. Now.
- Step out.
- Wait, but...
[Yu Jeong Rin]
You were right, sir.
It's the same guy.
[You, the Hollyhock]
So the same killer murdered
Yu Jeong Rin and Im Bok Hee?
Yes, the method matches Im Bok Hee's case.
We arrested a guy who wasn't the real killer
and even did a reenactment.
Jeez, if it had gone to trial...
Oh my.
I'm ashamed.
So what are you going to do now?
Since it's definitely the same killer,
we'll indict it together
with Yu Jeong Rin's case...
Come in.
Come sit.
Mr. Hwang thinks differently from you.
It's not two serial murder victims, but four.
The first victim was Choi Min Ja.
Don't you think that's a bit of a stretch?
Choi Min Ja and Hwang Kang Ae
were killed in completely different ways.
It can't be the same killer.
What's different?
Weekdays, after sunset,
crimes targeting women returning home.
And strangulation.
But Im Bok Hee was strangled with stockings.
The killer develops preferences over time.
He used to use
any of the victim's belongings,
but has now become fixated on stockings.
He found that, due to the elasticity,
stockings lead to a slower death
than other materials.
So the goal is a slow death?
Not the texture of it?
That way,
he can prolong the pleasure.
The pleasure of killing.
The next crimes will surely involve
strangulation with stockings.
I'm certain of it.
In any case, you still don't have
direct evidence, do you?
I'll continue my investigation my own way.
Mr. Cha, have you forgotten already?
That you almost wronged an innocent person?
Give me one more chance.
I'm confident this time.
This case...
Excuse me for a second.
Tae Joo
is still so adorable.
What should I do about you?
[You, the Hollyhock]
This book
was found next to Jeong Rin.
The guy from the bookstore gave it to her.
That mark...
That was because of Jeong Rin.
Which bookstore?
Kangseng Bookstore.
That handsome guy there.
Were you on your way home
after stopping by there?
Yes.
Anyone suspicious on the way?
Wait...
I think I know
who killed Jeong Rin.
Who is it?
Min Ji, over there...
Stop right there! I'll catch you!
Shh.
What's going on?
Did you see a woman come this way?
I think she went this way.
Darn it!
Hey, what if you get caught lying?
It's okay.
Let's hurry.
[Specialized Hand Washing for All Shoes]
Hello.
Ms. Kim, you're here.
Nothing special.
No criminal record, either.
One thing suspicious though,
he's been closing the laundry shop
early for months now.
He must be very busy.
Hope today's no different.
[Eun Ho Automatic Laundry]
Duck.
- Shall we go?
- Let's go.
You won't learn until you get hit.
Stop it, don't!
You punk!
Police, are you okay?
Stay still, you punk!
Kim Han Seop!
- Let go of me!
- Stay still.
Stay still, Kim Han Seop, you'll get hurt.
Who are you?
- I said let go!
- Stay still.
That woman is my wife.
Is it a crime to bring back my runaway wife?
You remember these students?
Three days ago, Dugang-ri underpass.
So?
This one was murdered
right after they ran into you.
What?
It wasn't me! Why would I?
At first, I thought it was a coincidence too.
Until I saw you were about
to stab people with scissors.
I was just trying to scare her.
If I meant to kill her,
I would've brought a knife.
A knife?
I mean,
a knife would be easier to use.
Jeez.
This guy isn't the killer.
Here.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
I ran away from him.
He used to beat me almost every day.
After that, he seemed to be
looking for me every night.
On the 19th around 8 PM,
you ran into these students, right?
Yes.
How long were you
hiding from Kim Han Seop then?
About an hour, I think.
I was there for quite a while,
worried he might come back.
Did Kim Han Seop come back that way again?
No.
Then, anyone who passed by on that road?
No people, though.
"No people?"
Did you notice anything suspicious?
Anything you can remember.
Well,
I'm not entirely sure, but...
Shh.
I'm certain I saw a scarecrow.
But later, it was gone.
A scarecrow...
There was a scarecrow, and...
And I think I heard
stray dogs too.
Where was that?
Hey!
What? It's just a scarecrow.
You startled me.
Min Ji.
Did you see a woman come this way?
I think she went this way.
That day,
the reason the stray dogs
were wary of the scarecrow,
and the reason the victims
weren't wary of him.
Look at this punk.
This guy's completely out of his mind.
You've walked right into my hands now.
You better hide well.
And watch your back.
I'm going to catch you.
Who's there?
Who is it?
Tae Joo?
It is you, Tae Joo.
Well,
why are you here?
I went to check the Yu Jeong Rin case.
I thought it might be you.
Put that thing away.
Why are you acting so scary?
So why are you here?
This isn't even your case anymore.
Exactly.
It's not my case anymore.
I heard you took over this case?
If you wanted it, you could've just told me.
Then we could've solved it
together as friends. Isn't it great?
If you dare say 'us' or 'friends'
in front of me again,
I'll kill you with my own hands!
Don't mess with me!
I'm not the old Kang Tae Joo anymore!
That guy was patient and naive, but I'm not!
Stay out of my sight as much as possible.
It won't take long.
I don't plan on staying here long anyway.
Kang Tae Joo!
I'll take this case back.
And you too.
What?
I will
keep you by my side.
Like back then.
You psycho!
I missed you, Kang Tae Joo.
- You punk!
- Hey, hey!
Hold on, hold on.
- This way.
- Okay.
[If you have a dream,
you can always start over]
I've waited for this day
for a long time.
For the past 30 years.
Hold on.
Yes?
Do you have water?
Yes, it's ready. Let's go.
[Strong rule of law,
humane and effective corrections]
[It is about striving
to live a righteous life]
You're late.
Have you been
waiting long?
Yes.
Finally, we meet.
The murderer I've been searching for
all this time.
Please help me!
It felt soft... like a woman's hand.
If you see anything suspicious
like a scarecrow, run away immediately.
It might be the killer.
Detective Kang, I'm the prosecutor
before I'm your friend.
If it's a weakness, we can find another one.
Hey, your sister is in the hospital.
After what happened to his sister,
what kind of brother wouldn't lose it?