ظآزThat dayظآز
ظآزNothing stays together foreverظآز
ظآزI've quit romanceظآز
ظآزWho hasn't failed againظآز
ظآزCrying in deathظآز
ظآزAnd in lifeظآز
ظآزEven nowظآز
ظآزWe keep learningظآز
ظآزIt's no surpriseظآز
ظآزBeing happy is so hardظآز
ظآزWeirdly, I became a role modelظآز
ظآزOn the day we met again, we said hiظآز
ظآزIt was a reminder,
a test, and a complaintظآز
ظآزWho can do anything without regretظآز
ظآزI am all rightظآز
ظآزMay you live in peaceظآز
ظآزLet the world roarظآز
ظآزSounds like a carnivalظآز
ظآزBeing alive is never dullظآز
ظآزHow wonderful to be freeظآز
ظآزI became even better without youظآز
ظآزNothing can be perfectظآز
ظآزWe bless each other in painظآز
ظآزWe nod and smileظآز
ظآزMay we both be wellظآز
= Love's Ambition=
=Episode 31=
You said
to get me clothes.
Haochen.
ظآزI go surfing, go diving, go driving,
and go flying to a different placeظآز
Haochen.
Did you talk to me just now?
I didn't hear it.
Could you repeat that?
Sorry.
Haochen.
Say it again, please.
Haoming.
What are you mumbling?
Grandma.
Did you hear that?
Haochen spoke to me!
I heard it.
My ears work fine.
Why are you so excited?
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
He is very smart.
He knows exactly
who treats him well.
This is his first step forward.
Thank you, Grandma.
For what?
Your care is all that matters.
Thank you.
Haochen.
Temperature's okay?
I'll adjust it for you, okay?
Need me to scrub your back?
Tell me if you need help.
I'll stay right here.
I won't move at all.
Right here.
Haochen.
It's ready.
Here.
Is it chilled?
Of course. It's very sweet.
Try it.
How's Dad been lately?
Mom said
he is doing fine.
Good then.
Did you tell Mom
the good news
that Haochen talks now?
Yes.
She's thrilled.
I really hope Haochen
can recover sooner to his former
lively and playful self.
He will.
Just give him more time.
I've told Dr. Wang about
Haochen's recent progress.
Dr. Wang said it's excellent.
This shows
Grandma's methods really work.
Right?
Actually, I've always thought
Grandma is
an exceptionally wise person.
She's attentive
and great at caring for children,
even
playing along with them.
Wherever
Grandma is present,
I feel completely at ease.
Grandma is
your steadfast anchor.
And you are
my steadfast anchor.
Why suddenly say
such cheesy things?
I saw your photo album
in your room today.
Or rather,
our photo album.
How did you find that?
The album
ends when we were splitting up.
I'm so glad
we can take more photos together.
Why take photos now?
I want to add this photo
to the album
as our new page.
Then I'll write
"Today's watermelon was sweet."
We have to keep recording.
Even when we grow old,
we will
admire the moon here
with endless things to talk about.
Now I finally understand
what mutual devotion really means.
Do you know?
It's like
you imagine,
and I do along.
Want more watermelon?
Okay.
The moon is bright tonight.
Look.
You've all heard the news, right?
In real estate circles,
there's been
a major development recently.
The North Waichuan area in East China.
You're interested in it?
This will be
my first major project
since taking over Jinda.
Only obtaining
such achievements
will silence the skeptics.
Mr. Qu.
I'll support you
and give it my all.
Weiping.
How are Shen Haoming
and Shen Jinsong?
Godfather.
Shen Haoming
has left Jingzhou
with Xu Yan and the child
to lie low somewhere.
And Shen Jinsong remains
in a coma.
Mr. Qu.
Do you think
Shen Haoming
can make a comeback?
I believe he
would never abandon
this Diamond Plot.
Monitor closely
who he associates with.
Tired?
Want some water?
This won't work.
Use mine.
Haochen.
Grandma's cooking is delicious.
Lunch is ready.
Alright.
Ignore me.
Take a break.
You've prepared the soil so well.
The seeds in this patch
will surely thrive better than others.
He talks to you.
Yet you still ignore him?
Not even saving face for him?
Dad isn't my real dad.
Mom isn't my real mom.
Brother isn't my real brother.
I'm not even my true self.
I don't know what to say.
I just don't understand
why he had to deceive me.
Why didn't he acknowledge me?
Haochen.
Have you considered
that back then, Shen Haoming
was just a kid himself?
When he accidentally
learned he had a son,
he was scared too.
But he never considered
abandoning you.
He wanted to protect you.
Of course,
Haoming's dad
also wanted to protect his son,
so used a wrong way.
However, their purposes
were to protect you.
Do you understand me?
But he's deceived me.
Exactly.
He's deceived you.
And it is wrong.
Lies
will eventually come to light.
Everyone
will pay the price for this.
They're upset too.
Whoever you are,
in this family,
they'd always love you deeply,
and their love will never change.
I know you can feel it,
right?
So I have to
forgive them?
Of course not.
You can have your own decision.
It's all up to you.
You can do whatever you want.
I just want to remind you
that we all love you very much.
This will never change.
I believe you can understand.
Really.
Grandma's cooking is delicious.
Potato!
Let's go
to have lunch.
Let's go.
Look at the potato.
Freshly dug from the ground.
Hello.
Where's the convenience store?
What?
It's not close.
Keep walking along
this road.
Then you'll reach a fork.
Turn left there.
Walk along.
Turn right at the next fork.
Walk about 500 meters more,
you'll see that.
Turn left first, then right.
Exactly.
Thank you.
No problem.
Haochen.
(Hongxin Zhenyuan
Supermarket and Restaurant)
Haochen!
I'm here.
At midnight,
why did you
come out
without telling me?
I was so worried about you.
Are you hurt?
Hungry?
Tell me then.
I'll cook for you.
Are you cold?
You're sweating.
Might catch a cold.
Don't get chilled.
Enough hangers?
Yes.
Grandma.
Haoming and I decided
to return to Jingzhou tomorrow.
So soon?
Haochen is getting better,
but Haoming's dad
is hospitalized.
So we thought
to get back soon.
Hasn't he awoken yet?
Not yet.
Although his vitals are stable,
he just hasn't awoken.
Go back then.
When people are ill,
they need family
the most.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll pack your luggage.
I've told you many times
to bring you to Jingzhou
to take good care
of you.
Now,
when trouble comes,
we still need your care.
Don't you remember?
I'm your safe harbor.
Yan.
No matter
what trouble or worries
you have,
you can always come home to me.
I'll always be here for you.
When we settle everything,
I'll bring Haochen to visit again.
That would make me so happy.
Okay.
Come on.
Here.
- I'll do it.
- It's soaked.
Wring it dry.
Take it.
Yes, like that.
Use both hands.
Oh my!
Come.
Yes, yes.
Okay. Wring it dry.
(Yan Studio)
Welcome back, Ms. Xu.
Yan, I miss you so much.
That's enough.
Have a seat.
Sit, sit.
Recently,
due to my personal matters,
I've delayed the progress.
But thanks to Lin
and your efforts,
Yan Studio is now operating smoothly.
I especially want to thank
our CFO Lin Tao,
who secured the bank loan
for Yan Studio,
solving our urgent needs.
Thank you.
I just did my job.
It's all due to Ms. Qiao's leadership.
Thank you, Ms. Qiao.
Alright.
Okay.
Let's begin then.
Tell me
the recent project progress.
Yao,
about the batik project,
now...
I've prepared
a plan for the batik collection.
Take a look.
For the new products,
we'll collaborate with
top ten fashion influencers
for videos.
It's almost done.
So he falsified
Yan Studio's
financial reports
and applied for the loan.
All to force you
to return and marry him?
That's why
you moved out, right?
I wanted to keep him calm.
That meant keeping distance
from Yu Yiming temporarily.
Earlier,
he acted diligent
and reliable,
but it was all an act.
He planned all this
long ago, right?
Recently,
I've been thinking
how to handle this.
I've recorded evidence.
I confronted him
and recorded this.
Hear it out.
When did I falsify the accounts?
If you're accusing me of that,
you stamped the seal!
Yes,
I admit
threatening you with loan fraud
was despicable,
but my love for you
is genuine.
I never meant to harm anyone.
I just want you to come back with me.
With this recording,
we can at least prove to the bank
that we aren't part of his scheme.
And we didn't know
about the loan fraud,
nor involved in it.
We've used part of the loan,
but fortunately not much.
I told parents
we're facing
the cash flow problem.
Then they gave us
the pension money
you gave them.
Now the money is ready.
We can repay the bank anytime.
I'm sorry, Yan.
You entrusted me with the company,
and I caused this mess.
This isn't your fault.
Besides,
you got the evidence.
You've done great enough.
By the way,
you mentioned
that Lin Tao raised
the profit margin to 21 percent,
to let us get the loan?
Yes.
Given our high-cost
handmade fabrics,
and the enormous expenses
for promotion,
our company
is in a phase
of seeking the break-even point.
It's impossible to achieve
a 21 percent profit margin.
How could the bank miss this?
The loan officer Feng
is Lin Tao's close friend.
Also...
That is not plausible.
Loan fraud is illegal
and leads to jail time.
Would this Feng
really take
such huge risks
just to help Lin Tao?
Even if there were oversights
in the review process,
both staff and supervisors
would face severe legal liabilities.
In this regard,
banks would be extremely cautious.
This is suspicious.
In that case,
there is something off.
(Manager's Office)
Ms. Qiao,
Lin Tao
has handled the documents.
Just stamp here.
Feng,
thank you for the loan.
(Loan Contract)
Don't worry.
Tao and I
are old friends.
We'll proceed
at the fastest pace.
Thank you.
Truly a lifesaver.
(Party B: Jingzhou Yan Studio Fashion Design Co., Ltd.)
It's nothing.
This should be okay.
Once the funds are released,
I'll notify you.
Feng,
when do you finish work today?
Let's have dinner together tonight.
I...
Ms. Qiao.
I've booked our return tickets.
We need to leave tonight.
Next time then.
Now that we've connected,
there'll be many opportunities.
Next time then.
So Lin Tao
didn't want you
to contact
that Feng.
Now,
the top priority
is to find Feng
and figure out
what's happening
with this loan.
Besides,
I know you don't want
Yu Yiming involved,
but this matter
has nothing to do
with your relationship.
I think
you should be honest with him.
Anyway,
that's how it is.
I know...
I know you'd be upset.
You didn't tell me
because you feared Lin Tao
would escalate things and implicate me.
You've been bearing
all this alone recently.
But from now on,
no matter what happens,
whether it's big or small,
you have to tell me.
I plan to visit my hometown
to find Feng
and see if I can figure out this.
Alright.
I'll go with you.
No need. I can go by myself.
No way.
What if Feng is colluding
with Lin Tao?
What if something happens?
I must go with you.
Alright.
(Yan Studio)
Currently,
apart from our production line's
steady output,
I want you all
to focus on
pushing forward
with the physical store expansion.
Four key points to note.
First,
window display designs.
Second,
pre-launch marketing campaigns.
Third,
staff service training.
Fourth,
supply chain reliability.
All departments must
offer timely feedback.
Besides,
there will be
more staff.
If you need anything,
inform HR.
Qiao Lin,
a mall in Tianjin
invites us to set up
a physical store there.
This is
a good opportunity.
You'll go discuss
the details thoroughly.
Okay.
Mr. Lin.
We're pushing forward
with the physical store project,
so the financial work
will increase.
Please handle it.
I'm glad
that the company is thriving.
Please compile
the budgets of all departments
and put them in my office.
I want
our petty cash reserve
adjusted to three percent.
No problem.
On Wednesday,
I'll discuss it with you.
Okay.
Please state
your budgets.
Lin Tao, take notes.
Huanhuan,
what's the biggest expense
in promotion?
It's mainly about
KOL collaborations
and organizing offline events.
We plan to launch
a physical store check-in campaign,
posting featuring Yan Studio...
(Yan Studio)
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
When will you return?
I'll go early tomorrow
and have a dinner.
I will be back
by the morning after next.
Don't worry.
It won't delay our trip back home.
Now that the company is back on track,
and everything goes smoothly,
I must keep
my promise.
I know.
I'm not pushing you.
Enough talk.
Time will prove everything.
(Qiao Lin.)
(Remember this place?)
Where you asked me to dinner last time.
I've prepared something special.
Balloons,
flowers,
and champagne.
Most importantly,
there's us two.
Will you marry me?
Yu Yiming?
Lin.
What's going on?
Why do you bring him here?
Lin.
Look, I've bought the ring.
Let's go back at 11 AM
this Saturday
to...
Lin won't go back with you,
nor will she marry you.
Broke your promise?
I've helped you.
Now you're backing out?
Didn't I make myself clear?
You should know the consequences.
We know about the loan.
You went to see Feng?
You assumed
that I would
fear escalation.
You also assumed
that I wouldn't dare approach the bank.
You thought
we would
accept this loan,
make regular payments,
and never mention it again.
But how is that possible?
If this were loan fraud,
I'd face legal consequences
because I stamped the seal
and it's my negligence.
That's what I planned to do.
When I met with Feng,
I wanted to explain the situation,
but then I discovered
you never
falsified the accounts.
You gave him
the authentic financial records,
so he approved the loan.
So, you didn't
want me to dine with him.
You lied to me,
gave me fake reports,
and made me stamp them,
in order to get me back
and marry you.
Lin Tao.
You had a conscience
and didn't commit loan fraud.
Otherwise,
we'd be at the police station.
I could sue you,
but I want to show some mercy.
So, please leave.
Lin Tao.
Stop all these schemes.
Especially leave Qiao Lin alone.
Or I won't let you off.
Sir, should we serve the dishes?
Get out!
What?
I've received the email.
You want me
to sign a performance-based agreement,
right?
Mr. Qu.
As the head
of the group,
you've planned
to bid for the North Waichuan plot,
and proposed
if the bid succeeds,
we'll terminate early
your one-year probation period.
Right?
This bid could transform
the real estate landscape.
The demands seem reasonable, right?
But if you fail,
Jinda's stock will plummet.
You're newly appointed.
The shareholders
have reservations.
Hence, they proposed
a performance-based agreement.
If you succeed,
your probation will end early.
If you fail,
the Chairman position
will be up for re-election.
Mr. Qu.
Don't get us wrong.
This isn't personal.
Every new chairman
must undergo
such challenges in their probation.
After all,
the shareholders want to see
solid financial performance.
That applies to everyone.
I'm back.
How's Haochen doing?
He's been doing great.
I met Miss Sun
and greeted her.
If there's
any problem with Haochen,
she'll contact us.
Anyway, don't worry.
Everything
is getting better.
Haochen
asked to go back to school.
That's truly remarkable.
My mom is also
grateful to you and Grandma.
If she puts it that way,
it feels too formal.
Haochen gets better,
and our family will be better.
Alright.
How's your physical store project?
Everything is on track.
The renovation
is more than halfway done.
And Yao has completed
the botanical dyeing series designs.
I'll see them today.
Great.
What's your plan?
Bid for the North Waichuan plot.
Qu Mingcheng made other shareholders
sue me and my dad,
demanding us
to compensate the group's losses.
Our accounts are frozen,
and we lost our positions at Jinda.
Everyone thinks
I couldn't win the bid
for this Diamond Plot.
I know I can't win forever,
but for Dad and Haochen,
I won't lose to Qu Mingcheng.
Which company will you use for the bid?
My dad's first company,
called Xinye.
Our core team members
have all resigned
and will stick with me.
I have the confidence and energy
to continue bidding.
And thank you for your help too.
I don't accept verbal thanks.
If you want to thank me,
do it properly
when you succeed.
Yes.
By the way,
you're meeting Mr. Huang, right?
Yes.
Your suit and tie
are upstairs.
See?
Thank you very much for your support.
I told you
I don't accept verbal thanks.
Haoming.
Is everything going smoothly
in the new company?
Pretty well.
I hope
I can collaborate with you.
To be honest,
without capital
or corporate backing,
how can I cooperate with you?
Four years ago,
when North Waichuan's
development plans were announced,
my team and I
started monitoring.
About land supply,
policy directions,
municipal planning,
and our competitors' strategies,
we've conducted the research.
I'll offer the proposal.
You'll offer the capital.
Let's bid jointly.
For this project,
I'm not pursuing profits,
but to defeat Qu Mingcheng.
Mr. Huang.
Mr. Qu is here.
Let him in.
Mr. Qu.
There's no denying
your offer is very generous,
but I have reservations.
Shen Haoming is young.
You can say
he doesn't hold much sway
in the group yet.
But Shen Jinsong
is the founder of Jinda Group.
He's managed the group for decades.
The shareholders
may seem to be on your side now.
But once Shen Jinsong recovers
and returns to the group,
where will their loyalties lie?
Shen Jinsong
can't even take care of himself now.
He's completely
out of this battlefield.
Nothing to fear.
Bring me the documents
about the bank credit loans.
Here.
This endorsement...
Okay.
Compile the data.
No. 9.
(Project Objectives and Significance)
Note this down.
Good news!
Mr. Chen
will invest in our project.
Really?
Fantastic!
How's this?
Can you keep up?
Mr. Huang.
You run marathons every year,
even full distances.
I need more practice.
Haoming,
I enjoy
teaming up with young people.
You're energetic
and resilient.
I run alone
by this lake every day,
with no one to share
such beautiful scenery.
By the way,
the proposal is ready.
We can submit it soon.
Haoming.
I know
your vision, energy,
and strategic mindset.
I'm getting old.
I am not
what I used to be.
I've wanted to retire.
Make some investments and enjoy life.
But working with you
makes me feel
rejuvenated.
I think
I could still work.
Mr. Huang.
Don't retire yet.
Stay and let us learn from you.
Let's go.
Haoming.
Sorry.
But for the second half,
I want to run alone.
That cunning Huang Chuming.
We made the proposal
as a joint venture until now.
The funding section especially
was crucial
for winning the bid.
But he
pulls out his investment
without warning.
Revise our bidding strategy now
is impossible.
With Mr. Huang's investment,
we would
at least have a support
and stand a chance
against Qu Mingcheng.
But he withdraws
his investment,
we stand no chance now.
In my opinion,
better to cut losses early
than crash and burn.
I suggest
we withdraw from this bid.
Why gamble
on such a risky bid?
Mr. Shen.
What do you think?
Continue.
We've been
prepping for ages.
I don't want to waste your hard work.
Let's revise the proposal
and submit it.
Do it with
the minimum 1 percent deposit.
Why?
Even if we fail, so what?
Consider this
our debut in the industry.
Winning doesn't matter.
I don't want others
to think losing one partner
makes us stuck
and even lose
the courage
to compete.
Keep discussing
the proposal.
Check if our project
has green space
development plans.
Still working?
It's late now.
We might fail
this Diamond Plot bidding,
but as a new company,
having a viable project
builds market reputation.
Found any suitable one?
Yes.
Take a look
at this.
(Shikumen Renovation Project)
Shikumen?
It is
a renovation project.
Pretty nice.
The collaboration
with Gubei Town
makes me realize
the governments'
efforts on cultural preservation.
It has reached
new heights recently.
So this direction is correct.
Exactly.
What?
Your hair.
Wrap it up
and get some rest.
Okay.
Need company?
No need.
I'll be up shortly.
Alright.
Any progress?
Yes.
Good then.
Go to sleep.
I heard Shen Haoming
landed a government-backed
renovation project.
Exactly.
The cooperation is confirmed.
He is
quite smart,
taking some projects
to sustain his startup.
Where's Weiping?
You set up a new firm for him.
As a rookie entrepreneur,
he's swamped.
Anything else?
Mr. Qu.
I know
you promised Weiping
to let Jinda's legal team
channel our projects
to his firm.
However,
I've reviewed
another firm's proposal
that outperforms
his firm
in every way.
But I promised Weiping.
Mr. Qu.
Appointing me to the board
has displeased
those shareholders.
If we channel our projects
to a new firm,
they might suspect
your relationship with Weiping.
How about this?
Let's have a transitional period.
Anyway,
we can channel
the projects to Weiping later.
Then explain this properly to him.
Avoid causing unnecessary trouble.
Rest assured.
(Han Weiping)
Officail Website : kissasian.biz
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Hello.
Meet me at the downstairs caf├ر.
Now.
(Jinda Group)
It's not up to you.
My godfather
has promised me
to sign a long-term agreement
with my firm.
You asked me here
just to discuss this?
Your godfather is busy
with the North Waichuan plot.
This is the top priority now.
Can't you distinguish priorities?
Steve.
You're behind this, right?
I strongly suspect
this agreement will still be mine.
Weiping.
I understand
how you feel right now.
However,
you did engage in
shady activities
for your godfather.
But now,
it's a critical period.
Mr. Qu has to be cautious.
Please understand.
Trying to kick me out now?
To take down the Shen family,
do you know how much I sacrificed?
The incident with Haochen last time
got me detained by police,
and I even lost my lawyer's license.
I've lost everything.
I'm going upstairs
to ask my godfather.
Aren't you afraid
it will cost your other hand too?
Young man,
don't be so impulsive.
Mr. Qu.
Want to see me?
Haoming.
Have a seat.
Actually,
this adversarial situation between us
isn't what I want.
I don't have children.
Since childhood,
you've been close to me.
To be honest,
sometimes
I genuinely envy your dad
for having a son like you.
My resentment
is solely toward your dad.
Think about it.
If he had shown
more consideration to an old comrade
like me,
then the ones
to celebrate success
would be us.
You asked me to come
not for sentimental talk, right?
Your dad's hospitalization
isn't what I want.
Now you've
started a small company
and are taking on
government projects.
Taking the safe route
seems wise.
If...
I mean, if.
If you want to,
I can
buy your shares
from you and your dad
at a favorable price.
As for the compensation lawsuit,
we can withdraw it.
This is the best for you.
Jinda
was built from scratch by my dad.
We won't sell
any shares.
This is
my best offer
to you two.
If you reject,
you and your dad will have
to go against the entire group.
You'll end up bankrupt.
(North Waichuan Plot 1137
Bidding Conference)
(North Waichuan Plot 1137 Bidding Conference)
Hello,
ladies and gentlemen,
morning.
Welcome to
the North Waichuan Plot 1137
bidding conference.
Today's bidding
will be supervised
by inspection authorities
(North Waichuan Plot 1137 Bidding Conference)
and municipal notary office
to ensure fairness,
justice, and transparency.
This bidding project
involves comprehensive development
of North Waichuan Plot 1137.
All participating companies
must strictly comply with
the People's Republic of China's
Bidding Law
and relevant regulations.
Maintain strict discipline.
Any illegal activities
will be severely punished.
And then
we invite supervisors to examine
the sealed bidding documents.
(North Waichuan Plot 1137
Bidding Conference)
During inspection,
raise objections if any,
otherwise documents
will be deemed sealed.
(Bidding Documents)
All seals intact,
meeting the requirements.
Hold on.
Sorry for interrupting.
These are
(North Waichuan Plot 1137 Bidding Conference)
internal documents
from Jinda, Shijia, Wanlin,
and my employer Shouke.
They detail
bidding strategy
and bidding collusion scheme.
I personally accuse
Jinda Group Chairman Qu Mingcheng
of orchestrating this
bidding collusion operation.
When arriving,
did you see that car downstairs?
I saw it.
My every move now
is being monitored by Qu Mingcheng.
He's afraid you'll make a move.
But he never expected
you would side with me.
Alright.
You can go now.
He'll come up shortly.
Representatives
from Jinda, Shijia and Wanlin
must come with us.
Besides,
Shouke's representative
as a whistleblower,
must assist investigations.
(North Waichuan Plot 1137
Bidding Conference)
Due to accidental reasons,
per investment committee decision,
this conference is suspended.
Resumption will be notified later.
Thank you.
ظآزLike fireworks that lovedظآز
ظآزRushing toward the starsظآز
ظآزUndaunted by painظآز
ظآزFearless of flamesظآز
ظآزEven if just a fleeting sparkleظآز
ظآزWe shed tearsظآز
ظآزDeep blue seas turn to foamظآز
ظآزWe regained freedomظآز
ظآزIf you remember meظآز
ظآزThen I'm pleasedظآز
ظآزI just wanna take my time tonightظآز
ظآزTo do all the things I said I'd tryظآز
ظآزI go surfing, go diving, go driving,
and go flying to a different placeظآز
ظآزI go drink, go party, and go danceظآز
ظآزEven if I'm lonelyظآز
ظآزCause I just have been hurt
too many timesظآز
ظآزI'm giving it all to get nothing backظآز
ظآزI was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even seeظآز
ظآزSee the world and how it flows.
We never let goظآز
ظآزSo I'll take my timeظآز
ظآزTo reigniteظآز
ظآزThe love I should deserveظآز
ظآزWhen the time is rightظآز
ظآزYou realizeظآز
ظآزIt will all be alrightظآز
ظآزCause I just have been hurt
too many timesظآز
ظآزI'm giving it all to get nothing backظآز
ظآزI was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even seeظآز
ظآزSee the world and how it flows.
We never let goظآز
ظآزSo I'll take my timeظآز
ظآزTo reigniteظآز
ظآزThe love I should deserveظآز
ظآزWhen the time is rightظآز
ظآزYou realizeظآز
ظآزIt will all be alrightظآز