ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
There are several unforgettable moments throughout our lives.
No.
To be more precise,
several paused temporal nodes.
ISAAC ASIMOV: THE END OF ETERNITY
DUAN
Busted, thief.
This is my second time
looking at him so closely.
Time does have magic
drawing us closer in height
and distance.
In the Pythagorean theorem,
A squared plus B squared
equals the square of C, the longest side.
Sang Zhi.
Sang Zhi!
What are you staring at?
Just now, a mother bird
brought back food to feed baby birds.
The two baby birds were fighting for it.
Then the mother bird flew away
with the food.
They were then stunned
for one or two minutes.
They were frozen.
Be quiet, everyone.
Sang Zhi.
Pay attention
and look at the board.
Sit down.
Let's read the third question aloud.
-"A triangle ABC -"A triangle ABC
-with side lengths -with side lengths
-of 5 cm, 13 cm, and 12 cm." -of 5 cm, 13 cm, and 12 cm."
Obviously,
we can see that the longest length
is C.
So
how do we get this?
Equals 5…
The conditions given
are that the side lengths are A and B.
What kind of triangle is this?
-"A right triangle." -"A right triangle."
Multiply the base by the height and divide by two.
Look at this.
You've picked this up, right?
Next question.
Angle one equals angle two.
Angle three is 108 degrees.
Sang Zhi!
Sang Zhi.
Where was I just now?
Angle four equals 72 degrees.
I haven't gotten there yet.
Where were you just now?
Silence.
Silence!
Angle one equals angle two,
so line AB is parallel to line CD.
As they are parallel lines,
same-side interior angles are supplementary.
-So angle three is-- -Stop.
It's not about the question.
It's your attitude!
Sang Zhi, tomorrow,
have your parents come in.
Sit down.
Let's continue.
Angle one equals angle two.
This means that these two straight lines
are parallel to each other.
The interior angles are supplementary.
Therefore, calculate angle four.
GRADE 8, CLASS 1
-Let's go home. -Go!
I'm sorry about earlier.
I pointed to the wrong line
and the teacher caught you again.
Your mom has already come in twice
in just half a month.
I don't know if I rubbed him the wrong way.
But when you replied
with his own question,
I felt like punching you,
let alone Mr. Chen.
Don't you think his voice is hypnotizing?
I would've dozed off
if I didn't do something.
You're right.
But why do you always get caught by him?
It never happened to me.
Ask her if she wants to go to the bookstore.
Let's go.
Do you want to go to the bookstore?
Why?
Fu Zhengchu invited us
and also some boys from his class.
Let's go together.
Why do you want to go?
To buy study materials.
Are you coming along?
No.
Coming?
Sang Yan, you've been away for a while.
When are you coming home?
Can you come back tomorrow?
I miss you so much.
So are you coming?
No, I'm not going.
But they're waiting over there.
Let's go, please.
Go ahead if you want.
I'm not in the mood today.
Is it because your parents have to come?
What do you plan to do?
They're not coming.
Even so,
Mr. Chen will call them.
That's why I asked my brother to come.
He replied.
I'm leaving.
-Wait. -Sang Zhi.
Bye.
Sang Zhi, why are you leaving?
Aren't you coming to the bookstore?
Is Sang Zhi not coming?
The teacher scolded her.
She's feeling down.
Are her parents coming again?
Her parents come more often than yours, Fu Zhengchu.
Shame on you.
Mind your own business.
Why won't he help me?
Sang Yan, you're heartless.
Sure.
SILLY DOG
You abandoned me after going to university!
Sure.
You're leaving me to struggle by myself!
ANGRY, GOING TO BE ANGRY, ANNOYED
How am I going to face Dad and Mom?
I won't let it go that easily, Silly Dog.
What should I do?
Doggy.
Come here.
You're so adorable.
Do you know? Sang Yan, that silly dog,
left me on my own and even angered me.
You think he's hateful, right?
Listen, you mustn't grow into a big silly dog like him
in the future.
Though you're a small silly dog,
don't grow up to be like him, okay?
You're good in this way.
Are you going to make me angry too?
Is that how it is?
I'm sure you'll become a big silly dog,
just like Sang Yan.
Zhizhi, welcome home.
Mom.
Listen.
-The-- -Hold on.
Take the fruit upstairs.
Sang Yan is back.
He's back?
Yes.
Be careful when you go upstairs.
-Okay. -He--
She's rather weird today.
Sang Yan!
What's up?
Did you get plastic surgery?
Come over and see
if the results are good.
What's wrong with you?
Are you amazed by my dashing look?
You're more narcissistic than me, Sang Yan.
Shut up.
Little demon, tell me now.
What have you done this time?
No, I did nothing.
No?
How is that possible?
Why else would you say you miss me
and ask me to come home?
Sang Yan, something did come up.
Is she your sister, Sang Yan?
Do you think she's my daughter?
Sang Yan.
Who is he?
My roommate, Duan Jiaxu.
Hello, little girl.
I'm Duan Jiaxu.
I'm your brother's friend.
Do we look alike?
The bathroom is over there.
Take a look in the mirror.
Who looks like you?
Really?
But your sister just asked me
if I got plastic surgery.
What do you mean?
Sang Yan, didn't you say
you weren't coming back today?
Little demon, don't tell me you mistook him for me
and a tweaked version of me at that!
Little demon,
what do you think about every day?
What is on your mind?
You…
Stop!
Isn't plastic surgery the obvious conclusion?
Look at your ugly face.
Besides, Mom didn't tell me
you brought a friend.
Moreover, he was the only one in the room.
Naturally, I mistook him for you!
Keep it down!
Why should I?
You're too loud!
You can't beat me.
Here, little girl.
Have some fruit.
Don't bother with him.
Duan Jiaxu,
do you want to shower before leaving?
No. Go get changed so we can go.
All right. I'm going to get changed.
-Hurry up. -Wait!
Sang Yan, I need your help.
Move.
I'm in a rush to get plastic surgery.
I'm sorry.
Too bad.
Are you leaving me for dead?
I don't even know what you're asking for.
Shoot. What is it?
Please say yes first.
I can't do that.
Are you going to report me to Mom?
Mom!
You were laughing just now. What happened?
Mom, Sang Yan beat me!
Mom!
-Mom, Sang Yan beat me! -Sang Yan.
Can you not do that to your sister?
Mom!
Stop that.
Why shush her? How dare you bully her!
Mom, Sang Yan beat me.
-He said I… -All right, dear.
Don't cry.
How could you?
I'll teach him a lesson.
Come with me.
-What's going on? You… -I didn't touch her.
Did you say you didn't?
I saw it with my eyes.
Xiaoduan is here.
-How could you do that? -I won't do it again.
You're her big brother!
Never again!
Good, you know you're wrong.
Can you get me a tissue?
Do you and your brother
do this often?
It's nothing. Don't worry.
Mom doesn't actually scold him.
We've done this since we were kids.
Didn't you ask Sang Yan for help just now?
Why did you frame him then?
Wait, little girl.
Hold back your tears.
What about this?
I'll talk to Sang Yan
and ask him to help you.
What do you need?
It won't work. He won't help me now.
No, Sang Yan isn't that petty.
Jiaxu, do you have time tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Yes, tomorrow.
What if I say
I'm not free?
No, you can't.
You must be available.
Why?
If you hadn't told Sang Yan
about the plastic surgery thing,
I wouldn't have fought with him
and he would have helped me.
You might have a point.
So tell me.
What do you need me to do?
Can you please
pretend to be my brother?
My real brother.
And then,
meet with my teacher.
Are you in trouble at school?
What have you done?
Can I not tell?
Sure.
Then
I'm busy tomorrow.
I wasn't paying attention in class.
I got called to answer a question.
I answered correctly,
but he wanted to meet with my parents.
Do you expect me to buy that?
I'm telling the truth.
If you don't believe me,
you'll find out tomorrow when you go.
Even if I lie to you now,
the teacher will tell you tomorrow.
True.
Little demon.
Get out.
Can't I stay here?
I have to get changed.
Weren't you doing it outside?
I want to do it here now.
If so, he should leave the room too.
I don't think he wants to watch either.
You two, get out.
I'm going to undress.
It took you long enough.
Close the door.
Jiaxu, are you coming or not tomorrow?
I've told you everything.
Why don't you ask Sang Yan?
No way!
I framed him just now.
If I were to tell him…
Sang Yan isn't like that.
What are you mumbling about, little demon?
A light bulb burned out.
Mrs. Sang, I'm leaving.
Leaving? Are you not staying for dinner?
I've prepared many dishes.
I have a part-time job later.
Enjoy your meal.
All right.
What about you, Sang Yan?
I'm not eating since he's not.
Fine. Take this trash out for me.
Take the boxes out first.
Hurry up.
I'll do it, Mrs. Sang.
No, of course not. I…
It's no big deal.
I'm leaving.
All right, thank you.
Come for dinner next time.
-Sure, Mrs. Sang. -Good.
-Bye, Mrs. Sang. -Where are the boxes, Mom?
They're right there.
Bye, little girl.
See you next time.
Bye?
Jiaxu, are you leaving so soon?
It's getting late.
Why don't you stay for dinner?
Maybe next time.
When is the next time?
Duan Jiaxu.
Don't waste your breath with an elementary student.
You're an elementary student.
I'm in eighth grade.
Gosh, you're an eighth-grader. Impressive.
Are you in eighth grade?
So,
you're 14?
Are you trying to say that I'm too short
to be in eighth grade?
Rightfully so. That's what he meant.
No, that's not what I meant.
Don't get me wrong.
I won't argue with you.
Anyway, I'll grow taller.
No worries at all. You won't grow more.
But it's good for you.
At 30, people will think that you're 18.
So is it because you're tall
that people assume you're my dad?
Bye.
You're 14.
What school do you go to?
Xuri Middle-High School.
Grade 8, Class 1.
And your name?
I'm Sang Zhi.
Sang Zhi?
Yes, "Zhi" as in innocence.
Duan Jiaxu.
-Let's go. -I'm coming.
So Sang Zhi,
you know when we'll meet next time, right?
Bye.
Close the gate when you leave.
Next time?
Hold on.
When will that be?
Tomorrow?
So is he coming tomorrow or not?
Why didn't he give me an exact answer?
CHAPTER ONE, WAITING
A SECRET KEPT
Mom.
Good morning.
Good morning, Sang Zhi!
Little demon.
-Can't you see me? -What's for breakfast?
Hey!
Little demon!
Hi!
Sang Yan, you're back.
Yes, this is my home.
Why can't I come back?
So you know this is your home?
When was the last time you were back?
You can ask Dad and Mom if they still recognize you.
I haven't seen you for a month
and you're giving me this attitude?
What attitude do you expect from me then?
Welcome.
A warm welcome to you.
Welcome home, Sang Yan.
Are you happy? Is this okay?
-I'm happy. -Let me give you a big hand.
-Well, stop it. -Enough.
-That's enough. -The egg crepe is ready.
-That's too much. -Sit down.
Hurry and try the egg crepe with tuna
that your dad made for you.
Nice.
"My name is Sang Zhi and this is how I talk."
Stop making fun of her.
-Come on. -Eat up.
Thank you, Dad.
Dad, I'm moving back
to the main campus.
So I might need to borrow your car.
Do you have a lot of things?
I can get you a moving company.
No, this is better than the campus bus.
I remember that the main campus
is near Zhizhi's school.
You can pick up Zhizhi from school from now on.
I'm in university now.
I'm not babysitting her.
I don't need him. I'm in 11th grade.
That had best be the case.
Dad, can I borrow your car this morning?
I'm fetching my roommate's things too.
Yes, as long as you don't bully Sang Zhi.
Fine, I'll try to.
Which roommate?
Why do you ask?
What do you want?
Sang Yan, how about I help you move?
Do you want to help me move?
Did I mishear you?
No, you didn't.
You need to go to school.
I can go after school.
You won't be done that early anyway.
May I?
Zhizhi.
Your art science subject tests are in a few days.
You have to study at school.
I've already done the revision.
I can take a few days off.
Do your revision.
Besides, I'm sure I'll have finished moving
by the time you come.
Mom, Dad.
Sang Yan hasn't been home in a long time.
I've been missing him so much.
I'm grown up now
and I should do something for him.
Sang Yan, look how sincere she is.
Just let her help.
-That's right. -She won't affect your studies.
Wait.
How can she help? My things are heavy.
She can't move them at all.
I'll have to keep her from getting hurt.
If she gets hurt,
I'll be in big trouble when I come home.
Just let her keep an eye on your things.
Isn't that good?
Fine, do what you like.
I'll call you after school.
Do you want this?
I'm eating this.
Hello.
I'm here.
You actually came?
Where are you?
I'm too busy to come get you.
Wait for me there.
Tell me where you are now.
I'll come find you.
Block 9, Room 525.
Block 9.
Got it.
Silly Dog.
It's Dad's car.
ISAAC ASIMOV: THE END OF ETERNITY
DUAN
Busted, thief.
Sang Zhi?
It has been some years.
I hardly recognized you.
I'm here to help my brother move.
I know. He told me.
But why did you only steal my things?
Is this yours?
I…
I didn't know it was yours.
Had I known, I wouldn't have touched it.
What do you mean by that?
Kiddo, where is your conscience?
I did you a great favor. Don't you remember?
No.
If you like this plushie, take it.
I was kidding.
I'm already in 11th grade.
I don't play with plushies anymore.
I see.
I'll throw it away then.
I…
I can play with it for a while.
Come on. I'll take you upstairs.
You can take your brother's shoes.
Let's go.
Jiaxu.
Did you get this fox plushie
from someone else?
I think so.
I can't remember.
We have to walk up five floors.
Can you do it?
This way.
Sang Yan.
You said you were too busy to get me.
You're not busy!
You just didn't want to come to get me.
I just finished up and sat down to rest.
No, you didn't.
You didn't move at all.
You didn't tidy up just now.
Mom asked you to fetch me.
-Give that to me. -Sang Yan.
Is this your sister?
Yes.
Greet Qian Fei.
Hello, Qian Fei. I'm Sang Zhi.
Little girl,
you're so adorable!
Keep your distance.
It's our first meeting.
Why can't I go near her?
Besides, I'm short-sighted.
You'll scare her if you get too close.
I'm sorry about that.
Don't be.
Come here, little girl.
Sit over here.
Sit over there.
I'm not little.
I said I'm not little.
All right,
girl.
What do we have for dinner?
We've finally moved here
and your sister is here too.
Let's not eat at the canteen.
There's a good hot pot place in the mall.
What do you say?
Let's eat barbecue.
There's a food street off campus.
Let's try that out.
Hot pot, please.
Haven't you had enough barbecue?
DIRECT ADMISSION RECOMMENDATION
Little demon.
Hey, little demon.
Do you want a hot pot or barbecue?
Jiaxu, let's have a hot pot tonight.
You guys go.
I have my part-time job later.
Seriously, Jiaxu?
Where are you going?
Don't tell me you have a girlfriend.
You can't be the only one dating.
-Introduce a girl to me. -Introduce one to me first.
Don't cut in line. Me first.
Any girl who isn't hot-tempered.
Any girl will do
as long as she likes me.
Qian Fei.
My brother told me
all the girls in school pursued him.
Well, little girl.
I have never seen someone
more thick-skinned than him!
I suppose Sang Yan
has been more handsome lately.
Get away from me.
You guys talk.
I'm off.
Girl.
If you like it, take it with you.
Bye.
He's leaving so soon.
Duan Jiaxu hasn't thrown that away.
What's wrong with him?
It's just a decoration on his bed.
It's completely useless.
By the way, Qian Fei.
Does Jiaxu have a girlfriend?
Did his girlfriend give him this?
He doesn't have a girlfriend.
He's busy every day
and has no time for dating.
I think it was a prize from some event.
It was from last semester.
If you don't like it, just leave it there.
That dog must have made a fool of you.
Dog?
Don't you know?
He and your brother are known
as the Twin Dogs of Nanwu.
I thought Sang Yan was the only dog.
Enough of that.
Do you want a hot pot or barbecue?
Neither.
What do you want?
I'll drive you home after.
No need. I want to go home now.
I'm not eating.
I can drive you home.
I'll take the bus.
Really?
Fine, it's almost time. Let's go.
I'm leaving.
-Bye! -Bye. See you next time.
"Asimov.
The End of Eternity.
But it resolves itself
into an identity.
There is a loop of small dimensions
with no tributaries
on either side."
Can you understand this?
Maybe this is the distance between us.
I can't understand the book he is reading.
I only know the characters.
Sang Yan, how is your thesis coming along?
I need more references.
-I'll go to the library tomorrow. -You're focused.
I haven't finished my thesis yet.
I haven't either.
Why are you back?
I brought some food for you.
Help yourselves.
-Okay. -Sure.
It's all your fault.
You're always bringing food from work.
That's why I'm so chubby. I blame you.
Jiaxu.
My sister called me just now
and said you left something with her.
Did I leave something with her?
Hold on.
I'll call her.
SILLY DOG
Did you find it?
Kiddo.
What did I leave behind with you?
No, you didn't leave something with me.
I left something at your place.
What is it?
An exercise book.
I'll ask Sang Yan
to bring it to you tomorrow morning.
But I haven't done my homework yet.
Are you asking me to do it for you?
No.
It's because it's an essay.
I might not have time to finish it.
Why don't you ask Sang Yan to do it for you?
He would break my legs.
Sang Zhi.
This homework
is a task assigned by your teacher.
You can be honest with the teacher,
apologize,
and say you will complete it afterward.
You shouldn't ask someone to do it for you.
What time do you usually arrive at school?
7:40 a.m.
So you wake up at 7:00 a.m.
Can you wake up at 6:00 a.m. tomorrow?
Why?
Tomorrow,
I'll wait for you at the bus stop at 6:40 a.m.
I'll help you write the essay.
Is that okay?
If so, you should plan out
what you will write.
After that, wash up and go to bed.
All right.
6:00 a.m.
Remember to set the alarm.
I'll call you then.
Go to sleep now.
Good night.
CALL LOG
LITTLE DEMON
-Your phone. -What is it?
What did you forget?
It's trivial.
What time are you going to the library?
First thing in the morning.
As early as possible.
Why so early?
I need to organize my research topic
to find breakthroughs for my arguments.
That's quite a lot of work.
ESSAY BOOKLET
That makes sense.
Remember to wake me up tomorrow morning.
Good night.
ALARM
ADD ALARM
ALARM SOUND
Good night.
ALARM
XURI MIDDLE-HIGH SCHOOL
Why isn't he here yet?
Will he really come?
You can converse the theorem
in this way too.
Therefore, we call the two theorems
reciprocal theorems.
Learn the converse theorem by heart.
Does he know I finish class at 4:20 p.m.?
I forgot to tell him.
For the triangle's legs,
A squared plus B squared.
Is he not planning to come?
Maybe I should have Sang Yan ask him.
A squared plus B squared…
That won't do.
Sang Yan will find out.
You keep sighing throughout the lesson.
Did I not explain it well enough?
Did I sigh?
No,
you didn't sigh.
I sighed.
Today's homework
will be the first ten questions
in the booklet.
Class dismissed.
All rise.
-Goodbye, sir. -Goodbye, sir.
Sang Zhi.
I'll wait for your parents in the office.
Shoot.
What should I do now?
So Sang Zhi,
you know when we'll meet next time, right?
What did he mean?
Will he come tomorrow?
I'm Duan Jiaxu.
Duan Jiaxu.
How is it written?