Happy Thanksgiving!
Happy Thanksgiving, dorks.
They didn't see you.
♪In my bones, yeah, I know it's platonic ♪
♪Fucking your ex is iconic ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be,
sue me, I gotta be ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be ♪
♪Wanted ♪
Night-night.
Wellsy?
♪Super hot, big fun ♪
♪Lights off...♪
♪I wanna know
what's your fantasy ♪
♪We can make it happen
at my sex party ♪
What the fuck?
You again.
No, not me again. You again.
Are you seriously hooking up on top of me?
- Well, this is my house.
- Yeah, where you presumably have a room.
It's you from the bathroom.
Yes, we've established it's me.
Did you follow me?
I was here first.
Well, it's not my fault
you won't leave me alone.
you can't survive two seconds
- without sticking your dick in someone.
- Oh.
No offense.
- All good.
- None taken.
- I take offense.
- No one asked you.
You know, we don't really need him.
- You wanna go back to mine?
- Mm-hmm.
Wait, no, no, wait, wait, wait!
She's leaving in a second.
Jesus.
- Happy now?
- A little bit.
Whatever.
I'm going outside.
So, you're breaking up
with your boyfriend?
What? I'm not breaking up with him.
You want to, though.
You guys have been together
since your freshman year, on and off.
But now you're not sure about your future
because the dude's gonna move to Vermont
and be a boring insurance salesman
and you, you wanna act.
How?
You told pretty much everyone
tonight at karaoke.
Oh, my God.
Okay, so what are you gonna do?
I don't know.
This whole thing.
I just...
My dad gave up so much
to be there for my mom when she...
And I know that meant everything to her.
And their relationship was beautiful.
And I want that.
But you don't want to move to Vermont.
No.
Okay, so what do you want, Allie?
I guess... I want to be in love.
But I don't want that to make it
impossible for me to, like, move to LA
or take a show to Edinburgh,
work my ass off on Broadway, you know?
I want to be able to do it all.
Even though I know it's more likely
I'll succeed at none of it.
- So...
- Hell no.
That's not dumb.
If that's what you want, go after it.
People who care about you will understand.
And if they don't,
they're not your people.
Okay, which one of your exes
taught you to be so insightful?
I don't have any exes. It's...
- the weed.
- Wait.
Dean Di Laurentis
has never had a girlfriend?
I like being the casual sex guy.
It's easy.
I have heard you're easy.
I'm Six Flags, baby.
Everybody wants a ride.
They come for a good time,
not a long time, and that's fine by me.
Is it?
Looking at it won't make him text.
No. No, you're so right.
Here, save me from myself.
What?
- What are you--
- When you break up with this guy,
which you will,
you're gonna want a fun ride
to distract you.
Call me.
Sorry, dude. I don't do roller coasters.
♪I was too scared to let myself sing ♪
♪All these pieces left behind ♪
♪Making it easier to find ♪
One sec.
Well, hello.
Yeah, I know.
I said I wouldn't call.
And yet?
And yet.
You're calling.
I broke up with Sean.
I'm sorry.
Hmm. No, you're not.
No. I'm not.
I really want to call him.
But you called me instead.
I did.
You lied.
About what?
You like roller coasters.
No.
I fucking love roller coasters.
♪I just wanna know
if maybe it would be okay ♪
♪If we could get together after hours
maybe at my place...♪
Okay.
I just broke up with Sean,
and I can't hurt his feelings.
- This is a one-time thing.
- Uh-huh.
Tell no one.
- I got it.
- Good.
♪Backs against the wall ♪
♪Baby, give it all ♪
♪I wanna believe ♪
♪Treat me like you need me...♪
♪Oh please baby don't be dense...♪
♪Careful with my body-ody
like a brand new Benz...♪
Okay, this is the last time.
♪...make it go just like the rest ♪
♪It gets better if you let me ♪
♪Dive into this ocean
make it ride just like a jet ski ♪
♪I can take you up
like falcon doors all on a teslie...♪
Okay, this is the last time.
♪...if you ready ♪
♪If you ready ♪
♪Touch me ♪
♪Squeeze me
treat me like you need me...♪
♪Baby give it all ♪
♪I wanna believe...♪
- I thought you said no one was home.
- They weren't supposed to be.
Okay, but...
Yeah, give me a second.
I forgot something in the bathroom.
- Hold on, hold on.
- Dude, dude, take it.
One second, all right.
I'm sorry. I just needed my--
Yeah, no. It's fine, man. Just...
- Just go.
- Okay, I'll go.
That was absolutely the last time.
♪Backs against the wall ♪
♪Baby, give it all ♪
♪Touch me ♪
♪Squeeze me
treat me like you need me ♪
I just think this is really important
to Garrett that this goes well.
That's what relationships are for, honeybun.
Supporting each other.
Helping each other grow as people.
Can't all be about sex and fun.
Mm.
Shit, the bus is almost here. Gotta go.
What? No, Garrett can just drive you.
No, it's fine. I love a bus.
You hate a bus.
It's fine.
Love you. Happy Thanksgiving.
Happy Thanksgiving.
♪I can't get enough of your love ♪
♪I can't get enough of your love...♪
All roads lead back to Dean.
This is just a ride.
Allie, this is...
- Beau Maxwell.
- Yeah.
- Joanna Maxwell's little brother.
- Oh, yeah. You know Jo?
Well, I don't "know her" know her,
but I know her in the way
that she's like a god who walks among us.
She booked a Lynn Nottage play,
like, a week after graduating,
and now she's Zendaya’s understudy
in Oleanna on Broadway.
Joanna Maxwell's, like, iconic.
You're allowed to just call her Joanna.
You know that.
Okay, sorry.
I bet you're so sick of theater talk.
You kidding? You're looking at the guy
who skipped his midterm
to go see J-Groff in Merrily.
No way. Did he spit on you?
- Oh, don't get him started.
- So much.
- I was in, like, the sixth row.
- Shut up!
Okay, favorite musical of all time.
Three, two, one.
-  In the Heights.
- Fuck off.
-  Stop!
- You guys just met.
Okay, okay, second favorite.
Three, two, one.
Little Shop.
Oh, my God, you guys!
What'd you say?
What?
♪Oh, my God ♪
♪Oh, my God, you guys...♪
What is this, hell?
You're receiving an education.
♪Elle saw right through
that salesgirl's lies...♪
What is this? What...
♪...but I'm not that blonde ♪
♪I may be in love, but I'm not stupid ♪
♪Lady, I've got eyes ♪
- Oh, my God!
- Oh!
♪Sorry, our mistake ♪
♪Courtney, take your break ♪
No, no, no.
I can't--
Don't listen to him, Allie, all right?
Dean was indoctrinated by Joanna
just like the rest of us.
- What? I don't know what you mean by that.
- Yeah, you do.
Dean, do you sing?
- Absolutely not.
- No, Dean was more of a dancer.
Stop. Stop.
- Please tell me there's a video.
- Oh, there's a video.
I will kill you.
Okay, the sunglasses are too good.
Why were there sunglasses, you ask?
No reason. No reason at all.
Okay, well, you are sending this to me.
- No, you're not.
- Obviously.
Need a ride back Friday?
Do I get to DJ?
Hell, yeah, you get to DJ.
As long as you exclusively play songs
that'll make Dean miserable.
On second thought,
I think you should take the bus.
Oh, no, no, don't listen to him, Allie.
He can hitchhike to New York.
See you Friday.
Are you alone now?
Can we talk about Aunt Kathy's
new British accent?
And she goes by Kiara now.
It's, like, a whole thing.
Wasn't she in London for like a week?
- Al?
- Huh? Um, no, yeah, totally.
Uh, okay, what's going on?
No, nothing.
It's just like, everyone's over.
Hey, Allie Hayes, I can hear your nails.
Who are you texting?
What? Nobody.
It's Sean. You're backsliding.
Am not.
Hey, it's okay.
It's my dad. He, um...
He can't find the remote again. He...
I swear he has ADHD,
but his generation's undiagnosable.
Oh, okay.
Okay, I should probably go help.
Love you, miss you. Gobble, gobble.
Hey.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Cute.
Yeah, my dad gets me one every year.
Holy shit.
I mean, I kind of hate you, but...
holy fucking shit.
Thanks?
No, I mean, seriously,
it's like Gwyneth Paltrow's AD tour
and the Guggenheim had a baby.
- You said this wasn't a date.
- It's not.
- Feels like a date.
It's a good bottle of wine
my parents won't miss.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Okay.
Do you want the tour?
Is it gonna make me hate you more?
Probably.
Your sister's closet
is the size of my bedroom.
I could literally live in it.
I don't know why one person
needs so many vintage bags.
Usually, we have a Basquiat there,
but it's on loan to the Whitney.
Okay, let's see it.
What?
Your big move.
Grand finale.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Fine.
There's a piano in the den,
and I usually end the tour there.
And I talk about the piano,
and then they ask if I play,
and then I say, "Kind of."
- Kind of?
- Exactly.
Then I sit down and I play "Mad World."
"Mad World?"
It's the only song I know, and it works.
It works, okay?
Can you be normal?
It's just me.
- I am being normal.
- No, you're not.
What would you be doing if I wasn't here?
You play chess by yourself?
I had to get better than Summer.
She's a chaos monster.
My dad taught us when we were little.
It was a family tradition.
That's sweet.
It's cutthroat.
Where is your family now?
St. Barts.
We have a-- We have a place there.
Sounds terrible.
Mm, doesn't it?
I'm so glad Jensen's
making us practice on Friday
because otherwise I'd be--
you know, I'd be laying on a beach
day drinking with Nick and destroying
Summer in beach volleyball.
God, you live a tough life, Di Laurentis.
The worst.
I'm sorry you can't be
with your family, though.
It seems like you miss them.
I get to be here with you.
Also...
Check.
- Come on!
- Never...
ever let the enemy distract you.
Okay.
Never let the enemy distract you.
♪Feel me ♪
♪Ah ooh ♪
♪Do you think about the way
we used to feel?♪
♪Oh, oh ♪
♪Your momma warned you
about the boys like me ♪
♪We're said to break your heart ♪
♪Ain't that true?♪
♪I wish you listened to your friends ♪
♪When they had told you, "Break apart"♪
♪Yeah ♪
♪Hey, it's never too late to make love ♪
♪But I don't want to have to make up ♪
♪No, I don't want to have to make up ♪
♪It's never too late to make love ♪
♪But I don't want to have to make up ♪
♪No, I don't want to have to make up ♪
♪It's never too late to make love ♪
♪But I don't want to have to make up ♪
♪No, I don't want to have to make up ♪
♪Ooh ♪
♪Do you think about the way
we used to feel ♪
♪Feel me ♪
♪Do you think about the way
we used to feel?♪
Be honest, how many of your neighbors
have seen you butt naked?
Literally all of them.
Sorry, it's the guys.
Take it.
Seriously?
Hello?
Hey! What?
Are you already asleep?
It’s called tryptophan, motherfuckers.
Where are you?
He's in fucking New York on Thanksgiving.
Yankees suck!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
Well, at least I'm not
freezing my ass off at the rink.
Last time I checked,
my ass was pretty intact.
-  Can confirm.
-  You guys are so dumb.
Dean, do you never
have a shirt on?
Wellsy, don't stoop to their level.
Happy Thanksgiving!
Happy Thanksgiving, dorks.
They didn't see you.
This was supposed to be a one-time thing.
I mean, Hannah's stupid happy
and Garrett's your friend.
- Like, I can't mess that up.
- How is this messing it up?
By making her thing about me.
She deserves this.
And the second people find out we're...
- They're gonna ask what this is.
- No, no. No one's gonna ask that.
They're not gonna ask you that.
People are gonna talk
and Sean will find out,
and I can't hurt him.
Like, I called you, what,
36 hours after I broke up with him?
That's less than 48. Oh, my God.
I-I-I fucked you less than 48 hours
after breaking up with Sean.
We had fun. We were safe.
We didn't hurt anyone.
Yeah, so let's keep it that way.
Allie, come on.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
- Allie.
-  ♪There you stood ♪
♪Behind your glasses ♪
♪There you stood ♪
♪There you stood, regret the past ♪
♪But regretting all the things
that past, but...♪
Hey.
- How was practice?
- It was fine.
- Hey.
- How are you?
Good.
- I can practice this downstairs if you...
- No, stay.
I'm just gonna close my eyes.
♪There you stood behind your glasses ♪
♪In a hazy yellow world ♪
♪Alone enough for me to ask ♪
♪Just alone enough ♪
♪To feel the hurt ♪
♪The glow ♪
♪The glow of star-born eyes ♪
♪Reflect the sky ♪
♪Until I find ♪
♪I'm sinking into your ♪
♪Yellow, yellow haze ♪
♪Lingering as you pour ♪
Why did you stop?
You're exhausted.
No, I like listening to you sing.
I like playing for you.
What do you think?
You sound beautiful.
About the song, the lyrics.
- You hate it.
- No.
No, I don't. At all.
I... I really like the melody.
I just... I don't get it.
I mean, well, maybe I'm just tired, but...
No, no, it's okay. I don't get it either.
What exactly is a yellow haze?
Justin said something
about the aura of falling in love.
Oh.
Is it getting worse?
- Well, have you talked to him about it?
- Yeah.
I thought I could fix it, but, I mean,
the showcase is in two weeks.
And my gut is telling me
you should just start over.
I just can't figure out how to tell Justin
his lyrics aren't working.
Well, have you tried,
"Hey, asshole, this isn't working"?
- Right?
- No.
No!
- You never had a problem giving me shit.
- Well, this is different. This is his art.
This is your art, too.
And your showcase piece.
Ah!
You've got this. I believe in you.
Hmm.
♪Justin, our song fucking sucks
and we're gonna lose the showcase ♪
Oh, we got a winner here.
♪It sounds so bad, so bad ♪
Actually, you know what, usually,
I like hearing you sing, but...
♪Oh, Garrett hates my singing ♪
♪But it's okay, 'cause he loves me ♪
Yeah, I do.
I...
I love you, Wellsy.
I love you, too.
You guys said "I love you"?
If you would have told me six months ago
that I'd be hot and single
and you'd be abandoning me to go spend
the night with Garrett Graham, I'd...
Okay, I'm the worst.
Being this happy when you're in a crisis?
I'm unpacking.
What? No, no, no, no.
You're in love. Go be in love.
Okay, you were texting Sean
over Thanksgiving.
You miss him.
Actually, I was not.
He's been giving me space.
And that's freaking you out?
Surprisingly, no.
I'm enjoying the space.
- Well, that's great.
- Totally.
Totally.
Except, if I'm enjoying the space,
then that means
I'm a terrible, shitty person
who hurts someone she supposedly loved
and then just moves on.
This is about your mom.
She said never give up on love.
And when she got sick,
my dad was there for her, you know?
Like, every step of the way.
Even when it got so hard.
So then do I just call it quits with Sean
because I'm not willing
to put in the work?
Like, did I give up on love?
Of course not.
If Sean's not the great love of your life,
that's okay.
You'll find another great love.
Or, I mean, hear me out.
Like, a fling?
Okay, uh...
flings have just not been super successful
for you, historically speaking.
What are you talking about?
I can fling.
-  Uh...
- I can!
Remember after the second Sean breakup?
All those dates with frat boys
who didn't believe in soap?
Yeah, okay, well,
maybe that was my mistake.
I don't need to date someone.
I just need a distraction.
A fuck buddy.
Okay, you know I love you.
And I think you're perfect.
And I will support you no matter what.
But you, Allie Hayes,
are a card-carrying member.
I know, I'm Team Boyfriend.
Team Boyfriend.
You like snuggling and inside jokes.
You want to tell a guy about your day
and meet his mom
and watch him run a 5K
and then complain
about having to watch him run a 5K.
It's a really stupid length for a race.
Hey, look, this stuff with Sean is hard.
But whether you move on
or you get back together with him,
bottom line is, I'm here for you.
I'm Team Allie.
So just know that and believe that.
And totally ignore this giant duffle
I am packing to abandon you yet again.
You're not abandoning me.
You're going to have super hot sex
all night with a guy who loves you.
But you're not taking that.
It's mine.
Maybe "all you can eat"
was not my most romantic idea?
Wellsy.
Saw you guys on Fifth Line.
Is Jules--
- They're everywhere.
- Like God.
We're supposed to be on a date.
Oh, wow, you really splurged, G.
- This one was my treat.
- Oh, then, rescinded.
So, how was y'all's break?
First time meeting Papa Graham, right?
Yeah, it was... it was fine.
Yeah. Family. Sucks.
Did you at least get that signed jersey
for the Hurricanes fundraiser?
That Phil Graham merch room is legit.
Uh, not this year.
What's the Hurricanes?
It's a local youth hockey program.
We do a fundraiser for them every year.
Logan was a Lil 'Cane.
Oh, is that still happening?
I thought the venue fell through.
Yeah, well, they double booked.
I'm trying to figure it out.
Hey, we were really
counting on that Phil donation.
I... I can reach out.
I'll sign a jersey,
and you can auction that.
Okay, big shot.
You're not in the pros yet.
I didn't mean...
I'm trying to help.
Uh, what if you did it at Malone's?
That's...
- Really?
- Yeah, I can run it by Della.
I'm sure she'll be happy to help.
What kind of vibe were you thinking?
♪I'll keep you, my dirty little secret ♪
♪Dirty little secret ♪
♪Don't tell anyone ♪
♪Or you'll be just another regret ♪
♪Just another regret ♪
♪Hope that you can keep it ♪
♪My dirty little secret ♪
♪Dirty little secret,
dirty little secret ♪
- ♪Who has to know?♪
♪Who has to know?♪
Give it up for After Hours, everybody.
And a big round of applause
to my buddy John Logan
for putting on this killer event!
Look at him.
Doesn't get any better-looking than that.
And he's single, ladies.
And we've already raised 2,000 bucks
for those Lil 'Canes,
but we want to raise a hell of a lot more
for those guys.
So get drunk, hit up our silent auction,
and get some cool shit.
Sadly, the photo booth is out of order,
but there's still a lot of fun to be had.
The band is taking requests.
So scan those QR codes and let them know
what songs you want to hear.
All right, you guys ready?
Let's have some fun.
♪Let me know what I've done wrong ♪
♪When I've known this all along...♪
So, what'd you think?
"Dirty Little Secret"?
That was mine.
Subtle.
Just reminding you in case you forgot,
I can keep a secret.
I get that you're worried,
but there's no reason
we can't just keep doing
what we've been doing.
- Hooking up all over campus?
- Having fun.
Just meet me in the bathroom
in, let's say, five minutes.
You're delusional.
Everyone we know is here.
And I'm not that kind of girl.
But you want to be.
Take these to your boys.
For the record, I am not delusional.
I just know what I want.
Go.
♪Go around a time or two ♪
♪Just to waste my time with you...♪
You see how quick they are?
They're going to capitalize on mistakes.
Control is key. Tucker, you cannot
let them get a step on you.
- Not a single one.
- No, Graham, I'm not having this.
Put that thing away.
We have St. A's tomorrow.
We don't go to bars
to gripe and moan about hockey.
We go to bars to score, okay?
What the fuck is wrong with you people?
- Fellas.
- Thank the Lord.
Beau, tell them to stop
talking hockey shit.
Oh, no, no. Keep talking hockey shit.
That's why I came over here.
-  Why?
- Puck bunnies, 11 o'clock.
- Hey guys.
- Oh, hello.
Hi, I'm Beau. Nice to meet you.
- ♪These sleeping dogs won't lie...♪
- Here you go.
♪And all I've tried to hide ♪
♪It's eating me apart...♪
We need more pigs in a blanket,
napkins, and--
That really doesn't bother you?
No, I trust Garrett.
And the puck bunnies
are actually kind of cool.
Yeah.
They know what they want.
God, it's so hot when someone
knows what they want.
If you really want a fling,
I think you should go for it.
- You think?
- Yeah, you're single.
Embrace that.
Just pick someone
who will never catch feelings for you.
Someone down for anything.
Like the anti-Sean.
Yeah, you make a good point.
Yeah, someone with zero expectations
who just wants sex.
Just sex.
All right, we've got another request.
This one goes out to Maverick.
♪Check it out
going out on the late night ♪
♪Looking tight, feeling nice
it's a cock fight ♪
♪I can tell, I just know
that it's going down ♪
♪Tonight...♪
I love a throwback.
Right?
♪You don't really want
to mess with me tonight ♪
♪Just stop and take a second ♪
♪I was fine
before you walked into my life ♪
♪'Cause you know it's over ♪
♪Before it began ♪
♪Keep your drink, just give me the money ♪
♪It's just you and your hand tonight ♪
♪Midnight, I'm drunk ♪
♪I don't give a fuck ♪
♪Wanna dance by myself
guess you're outta luck ♪
♪Back up, I'm not the one ♪
♪Buh-bye...♪
Okay, back to work.
♪Listen up, it's just not happening ♪
♪You can say what you want
to your boyfriends ♪
♪Just let me have my fun tonight ♪
♪All right...♪
Is that your answer?
Take a look around.
Any girl would be happy
to stick her tongue down your throat.
I don't want any girl.
Well, guess you're stuck with your hand.
♪'Cause you know it's over ♪
♪Before it began ♪
♪Keep your drink, just give me the money ♪
♪It's just you and your hand ♪
Thanks.
This next one is for fans
of One Direction.
Hey, Wellsy.
I need those freshmen
selling raffle tickets
and not listening to GHA over there
talking strategy.
GHA?
Uh, General Hard Ass.
What's so important
about this game tomorrow?
St. Anthony's?
Ever since they beat Eastwood,
they've been gunning
for our top spot in the conference.
- Are they close?
- They're on a ten-game streak.
So they're close.
If we lose, they'll be number one
in the conference.
Shit.
That's what's in his head right now.
But there's nothing we
can do about that tonight.
We need people drunk and happy
and spending money.
Can you help?
Aye, aye, captain.
Thanks.
And, uh...
For all this.
What are friends for?
♪Oh, I just wanna take you
anywhere that you'd like ♪
♪We could go out any day, any night ♪
♪Baby, I'll take you there...♪
They've scored at least three goals
by end of the first.
I mean, their zone is suffocating--
A little bird told me that you freshmen
need to get off your asses
and go sell some raffle tickets.
It's Logan.
Was it Logan?
It was Logan.
Okay, this is a party.
And?
And parties are supposed to be fun.
Well, so is winning.
Jensen wants me to step up more
as captain, so I'm stepping up.
Well, others have suggested
you might be boring everyone to death.
I'm guessing that was also Logan.
This fundraiser means a lot to him.
It's sweet.
Sweet doesn't win games.
Okay, I heard carbs are good, though.
Thank you.
♪And you just wanna take me home...♪
Have you talked to him yet?
Uh, yeah, no, sound check
didn't really seem like the time to be...
like, "Justin, I don't like
your lyrics or our song,
which, by the way, used to be about you,
but I don't have a crush on you anymore,
so I really don't know
what it should be about,
but it should not be about yellow haze."
Hmm.
Well, maybe we work on the wording
of that a little.
Okay, party people.
A few of our silent auction items
are currently going for way undervalue,
so if you act fast,
you could get them for a steal.
A steal. Now, um, I know there are
mostly Boston fans in the house.
That's right!
And as a born and bred New Yorker,
I happen to think those people
are living a sad, desperate existence--
Ow! New York!
- Get out of here!
-  Hey, Della.
We love you, but this one...
This one.
This one's part of the family.
I have box seats
to a New York Rangers game
and a meet-and-greet
with the legend himself,
Phil Graham!
Yeah, so don't be cheap!
- Did you...?
- Nope.
...for all the beautiful,
intelligent supporters...
And that's right, Rangers fans,
I'm looking at you.
Garrett.
Did you call my fucking dad?
Hey, I hope your son enjoys the camp.
Thanks.
What the hell, dude? He just donated.
Did you call my dad?
Look, Phil gives something every year.
All right? You obviously
just didn't ask him right.
That's not...
- He's...
- A self-centered pompous asshole?
Yeah, my mom's in rehab
for the fifth time.
I get it, okay?
But who cares, all right?
It's for a good cause.
You don't know what you're talking about.
You never once considered
why I didn't want you to call.
Are you kidding?
All we ever do
is think about what you want.
Do you know how much hockey costs?
Genuine question.
Because these kids need the money.
I needed the money.
This fundraiser
is the only fucking reason I'm here.
It's not all about money.
Spoken like a person
with a shit ton of it.
Back for a second set.
Ladies and gentlemen,
give it up for After Hours!
All right, we're gonna take a break
from requests.
We're gonna play something
brand-new for you, it's an original.
Written with one and only Hannah Wells.
You didn't tell me
he was going to sing your song.
Oh, you didn't know. Shit.
Hey, well, on the bright side,
you're about to find out if it's any good.
Maybe people will love it.
♪There you stood behind your glasses ♪
♪In a hazy yellow world...♪
Oh, God.
♪Alone enough for me to ask just ♪
♪Alone enough to feel the hurt ♪
♪Echoes weaving through the walls ♪
♪They're keeping secrets in the night ♪
♪We are indivisible ♪
♪Together we're a number prime ♪
♪The glow ♪
♪The glow of star-born eyes
reflect the sky ♪
♪Until I find I'm sinking into your ♪
♪Yellow, yellow haze ♪
♪Lingering as it pours ♪
♪Yellow, yellow rain ♪
♪What was it all for?♪
Yellow rain?
Like pee?
♪Sinking into your ♪
♪Yellow, yellow haze...♪
No, it-it's catchy. It's catchy.
♪Yellow, yellow ♪
There you are.
What'd you think?
What did--
The song is not ready.
Well, I mean, I thought--
I thought it went well.
No, it's supposed to grab people.
Like, make them feel things.
Yeah, they seemed really into it.
The lyrics don't even make sense.
They're poetic.
No, we need to start again.
From the beginning.
No.
What?
Hannah, stop fucking with my head.
I made something I'm proud of.
I performed it.
I put my heart on the line.
And you go on and on
about how you don't feel it.
How you don't connect.
How the song doesn't sound like you.
Of course it doesn't.
Because you refuse
to put yourself in this.
You...
You want to feel something, Hannah?
Try writing your own lyrics.
I'm done.
And in first place...
Grace Ivers.
Please collect your prizes
from Della at the bar.
Congratulations to all
of our lucky winners tonight.
A lot of people got what they wanted,
but not all of us.
So if there's any last-minute requests,
changes of heart,
remember that the photo booth
is out of order.
Um, okay, yeah. Good night.
Good night.
He's been weird tonight, right?
So weird.
♪I cannot wait to get around you
see that look upon your face ♪
♪Touch me ♪
♪Squeeze me
treat me like you need me ♪
♪Baby make it easy ♪
♪Backs against the wall ♪
♪Baby give it all ♪
♪I want to believe...♪
Change your mind?
No. Maybe.
- Just every time we do this, I feel so--
- Amazing.
Bad. I feel bad.
- Guilty.
- Wait, are you Catholic?
No. I'm just a girl.
I have to think about
what everyone else feels
before I can figure out what I'm feeling.
And I can't even do that right now
because this fucking breakup
is totally messing with my head.
- I don't even know what to think.
- Then don't. Don't think.
Tell me what you want.
Allie Cat.
This is not a relationship, okay?
No strings, no feelings, just sex.
Just fucking kiss me.
♪Baby, make it easy ♪
♪Backs against the wall ♪
♪Baby, give it all ♪
♪I wanna believe it ♪
♪Treat me like you need me...♪
Meet at mine in an hour.
♪How I crystallize ♪
♪Everything I see ♪
♪Through my rose tint eyes ♪
This is a party.
♪It's just the way I feel...♪
Parties are supposed to be fun.
Are you having fun?
Not really. You?
Yeah, not really.
Justin and I broke up.
Oh, not words I was expecting to hear
from my girlfriend about another guy.
I have two weeks to write another song.
There's plenty of time.
You and Logan gonna be okay?
We'll be fine.
Yesterday when he asked about your dad,
it could have been an opening
to tell him.
Tell him what?
About Thanksgiving?
What you told me.
Phil's a dick.
Logan knows that. Everybody does.
That's all they have to know.
Yeah, well, what happens
when Phil shows up to a game?
When I win, he nods.
And when I lose, he says nothing.
He won't be that hard to ignore.
I think you should tell someone.
Jensen, Logan.
They care about you.
I don't need them to know.
I mean, that's why I have you.
I trust you.
- You wanna go home?
- I wish.
I told Della I'd oversee cleanup,
and I really should get started
on the song.
Okay, you go.
I'll stay at my place tonight.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
You get some sleep for the game tomorrow.
Big scary game against big scary St. A's.
You scare the shit out of them, you know.
Look how hard
they're trying to please you.
They're not trying to please me.
They're trying to win.
Which you will.
See you tomorrow, okay?
I'll be in the stands with the sign
that says, "I heart Garrett Graham."
Might be kind of hard to spot you.
There are a lot of those signs.
- I hate you.
- I love you, too.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
♪Twist it up, make it art ♪
♪Oh, you twist it up, twist it up ♪
♪Looking for something real ♪
♪Twist it up, make it art ♪
♪Oh, you twist it up, twist it up ♪
♪Looking for something real ♪
♪Me and the boys in the hotel lobby ♪
♪Me and the boys in the hotel lobby...♪
Fuck me.
♪Me and the boys in the hotel lobby ♪
♪Low tide, moon's so bright ♪
♪Moving my hips from left to right ♪
♪My, my, check my phone ♪
♪Feel it in my belly
when you're driving home like ♪
♪Low tide, moon's so bright ♪
♪Moving my hips from left to right ♪
♪My, my, check my phone ♪
♪Feel it in my belly
when you're driving home like ♪
♪Like Cinderella making babies
on the company's dime...♪
Hannah, I got a bar to close.
Sorry. I'm going.
♪We're making pennies out of paper ♪
♪Better find a new slime ♪
♪Me and the boys in the hotel lobby ♪
♪Me and the boys in the hotel lobby...♪
Where you going?
- Oh, shit.
- What?
Okay, wait, you gotta go. Like, right now.
Hannah's coming home.
- I don't--
- It doesn't matter. You can't be here.
- Okay.
- Hustle!
- You look so good.
Shut up.
- Go.
- Okay, bye.
Oh, shit.
You forgot your jacket...
Wow.
Sean, I...
We just broke up, Al.
- I wasn't...
- Yeah, you were.
You really can't be alone, can you?
No, Sean. It wasn't like that, I swear.
Oh, come on. Sean!
- Night, guys. Good luck tomorrow.
- Thanks.
Yeah, if you're on the ice with Delaney,
you just gotta do what G says.
He can't hold up against all the pressure.
Who?
St. A's new center, Aaron Delaney.
Dude's a beast.
♪I've been numb, I'm dying to feel ♪
♪Touching a grave that isn't real ♪
♪Touching a ghost that I can't see ♪
♪But the ghost is me ♪
♪A melting candle on a piece of cake ♪
♪I can't tell if I'm awake ♪
♪There is a ghost that stares at me ♪
♪But the ghost is me ♪
♪The ghost is me ♪
♪Fall through the floor ♪
♪Walk through walls ♪
♪Looking at pictures in the hall ♪
♪Staring in mirrors so I can see ♪
♪That the ghost is me ♪
♪Showing up when you least expect ♪
♪A little girl that died in a wreck ♪
♪Alive again and finally free ♪
♪The ghost is me ♪