ظآزJust To Meet You, you fell for meظآز
ظآزJust to meet me, into my trap you fellظآز
ظآزWanna try a breathless love?ظآز
ظآزEvery move hits the heart, close and sureظآز
ظآزJust To Meet You, you love my playful charmظآز
ظآزJust to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for youظآز
ظآزWanna play another brand-new game?ظآز
ظآزLayer by layer, we close the gapظآز
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 16=
=Niannian's In Danger=
Could Li Zhongtian have known all along
my mother's death was tied to Liu Yexi.
For the family's hollow reputation,
he'd really sacrifice anything.
No wonder I was kept in the dark twice.
Niannian.
You know what.
When I was little,
so many people
would insult my mother
as a useless woman,
saying even if she could paint,
she brought nothing to the family.
She's just a burden.
They said I was an illegitimate son.
Like I never should've been born.
No, Ye Lang.
That's all past.
I thought
I'd accepted my mother's death.
But now I realize
I never knew the truth.
Maybe I shouldn't have been born.
I only bring trouble to others.
That's not true.
You deserve to be loved.
You always have.
Niannian.
I really only
have you with me.
I'm here.
I want to take you to see her.
Mom.
I finally know the truth.
I'm sorry.
It took me all this time
to figure it out.
I met someone truly wonderful.
She is Jiang Niannian.
After living a second life,
and meeting you again,
I finally understand
love means understanding,
respect,
not making choices for you,
but facing this world with you.
Niannian.
I finally know how to love you.
But we are not
who we were in our last life.
So...
You're not going to forgive me?
Niannian.
I know I was wrong.
I really know I was wrong.
Please don't push me away anymore.
Niannian.
I'll change whatever you want me to.
I'm not rejecting you.
I just feel like
nothing matters anymore.
You helped Xiaodi get better.
I'm really grateful.
But from now on,
don't carry everything alone.
If anything happens,
you have to tell me.
Okay?
ظآزAre you real, or just a dream?ظآز
You scared me to death.
ظآزLike a chance encounter in plain sightظآز
ظآزAre you an angel,
or from the dark?ظآز
ظآزYou're as beautiful as the moonlightظآز
Niannian.
Would you wear it again?
Mm.
ظآزJust To Meet You, you fell for meظآز
ظآزJust to meet me, into my trap you fellظآز
ظآزWanna┬بtry a breathless love?ظآز
ظآزEvery move hits the heart, close and sureظآز
ظآزJust To Meet You, you love my┬بplayful charmظآز
I swear
I'll spend this whole life
repaying everything
I owe you from both lifetimes.
Then your probation period
starts today.
Okay.
Even if it lasts ten years,
twenty or thirty, I'm still willing.
As long as you stay by my side,
I'll do whatever you say.
I didn't expect
the mighty Young Master Li
to cry like this.
Come on.
Let's go home.
Ye Lang,
I won't let you off easy.
I'll make you know
what it's like to lose it all.
Careful.
Seeing the way you protected me,
people might think
I'm made of glass.
My baby
isn't to be touched.
Need me to carry you?
No.
Jiang Niannian!
Jiang Niannian.
You've wed the rich 4 times.
(Shameless Blood Peony)
With Ye Lang,
you killed three husbands.
Your crimes are unforgivable!
(No Monopoly)
Shameless woman!
- Shameless!
- Bloody Peony?
- You'll get
- You're a curse.
the defamation verdict soon.
Don't worry.
I'll handle everything.
Jiang Niannian, you gold-digging woman.
Shameless!
Father.
These are my shares and post at the Li Group.
I really can't keep this up.
Let my brother take them.
After all,
I was never the son you favored.
I'm exhausted.
I'm going to rest in the sanatorium.
Zhong killed himself crashing into a wall?
That's enough.
Stop looking into
Liu Yexi's death.
Lay her to rest tomorrow morning.
The Li family
can't take any more of this.
Tell Ye Lang
to deal with the public opinion mess.
Why are you still here?
I'll take my leave, Father.
Okay.
(Now I can do it my way.)
(No one can stop me now.)
Brat.
The Li family
are all insane!
One day,
I'll have you kneeling at my feet!
Hong.
Mom.
I brought you calming herbal soup.
Only you treat me well.
Mom.
Lately, I keep remembering
how you used to sing me to sleep.
My silly son.
You're all grown up,
why are you still like a kid?
Here.
Drink the soup.
Okay.
Mom.
Can you sing that lullaby
you used to sing to me?
Of course.
As many times as you want.
For you,
I would
do anything.
ظآزSleep, baby, sleepظآز
ظآزYour mother...ظآز
What?
Not happy
tying the tie for me?
If you keep frowning like that,
I'll kiss you till you smile.
Quit it.
I'm serious.
Those people yesterday
claimed to be my ex's relatives.
Something felt off.
Remember Li Hong leaving sick?
I think he sent those people.
He wants the company to collapse
while I'm in charge, then take over.
Don't worry.
I can handle
those shareholders.
I'm not worried about you.
Ye Lang.
You're going to be late.
Instead of dealing with them,
I'd rather be here with you.
ظآزWarm light, softly hazyظآز
Ye Lang.
Alright.
Enough for this.
ظآزThat restless heartظآز
ظآزI falling for you, I falling youظآز
ظآزLost in your deep eyesظآز
ظآزYou slowly melt my frozen winterظآز
ظآزI slowly believe the only truthظآز
I know you're going to see Xiaodi.
So whatever it is,
let's talk tonight.
ظآزI slowly become certainظآز
ظآزYou're etched clearly into my memoryظآز
Hello.
Ye Lang
can't protect you forever.
Go to hell.
Jiang Niannian.
Save your strength.
Once the car goes over,
no one can save you.
You'd better pray for a better next life.
Niannian.
Niannian!
Don't be scared.
I'm here.
I'll get you out.
What happened?
You got hurt?
Don't scare me.
Are you okay?
I...
I'm good.
Come on.
Niannian!
There was no crash in my previous life.
Someone must be behind this.
And...
That person might be like me,
reborn knowing everything.
Wait for me.
Hello?
Anyone there?
Keep calling.
By the time Ye Lang finds you,
you'll be frozen solid.
ظآزStitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red duskظآز
ظآزYou return reborn,
seeing through all my cracksظآز
ظآزThis tenderness, a trap or a gift?ظآز
ظآزStill, I'd wager my next life on itظآز
ظآزJust for a moment to recognize you againظآز
ظآزYou are the blazing light in my despairظآز
ظآزLighting the edges of my frozen wingsظآز
ظآزI burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fireظآز
ظآزBreaking free
from dead vines in the ashesظآز
ظآزYou are the brightest star in the nightظآز
ظآزAwakening my dormant fateظآز
ظآزFreeing me from this half-life prisonظآز
ظآزAs the bells shatter the pastظآز
ظآزLife finds its way againظآز