=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 14=
(Grace Garden)
Maybe
some rare treasures
will be on display.
I've heard Master Yili'er
has a remarkable skill
for identifying gold and treasures.
If he identifies anything authentic,
he'll even spend a fortune to buy it.
This is my family heirloom.
How I wish
I could be so fortunate.
I wonder if Master Yili'er
will teach others.
It would be even better
if he could teach me.
It's starting. Let's get in.
Come on.
Your Grace.
The show begins.
Master Yili'er is here.
There you are, Master.
Master,
take a look at my treasure.
Look at mine.
This is my family heirloom.
My dear guests,
you've all come with your treasures.
I'll identify them one by one.
All right.
If the treasure is genuine,
you'll get 1,000 pieces of gold.
But if it's fake,
it'll be destroyed right here.
What?
Destroyed?
Mine is real. I'm not afraid.
- Right.
- Go ahead.
So many dignitaries.
Peerless in Youzhou, indeed.
If you smell like this,
even the best nose
will no longer work.
Go to the woodshed
and smell the firewood
to restore this sense.
You mortals are such a hassle.
It seems
you're here to collect scents
instead of finding the Lord
of Jiling Temple.
Can you sense if Song Xingyu is here?
He stole the Glazed Pagoda,
a magic tool,
to evade my spiritual perception.
Then how will you lure him out?
Yili'er made a deal with Song Xingyu.
But now he wants you.
So they've grown estranged.
Yili'er
is the one we need to crack.
What a peculiar smell.
Precious sword.
Sword.
It's pretty good.
This sword...
I'll offer 5,000 pieces of gold.
- 5,000 pieces?
- 5,000?
Now destroy
all the counterfeits!
What?
All of them?
Really?
They can't all be fake, huh?
But...
It doesn't look fake at all.
It was really smashed.
And even this one?
Again.
So much gold.
This is too much.
Thank you, Master.
Can you even move that?
You've made a fortune.
This man is truly lucky.
Congratulations.
A genuine item
will be worth a hundredfold.
A counterfeit will be destroyed.
It's a huge gamble, indeed.
Master.
Master, Master.
This is mine.
Look at mine.
Master, please take a look.
Look.
Is this jade vase
genuine or fake?
Where did you get it?
At a young age,
my grandfather got this jade piece
from a renowned master
when he traveled
with my ancestors.
Yili'er is just
what they say he is.
Not exactly.
Calm down and see for yourself.
How much is it worth?
Antiques oppose wind energy.
If the wisps of wind can tightly
connect with the antique,
it means it's real.
Conversely,
it's fake.
It's...
What's this?
A drop of water falls on the jade.
If it stays as a dewdrop
without dispersing,
it's real jade.
This item doesn't match.
It doesn't?
But that is genuine.
So we're watching a show
"a deceitful substitution."
Destroy it now.
Destroy? No.
You can't destroy it.
Don't listen to him.
Hey.
Yeah.
There's no way this is fake.
Oh no. I...
Move, move.
Get out of the way.
What are you doing?
Check mine, please.
It's from the previous dynasty.
Look at this.
- Previous dynasty?
- Looks nice.
Nice, isn't it?
It's finely crafted
with smooth lines.
That's right.
Sadly, it's too thick and heavy.
Not from the previous dynasty.
It's a current forgery.
There's no way
this is an antique.
According to the rules,
a fake must be destroyed here.
Since it's a fake,
why not sell it to me?
Who is she?
What is that?
Why does it give off a strange scent?
It's a bracelet made of agarwood.
Very precious.
Miss, it's my honor
to have you live here.
Take this
as a welcoming gift.
People usually
have a deal with newly shaped spirits
as their servants.
I've never seen anyone
who has a deal
with such a powerful spirit.
Who says I'm his servant?
I'm the master and he's the servant.
I command him.
Miss,
if you don't mind,
will you hand him over
to me?
Name your price.
You're carrying the token
of the Lord of Jiling Temple.
How dare you want another one?
I don't dare to let my spirit
snatch his servant.
How do you know?
No wonder you said
your spirit was disobedient.
Have you also heard that?
The Lord of Jiling Temple is in trouble.
Are you going to abandon him?
It seems you don't know.
He offended the Sovereign
and fled to the Mortal World.
Now,
he has been tracked down.
I think
if he gets caught,
he should be executed immediately.
Otherwise, if he escapes again
or if he
gets locked up for centuries,
he won't answer when you call him.
And you can't casually get a new spirit.
Then your life
will pass by quickly.
Miss,
if I end up having no spirit,
will you give me yours?
What will you give me in return?
What do you want?
Who's that?
Song Xingyu?
(Song Xingyu, Lord of Jiling Temple)
Greetings, My Lord.
Why am I losing control of my mouth?
Look, My Lord.
These are the treasures
I've collected for you.
They're sparkling and valuable.
Tell me.
When stealing during the day,
did you see a woman with a spirit?
I'm very familiar with them.
Do you mean
the spirit holding a sword?
Does the woman have spirit power?
No.
She's a mere mortal.
So, Fang Chang didn't lie.
How powerful is the spirit
by her side?
I can't tell
how powerful he is.
But he can use the mortal's sword.
That sword is powerful.
Let's do something to separate them.
My Lord,
can you kill that spirit
and give me his sword?
Get lost!
Who is the Lord, you or me?
How dare you order me around?
I'm sorry, My Lord.
I'll go figure out how to separate them.
No need.
I'll find a way to separate them.
By then,
you just hold that spirit off.
Yes.
If you manage to snatch the sword,
bring it back to me.
Yes.
This Gold-threaded Glove
can block the aura of magic tools.
Wear it to get the sword.
Yes.
My Lord,
can I have that tower?
Get out!
Yes.
- My ball.
- Young Master, don't go.
Don't go there. Come back.
Young Master.
Is he all right?
- Dangerous.
- Is he fine?
Be very careful.
My ball.
Let's go.
I was really freaked out.
Nothing must happen to Young Master.
You know what? After the fete was over,
Master had a stunning woman
stay here.
Maybe she'll be his new bride.
Four ladies can't help feeling restless.
Just now,
I saw them head aggressively
toward the woodshed
to give her a hard time.
Looks like Master
wants another child.
Because his children,
male or female,
always die young.
People are gossiping.
These years, Master has been wealthier.
But among his children,
only Young Master Luda
grew up to adulthood.
(Luda?)
Maybe it's a curse.
Young Master Luda
went to the capital at ten
and never returned.
Master
doesn't seem to want him back.
Simu.
Yili'er's son is Luda,
a senior official
in the Capital.
Then?
Another friend of yours?
I'm not worthy of a friend like that.
He's the High Priest's favorite pupil,
Young Priest Luda.
He's very likely to be High Priest.
In the Chong Court,
everybody knows him.
That explains
why Yili'er can have
so many treasures
from the royal court.
You think
he's also involved in this?
I don't think so.
He scorns such things.
Have mercy upon us.
There's confusion.
He looks very ethereal.
It's said to be
the most important gift
for becoming a priest.
What are you going to do
to Yili'er and Song Xingyu?
Now that I'm here,
I'll wait until they come to me.
How arrogant.
(Jiang Ai, Left Hand of the Void)
Thinking of sending Simu
another present?
If you keep waiting,
you'll be like a waiting husband.
Her Grace has been away for so long.
Without constraints,
you seem pretty carefree.
Simu has never constrained me.
But look at you.
When Her Grace is away,
you're in charge.
Shouldn't you feel happier?
Why are you acting like a resentful man?
Oh, I see.
Her Grace has been
in the Mortal World for so long.
Is she seeing another man?
Oh, you must be heartbroken.
Hitting a nerve?
You called me over for a discussion.
Since you have so much free time,
why don't you
authorize the fund request
for two billion spirit stones?
Her Grace approved it before she left.
When are you going to stop stalling?
I suddenly remembered
I had work to do.
I should go.
Go to the Mortal World.
If Her Grace has a problem,
inform me immediately.
- Yes.
Spring water ginseng.
Xiling mutton.
North Sea snow lotus.
That's so you.
After just a few days,
you can identify food with clarity.
So, you wrote a note
and asked me to have the servants
prepare this, right?
Exactly.
I'm just curious
about how well you're doing
with your sense of smell.
It's me, Miss.
May I come in and talk to you?
This is your house.
Don't be so formal.
Miss He,
I have a favor to ask of you.
What favor?
My son Luda
lived in the Capital.
Suddenly, he's coming back to see us.
I'm wondering
if you can have your spirit
stop my son from coming here
and get him back to the Capital.
I've heard Luda
went to the Capital at ten
and never came back.
Why?
Are you afraid
he'll know about your evil deal?
Or are you afraid
to lose this son?
Miss,
you must be joking.
We've been living here
for a couple of days.
So you go help him.
But you...
Don't worry about me.
Thank you, Miss.
I'd like to see
what you and Song Xingyu
are up to.
Young man,
fancy meeting you here.
You know what?
I got back from out of town
and found a way to make a fortune.
Tell me about it.
- You...
- Simu is right.
As long as we wait...
You'll come on your own.
I don't want this sword.
I have to go now.
Be careful with fire in dry weather.
(Young Priest Luda of the Chong court)
Seventeen?
It's you.
Why are you like this?
What a surprise.
You know me, Young Priest.
How come you suddenly showed up?
To be honest,
your father sent me
to make you return to the Capital.
You know my father?
This is
just his excuse
to lure me away.
He wants to kill
my friend and me.
Then let's hurry back.
You believe me already?
What if I lied?
There's no evil
in your eyes.
Will your friend
be all right?
Don't worry.
She's smart.
She won't be fooled
the same way again.
Father.
Mother.
Look.
Now I can
hold the two of you
with just one arm.
You always said you loved me,
but you both left me.
I'm left all alone.
Simu.
Simu,
I'm leaving.
A mortal doesn't live forever.
I can't stay any longer.
Simu,
I can't live
without your mother.
I must leave with her.
Didn't you promise
to live with me?
Why did you break your promise too?
Why did every one of you
have to abandon me?
I don't want to be alone.
I just don't want that.
Simu,
you can leave with us.
Death will end everything.
There will be no more pain.
When you're dead,
the three of us will reunite.
Stop acting.
My parents
only want me
to live a good life.
You failed to find my vital center,
so you tried to kill me in my dream.
Lord of Jiling Temple,
you tried really hard.
You're such a loyal servant.
I guess Song Xingyu
must have promised you
that after killing me,
he will become the Sovereign
and give you all the glory and wealth
in this world.
But have you ever thought
about what will happen
if he fails?
Song Xingyu,
it's really not easy for me
to get to see you.
He Simu,
you've fallen this far.
Why are you still talking tough?
You're greedy, short-sighted,
reckless, and foolish.
In the past 300 years,
you haven't grown at all.
You...
Give me the Spirits Lantern!
It's not with me.
Even if I die,
it won't take you as its master.
Then...
Go get the Lantern back.
Now you have no spirit power
and very little magic.
If you can't get it back,
I will...
I will throw you
into South Sea Ice Coffin
and lock you up forever.
I have a question.
If I'm satisfied with your answer,
I suppose I can give you
the Lantern.
Why do you want to be the Sovereign?
In this world,
every spirit wants that.
The Sovereign can do anything
and gets anything
he or she wants.
All the treasures in this world
will belong to me.
And then?
Spirits can't feel or enjoy
the sensual pleasures
or luxuries.
So what's the point
of having them?
If it's not a precious position,
why do you refuse to give it up?
I'm not satisfied with your answer.
I won't give this position
to someone I hate.
In that case,
I'll kill you and take it!
You're back sooner than expected.
I think I'm back at a perfect time.
Luda?
Father,
what are you doing?
He had a deal with a spirit
in exchange for your family fortune
and your rapid promotion.
These years, all your siblings
died at a young age
just because his misdeeds
backfired on him.
Father.
Is she
telling the truth?
Please spare me, sir.
Treasure Vault.
My... My treasures.
My collections of over ten years.
Father.
It's all over.
- Oh no.
- Father.
All is lost.
Father.
Sorry.
He slipped away.
It's all right.
Next time, he won't be
so fortunate.
Are you all right?
What could go wrong with me?
Why were you so obedient this time?
You did what I told you to.
I don't know your plan.
So I believe
I shouldn't cause you any trouble.
You smell so good.
In the dream
Song Xingyu fabricated,
I smelled the pleasant aroma
from your scented pouch.
♪Touched memories♪
In that case,
why not smell a little more?
♪Sink into my heart♪
And since that night,
you've kept a straight face.
I suspect
you'll settle the score with me
after your power's back.
So I might as well be bolder.
♪A lifetime is given
for a name to be remembered♪
♪There are passions and pains♪
♪Hope we'll experience them together♪
♪Before we forget or grow apart♪
Besides,
when I was away from you...
♪Grows dim and fades away♪
I flattered myself
and worried about you.
♪I care for no one but you♪
♪I'll come near and run to you♪
So you know
you always flatter yourself.
♪Eternity and radiance♪
♪Worth more than any barren land♪
♪I might as well
spend the rest of my life♪
♪Walking with you through eternity♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪