Your dad gave you this?
[Episode 2: Our Beginning]
How nice.
I only get to eat McDonald's
when I get a perfect score.
You can play with it later.
Great.
Tuo!
Tuo.
Where are you going?
I want to go to the beach to find my mom.
My dad said she moved to this address,
[No.165, Futian Road, Wanli District]
but I don't know how to get there.
I haven't seen my mom for a long time.
I miss her so much.
I'll take you to find her.
You know how to get there?
Don't be silly.
We can look it up online with my phone.
Don't cry.
I'll take you to find your mom.
[Yixin Kindergarten]
Are we there yet?
Almost there.
Stop asking.
Do you really know the way?
Tuo said his mom lives by the sea,
but we've been walking forever
and haven't seen any water.
We're almost there.
Don't worry.
The sea!
Lu Junxi,
you really found it!
I told you I knew the way,
but you didn't believe me.
We'll find your mom soon.
Let's take a photo.
Let's take a photo with this first,
and then we'll go find Tuo's mom.
Look here.
That day,
we didn't find Tuo's mom.
Instead, we ended up at the police station
for getting lost
and got chewed out badly by the adults.
But because of this adventure,
our trio was officially formed.
[Secret Lover]
Keep sleeping.
Why don't you just sleep on the floor?
Stop it,
Tuo.
Stop it.
I told you to put on sunscreen
before playing basketball,
but you wouldn't listen.
Now you're all sunburned.
So you were just applying ointment for me?
What else would I be doing?
Your whole neck is red.
Just bear with the pain for a bit.
That day, I saw you struggling
to hold it in,
so I thought I'd help you out.
I've heard close friends
often play around like that.
Really?
Why would I lie?
So that's how it is.
You should have told me earlier.
I thought...
Thought what?
Never mind.
Apply it thicker.
Maybe it'll help me heal faster.
Do you want to play later?
Play what?
Takara.
I bought some new equipment.
Wanna log in?
Be careful.
Sure.
But I've used up all the money
I topped up last month.
I'll transfer you some.
Really?
Thanks.
I'll pay you back as soon as I can.
It's fine.
Just pay me back when you have money.
That won't do.
The allowance your dad gives you
each month is limited too.
What will you do
if you don't have enough for yourself?
It's alright.
Don't you want anything for yourself?
I do.
But...
It's a secret.
Yeah, right.
Alright, I've topped up my account.
Let's battle.
Bring it on.
Let's see who'll take down
the Dark Lord of Phoenix City first.
Get out of my way!
Keep up!
Which idiot
is healing the Dark Lord?
Hurry up!
Yes!
I won again!
You won again.
I told you,
I'm the king of the game.
You said you wanted to go to a beach
with hot guys,
but here we are again.
We come every year,
yet she's still so excited about it.
Xiaoyang is just complaining for show.
This is where our trio began.
We'll never get tired of coming here.
If you hadn't said that to me that day,
this place would have been
where I realized
my mom had decided to abandon me.
Don't cry.
It's okay not to have a mom.
I'll share my mom with you.
My dad and
my elder brother,
I'll share them with you too.
Me too.
I'll share everything with you.
From now on, we're a trio,
the very best of friends.
Let's bump heads.
Come on, let's take a photo!
Let's go.
We'll be busy with club recruitment
starting tomorrow.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Over here.
Three,
two,
one,
smile!
Hey, junior!
Over here!
Welcome to join the Magic Club!
Hello. Hello.
Welcome to join the Taekwondo Club!
[October 11, 2023, 5th Floor Theater]
Hurry up!
[Xingwu Dance Club]
[Romeo and Juliet:
Next Generation Edition]
[Xingwu Drama Club — We Welcome You!]
[Performance Venue: 5th Floor Theater,
Xingwu University of Science and Technology]
[Romeo and Juliet:
Next Generation Edition]
Where are Junxi and Tuo?
Hello, has anyone seen Junxi and Tuo?
Over here, Senior!
Can you two do me a favor?
Please, do me this favor.
You know what?
The ones who were supposed
to play Romeo and Juliet,
what were their names again?
Xiaoyi and Junwei.
They went out for barbecue last night
and got food poisoning,
and now they're in the hospital
on IV drips!
I don't understand
what those two were thinking.
Both lead actors are out of commission?
Yes.
We only have 20 minutes left.
I know.
But wait,
how are we supposed to perform now?
You two have been helping
Romeo and Juliet
rehearse their lines, right?
You should know all the lines
by now, right?
I...
Okay. All right.
Come on, makeup and costume team,
over here.
Take these two to get changed now.
Get in position in 10 minutes,
alright?
I want to see you both ready
in 10 minutes.
Hurry up. Chop chop.
Let's go!
Come on!
Junxi!
Tuo!
Let's go.
Come on.
Tuo!
Let's go.
Junxi!
Why do you have to be Romeo?
What's so important about a surname?
It's neither a part of your body,
nor does it have anything
to do with your soul.
Alright.
As long as you say you love me,
I can give up my name.
Tuo.
Why are you so good?
Tuo is such an amazing actor.
No matter what your name is,
you're perfect all the same.
Romeo.
Change your name,
and you'll have me entirely.
Alright,
as you wish.
My love.
Death has taken your breath,
but not your beauty.
You are not conquered.
Your lips
and your cheeks
are still just as rosy.
The ghastly pale of death
has yet to touch you.
Don't be nervous.
It's just a fake kiss through
stage positioning.
I was right to choose these two.
You guys!
You two were absolutely amazing!
You two
were incredible!
Did you see the audience's reaction?
They loved you!
That kiss you did
was a stroke of genius!
Tuo!
Great!
Let me tell you,
there's no need to worry about...
Tuo!
The recruitment of our juniors anymore!
Hey, love you guys!
We agreed on fake kissing.
Why did you actually kiss me?
Don't you want more juniors
to join our drama club?
Of course I do.
Then what's the problem?
Good audience reaction means
more potential members.
Besides, it's not like
we never kissed before.
Even so,
you should have asked me first, okay?
This time it was you who kissed me,
not the other way around.
You pulled me in to kiss you.
I didn't choose to kiss you myself.
Besides, you knew that
I was going to confess my love to Xiaoyang
after the welcome party.
I don't want you to confess to her.
What do you mean?
You don't want me to?
Then why did you agree
to be my dating coach?
I didn't want to coach you either.
I only coached you because
I wanted an excuse to get close to you,
to make you get used to me, accept me,
give up on Xiaoyang, and like me instead.
What are you talking about?
I do like you.
We've always been friends.
We've...
Always been...
I don't want to just be your friend.
I want to be with you,
as your boyfriend.
You're joking, right?
Hurry up. Chop chop.
There's not much time left.
Change your costumes
and pack up the props quickly.
The next club will be here soon.
Hurry up. Chop chop.
You're kidding, right?
Tuo!
The 12 basic principles of animation
are the fundamental techniques
in animation production,
originated from
Disney animators Ollie Johnston
and Frank Thomas's
1981 book,
"The Illusion of Life: Disney Animation."
These principles are widely used
in animation production,
and have influenced the production of
various types of animation.
I didn't want to coach you either.
I only coached you because
I wanted an excuse to get close to you,
to make you get used to me, accept me,
give up on Xiaoyang, and like me instead.
Tuo.
I'm so hungry.
So, so hungry.
Let's eat.
Tuo.
What's going on with you lately?
You've been down since the welcome party.
Got dumped?
Who got dumped?
Me?
Of course not.
I haven't even confessed yet.
How could I be dumped?
Tuo's been acting strange too.
He hasn't been walking to school with us
since the welcome party.
Could it be
he's found someone new
and forgotten the old?
Tuo has a new crush?
Since when?
Who is it?
From which department? Which class?
You're crazy.
I was just kidding.
Why are you so nervous?
Kidding?
Don't joke about that, okay?
He's already popular enough with girls.
Do you mind?
I...
I don't have class this afternoon.
I'll head home first.
[You haven't been to school for days.]
[Reply when you see this message.]
[It's rude to read and not reply.]
[Tuo, I even went to your place
but couldn't find you. Where are you?]
[If you don't reply soon,
I'll tell my mom.]
[Are you still mad?]
Tuo.
Where have you been lately?
I couldn't find you at your place,
and you haven't replied
to any of my messages.
Junxi!
Great, you have an umbrella.
Let's go home together.
Take the umbrella.
I have to go catch up with Tuo.
What the hell?
Wait for me!
Han Tuo!
If you keep running,
I'll never speak to you again!
You jerk.
Think you're so great
with those long legs?
You're burning up.
Are you having a fever?
If it's just out of pity,
I don't need it.
Tuo!
If you keep walking,
our friendship is over!
Tuo!
I really won't talk to you anymore.
I'm done with you.
Yet here I am anyway.
I must be an idiot.
Tuo.
Let me in.
Go away.
You're sick. Stop acting tough.
Let go.
It's none of your business
even if I die from this illness.
Go away.
You've got me all confused,
and now you're ignoring me?
Open the door.
Weren't you going to confess
to Lin Xiaoyang?
Go ahead.
I won't stop you anymore.
Right!
I was going to confess to Xiaoyang
and be with her,
but because of you,
everything has become a mess.
All I could think about is you,
so I forgot to confess to Xiaoyang
and forgot to log in the game
for team battles.
Are you saying
you've been thinking about me
all the time?
You've been thinking about me,
and only me?
Who would think about you?
Always causing trouble
and making me worry.
You might as well die from your illness!
You like me.
You like me the same way I like you.
[In the Next Episode]
So you two have made up...
No, you two are even closer now, right?
Lu Junxi!
I'm coming!
Here's my application form.
I'm not a junior. Can I still apply?
Go ahead and
keep taking care of your juniors.
They're always chatting around you anyway.
Why is it that
I suddenly feel suffocated?