[PA chiming]
[woman on PA] May I have your attention,
please.
Baggage from flight TX-551 is now arriving
from Fort-de-France at carousel four.
Again, baggage from flight TX-551
is arriving at carousel four.
For security reasons, please keep
your belongings within sight at all times.
CUSTOMS & INDIRECT TAXES
Any unclaimed baggage
will be confiscated and destroyed.
Thank you for your compliance.
Ma'am, bag inspection.
Place your suitcases
on the belt here, please.
- You coming in from…
- Martinique.
Anything to declare?
- Huh?
- Any plants or computer equipment
exceeding the authorized quantity?
- Everything in order?
- No. Yes.
Yes? No?
Nothing to declare.
[tense music playing]
Over here, ma'am.
Open your suitcase, please.
[tense music continues]
[suitcase unzipping]
[dog barking]
[tense music building]
- [man] Go on.
- [woman] Find. Find.
[man] Find.
[woman] Go on. Search.
Look. Good boy. Here, too.
Find. That's it. Find.
Stop. Stop. Not that.
Stop. Stop. Give it here.
Drop it. Drop it. Stop.
- [man] Hey, Rafale. Let's go.
- [dog whines and yips]
Sorry for the inconvenience, ma'am.
[tense music fading]
[indistinct chatter]
- [recording chimes]
- Made it through.
Annabelle?
Whatever goes down, I've got you.
Through blood, life is never happenstance.
- Xhésus.
- I'm sorry?
Xhésus. Think "Jesus," but with a "xh."
Forget it.
No, no, I'm fine. I've got it.
This way.
Let me. I've got it.
[door closes]
Hungry?
WE'RE AT THE HOTEL,
IS THAT NORMAL?
[clicks tongue]
[Xhésus] I left, I'm sorry.
Didn't want to wake you.
I had a last-minute errand to run.
Yeah, of course.
Want me to bring you some?
No worries. I'll let you go, I'm at work.
Me too, Mom.
- [laughs softly] Sorry.
- No worries.
Gotta stop by the pharmacy
or I'll just forget again.
So, how does this thing work?
We can take care of business now,
or if you want, we can grab a bite first.
Your pick.
My treat.
[indistinct hushed chatter]
[Xhésus] To be honest, I'm impressed.
Hiding the stash.
I didn't believe you'd pull it off,
but not bad.
How'd you manage?
Got someone on the inside?
Inside what?
[laughs softly]
Gimme a sec.
Gotta call my mother
and tell her I picked up her medicine.
Okay, no worries.
- Is she sick?
- No.
[chuckles] Hypochondriac.
[laughs softly]
[phone vibrating]
KING
If you're with Jesus it's all good.
Résus. Yes I'm with him.
["Destinée" by Yaniss Odua playing]
[bell dings]
- Ah, Kingsley.
- How are you, Auntie?
Fine, and you?
The monsters here?
- Well, yes, but they're about to--
- Just popping in.
Kingsley!
What up, champ? Mmm! Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[chuckles] You've put on muscle!
I won't be able to pick you up soon.
- [laughs]
- [Nolan] King!
[Kingsley] Hey, little buddy!
- [Thaïs] King!
- [Kingsley chuckling]
Come on. I've got a surprise.
Hmm, hmm.
It's a'ight.
Hmm. Not very soft.
Hmm.
Check this out.
- Cool or what?
- [Nolan] Mmm.
That's so cool.
Pick one, and when you're home,
that's what will be waiting for you.
And when is that?
- Soon.
- But how soon?
When you count to 878,456.
- That's not fair!
- [laughs]
Wow.
- [Mathis] Hey, King.
- Hmm?
Have you seen Léo?
- What?
- Have you seen his video?
What video?
Wait, when did you guys get phones?
No, Auntie Régine showed us the video.
She yelled at us,
said we were all just a bunch of punks.
Whoa.
Check it out, that desk is so pretty.
Look at that bed there.
[Léo on video] I shot that asshole
in his face! Boom!
- In his mouth! For real!
- Damn, what a dumbass!
I ride for my fam, understood?
- I'm armed, so don't fuck around, fuckers.
- [clicks tongue]
- [woman] Jérôme? Come look at this.
- No, Mama, I don't have time.
Oh no?
What do you mean, you don't have time?
Come look at this now.
What is it?
I told you before not to bring any kids
into your damn affairs.
Come on, Mama. You know I'm better
than to do something like that.
Yeah? Then explain this.
[Léo on video] I shot that asshole
in his face!
Boom!
In his mouth! For real!
I ride for my fam, understood?
I'm armed, so don't fuck around, fuckers.
We're inadmissible.
[imitates gun firing]
What is this supposed to be, Mama?
- It's what you do!
- [SherKhan clicks tongue]
This money's what we do.
I don't interfere in your business, son.
But you better
leave the kids out of it, Jérôme.
And especially if guns are involved.
When it comes to the kids,
you're forbidden.
Mama, I don't have guns.
I have no idea what that is.
Yes, you do.
He's a Lafleur, one of Marilyn's.
She sold plants at the local market.
We went to her funeral, me and your Mama.
[dark music playing]
NEW MESSAGE
- Where they from?
- Saint-Joseph.
[woman] Jérôme! Have you eaten?
Jérôme!
[darkly intriguing music playing]
[Léo on video] Boom! In his mouth!
For real!
I ride for my fam, understood?
I'm armed, so don't fuck around, fuckers.
We're inadmissible.
[darkly intriguing music continues]
[music fades]
The smell bother you?
It's fine.
We need a deposit first, 10%.
Sixty grand?
Sixty-four. Don't cheap out.
When?
Tomorrow.
Got a problem?
No.
Better not.
The Señora doesn't take bad news well,
if you know what I'm saying.
So don't mess this up.
Be on time, be reliable, never default.
The more she loves,
the more she chastises.
You have no idea
the number of friends she's cut down
just for standing up to her.
I mixed up my left and my right
when giving her directions once.
[sighs] I got it.
[clears throat]
- [sizzling]
- [Kylian groaning]
What the fuck?
I like marking my territory.
All right, get out.
I'll send you
the coordinates for next time.
[indistinct chatter]
[scooter rides off]
[chatter continues]
Kiki? What you doing here?
What about you?
You see that little idiot's video?
I'm gonna break his teeth.
SherKhan will figure it out.
He's gonna be like a bloodhound on you.
It's just a dumb video on TikTok.
Let's not go nuts.
What you up to here?
What, you get burned?
It's nothing, don't worry.
How's it going, dude?
- Hey, gimme your phone.
- Hey!
- Now.
- I don't have it. I don't have it.
Hey, gimme that!
Log in now and wipe your account.
What? Hell no, you crazy!
Hey! Do it now or I'm sending you
to live with Auntie Régine.
I'll talk to the judge.
[Léo scoffs]
[Kylian] You understand
the problem this caused?
King brought you on to the team,
he trusted you,
and you're blasting your face
all over the internet.
- Because of you, King here is a dead man.
- No, please don't say that!
He is. He'll be killed and so will you.
No.
Yes.
It's too late for King.
He'll be killed cause of you.
Thaïs, Nolan, Mathis,
they'll never come home again.
Because we'll be a family of bandits.
You hear me?
You're gonna have
to watch your back from now on.
- All right.
- No way, man. It's better he know.
You're going overboard now. It's good.
- [bell ringing]
- Go on, get. We'll talk later.
Well, have fun?
[poignant music playing]
And Annabelle?
It's going. We're almost there.
Okay.
Thank you, bro.
I feel less alone. Appreciate it.
[poignant music continues]
- [both laughing]
- [Xhésus] Complete nightmare.
Yeah, that's not cool.
Time to get to work.
[Annabelle] There.
Very clever.
Where's the cash?
Don't have it on me.
First, I take these to my guys.
We test each bag, and if it's all good,
I come back with the money.
Mmm-mmm. I'm sorry, but no.
- What do you think this was?
- I don't know.
Can you test them here?
Need machines for that.
You know, equipment and shit.
I never touch cocaine.
I'm in the dark. I just smoke.
And you?
Same.
- Thanks.
- I'll be back in a few hours.
Have some fun.
There's a pool, a spa.
You can book a massage if you want.
Can I have your number?
Of course.
06-39-98-23-54.
- [phone ringing]
- [laughs softly]
- Hello?
- [voice echoes]
Don't worry about it. I get it.
Later.
[door opens]
[door closes]
DUCOS PENITENTIARY
You want half of what I earn
when we can barely afford food?
You think I'm the dumb one?
That I'm not up to speed?
Those little idiots might think
you're a saint with your lotus ring,
but that don't work on me, okay?
Your dumb ass is out there
bragging about getting all that dough.
I haven't done shit.
You will, though, son. I know you.
But it makes me happy
that you would still tell me the truth.
It means that you and I
are still connected.
You know I came for help.
This is how you respond?
By threatening my family?
Your family?
And me, I'm not your family?
Ah, your real family.
But if I'm not your family,
get out of here!
Get the fuck out, boy.
You better not come back, I'm serious.
Beat it!
[chair scrapes]
Wait.
Sit down, son. Come on.
Sit down. Sit down.
Don't push me away.
I wasn't there for you, but I'm sure
I'm not the first dad to do wrong.
Give me a chance. I'm begging you, son.
Don't ever send Jocelyn.
Just cut me into the business.
50%? Are you mad?
Okay, 40%.
Why? You don't deserve to get anything!
Because you're my son.
You know…
I've only got one photo…
in my cell.
It's of you.
Here, look.
[pensive music playing]
With Dylan.
It's the only one I have.
Don't let me go, son.
Let me think it over.
Okay, think on it.
Hold on to the photo.
[pensive music continues]
- [pensive music building]
- [cell door buzzes]
[pensive music continues]
["Fix Dem" by Niko & DJ Digital playing]
SIX YEARS EARLIER
Matthew!
Was this you?
- Matthew!
- Kylian, they did this on you?
Yes.
Hey, my brother didn't do this.
Get lost.
[grunts]
[groaning]
Ahh!
[panting] Now you better
go tell your mother who beat you!
["Fix Dem" continues playing]
You let it slide, game over.
Teach them a lesson for what they did,
what they're doing, and what they will do.
[Kylian] Yeah.
Never let anybody think they're above you.
Never.
If they do, they gotta pay.
[Marilyn] Dinner time!
No, guys. We can't move this way.
They're waiting.
Gotta trap them from behind.
Ambre?
- What?
- He can't get out.
- [Marilyn] Dinner!
- Shh. You're distracting him.
Gotta make them think
we're coming from the opposite side!
How come?
You dumb? He's not talking to us.
How come you're all still in here?
Dylan, you spend way too much time
on that computer.
[Dylan] No, Mama! No!
Come eat!
Who's Milord?
It's Dylan, idiot.
But why are you called "Milord"?
Milord means you come from a high place.
High what?
High society.
You're at the very top.
There's no one else above you.
[determined music playing]
Hey, Kylian Lafleur.
Who's gonna protect you now, huh?
Stop!
Let me go! Let me go!
- [kid laughing]
- [slaps]
The wild pigs are gonna eat you up
till there's nothing left.
Anyone!
Over here!
Someone help!
Help me!
[determined music continues]
[bird screeching]
Mama?
[bird screeches]
- [pig squeals]
- [gasps]
[squealing continues]
[tapping] Hey, little man.
You okay?
Buddy?
[music fades]
[man 1 on TV] Good things
get out of control.
We've created a monster
that's putting us all out of jobs,
and I'll tell you…
[man 2] All right, Ed, I'll be serious.
As old Abe Martin used to say,
it's amazing how a few facts
will break up an argument.
[man 1] The trouble is
a lot of us don't get the whole picture.
[man 2] You know,
I wish you had been with me
at the workshop of an old friend
the other afternoon.
[automated voice] The number
you have dialed is not in service.
Please check the number and try again.
[phone beeps]
- The number you have dialed--
- That asshole!
[suspenseful music playing]
You're all set, sir. Room 430.
Your luggage
has already been moved to your room.
Elevators are on the right.
- Fourth floor.
- Thank you.
Excuse me, do you have the number
of the man who reserved my room, please?
Uh, which room would that be, ma'am?
It's on the fifth floor.
Way back, at the end of the hall.
On the right, next to the elevator.
502?
- Yes.
- Do you have your key card?
Key card?
- Uh, are you sure that--
- Yes, I'm sure! God damn it!
[Annabelle huffs]
I have it! Here! Here!
Here, here!
[typing]
Yes, room 502.
I see you're staying for one night?
And it's booked under the name…
"Xhésus Andrei."
Yes, that's him. You have his number?
Yes, he did leave his number,
but I can't give it out.
- It's an emergency.
- I'm sorry, if he didn't give it to you--
He did, but I must have saved it wrong.
It won't go through.
[sighs] Could you check if it's the same?
That's the number I have.
It's not in service.
I can't help you, I'm afraid.
Listen, it's all paid for, everything.
Even the mini-bar and the spa.
- [somber music playing]
- [crying]
[sobbing]
- [stifling tears]
- [phone ringing]
Hello?
[Kingsley] Hello?
- What?
- Well, do you have the cakes?
I will soon.
- He's happy with the sugar?
- Yeah.
- When's he bringing them?
- Real soon.
- Everything good?
- Yes.
Great. Call me when you have the cakes.
[line disconnects]
[cries softly]
All right, you remember?
Once it's sold,
log it in the ledger like Mama showed you.
- And then?
- I write in more.
Exactly. So someone gives you five euros…
I put ten in the ledger.
Don't listen to any of that, Cass.
He's feeding you bullshit.
You could even put in 20.
- Isn't it here?
- Oh!
Who's this?
[Kingsley] What the…
These tomatoes…
Can I help you, sweetheart?
What are you looking for?
- I've got onions, tomatoes--
- Excuse me, ma'am.
- You've got the wrong stand.
- The wrong stand?
Our mother worked this spot
for over 20 years.
Listen to me, honey,
I paid for my stand like everybody else.
- Where even is your Mama?
- Dead and buried.
Okay.
And we are taking over her business.
Well, you need to find another spot.
This one is ours now.
THEY TOOK MAMA'S STAND
COME QUICK
Okay, ma'am. You tried,
but we're not moving. Now get lost.
- This is the Lafleur spot, got it?
- Wait a minute, man.
- You best watch your mouth!
- All right, buddy. Chill.
It's for your own good.
Move your stuff
and pack up the shit, okay?
- Get out of here, dumbass.
- Don't touch me, punk!
- I said don't touch me!
- [woman] Get off him!
Someone do something!
- You little brat!
- [crates clatter]
- [woman 1] Stop it! Someone grab her!
- [woman 2] What are you doing?
- [man] Come at me!
- [blows landing]
- [man] Yo! Knock it off! Stop!
- [woman] You're gonna pay for that!
- [man] Come on! You want some of this?
- [Marvin] Stop!
- [woman] Stop!
- [man] I'll kill you! You hear me?
- [all clamoring loudly]
- Police! Police!
Police! That's enough!
What's going on here?
These kids here are messed up!
They attacked us!
- [Ambre] They're squatting in our spot.
- For real.
- [woman] We're not squatting.
- Take a breath.
Do you have your permit on you?
Don't have a permit,
but our mother sold
her plants and herbs here since forever.
Your mother was Marilyn Lafleur?
[all] Yes.
I remember. She was right there.
I'd come see her a lot.
I'm very sorry for your loss.
It's our stand.
[crowd murmuring]
What are you doing here?
Who said you could be here?
Hey, may I?
["On s'était dit" by Amah Fofana playing]
Three days after her death.
Nice.
"Automatically renewable…
for three years"?
It looks like my hands are tied.
I'm sorry.
[somber rap song continues]
[camera clicks]
[motorcycle approaching]
[man 1] Yo, son.
Damn, you gain weight again?
[man 2] Why you gotta be so cruel?
You think I want to be
a skinny bitch like you?
The wind picks up, you'll blow away.
- Yo, Fatso, what's up?
- Ain't got much time.
Really?
Milord's cashing in.
- For real?
- Right now.
Four o'clock, bring it here.
And better not tell me anything's missing.
No sweat, I'm on it.
All right, guys. [whistles]
["Belle Époque"
by X-Man & Jkevlar playing]
[dramatic rap song playing]
[dramatic rap song continues]
- [dramatic rap song continues]
- [inaudible]
[dramatic rap song continues]
[rap song fading]
[bag unzipping]
[indistinct chatter]
- [car starting]
- It's like being on a vacation kinda, but…
- Shorter.
- Smaller, yeah.
Shorter.
Got a girlfriend?
Mmm, nah, don't have time for that.
Why, want to be my girl?
Pfft, don't be silly.
[woman] Maeva?
Okay. See ya, man.
[Léo] See ya tomorrow.
[SherKhan] Casanova.
Who's that, your chick?
You an actor? Saw your little movie.
"We're inadmissible."
[imitates gun firing and chuckles]
All right, let's do this.
Get in.
Hurry up. Get in, now.
You know who I am?
SherKhan. You're the boss in Trénelle.
I'm the boss everywhere.
Where you from?
What the fuck do you care?
[laughs softly]
We got a badass.
Want to be a badass?
Want to be a badass, kid?
So why'd you say "in the mouth"
in your videos, punk?
Answer me, bitch.
You're not gonna kill me, man.
It's disproportionate.
[laughing]
How 'bout I just shoot you
in your knee, then? Is that proportionate?
Answer me or I'll blow your leg off!
I… tried to impress my friends.
Your friends?
Are you fucking with me, kid?
No, I swear, I was making it all up.
Look at this gun.
It's gonna be so damn loud!
You have no idea how much it'll bleed.
You'll have a giant hole.
Is that what you want?
I promise it's the truth. I want my mama.
You're one of them Lafleurs, huh?
All right, get out, punk.
Move.
[softly] Go fuck yourself, SherKhan.
You and your stupid Glock.
[Kylian sighs]
What's going on?
That punk-ass bitch.
That's the harvest?
No. It's our reserves.
Sentinel's disappeared.
With the harvest?
[Fatso] Seems so.
[exhales deeply]
You called him, right?
Only ten million times.
Fuck.
[sighs]
We will find him.
Before tomorrow? Where's he live?
[sighs]
I think he stays with his mother
when she's on vacation.
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues]
[suspenseful music building]
[Fatso] Yo, what up, boss?
You fucked up, son.
Sick of your shit!
I'll fucking take it all!
Sébastien!
Told you, stay in your room, God damn!
Drop it!
[pleading] We tried.
It… It didn't work.
Please, drop it.
[suspenseful music continues]
Okay, guys. I'm sorry.
Shit. God damn it.
I'm sorry, guys. I fucked up.
I needed money for my baby. I panicked.
I'll pay it all back with interest.
You're sorry?
Sorry, Milord.
He's sorry, guys.
You don't have to kill him.
[sighs]
- [door closing in background]
- [Sentinel groaning]
[woman] Stop it, please!
- [groaning continues]
- ["Mozart" by Mercenaire playing]
["Mozart" continues playing]
["Saydia" by Marginal playing]
- Whoa!
- [cars honking]
["Saydia" continues playing]
- [shower running]
- ["Saydia" continues playing]
[song fading into background]
[line ringing]
[Kingsley] Hey, Belle.
- Hello? You good?
- No, King, I'm real bad.
What's going on?
Tell me.
He screwed me. He left me.
He told me he'd come back.
- What?
- And I listened.
He gave me a fake number.
I'm in deep shit.
- [exhales]
- Tell me everything.
What the fuck are you talking about?
[voice breaking] Xhésus.
He disappeared.
What the fuck are you saying?
I'm fucked.
Wait, wait, wait.
But where are the cakes?
Annabelle, answer me.
They're with him.
What? You let him take the cakes?
What is wrong with you? Are you nuts?
- [knock on door]
- Why didn't you tell me earlier?
- Now it's too late. You fucked up.
- King, hold on a second.
[faintly] Hold on?
What do you mean, hold on?
Yo, what's going on? Hello?
Hello? Hello, Belle?
Hello? Come on, answer me!
King, it's him. Call you back.
What's happening? I--
[breathes deeply]
You got it?
[door closes]
You okay?
You gave me a fake number!
I shut my phone off. I always do that.
It makes it harder to be traced.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm sorry. Really.
It took longer than I expected.
I thought you were enjoying the pool.
Didn't you check it out?
What about the spa?
Shit.
This sucks.
Come here.
[Annabelle crying softly]
I'm so sorry.
I thought you trusted me.
[Annabelle sobs] Yeah, you wish.
- [motorcycle revving]
- Whoo!
Yes!
- [exhales]
- ["Si Balan" by Shannon playing]
["Si Balan" continues playing]
Yo, dude.
[Kingsley] Yo, what up?
- What's good? How you doing?
- Oh, you know.
Hey.
Nice ride.
- Here.
- Thanks, bro.
- [Kingsley] Yeah.
- That Margot from Instagram?
Come on, you know.
["Si Balan" continues playing]
[bikes revving]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [rap song continues]
[indistinct hushed chatter]
[hushed chatter continues]
Give us a sec.
- Khan.
- Hmm?
You mentioned some guys from Saint-Joseph.
You see him there?
He's from Saint-Joseph.
Name's Kingsley Lafleur.
How'd you find that out?
The Snoop. He told me.
Go bring him here.
[engines revving loudly]
[indistinct chatter]
SherKhan wants to see you.
SherKhan? Who's that?
- You're blocking the view.
- [laughs]
Got a perfect eyeline.
He can see me from there.
If he's got something to say,
he can come here.
[blows kiss]
[rap song continues]
[Kingsley] Anyway.
He's being disrespectful.
For real.
Needs to be taken down a peg.
[menacing music playing]
[tires screeching]
- Hold on tight!
- [menacing music continues]
[SherKhan] Hey, Lafleur!
Let me get off, King!
- [car horn blaring]
- [tires squealing]
Yo, move! Fuck!
[SherKhan] I'm gonna rip your head off!
Lafleur! You're fucking dead!
[menacing music continues]
- [bike driving off]
- [music fading]
If I tell you I want to get off,
you let me off, asshole.
You see that guy?
If I let you off, you'd be dead.
He'd have killed you.
I saved your life, you know.
SherKhan? Ha! I would eat him alive.
Mmm-mmm.
You want another?
[dark music playing]
He's called Kingsley Lafleur.
A little bitch from Saint-Joseph.
This bro's got it fucking coming!
I'm not playing.
Whoever gets him, ten grand.
I want this bitch found.
Y'all find him right now.
[darkly intriguing music playing]
[Kylian] SherKhan.
Yo, prove that it's you.
[Kylian] Doesn't matter.
Listen carefully.
- You're messing up our business.
- Hmm?
You heard me.
That video's gone viral.
It's already in the prefect's office.
So listen good.
I have your dope.
Hold on.
- You stole from me, Milord?
- Calm down, SherKhan.
- That's not my style.
- Oh, I'mma calm down.
I'm gonna butcher you.
That'll calm me down and then some.
[Kylian] You're not crazy.
Your dope's being sold in Paris.
It'll bring in 400,000 euros, I guarantee.
One week, and it's yours.
On one condition.
Oh, you fucking nuts!
You negotiating with my own merchandise?
You smoking crack?
Your dumb little video
got the attention of the authorities.
All cause you had to be a child.
Oh, come on.
Say this to my face, Milord, I dare you.
[Kylian] So here's our new deal.
You take what we offer you
and leave the Lafleur kid alone.
- And as a deposit…
- Yo.
[rooster crowing]
[car alarm chirps]
- Why are you protecting him?
- I'm protecting my business.
Yours as well.
Keep your phone on. I'll be in touch.
- And call off the hit on the Lafleur kid.
- And if I refuse?
[call disconnects]
[bikes revving]
[bikes riding off]
[sighs]
I've collected it all.
Deposit of 64,000.
Like you asked.
I'll send you the time, the date,
and the location of the delivery.
Keep yourself alive till then.
[engine revving]
["PLP VME" by Lé Will & Deuspi playing]
[phone buzzing]
We in business.
[man laughing]
JC - I warned you.
It's over. Forget about me.
["PLP VME" continues playing]
[dramatic rap song continues playing]