This is Samantha Vera,
the model.
We know each other already, Doc.
She was my fiancée.
There’s really no one
like The Samantha Vera.
The school year just started and
she plans the best parties.
Do you remember when I told you
that you’ll be marrying
the son of my best friend?
His name is Clyden.
BS Biology. Cum Laude.
Don’t get all giddy.
We can’t marry each other.
I agree.
Come on, get dressed.
We're going to a party.
She's not coming.
It’s just us.
What?
You want to show off your
dad’s bastard child to everyone?
- Mom!
- Let’s go!
We bought you a house.
Yes!
No fucking way.
What the hell?
Why? Is there a problem?
I don’t think there’s a problem.
Is there, sweetheart?
Right! No problem.
We’re just shocked
with the big news.
But we’re both happy and
excited at the same time.
We’ll be together every day.
But, hon… Don’t you
think it’s going too fast?
I mean, they’re still students.
Maybe they can just live
together after the wedding?
Well, I get your point,
but that’s where it’s
all headed anyway, right?
That will be good for them to
get to know each other better.
Yes.
So you guys can practice
being a husband and a wife.
Well, that's right.
So, when are they moving in?
In about a month's time.
I can’t wait
for you to graduate
so that we can finally
get our first grandson!
- Really?
- That’s true!
A grandchild?
What the fuck is happening?
- This can’t be my life now.
- Probably our grandson
will look so handsome, and
I hope he gets your nose.
I hope he gets your eyes!
Don’t worry, I’ll make sure
that won’t happen.
That’s never gonna happen,
not even in your dreams.
Just thinking about it
makes me want to puke.
If you're disgusted, trust me,
I’m even more disgusted.
You two better get ready.
I’ll handle everything from here.
Yes, Dad.
Excuse us, we’ll just talk.
A talk between fiancés.
- Okay.
- Okay. Go ahead.
Live together?
Fuck this.
You think I want to live with you?
I don’t need your presence
while I'm studying.
Then say no.
We can still be engaged
without living together.
Why me?
Why not you?
Just tell your dad you don’t want to.
I can’t say no to my dad.
No one can.
See?
You can’t.
My dad isn’t any regular dad.
What he wants, he gets.
And you?
Why can't you just tell
your dad you don’t want it?
I just can’t.
Jeez.
So you’re not any different then.
If you can’t say no,
then we have to deal with this.
You’ll have to adjust to me.
Me? Adjust to you?
- Why not?
- Why, yes?
Are you out of your mind?
I need more time to study.
Wow!
You think you're high and mighty
just because you're
studying med, huh?
And you think your time
is more important than mine?
And you think
you’re such a princess, huh?
You will adjust to me.
If they spoil you at home,
well guess what, I'm not them.
That won’t work on me.
What the fuck are you doing?
They’re looking at us.
Just play along.
Fuck you.
Did she just say, “I love you”?
I think so.
- They’re really meant for each other.
- Yes.
What did you say earlier?
That I’m spoiled?
Can you even hear yourself?
Do you know how rude you are?
Rude?
Yes, I know.
Why?
Why can’t you just be kind?
You know, try it. It’s not that hard.
I am kind…
to kind people.
So you’re saying that I’m not kind?
Are you?
I don’t know what
to do with you anymore.
It’s not like we can do
anything about it,
so let’s just plan.
Shit.
It’s my last year
in college this August,
and you’re ruining it.
Why are you mad at me?
Am I the one buying the house?
You think I want to live with you?
Not at all.
So maybe try being
mad at someone else.
I suggest your dad.
Can you be serious for a second?
I am serious.
Do you think I’m joking?
Okay.
Here's the plan—
No helpers, no drivers, nothing.
To avoid gossip.
So, if you don't have
any better suggestions,
let's just stick to the plan.
And I’m staying in that house
for one month only,
just to please my parents.
I’m going back
to my condo eventually.
Do whatever you want.
For now, we have
to follow what they say.
This whole pretending thing
will be over soon anyway.
I agree.
I really hope this ends soon!
I can’t wait for
that time to happen!
Deal?
Deal.
One month, Sam!
It’s just one month!
Just literally co-exist with
that rude guy in the same house!
No need for small talk
or anything.
Okay. For now,
just keep calm.
Something’s missing…
- Naomi.
- What are you doing here?
I’m just curious if you borrowed
some of my makeup?
But I don’t mind. In fact, here.
I even brought more for you.
Are you accusing me
of stealing your makeup?
Huh? No!
I was just asking.
I mean, it’s totally fine,
I was just wondering.
I did not steal
your makeup, okay?
Now, go away.
Wait.
Naomi, if you want more makeup,
you can ask me for some.
I can lend you
the brands I like and—
I don’t need you
to buy me makeup, okay?
I can ask Dad to buy me makeup.
Now, leave.
Sorry.
That was a lie.
She couldn’t ask anything
from Mom or Dad.
Neither her needs nor
the things she wanted to buy.
Of course, I understand why
she had to borrow my things.
Rubylyn, did you preheat
the oven like I told you?
Yes, ma’am. I set it to 340.
Didn't I say 375?
Sorry, ma'am. I'll fix it.
I keep on repeating
myself, Rubylyn.
I'll fix it, ma'am.
So annoying.
- Mom.
- Hi, Maui!
Look what I made.
I’m making cookies.
You should try it when it’s done.
And also, bring some for Clyden.
Mom, I’m here to talk
about Naom—
I knew it!
I already know
what this is about,
you want to talk about
moving in with Clyden?
That was quick, I knew it!
You know, sweetheart,
love is
like baking!
Huh?
You need to have
all the ingredients
of patience,
warmth,
and understanding
to truly savor the sweetness.
Sometimes, it might burn
or get undercooked.
But in time,
you'll perfect it.
Mom, can I talk
about something else?
Okay. Sure. What is it?
Naomi is a college freshie now.
Rubylyn!
This is done.
Start baking it.
Go ahead. What?
So, she might need
new clothes, school supplies,
and other things.
Oh!
Sweetheart, I’m not her mom.
And she has
her allowance anyway.
She’s old enough,
she can take care of herself.
Okay.
I left some of my clothes,
makeup, and camera—
Wait!
Let’s take a picture.
Nice! Baking with my daughter,
mommy duties!
- So, Mom… I left—
- Look at this.
The picture would’ve been great,
but you weren’t
smiling properly.
What a shame.
I left it in my room
for her to use,
so please give it to her.
I'll tell Rubylyn,
she can take care of it.
Well… All right—
Are you ready?
To move in with Clyden?
Joy?
More like anger.
Do you want to go inside?
Nice, right?
I picked out this house.
They let you choose?
They didn’t even ask me about it.
I suggested it.
If I'm forced to live
in a house with you,
a woman I don't even know—
Might as well make sure
the house is nice.
And,
just a consolation.
I might even like living here.
To be fair, you have good taste.
Hey, guys!
Did you miss your dad?
Come here!
Sam, this is Maple.
She's calm right now,
but don’t get her angry.
You’ve met Summer, right?
She’s the sweetest.
But she’s a bit stubborn.
Just like you.
Me? Stubborn?
And this one, my big boy, Hail.
He’s just like me.
Has a bad attitude?
Rude and annoying?
No.
He’s nice
and loyal.
But don’t get too close to them,
they’re a bit picky with people.
Hi, Hail!
Huh?
Oh no!
Hail!
Don’t do that again.
Well, I think he likes you.
He got excited.
So that’s the pool
slash living room area.
And, stairs
all the way to the bedrooms.
And there’s a lounge,
mini lounge over there,
underneath the stairs.
Then, kitchen.
Then bathroom, fridge,
dining area.
So,
let’s check out the rooms?
- This house has three bedrooms.
- Good!
So we’re not forced
to sleep in one room.
Definitely.
You know, we really should
have separate rooms
and keep our interactions
to a minimum.
Let’s just literally
co-exist together
and get through this one month.
Whatever, you can have
the master’s bedroom.
No, you can have it.
You’re the one who
chose this house, anyway.
It’s yours.
I’ll sleep in the guest room.
- Well, actually, I don’t sleep.
- Really?
Because I can never
survive a day without sleep.
And then, welcome to med school!
So don’t worry,
our interactions are
gonna be very,
very minimal.
So when I’m studying, please,
don’t be noisy.
Me?
I’m not noisy.
Anyway, I need to unpack,
and I’ll have that room.
Bye.
Okay, seriously?
How am I supposed
to live like this?
I’m stuck in this
house with him.
Him! Of all people…
And then what?
So, this is the
master’s bedroom.
Pretend we’re a couple?
I barely know that guy!
it’s like we’re just
roommates but…
with a ring.
This is not how
I imagined my life at all!
Okay, one last chapter.
Then you can sleep.
One last, one last.
It’s too early!
Seriously?
You guys didn’t
let me sleep last night.
Good morning, baby!
Baby dogs.
Beer?
All these…
Junk food.
Chips for breakfast?
Really?
Why not?
You want some?
No!
Oh my god.
Summer…
Bad dog!
Hey, Sam,
where are you staying now?
Hasn’t it been almost two weeks
since we last
went to your condo?
She’s right. Have you gone
back home already?
Should I tell them?
They’re my friends.
I’m sure they’ll understand.
Oh, no. Are you okay?
Is it me?
I’ve been thinking
that maybe I should've
loved Kalix more.
Maybe I should’ve
given him everything so—
so he wouldn’t
have cheated, right?
Right?
So it was my fault? It was all me.
Luna, don’t say that.
Fuck that Kalix, seriously.
Luna, I know it’s hard right now
but you have to be thankful that
you’re out of that relationship.
You deserve someone,
who loves you fully.
You deserve to be happy,
not trapped in something
that’s making you miserable.
Sounds like
that’s based on experience.
Fuck Kalix.
If you want to
share anything with us,
just let us know.
We’ll listen.
Maybe we can help out.
Should I tell them?
Should I just say it?
No, they’re already dealing
with their own problems.
I don't want to burden them.
I’m okay, Sev.
Don’t worry about me.
Just know that we’re
always here for you, okay?
- I’m still okay. I can still manage.
- [background chattering]
They don’t need to know.
Come on, she was already okay.
Now you’re making a mess.
- Should I go after Kalix?
- Don’t!
I mean, yes!
Look, it’s your dad.
I won’t be surprised
if they discover he’s actually
protecting rich drug lords.
I’m tired.
I don’t wanna engage in
this conversation about my dad.
Of course.
I don’t understand you, really.
Sometimes, you’re nice.
But most of the time you’re rude.
What did I ever do to you, huh?
I’m the only one
you’re treating like this.
I hate your dad.
Actually, I hate your whole family.
It’s fucking pathetic to be honest.
What about you?
You’re more pathetic
than my family.
How so?
I do not steal taxpayers' money.
Can’t you see
how pathetic you are?
You’re trying so hard
to impress your dad
just because you badly want
recognition from him.
And because of that,
you’re not enjoying
your life anymore.
All you do is study and
stay all night in your room.
You probably
don’t have any friends.
‘Cause your whole life revolves
around med school!
Get a life!
- Go on.
- Go on?
You can’t even
say no to your dad
just because you want
to play, “The Best Son.”
No wonder why your
brothers are so mad at you.
Because you don’t care
about how others feel.
Even your own brothers!
Shit,
was I too hard on him?
Hey, I’m—
For the record—
I fucking hate
being the best son.
And you know
where that shit got me?
Here.
In this house! With you!
And it makes me sick!
Cy, wait.
I need to apologize.
I don’t like hurting
people’s feelings.
I should really say sorry.
Can we talk now?
Can I talk to him now?
But he looks busy.
Clyden?
Can we talk?
I really want to apologize.
Hi! I really want to apologize
for what I said the other day.
I was trying to say sorry
in person—
Sam? Is it a good idea?
What?
Just remember that the
party's set this weekend, okay?
All the proceeds
will go to the orphanage.
Guys, I’m so excited to see
how much we can raise.
Can I just say,
this is such a good idea.
I mean, a fundraising
event for charity?
You always manage to come up
with these great ideas, Sam!
That’s true.
Sam's org events are
always for a good cause.
You're always thinking
of ways to give back.
It’s giving, charity queen!
Well, it’s the least I can do.
You know what, I'm really
looking forward to this party.
I need to de-stress, you know.
I’m so stressed at home
and I haven’t been
sleeping well lately.
Wait... What home?
I thought you live in a condo?
Right. What’s going on?
Why are you stressed?
There’s just a situation
I need to deal with.
Nothing major.
Anyway, back to the party!
Okay. Should we get a DJ?
Of course!
Guys, we will party all night!
I feel good.
Hey!
So good!
Hi!
Enjoy!
Adi! I didn’t expect
you guys to be here.
Well, I just got
dragged by a friend
so I dragged other friends, too!
Yo, Sam!
- Solid party, by the way.
- Thank you.
Girls! You’ve met them, right?
- Yes.
- ‘Sup?
Guys, remember them
At the party?
That’s good.
Let’s start?
Let’s drink!
Give me a drink?
- Cheers!
You know…
I was surprised at the entrance.
There's a fee for outsiders.
It’s for a good cause
though, Adi.
Just enjoy the night.
Whatever you say.
What time are you
leaving later?
Order one more!
Do you want more?
One more, guys!
Okay.
One more, one more!
- One more!
One more, one more.
- Let’s go!
- Okay, game. Game!
Cheers!
- Cheers!
In the club,
I can just be myself.
Let's go, Kalix!
Kalix—
No expectations from anyone.
Not even my parents.
I’m not some
Senator’s daughter here.
- Cheers!
I’m just me.
Sam, are you okay?
- Who?
- Are you okay?
Hi, crush!
Girls, my former crush.
- She’s drunk.
- Really?
Yes!
- Do you need water?
- She needs it.
I’m good.
- Sam?
- Sam!
Bro!
Sam, watch your step.
Okay.
We’re here!
Sam, are you sure
about this address?
Fuck, is this a set up?
Bro, you’ve been watching
too many murder documentaries.
Hey, drunkard!
Is this the right address?
Yes. It’s right.
We’re here!
Guys! You guys, you can go na!
Go ahead.
I can manage myself.
- Are you sure?
- Go!
Yeah.
Hi!
Cy.
KJ.
You know this guy?
I’m in trouble.
Yes.
He’s a family friend.
Why is Sam going home here?
Who are you?
They’re my friends.
Say hi!
- Hi!
- Okay, so—
Here is my friend also.
He’s my ex-crush actually.
Hey, what the hell!
Friends.
We’re just friends.
Really? Are you guys
just friends?
Just kidding.
- Sorry.
- You can go now.
Thanks.
Let’s go.
- Goodnight!
- Bye!
Bye, guys! Thank you so much!
I’ll see you soon! Bye!
I can go—
It’s okay. I can manage.
I take care of everyone,
but no one takes care of me.
Go back to studying!
I can handle myself. Okay?
You can’t.
You should’ve texted me
so I could’ve picked you up.
What?
We’re in a fight. Remember?
You’re mad at me.
I was.
But I’m not anymore.
I don’t have the time to be mad,
sulk,
or even feel anything at all.
I’m sorry about what I said.
Well,
you’re right
about my brothers hating me.
Sorry, too, for the way
I spoke to you,
I was pretty harsh.
It’s fine.
Maybe it’s true.
Maybe my dad really is corrupt,
and I’m just in denial.
Do you know why I keep
holding those charity events?
No, why?
It’s because I feel guilty
that my dad is likely
misusing public funds.
It’s the least I can do
to make up for it.
It’s good that you want to help.
But
it would be even better
if you were doing it
because they
truly matter to you.
Not just because
you’re feeling guilty.
But, good job
on those baby steps.
I like this,
when we’re nice to each other.
Can’t we stay like this?
Ceasefire, please.
Really?
You’re the one who
usually starts it, though.
I just hope you still
remember this tomorrow.
Sam, wake up.
Sam, you have to sleep
in your room.
Sam!
Sam! Wake up, Sam!
Your parents
are in the driveway.
We need to go
to the master’s bedroom.
We’re supposed to sleep
next to each other there.
- Come on!
- Huh? Wait—
So they left the main door open.
At least the gate was locked.
- Shit!
- There’s nothing here.
Nothing at all!
Come on, let’s go back!
Yes. They don’t even
have security, hon.
No flowers either.
Come on, Maui.
- Wait.
- What?
- Where’s my ring?
- Where did you put it?
I don’t know, look for it.
It looks kinda bare.
At least it’s clean.
Yes.
Which bag did you use yesterday?
I found it.
- Hon, let’s go up. Let’s check.
- Let’s go.
They’re still not here?
We forgot the blankets again!
Go back!
Just get everything. Let’s go.
Maui?
- Hey! Lie down already!
- Yes!
Wait! Ouch!
She turned it
into a walk-in closet.
They don’t have
a walk-in closet.
That’s too bad.
The door! Close it.
Let’s check the other room.
This door is so heavy.
Oh my god!
Hon, what are they doing?
Mom! Dad! You’re here!
- Hi!
- We weren’t expecting you.
Sorry… Sorry!
Oh my god. Just like us
back then, hon. It’s so—
Let’s go, let's go.
- We didn’t have to see that!
- We’ll just see you down.
Lock the door!
That wasn’t part of the plan.
We needed to look convincing.
What are you talking about?
So, what now?
What are we going to do?
Well, I don’t know either!
It’s fine. I’ll go down instead.
I’ll just tell them
you were busy studying all night
and you’re really sleepy.
Fine.
Don’t you wear a bra?
Huh?
I mean,
don’t get me wrong.
I don’t really care.
I just thought maybe
you forgot to wear one.
Fuck my life!
You don’t wear briefs, either.
So, you were checking this out?
Huh?
- Hey!
- Hey.
So, here’s where we spend
most of our time together.
We always eat meals together.
- It’s our bonding moment.
- Yes.
Why are your placemats
so far apart?
‘Cause Cy sometimes
studies while eating,
and I sit over here
so I won’t distract him.
Yeah!
But you know, sweetheart,
it's really best that you
sit together when you eat,
so your bond
will be even stronger.
Don't just focus on studying!
Don't worry about that, Auntie.
We spend a lot
of quality time together.
Especially last night, right?
You know,
I’ve noticed it feels kind of
empty around your living area.
You don't have any personal
touches around the house,
like some paintings or pictures
of the two of you together!
And flowers, hon!
It just doesn’t feel
like a home yet.
Yes. We plan to decorate
the house, Dad.
We’re just busy lately.
Also Senator,
we’re budgeting our money
correctly.
How much do you need?
If you need anything, just ask.
About that Senator, don’t worry.
I’ll handle it.
I really like you.
You're a man of the house.
They’re still snooping around.
What should we do?
You are so beautiful!
Beautiful!
I really can't wait to marry you.
Hon.
I know!
I can’t wait to marry you.
Hon, I think we better go
and leave the kids alone.
We better get going.
You know kids, we'll just
show ourselves out, okay?
- All right!
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Let’s go! Let’s go.
Thank you for visiting us.
Take care Mom and Dad.
I’ll see you soon.
We’ll visit again like always.
Makes me jealous,
they’re just like how
we used to be before.
Fuck.
It worked.
It worked, it worked.
What the hell is your problem?
What problem?
All the things you did earlier.
It was over the top.
Which one?
Everything!
“I really can't wait to marry you.”
Don’t tell me you
felt giddy over that.
Looks like you're
even blushing right now.
As if!
What makes you think that
would work on me, huh?
For the record,
you’re not my type,
and I don’t like you.
You’re my type,
but I don’t like you.
What?
Did I hear that right?
I’m your type?
You heard me, didn’t you?
No need to repeat myself.
So what exactly is your type?
And how am I your type?
You’re so full of yourself!
I knew it.
You’re such an asshole!
Your dad’s an asshole.
What?
I’m leaving tomorrow,
just to get away from you.
Then go!
I wasn’t asking.
Good morning, Ma’am.
What brings you here?
Hi! Is Naomi here?
She’s in her room, ma’am.
Okay, thank you.
Welcome, ma’am.
Hi!
How are you?
Why are you here?
I just wanna say hi.
I’m okay. You can go now.
By the way, that shirt
really looks cute on you.
You can have it.
And the camera?
I don’t use it anymore.
It would be better if you have it.
Please stop giving me
your hand-me-downs
like I’m a charity case.
Don’t you know
how offensive that is?
I’m sorry.
No. Just leave!
Please bring all of that up
to the dressing room, okay?
- Yes, ma’am.
- Okay.
Maui! Hi!
What are you doing here?
- Mom.
- Hi, sweetheart.
You missed me already?
I just came to check on Naomi.
Naomi?
She’s perfectly fine.
She got into your school
because that’s what she wanted.
You know that, right?
She's just jealous.
Mom, don’t say that.
I’m just telling you the truth.
And mom, why did you
shop so much?
That’s so excessive!
Maui…
You know, when
you're a senator’s wife
you have to look glamorous.
What will people say
about me if I look pathetic?
But aren’t senators supposed
to work for the people?
You don’t need to impress them
with luxurious clothes.
Well, someday you’ll
understand me too.
And you know, Maui,
even if I shop every day,
we’ll never run out of money.
I can’t deal with this now, Mom.
Stay for lunch.
I can't.
I have somewhere I still need to go.
Are you home?
Yanna,
you should’ve just
waited inside;
that's bad for the baby.
Oh my gosh, the baby bump.
It still feels so weird.
What's the problem?
Why did you have to drive
all the way out here?
I just need
my best friend right now.
So?
I don’t know, Yanna.
I really want to
get closer to Naomi,
but it’s like I always mess up.
It feels like I'm always
doing something wrong.
Every time I try to reach out,
she ends up mad at me.
I don’t get it.
What am I doing wrong?
Just try to be
understanding for now.
The day will come
when things will be okay
between the two of you.
Just be patient with her.
You know she’s going
through a tough time, right?
You’re right.
I just need that one
breakthrough moment, you know?
I just need to break the ice,
and we’ll find something
in common to connect on.
What else are you
thinking about?
Tell me, I’ve got time.
Well…
I’ve been bothered by my dad.
I’ve had suspicions
that he’s not all clean,
but the news about him
lately is just getting worse.
Worse than I imagined.
And my mom isn’t helping either.
It seems like
she’s enjoying everything!
You know, my conscience
just can’t handle it anymore.
How can I live this kind of life
when everything
we have comes from—
Crime? From corruption?
What if you stop asking for
an allowance from your parents
first to ease your guilt?
Get a part-time job!
That’s a good idea.
I just hope they let me.
But I doubt it.
Also, what would
I even do, Yanna?
I don’t have any skills
for a part-time job, you know.
Come on!
There are plenty! You could
be an event planner
or even a bartender.
Stylist!
I know, right.
Speaking of fashion…
What if I become a model?
Where did that come from?
What are you talking about?
When I was a kid,
I had this doll who
was a fashion model,
and she was my favorite.
That's when I thought,
I want to be a model too,
just like her.
Know what I mean?
- See?
- Wait, you know what?
You’d actually be
perfect as a model!
You have so much potential,
I swear,
I can totally see it.
- Really?
- Yes!
You know what,
that doll story is true
but me becoming a model?
Come on, Yanna!
I was just joking.
Come on! I was just joking
about being pregnant,
but look at me now.
Seriously though,
you'd be perfect as a model.
If they won’t let you
get a part-time job,
just bear with it for now.
You’re only one year away
from graduating.
After that,
look for a job right away
so you can be financially
independent from your parents.
That way,
your conscience is clear.
Right.
Model!
Show your godchild!
- Like this?
- Stomachache.
- See?
- Headache.
What else do you want?
A stiff neck?
Thanks for listening
to all my problems,
even though it was sudden.
I feel so much better
after talking to you.
You know, since you left,
I haven’t had anyone to talk to.
Our friends’ dealing with
their own problems, too.
And I don’t want to add to it.
You know what I mean?
And it’s fine if it’s me?
I’m kidding! Just kidding.
What about Clyden?
Why don’t you open up to him?
He’s so annoying, Yanna!
Why did you have to
make me remember his face?
Now I’m pissed.
You know what ever since
we started living together,
he just—
Living together?
Whoa, Samantha!
Are you ranting right now?
Hey! I’ve never seen you
like this before.
It’s because
I’ve never met anyone
who's as annoying as him.
If you were
in my position right now,
you'd probably
feel the same way.
Actually, you might have even
punched him already,
but I’m still calm.
I’m calm.
You know,
I haven’t even met him yet,
but I feel like you two
would be a good match.
Don’t say that again.
You know what,
I’m just gonna go home!
Home?
To the house!
To him?
Your future husband?
Whatever!
I wonder what we’re going
to argue about tonight.
Just take care, okay?
If you need anything,
contact me.
I’m one call away.
And I can drive all the way
here again, you know.
Thank you.
I love you—
both.
Your godchild
and I love you too.
Take care.
Okay. Bye!
- And be calm.
- I’m calm.
Hi!
Hi. Did you go drinking again?
No. I just visited Yanna.
Oh, okay. Let’s go inside.
Were you worried about me?
Why aren't you asleep yet,
and why is Summer still awake?
She’s waiting for her mom.
Sam, you need to
sleep in your room.
Yes, Summer.
Don't worry,
she’s just asleep.
I’ll take good care of your mom,
and make sure she's comfortable.
To our social butterfly,
you have the kindest
and purest soul ever.
We love you so much.
You are so kind and generous.
So, this is who you are.
Good morning, Clyden.
Good morning, Sam.
Sorry, I just went
inside your room
‘cause you weren’t answering.
Are you okay?
You look good.
That’s one thing
I can promise you, Sam.
I’ll always be honest with you.
You’re wearing our
engagement ring today?
I always do.
Can I call you, Maui?
Only my family
gets to call me that.
Why? Am I not family?
I’m your future husband,
to be exact.
Let’s talk more.
Get your hands off her.
Okay.
You don’t know
anything about me.
It’s annoying.
Naomi!
Can you give me a hug?