(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
[Bloom Life]
[Year 2014]
You ran pretty fast, didn't you?
Not bad-looking either.
Where are you running off to?
You're actually quite good-looking.
Run?
Where to?
Where are you running to?
What are you doing?
Director,
I understand
what happened now.
As for Xia Zi,
I will take her back.
Mother of Xia Zi,
Xia Zi may be doing well in school,
but she also needs to follow the rules.
Xia Zi!
Do you know what you did wrong?
Did you use the self-defense techniques
I taught you?
Did you use the
"three-move victory" technique too late?
Don't you know how to read the situation?
In the face of three punks,
how could you three girls take them on?
If you can't beat them,
running away is the best strategy.
Director,
I will definitely discipline her well
when we get home.
I'll be leaving now.
I still have to get back to work.
Who are you?
What are you trying to do?
What do you want?
Just you wait!
[Episode 3: There's more than
just nightingales in the rose garden]
Sadiq was a jerk when he was a kid.
I didn't expect his family to
own such a big silk shop.
Come closer to talk.
Let me tell you.
Their family has more than
just these businesses.
Do you see the woman in the back?
Gulhumar.
She's truly somebody.
Everyone in the old town knows her.
So beautiful!
How gorgeous!
My bride is so beautiful.
You look good!
So beautiful!
You look good.
Take a look.
Red still complements
the bride's complexion best.
This red outfit is more festive.
That's right.
But,
Mom, I've always wanted to wear white.
Exactly.
Ever since she was a child, her dream
was to wear a white wedding dress.
Exactly, Auntie.
White wedding dresses are
really trending right now.
Minawar looks like a princess in white.
It looks good on her.
Isn't it?
She's so pretty,
and she's also the pillar of
our song and dance troupe.
Everyone loves her.
Not like our Qunduzay.
I asked her to come by and watch the shop,
but she couldn't be bothered.
Mom, why are you talking about me?
But,
if you are marrying into
a wealthy family like ours,
you should wear
our shop's signature piece,
which is the red silk.
A wedding should be red and prosperous.
It's so festive. How beautiful!
What do you think?
I...
Red looks festive.
If you want it to be festive,
then let us bridesmaids wear it.
There are so many of us bridesmaids.
If everyone wears red,
it will be even more festive.
Looks good, no?
Auntie, your silk is really beautiful.
Exactly.
So red and prosperous.
Exactly, Auntie.
There are 8 of us in the bridal party.
That's 8 of us wearing red.
Exactly.
Imagine everyone wearing red
while holding up your white dress for you.
Right, how beautiful that would be!
I want to wear it.
I want to wear it too.
Let us wear red.
Qunduzay can wear it too.
I'll take a call.
Auntie, this silk is so comfortable
and so soft to the touch.
What style do you think we should make?
Thank you.
Grandma.
The flowers of our family
are so beautiful!
So beautiful!
Just like flowers.
Where is my dad?
Your dad went out early in the morning.
I don't know where he went.
He's probably hiding somewhere crying.
How pretty!
All of you better come back early, okay?
Okay.
Don't worry, Mom.
Today is Minawar's
final bachelorette party.
Okay.
Let's go.
Please be safe!
I promise to bring everyone back safely.
Bye bye!
It looks good.
I've been well.
How about you?
My friend, you're here.
I ran into him this morning
and asked if he wanted to come over today.
I didn't expect him to actually come.
We happened to be short of a photographer.
Thanks for your hard work.
My pleasure.
No problem.
Right?
Yes.
Go have fun.
Why are you everywhere?
What are you talking about?
I'm here to take photos.
Take photos?
I think you're just trying to
get on my good side.
Don't you tell anyone
about my work.
You're being too cynical.
Don't worry.
I'll keep it a secret.
Hello, buddies!
You're dressed so nicely today.
You're dressed well too.
Bro!
Long time no see.
It's been a long time.
How did you get so buff?
Xia Zi.
So formal-looking!
Who is this friend?
-He's Arzugul's friend.
-He’s from our homestay.
Let's take a photo.
Let's go.
Let's all take a photo together!
Um,
friend?
Could you do us a favor
and take a picture of us?
Thanks.
Come.
Look at me.
Get ready.
Smile!
3,
2,
1.
Cheese!
Hi.
Adili.
No, no.
This is a wedding gift for you.
We've known each other for so many years.
Even if we're only friends,
I should give you a decent gift.
But...
I wouldn't accept gold from any man
other than my husband and my father.
6 months ago,
before I went abroad,
I asked you what gift you wanted.
You said you wanted someone
who could give you a gold necklace.
I thought you wanted me to give it to you.
But when I came back,
you already had a boyfriend.
I've been wanting to ask you
for the past 6 months,
why did you
change so quickly?
Actually,
I have never changed.
You've always known what I want.
I know you want to leave this place.
I've been saving up money.
But how much longer do I have to wait?
Adili.
In a few years, I'll be old.
Give this to the girl who’ll marry you.
Thank you.
Blessed marriage!
♪There's no intentional reason ♪
Thank you
♪I just love being proud and wild♪
Cheers
♪Until you leave me again♪
♪I love freedom♪
Come on, brothers.
Come on, let’s have a drink!
Cheers.
Come on.
This is our local specialty,
called "roasted sheep spleen".
You don't dare to try?
Isn't it delicious?
Not bad.
Congratulations!
You got prettier with age,
and you're getting married now.
Don't just talk about me.
You should hurry up too.
Look how formally he's dressed.
He must have heard
your colleagues are all beauties.
Come on.
Everyone knows he's here for you.
Xia Zi.
Is your service really
this good these days?
Why are outside guests
allowed to join such private events?
He's here to help as a photographer.
Right.
I suddenly remembered,
previously,
did Arzugul and Minawar both
had a crush on Fang Nan?
Don't go saying things like that.
I didn't.
No.
You didn't?
But it's not entirely accurate
to say not at all.
I might have liked him
for 2 or 3 months,
but I was just a kid then.
I was 2 heads shorter than I am now.
And in 6 months, you became just as tall
and as pretty as you are now.
There were so many boys
chasing after you.
You must have forgotten him long ago.
Exactly.
But Arzugul is different.
She worked so hard to get into
a university in Shanghai.
One summer, she even came all the way back
for some class reunion,
just to see you once.
But you didn't even come.
Tell us,
where did you go?
So,
that's how many things are.
A series of unfortunate events.
When you need them,
they aren't there.
What you want,
they can't give.
Even if you've tried really hard,
but
when there's no way,
there's just nothing to be done.
Don't you agree, my friend?
♪My lover♪
♪My flower-like lover♪
♪My dear lover♪
♪Ah, oh, my dear♪
♪My beloved, whose eyes burn like flames♪
Not bad!
Come on, let's toast!
Come on, cheers!
Let's have a toast too!
Cheers!
Come on, princess.
Look,
a surprise for you.
Let's go.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Yes.
Sit.
Sit down.
Your Highness,
have a grape.
Let me
massage your shoulders.
Then let me
massage your legs.
You two maids
have served me very well today.
I will reward you
by letting you sleep with me tonight.
What?
Shouldn’t you give us gold necklace?
Yeah.
How dare you!
You are the princess today.
Whatever you wish for tonight,
we will satisfy you.
I want to dance the sanam.
Go ahead, Your Highness.
Dance now.
You can't do it. You're drunk.
I can. Let's do it together.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
Let's dance together. Come.
Wait for me!
My shoe broke!
Minawar!
Wishing you a happy marriage!
Arzugul!
Be forever free!
Laili!
Be happy everyday!
I want to climb the Kunlun Tower.
Kunlun Tower is closed at night.
You can't go.
Then I want to see the golden sunrise
over the snow mountain.
You're drunk. Don't go.
No, I want to go!
I'm getting married,
so I must go see it.
You can't visit the snow-capped mountains
after you get married?
I just want to see the sunrise.
Let's go see the golden sunrise
over the snow mountain, shall we?
You're awake.
Sleep a little longer.
I'll wake you up when
the sun is about to come out.
How did I end up here?
You were clamoring to see
the golden sunrise over the snow mountain,
and wanted to dance at
the foot of the snow-capped mountains.
I drank too much.
You can't trust the words of a drunkard.
Take me back quickly now.
Look outside.
In the past, when I saw Muztagh Ata,
it felt
like it was so far away from us.
But today,
it feels like it's right in front of me.
It's almost like I could touch it
if I just reach out.
But, I still can't reach it.
Just looking at it is enough.
Let's go back.
Wait a little longer.
The sun is about to rise.
Minawar!
Quick, look.
Thank you
for today.
Minawar.
I have one last thing to say.
In the past,
whenever you wanted to see me,
I would do everything I could to show up.
But not anymore.
I wish to preserve some of my dignity.
Goodbye.
Your resume is excellent.
It was a pleasure talking to you today.
Please wait for our notification.
I saw your job postings
and saw that
you're still hiring designers.
I studied architectural design in college.
Can you give me a chance?
I can start from the bottom.
Please just wait for further notice.
Babes! Our itinerary today is to
check out the top 10 homestays
in the old town.
Everyone will experience
Our family's...
the best of Kashgar’s charm!
It's guaranteed to blow up
your social media feeds!
Among these top 10
most beautiful homestays,
some are famous for their food,
some are decorated with the most complete
Southern Xinjiang handicrafts
that boasts unique ethnic features.
There is another one...
Uncle.
that would continuously
sing and dance for 15 hours.
Has your homestay
really been open for over a 100 years?
Young man.
didn't I show you the last time?
The title deed written on sheepskin?
Have you ever thought about
letting someone else
run this homestay?
Who would give their home up
to someone else?
How dare you
boss around the house as an outsider?
I'm not dead yet, young man.
Uncle,
that's not what I meant.
This is the first time I've seen a shop
with such a long history.
Standing here,
it's as if I've traveled through
the corridor of time and space,
and back to Kashgar 100 years ago.
It's like I started...
a dialogue through time and space.
Young man,
you have a great eye.
Tell me,
what's so good about
this old homestay of ours?
Uncle.
When I was in Shanghai,
I worked overtime every day,
going home only in
the wee hours of the morning.
And after going home,
I was still too anxious to sleep.
You have no idea
how long it’s been since I’ve seen
such beautiful sunshine in Kashgar.
These 2 days,
I've slept very soundly,
and very peacefully.
I really appreciate it.
I...
I'm so, so grateful to you.
Young man.
It was fate that brought you
to our homestay.
Old man, come up quickly!
The faucet is leaking again!
Okay.
I'll be right there!
Thank you, Uncle.
I'll be right over!
I'm on my way!
Why are you trying to act like
such a hipster?
When you get off work
in the early morning,
don't you get
your travel expenses reimbursed?
Don't create a persona for yourself.
I'm telling you,
don't set your sights on our homestay.
Don't tease our bird.
Are we businesspeople
not allowed to have sentiments anymore?
Then you should go check out
the other homestays.
To be honest,
I've looked at many homestays.
Either
I like them but lack the budget,
or I have the budget
but don't like them.
To put it bluntly, you're just broke.
Does telling the truth
do you any good?
My friend,
house hunting is a long game.
Haste makes waste.
The homestay market is saturated
in many areas
but it's still growing in Kashgar.
Opening a day earlier
means making money a day earlier.
You're really obsessed with money.
Who can compare with you?
You have an apartment in Shanghai
to fall back on.
Don't make fun of me.
My uncle will see your true colors
sooner or later.
Worry about yourself first.
You won't be able to hide the fact that
you're unemployed for long.
Hello, Aunt Jiang.
Xia Zi.
I heard you're back.
Yes, I am.
You probably don't know
about your mother's condition, do you?
The famous traditional Chinese medicine
doctor, Director Chang,
is holding a clinic in the village today.
[Chang Yue, TCM specialist at
Silk Road Hospital,  Kashgar Prefecture]
Please line up in an orderly manner.
The famous traditional Chinese medicine
doctor, Director Chang,
is holding a clinic in the village today.
Please line up in an orderly manner.
Feeling any better?
My child had stomachaches for years,
and you cured it with just 2 needles.
Dr. Chang, you're amazing.
So amazing!
Mom—
My whole family is here.
Look, he's my dad.
My mom, my brother, and his wife.
Hello.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Feeling better?
Much better.
It's time to remove the needles.
Sir!
Oh, my medicine.
Drink it.
Well done.
These elderly
take the medicine home,
but don't take it regularly.
so the effect is poor.
After they take the medicine home,
they quickly forget about it.
They only come for medicine when
milk and naan are distributed.
They would give the milk and naan
to their children.
So you must watch them finish it.
Okay, Dr. Chang.
You don't mind the fatigue either.
Instead of seeing patients
in the hospital,
you came all this way to see them.
If I don't come down,
how can they understand
and accept traditional Chinese medicine?
I tell them,
you may focus on
dry versus damp heat,
but we focus on damp heat
and qi stagnation.
They are all connected,
just different paths
to the same destination.
Right?
Yes.
You make a good point,
but can your body take it?
I know my own body.
What do you know?
Aunt Jiang told me that
your heart skips a beat tens
of thousands times a day.
She suggests you have surgery.
I'm fine.
I'll take care of it myself.
I just need some medicine.
It's an emotional issue.
Your dad has been gone
for more than half a year,
and no matter how much
I come to terms with it,
well...
I will still
feel a little sad.
I'm really at my wit's end with you.
Why are you always
pushing yourself so hard?
Why haven't you returned to Shanghai?
Are you kicking me out?
I'll go back when I'm done.
Are you not leaving
because you're worried about me?
Let me warn you.
I’ve raised you to be so outstanding,
with the hopes that
as compared to our generation,
you can make choices without any burden.
I don't want you to
sacrifice yourself for anyone,
nor will I allow anyone to bully you,
including myself.
So if you need to go back to Shanghai,
please go back immediately.
I'll go back right after
Minawar's wedding.
You'll go to her wedding, right?
I'll see.
We've been really busy at the hospital.
Old man,
this was actually
the rug we used when we got married.
Yes, it's been almost thirty years
in a blink of an eye.
Mom, you're not asleep yet?
My precious daughter
is getting married tomorrow.
How can any mother sleep?
I bought this for you
when you were just born.
when you went to primary school.
And this one
was for when you got into high school.
I got this one
when you started working.
Why did you buy so much?
Here, for you.
My secret stash that
I have been saving up for you.
Thank you, Mom.
Don't cry, silly child.
Don't cry.
What mother doesn't start saving a dowry
as soon as her daughter is born?
Mom.
You don't have to worry.
Sadiq's business has reached Europe.
You always knew
that my biggest dream
was to dance on a bigger stage.
He’ll definitely help me
go to Europe to dance.
You will go far
and live the life you want.
Mom is happy for you.
Don't cry. Don't cry.
Back then,
I also wanted to
go to Beijing to learn to dance.
Later,
I met your father
and had you,
so I stayed at this homestay.
In a blink of an eye,
most of my life has passed.
Promise me
you must live
better than I did.
I will. I promise you, Mom.
Don't worry. I will.
I definitely will.
I promise.
♪Congratulations♪
They're coming!
♪Celebrating a wedding with joyful steps♪
♪May this couple’s hearts
always resonate together♪
Brother, what are you doing?
We have to leave soon.
The car is parked outside.
Let's sit a little longer. No rush.
Come, have some dessert.
What's going on?
The bride and groom
still need to serve tea to their parents.
Where did that rule come from?
It's okay.
What is this?
How dirty!
The car is loaded.
We can leave now.
You guys get in first. I'll wait a bit.
Okay.
Come, get in.
Let's go!
♪Along the way to Atushi♪
♪The garden of Boshkeranmu is filled with
the sweet fragrance of flowers♪
♪ I can smell the fragrance of
the Boshkeranmu flowers ♪
♪The pain of a burning passion♪
♪It's so torturing♪
♪Gülayayim♪
♪My pain, Gülayayim♪
♪What should I do, my lover?♪
♪My heart burns for you always♪
♪I belong to you, my lover♪
What are they doing?
♪Who else will I belong to, if not you?♪
In Xinjiang, people who can't dance
dare not attend weddings.
♪You are the one I met
at the bazaar in Kashgar♪
They are sending blessings
and red envelopes to the groom.
♪You are whom I
fell in love  at first sight♪
♪Hey, you are whom I
fell in love at first sight♪
♪I came to your alley from my alley♪
This is from your dad.
This is the key to my house's front door.
My granddaughter, you must be happy.
You will always be Grandma's good girl.
♪The snowflakes are falling♪
♪In this last December♪
♪The wind plays with the snowflake ♪
♪On either side of the streetlight♪
♪The snowflakes are falling♪
♪In this last December♪
♪The wind plays with the snowflake ♪
Congratulations!
What is this?
They're competing.
The groom's side will look for a chance
to get under the red veil
and lift the bride's veil.
The bride's family must find a way
to keep them out with the veil.
If the veil is lifted,
it means the bride is captured.
How could she do this?
She just grabbed it?
Does she know the rules?
The veil is torn.
So,
the groom's side has won?
Yes.
It's just a game that adults play.
It's fine.
Sadiq's family is going too far.
I'm really worried about her
marrying into that family.
Why did you come in this outfit?
I just finished a home visit.
It's good enough I could make it.
What a busy bee.
Arzugul.
What's the name of the apartment
you bought in Shanghai?
Rose Garden. What's wrong?
The construction has been
halted for so long!
Give it to me. Let me take a look.
-Let me see.
-What's there to see?
Will construction at
Rose Garden ever resume?
It's fine. It's just halted.
So, are you still paying the mortgage?
Yes. What else can I do?
This is such a serious matter.
How long do you plan to
keep this from me?
Arzugul,
you put all your savings
into this house.
Will they stop building it?
Fine.
We're going to Shanghai tomorrow.
I'll go with you.
What are we going for?
We homeowners are currently
in negotiations with the developer.
Stay out of it.
I can handle it myself.
What experience do you have?
I must go with you.
And what will you do?
You'll just cause more trouble.
How will I cause trouble?
Arzugul,
if your mother goes with you,
she can at least cook for you
and help you out.
This is such a big deal.
It's not just your mom—
we're worried too.
Exactly.
This is so annoying.
Laili, help me buy a flight ticket.
I said no.
Buy me a flight ticket.
No, we are not going.
This is such a big deal
and you didn't even tell me.
I'm not going back to Shanghai!
I lost my job.
I was laid off.
I just found out a few days ago.
It's fine.
Calm down, both of you.
Arzugul is so outstanding.
I'm sure plenty of companies
have reached out to her.
Yue, don't you think so?
Yes.
You're right.
Arzugul!
Xia Zi.
What's wrong with you today?
With so many people around,
what do you mean
by leaving so suddenly?
No.
Minawar.
She didn't mean that.
She has her own issues.
Don't talk about me.
I don't understand.
You're such a headstrong person.
Today, from you to Uncle to Auntie,
everyone seemed to be
bowing down to their family.
Was it really necessary?
Don't talk about this today.
I'm just upset for her.
I feel bad for her.
Who are they to do so?
What gives them the right
to treat her this way?
It's her wedding.
Why should they?
Aunt Chang Yue.
What's wrong?
Minawar is so beautiful today.
You and Sadiq really are enemies
who were destined to meet.
I remember when you were
around 14 or 15,
Sadiq and two punks
got into a fight with you.
It went all the way up to
the Office of Academic Affairs.
I was the one who
taught him a lesson afterwards.
It was you?
Why do I remember it being Dad?
How could it be your dad?
Your dad was working on
a mission abroad at the time.
Just you wait!
So it was Aunt Chang Yue.
That's so cool.
I'm not going to Shanghai.
The moon waxes and wanes,
and bad things happen,
but they will pass.
But Mom believes in you.
I've raised you to be someone
who's not easily bullied.