WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
EPISODE 10
Hee-joo.
Did you sleep well?
Yeah.
I want to sleep more.
Go back to sleep.
- But you'll be late for work.
- What?
What time is it?
- Right now?
- Yeah.
It's Saturday.
I can't believe you!
Get up.
Don't.
- Get up.
- Don't!
I had a dream.
The toothpaste!
Squeeze it from the bottom
and not the middle!
How many times have I told you?
Who takes off their clothes
inside out like this?
What about you?
You always do that with your socks.
When did I do that?
All the time.
So when I put it in the basket,
- I do this.
- When? Tell me the exact time.
- So childish.
- I am not.
In the dream,
we were ordinary just like everyone else.
The peaceful happiness
everyone gets to enjoy in life.
Why was that so hard for us?
We just…
wanted to love and rely on each other,
cherish each other,
and stay together for a long, long time.
SPOKESPERSON PAIK SA-EON
NAME: PARK DO-JAE
NAME BEFORE ADOPTION: YUN MIN-SEONG
HEE-JOO
The person you're calling is…
What the hell?
Where is he?
PAIK SA-EON'S COMING TOO,
LET'S PLAY TOGETHER.
I thought he wanted to play.
Where did he go?
Is it you?
Are you "Master"?
The negotiation team's timeline.
OFFICE BUILDING FIRE IN YEOUIDO
Did you see it?
What do you think?
Don't act alone from now on.
So why did you leave me out?
I want to join in on the fun too.
I'll give you a job.
Make sure she doesn't back out.
YONGJU SILVER CARE HOSPITAL
Where's Hong Hee-joo?
So why did you lie?
You're the one who lied!
Sir?
A call came in a moment ago.
This…
JUAN FISHING
Going somewhere?
Why?
Did you do something that made you want
to run away from me?
- Stop.
- What do you mean?
I know you're the one behind it all.
Leave him alone.
Right.
You must've seen my face
on the news.
So what?
Did you tell that bastard?
That kid…
did nothing wrong.
It was your grandfather and parents
who tried to kill you.
Why are you trying to take revenge
on the wrong person?
What do you mean, he did nothing wrong?
He's enjoyed my life for decades.
He got to live under my name!
I never should've let you live.
When Paik Jang-ho tried to kill you,
I should've let him.
There's no point in regretting it now.
It's too late.
Don't get in the way.
Don't take his side either.
I'm going to…
destroy him.
You're the real Paik Sa-eon.
You caught me.
Is that why you used Hong Hee-joo as bait
to lure me in?
Did you call Paik Sa-eon too?
The three of us should meet
and talk face-to-face.
Yeah.
I'll give you your chance,
so shut up and wait.
I don't need you anymore.
Goodbye.
SECRETARIAT
PRESIDENTIAL OFFICE
What's this?
You bastard!
Were you one of Paik Sa-eon's lackeys?
Then let's play some more.
This is going to be fun!
UNKNOWN CALLER
Let's play,
Paik Sa-eon.
If you bring the cops,
Hong Hee-joo dies.
Got it?
Play with me.
Let's play, Paik Sa-eon.
Hee-joo…
Hee-joo.
Park Do-jae.
Park Do-jae, wake up.
Wake up, Do-jae!
Where's Hee-joo?
What did you do with her?
He's here…
Hee-joo!
Yeah!
Come on.
Hee-joo!
Are you up, Sis?
Stop.
I don't want to.
Stop the car, asshole!
Hee-joo!
Are you okay?
- Were you hurt?
- I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Is it you?
Are you him?
You look…
great.
For someone who used to fish
with your bare hands here.
So, what is it that you want?
Your name? Your place?
Do you want them back?
Really?
Yeah!
Take them all back!
I never wanted them in the first place.
Just take them all back!
Really?
Will you give me Hong Hee-joo too?
Well?
Will Hong Hee-joo be my wife now?
Park Do-jae!
How touching.
It really is.
Get him.
Go after him.
Don't talk.
I called an ambulance.
It's true.
I intentionally stayed
by your side.
Because…
I believed you were Paik Sa-eon,
who killed my brother.
I can give her everything.
If that's what Hee-joo wants,
I'll give as much as she needs.
Then promise me.
If I make an effort
and we can change,
promise you'll never make this call again.
On the mountain,
I was the one
who pushed her.
Change of plan.
Today's D-Day.
Just like when I lost my only family,
I wanted you…
to feel the pain
of losing someone precious to you.
You got it wrong.
It wasn't him. It was that bastard.
Then who on earth are you?
Why aren't you Paik Sa-eon?
All this time,
what the hell have I been doing?
Park Do-jae.
Park Do-jae!
Wake up!
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Park Do-jae,
and I'm the new trainee reporter.
- The Presidential Office?
- Yes, as a special administrative officer.
But you know,
you never know when or how
I'll be replaced as the spokesperson.
It doesn't matter. It's an honor.
I'll work hard.
Also, thank you so much
for choosing me, sir.
Were you hurt?
I entrusted everything to him.
On the day you were kidnapped,
I had him track the phone and location
and get you bodyguards.
On top of that,
I entrusted you to Park Do-jae myself.
It's not your fault.
Don't blame yourself.
Where did it all go wrong?
He's right.
I used to live here, catching fish.
All of these assholes.
They're all coming at me.
They must have a death wish.
His first death anniversary is coming up.
In three days, right?
Exactly a year ago, around this time,
when I saw the news
that Paik Jang-ho had died,
it all came back to me.
His face was like on every channel,
and it came back to me.
Help!
The face of the man
who pushed me into the water.
So,
do you know what I thought?
"What a shame."
"I should've killed that bastard myself."
With my hands.
I should've done it myself.
What?
Are my hands weird?
Are they dirty?
Are you crying?
Why? Do you pity me?
No.
I pity myself.
I was tricked.
I was told you died.
No, he said he killed you.
That old bastard tricked me.
What the hell are you saying?
You all wanted me dead and gone.
Do you know
why I didn't come after you people first?
Because I knew you'd kill me again.
You'd lock me up again!
No, no.
No, my baby…
My baby…
- I just…
- You just what? Tell me.
Are you happy I'm alive?
Are you happy to see me?
I…
I never…
want to lose you again.
I mean that.
No!
- Professor!
- Who are you?
Get him.
Get back, or else I'll kill him.
See you soon, old man!
I'll give you a show of a lifetime!
Did you find him?
No.
Honey, how could you still treat him
like this?
He went to hell and back!
- How could you?
- Hell?
He's making our lives
a living hell right now.
Snap out of it!
Was living ever heaven on earth for you?
I don't know about you,
but I've never had a single day of peace.
Stop playing the victim.
What if we find him?
Can you proudly call him our son
in front of the world?
Can you care for him all your life?
He's…
the monster we created.
He's nothing more…
and nothing less.
He takes after you a lot.
But do you know something?
Neither you nor he
takes after Paik Jang-ho.
Why are you bringing that up now?
There's someone else
who takes after Paik Jang-ho.
What?
There's nothing you can do about it
even if you find out now.
Paik Jang-ho's dead.
That son is rising much faster
than you are.
The Paik family
values the presidential race
more than life itself,
and unless you give it up,
what can you possibly do?
Yesterday afternoon,
the Seongnang Police Station
announced the arrest of a suspect
believed to be an accomplice
in the Paik Sa-eon threat case
and stated that his residence
had been searched.
Reporter Kim Jeong-seon
has more on the details.
Police investigators are raiding
the suspect's residence in Seoul.
The search lasted five hours…
Are they saying
that's where Park Do-jae lives?
No way.
What's going on?
Why would he do that to Mr. Paik?
Is Mr. Paik okay?
I spoke with him on the phone earlier.
He didn't sound okay.
Well, how can he be okay?
He kept him by his side
and trusted him more than anyone.
What happens now?
Mr. Park will be investigated
and punished for it.
And the spokesperson said
he'd clarify his position soon.
We'll continue with the latest updates.
While the police were investigating
the motive and circumstances
of the crime with the arrested accomplice,
they identified
two of the criminal's hideouts
and conducted a focused search.
During this process, a weapon believed
to have been used in the crime was found…
- He won't pick up.
- …thoroughly investigated.
Based on the unidentifiable fingerprints…
PAIK SA-EON
…the suspect is likely an unregistered
person with no official family ties.
FATHER
We're analyzing the computer hardware
obtained from Park Do-jae's residence,
and it appears to have been used
for backdoor hacking.
Is that how he wiretapped me
and tracked my location?
Yes, but there was another target
of the hacking besides you,
and we suspect it was his accomplice.
The one who made the threats?
So, doesn't that mean
we can track his location right now?
The problem is
that the program is encrypted.
We don't know
how long it'll take to decrypt it.
Then to ask Park Do-jae for it
would be the fastest way.
Yes, but he's exercising
his right to remain silent.
And as I told you, this morning…
How is he?
Fortunately, it's not life-threatening.
PARK * JAE
Serves you right.
You're unbelievable.
But then,
it's understandable.
Turns out you were helping
the culprit all this time,
and he made a fool of you.
You feel empty and embarrassed.
I bet you wanted to disappear.
You got me wrong and sought revenge
because you were deceived.
But you tried to hurt Hee-joo too.
That's a different issue.
That's attempted murder. You know that?
You have no right to blame me.
You've had a good life
living as Paik Sa-eon.
- Am I wrong?
- You're right.
I'll make sure everyone,
including me, pays for their sins.
So help me catch him first.
Don't be ridiculous.
You will expose the Paik family's secrets
and give up the highest power
in the country?
I won't fall for it.
I won't be fooled twice.
Then why did you save me?
Have you ever thought
that I might not be the person you hate,
even just once?
I have no intention of showing mercy.
If you want a lighter sentence,
cooperate with the police.
Have you…
never doubted me?
Thinking you might have seen
through my true intentions,
I was always on edge.
Because you…
could've seen right through me.
I trusted you.
I don't trust anyone.
But I trusted you.
I know it's late,
but would you…
consider trusting me now?
YUN HYEON-SEONG
So,
Mr. Jeong Jin-seok raised Sa-eon,
and the real son, thought to be dead,
has returned and is trying to kill Sa-eon.
And that ass…
And that bad guy
is the boy from the villa?
You're good at summarizing.
You should be hearing it
from the person involved,
but I know you would've found out anyway.
You can hear the rest from him.
"The rest"?
Is there more?
Poor Sa-eon.
It must've been so hard
and lonely for him.
Carrying all of those secrets alone.
He didn't have to act tough.
Take care of him.
You see, Sa-eon is not one to talk
about his personal life.
But he told you. That means…
the green light.
"Green light"?
For us?
Hurry up and call him!
Ask if he's eaten.
Invite him out if he hasn't.
Tell him you'll eat with him.
Me? Be his friend?
SPOKESPERSON PAIK SA-EON
Look.
You guys are connected.
Yeah.
Hello?
They found it?
I'll drive.
No, I'll do it.
Get in.
After skeletonization,
it becomes hard to identify a body
as well as the time of death.
Still, personal effects were found.
It'd be helpful if you could confirm them.
EVIDENCE
This bead…
is mine.
I lost in a game of marbles.
So I gave it to Yeong-seok.
And this is Min-woo's ring.
It's a big ring though.
His mom gave it to him…
after promising she'll be right back.
Though she didn't come back…
Then…
I guess that belonged to Jin-yeong.
The child who loved cars. Lee Jin-yeong.
Am I right?
Here. Drink this.
Thank you.
Stop it. This is nothing.
Thank you for remembering
my friends with me.
You-ri, of all the people I know,
you're the most cheerful.
So, whenever painful memories
I didn't want to remember flooded in,
I've managed to hold on.
It's all thanks to you.
Thank you.
The real Paik Sa-eon is alive,
and he's the one behind the threats?
Yeah.
The pieces are finally coming together.
When I was young, I remember going out
to the yard after hearing Yu-jin cry.
Yu-jin! Are you okay?
He looked around our age,
so I thought he was Paik Sa-eon.
But…
when I first saw Paik Sa-eon,
he was much taller than the boy I saw.
So I thought maybe the boy wasn't him.
The boy you saw
was probably the real Paik Sa-eon.
Probably.
And not long after that,
the car accident happened.
And the real Paik Sa-eon disappeared.
Then…
are you saying
the car accident might not be an accident?
What if…
Yu-jin saw
the face of the real Paik Sa-eon,
the one the Paik family was hiding?
Why didn't you answer my calls?
What are you doing here?
No, how dare you come here?
Are you really trying to push Hee-joo out
and take her place?
Why are you smiling?
Did I say something funny?
Hee-joo, let's talk later.
I should go.
They're making a fuss over catching
the culprit and the accomplice.
What's going on?
If this keeps up,
won't it affect the presidential race?
What if you can't become
the future president's daughter-in-law?
I should've just married you off
to the Yeonghwa Construction family.
I was wrong.
No.
It's not my fault. She's the problem.
This happened because that wench
ran off before the wedding!
I regret it too.
What?
I regret loving you.
No.
That wasn't love.
You…
Now that In-a's talking,
are you talking too?
I thought being obedient
was a way to show you love.
If I did as you said,
I thought you'd love me back one day, but…
HOME
Now that I've been loved…
and loved someone, I know.
Love…
isn't about forcing
one-sided sacrifice like you do
or being unconditionally obedient like me.
"Sacrifice"?
Did I do this for my own benefit?
I did it because I wanted something better
for you!
Stop gaslighting me!
I won't listen to you anymore.
Also, I'll never be
the president's daughter-in-law.
So wake up, please.
How dare she,
after everything I've done for her!
Drink this.
How did I forget?
Do you remember the DNA report
from before?
I said I didn't know who sent it.
Yeah.
I think I now know who sent it.
Who?
Hong Hee-joo.
It's our wedding vows.
You don't need to read it all.
Just remember this.
One, the groom cannot initiate a divorce.
Two, divorce is prohibited
under any circumstances.
Three, we will actively announce
to the public
that we are a married couple.
If any of these are violated,
the penalty…
will be two billion won.
What are you doing?
I understand what it means now.
For me, it was way before that.
Way before.
You said "way before."
I don't know exactly when that is,
but I'm certain
that it was before three years ago.
Before the wedding,
the person who sent the DNA report to In-a
was you, wasn't it?
Is Hong Hee-joo marrying the son
of the Yeonghwa Construction family?
Is that true?
The only woman willing to sell
her daughter to him is Hee-joo's mom.
The wedding will be held
as planned tomorrow.
However, let's switch the bride.
It won't be you. It'll be your sister.
I wasn't a stand-in.
From the very start,
I was your wife.
Once all of this is over,
will you marry me?
No.
Once all of this is over…
I'll propose to you.
I love you,
Hong Hee-joo.
Of the four discovered remains,
three were identified
with the help of personal items,
but for the remaining one,
we have no clue.
It will take some time
to analyze the remains and see
if the DNA matches yours.
INCIDENT REPORT
YUN HYEON-SEONG
Hyeon-seong!
Where are you?
Come out!
Hyeon-seong!
I found my friends thanks to you.
Thank you.
There's still one unidentified person.
One of the twins?
Yes.
I was going to self-destruct too.
After I get my revenge,
once the goals and targets
that kept me going were gone,
I was going to disappear too.
What about now?
Did you change your mind?
Of course.
I'm going to live a life
after taking revenge.
With the person
I want to be with for the rest of my life.
Will you try it again?
It's a shame your brother died,
but what about the rest of your life?
This is all because of him.
How many lives need to be destroyed
before this comes to an end?
It's not…
over yet.
We have to catch him.
After that,
I'll think about what comes next.
I was relieved.
When I learned
that you weren't the Paik Sa-eon
I thought you were.
I'm in.
How many?
Park Do-jae said he planted spy chips
and tracking devices
in all the mobile devices
and transportation the guy uses.
Out of the three, two are inactive,
but one is still active.
Check the GPS and pinpoint
the exact location, quickly.
I heard Sa-eon caught the accomplice.
What about the culprit?
We found out
who the culprit is.
Who is it?
I knew it.
You're not surprised at all.
But then, I guess you already knew.
Nothing gets by you
in this family, Father.
Just finish what you were saying.
Who's the culprit?
Before I tell you,
I have to ask you something.
The reason you covered up
our car accident.
What deal did you make
with Chairman Paik Jang-ho?
The bastard who ran my kids over.
I chased him to the Philippines
and got him to confess
just before I was about to take his life.
So don't try to deny it.
Have you calculated it thoroughly?
After you shoot me,
what will you have left?
You invested tens of billions of won
in my presidential campaign.
You already lost your son.
And if you shoot me,
you'll also lose the money.
Are you okay with that?
You know me well.
You know I'm someone who's more sensitive
to losses than to gains.
Would it be a little better
if the losses weren't all on you?
By now,
they should be walking side by side.
What does that mean?
On the road to the afterlife.
Your son and my grandson.
How's that?
Is it starting to add up now?
Tell us now.
What did you throw away?
And what did you gain?
Hurry and come to the memorial service.
I've got a bad feeling.
Mr. Hong.
What do you think you're doing?
YUNHWA-RI
We got it.
He's near Yunhwa-ri, Sanseong-myeon.
We got the bastard.
- Head out.
- Yes, sir.
Didn't I warn you?
That if that thing in your family
was still alive,
I'd chop it up from head to toe
and scatter the pieces.
Give him to me.
Where is he?
Guards!
It's a fire! Evacuate!
Dad!
We have to go!
It's a fire!
- Yes, Detective Kang.
- We got his location.
We're on our way
to Yunhwa-ri 24, Sanseong-myeon.
Where?
Are you okay?
I can't find Hee-joo! We were together.
I'll find her.
Hee-joo!
UNKNOWN CALLER
Paik Sa-eon.
I'll kill her.
I'm really going to kill her.
Your wife.
I know now
for sure
what you cherish most in the world.
Hee-joo.
Answer him, Sis.
Your husband's calling.
Paik Sa-eon!
If you lay a finger on her,
I'll kill you.
Let her go now.
I'm the one you want.
Don't mess with anyone else.
Settle this with me.
Don't get worked up.
I get excited when you get worked up.
Your turn will come soon,
so don't make a fuss and just wait.
You're far from being ruined.
Paik Jang-ho's grandson
being successful
and perfectly fine, just like you,
that's exactly what that old man wanted.
I can't let that happen.
I'll make him rise up from his grave!
This is just a little taste.
You don't know what real pain is yet.
I really want you to suffer properly.
Why?
Because…
Help!
Help me!
Because you just watched me
dying in pain.
So I'm going to watch too.
I'll watch you struggle,
begging for your life,
on the verge of choking.
You should experience
that kind of torment for once.
That once pleasant scent from your body
will turn into the pungent smell of blood.
I'll make you suffer.
UNKNOWN CALLER
Hee-joo, don't worry.
I'm coming.
- I'm coming right now.
- Don't come.
I told you.
For once,
I want to protect you.
Just remember this.
I love you…
so very much.
Hee-joo.
I love you.
You crazy bitch! Again with that?
Do you remember?
Once you start,
you see it through to the end.
That's what you said.
Since I started it,
I'm going to end it.
I'll make sure
you never make him suffer again!
Hee-joo…
Hee-joo!
The accident vehicle has been lifted,
and the search team is using boats
to search the surrounding area.
A vehicle that fell into the upper stream
of the Cheonghan River
this morning has been found.
The impact of the crash was so severe
that the guardrail
was completely torn off.
The rescue team found the vehicle
at a depth of about 20 meters,
but the passengers
have not been found yet.
According to the police investigation,
this vehicle that crashed into the river
was being driven by…
Paik Sa-eon's wife after being abducted.
This news has left many in shock.
The police have released
a composite sketch of the suspect
and issued an emergency wanted notice.
In relation to this, Spokesperson Paik
will hold a press conference
to announce his position.
- There he is.
Hurry! Take photos of him.
That's enough! Please!
This isn't a scandal. It's an incident!
A criminal case!
First, I have something to say
to the people.
For a long time,
I've kept something hidden.
I am…
not the son of Presidential Candidate…
Paik Ui-yong.
I am not the grandson…
of Chairman Paik Jang-ho.
Both the name Paik Sa-eon
and my identity as Paik Ui-yong's son
are all fake.
SPOKESPERSON PAIK,
"I'M NOT PAIK SA-EON…"
It does not belong to me.
If there is one thing
I can say truthfully about myself,
it's that…
I'm married, and I have a wife.
My wife was kidnapped
on the 20th, two days ago,
by the person who had been threatening
to kill me.
Investigations and searches are ongoing,
but my wife's whereabouts
have not yet been determined.
In relation to this, I stand before you
not as Spokesperson Paik Sa-eon
but as…
a husband,
to humbly request
your cooperation and help.
My wife's name is…
Hong Hee-joo.
She's 28 years old, 167cm tall…
That's Hong…
Did you not know either?
At the time of her disappearance,
she was wearing a black suit
and black shoes
and had long, straight hair.
And she's the sign language interpreter
of the Presidential Office.
I look forward
to working with you as well.
Is there something you want to do?
Well…
There is.
Things that I never imagined
we could do together.
I know it's ridiculous,
but I imagined it sometimes.
Us being…
completely ordinary
just like everyone else.
There's a lot I haven't done for her.
Let's be happy together.
I haven't made her happy yet.
Once all of this is over…
I'll propose to you.
If I had known I wouldn't get the chance,
I would've just given her everything.
SPOKESPERSON PAIK
DEVASTATED BY HIS WIFE'S ABDUCTION
Hee-joo…
Please.
If anyone has seen my wife,
please report it now.
Please, I ask for your attention and help
so that my wife can return safely.
WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
Why was I born?
I always thought about it.
If I have to live someone else's life
against my will,
why was I born?
But I think I found the answer.
To why I was born
and why I had to live as Paik Sa-eon.
It was…
to meet you.
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce