GLORY
PUNISHMENTS OF THE LAW ON MINORS
I used to think about something.
You have reached your destination. End of listing.
When I ask you something, answer me, bastard!
How dare you be insolent?
What should someone, anyone, give me
trying to help?
Hell!
Where are you going?!
You think someone will help you
if you run away from there?
Let's wrap it all up today!
Stop beating her!
Stop it! I'll fucking kill you!
Sun, don't. Don't!
Mom will take care of everything.
- Don't.
- No!
I will kill him! I have to, mom!
I'm a minor, I'll be fine.
- Move away, mom.
- Don't, please!
Don't!
If I have to, I will. Don't you, Sun!
Sun!
You bastards are crazy.
You're quite a role model, aren't you?
You are a fantastic role model!
You need to be beaten again! Fuck it!
Are you going to stab me with that?
Is it? Come on!
Stab me! Stupid stupid! Hell!
You're both out of your mind.
Good. Let's end it all today.
Let's go. Can you?
Where are you going to stab me?
Maybe a friend or some god.
Don't touch Sun-au.
I will kill you.
Maybe even time.
Or a sharp weapon.
Let's all die then, you fucking bastard!
I'M LOOKING FOR AN OLDER WOMAN AS AN ASSISTANT
CALL ME
SEOUL JOO GENERAL HOSPITAL
You have a total of 12 stitches.
I will prescribe you antibiotics.
Do not drink or smoke.
I'm a high school student.
Exactly. Don't.
Bandage the wound every three days.
Yeo-jeong, the professor comes to visit.
Good.
Mrs. Kim.
Can I have a sip?
- You mean coffee?
- No.
Do not let it near the vending machine.
Good.
A full stomach gives the body strength!
LEE SE-DOL - ALPHAGO 3
FIVE YEARS LATER
Who is Lee Se-dol?
Thank you for teaching me.
You will be a great doctor.
This is the last hour?
Why?
We must continue. You didn't beat me.
I don't want to beat you.
I have to go. I have extra hours.
Do you want to buy a house?
I don't earn enough for that.
Yes, houses are given away.
anyway,
how can you just leave
after spending so much time together?
Can you at least tell me where you're going?
I understand.
You're rushing somewhere at full speed, even now.
But I don't know where.
just so you know
I would also like to leave somehow,
but I get lost easily.
Your mother is the principal
at Seoul Joo Hospital, right?
You have reached your destination.
From the moment you were born
they must have told you
that you have reached your destination.
And so countless times.
I watch the forecast channel in the morning.
Some winters are warmer than normal.
Dense fog appears
when a warm winter is followed by a cold wave.
Since they are warm,
people don't realize how cold it is.
Their life is peaceful and happy.
CAFE GYODAE
Where will we meet? Let me know the location.
LEE SEOK-JAE
The basic information is on the back of the photos.
There is also other information.
I want new information.
And about director Kim Shin-tae.
Good.
You can pay me the minimum
for eight hours of work.
As well as transportation, food and other expenses.
Good.
We will not always work according to the law.
My work has to be a priority.
Good.
It will last a long time,
but no one's hands will be bloody.
Good.
Do you drive?
I can't drive.
Learn.
Good.
What grade is your daughter in?
She won't cause you any trouble.
She's grown up, she takes care of herself.
You don't have to worry...
Send her by train on weekends
to the station in Seoul for two hours.
I will teach her.
You can also pay me the minimum.
Thank you, ma'am.
I will bring you good news.
DRIVING SCHOOL
HOUR IN PROGRESS
Excuse me!
Turn off the turn signal
and drive straight.
SEMYEONG
MATHEMATICS FOR SECONDARY SCHOOL
How far did we go last time?
Isn't it illegal
teach kids for money?
It is.
But I don't follow too many laws.
DRIVER'S LICENSE
God!
For God's sake!
Do you know how to use a camera?
This square is called the SD card.
I'll give you more.
He's going here.
It has to click. And you can take photos.
To extract press here and it will pop up.
If you leave it in the locker, I'll pick it up.
Do you understand?
And what about the photos?
They are here.
Try it.
I have so much to learn.
I think it's going to crack.
Yes, if you put it like that, it will crack.
The gold part must be down.
Good.
I don't see anything.
Yeon-jin, sometimes I wonder something.
Solidarity among victims
and among the perpetrators.
Which one of them is stronger?
My soul sings to You, Savior
Sings how big you are
When I pass through the forest...
Photos are still bad.
I'm sorry.
But I think you will recognize her.
DUGA EYE CLINIC
DR. GLASSES (LENSES
SHOP WITH LENSES
FOR DISEASES OF THE CORNEA AND DOLTONISM
Repeat that.
You were babbling about it. Why are you silent?
What did you say about my eyes?
What about my eyes, cunt?!
What color is this?
Now try to answer me!
He fainted. Stop it.
Supčino.
I may not see colors, but I'm not blind.
I know he's unconscious!
It seems you couldn't become
good wife.
At least you try to hide it.
- I told her she shouldn't because it's dangerous.
- It's okay.
Whoa, Ye-sol! You've grown so much.
I too will be a forecaster when I grow up.
You listened to Ha Ye-sol and the forecast.
Mom, these shoes are green, aren't they?
They are actually red.
Ha Ye-sol, look at me.
The color of the shoes is not important.
The important thing is that they are expensive
and that they are difficult to obtain.
And it is even more important
that you can have them all, no matter how many there are.
All prices are written in numbers,
and not colors.
Do you understand?
I shouldn't tell dad about that?
Mr. Jeon!
This is the owner.
Look at him! How long have we not seen each other?
- Hello!
- Hi.
Miss.
Beautiful as always.
If you called me,
I would roll out the red carpet.
Yes, exactly.
When I was in Spain,
we were neighbors.
This is my friend.
I recommend it for membership.
Think about it.
Don't dramatize
Do you need to think?
when is membership purchased?
How was today?
Our club has the best pitches in Korea.
When people try them once,
they always come back.
When you exercise, everywhere is wonderful.
Dumplings are delicious.
It's hard to get in here.
You need to apply
at least four referrals from active members.
It has all the prerequisites for membership.
Her son is the director of Jaepyong Construction.
I will definitely look into your application.
I have to go now.
- I'll call you.
- Good.
I will not be accepting new members.
Reject her application.
Hell!
Pull the dumplings from the restaurant.
Throw them in the fucking trash.
Good, sir.
GO CLUB PAGODA
Park, leave the keys and go home.
It's Friday.
Thanks.
Mr. Choi is already here.
I secured the building rights
in Jeongbok-dong.
And I made a deal with the city
to open the square for go
as soon as the arrangement is completed.
The job was overdue
since we changed contractors.
That was good.
Great.
Young people today are not interested in it.
You don't see that often.
Park, the owner of the bakery,
he lost two games to her.
Seething with rage.
The stake is 20,000 won per game.
Seriously?
Remove that group first.
It won't save you.
Surrender and you lose by ten points.
She fixed it.
Impressive.
- He lost 20,000?
- Did you see that?
- Boom!
- She's good.
AIRPORT LINE
I'm in Seoul.
I'm free tomorrow. Entertain me.
Oops, wrong number.
It's not normal!
You thought I was Jae-jun?
Damn, you're so funny!
Come on, open more!
You got a good one this time.
The iPad is in the back.
Can you ride in Jae-jun's car?
You can definitely buy girls with it.
The work would not be bearable
without such privilege.
Six-nine.
Six-nine-six-nine.
That's the code!
- A beautiful series of numbers.
- You're disgusting.
He is divorced.
It has a bunch of buildings, land and whatnot.
There are even horses in Jeju.
I thought it was stupid, but great!
Can you investigate his ex?
Her looks, school, family, anything.
For 300,000 won? How much will you need?
Why the rush?
I'll do it for 450,000. I'm busy.
He's taking me to Jeju next week.
I have to decide if I want to sleep with him.
Of course! Be careful not to crash.
I have to watch out. I almost said "whore".
Jesus. I don't even want to insult you.
Do you know what the only place is
which has class grades?
Aircraft.
First class, business and economic.
Only a curtain separates them,
but no one is allowed to cross it.
What are you blabbing about?
I'm telling you to stay behind the curtain
because you earn barely enough
to feed yourself.
I will cross the curtain.
Stop Jae-jun's car.
That's interesting?
The game was already decided,
but she decided to stretch it.
Why?
Who?
In the go club.
What was it?
I'm going to sleep and then I'm going to work.
It gives me a headache. Not you?
It is neat, fun and pleasing to the eye.
Why do you smoke? That's not healthy.
You're right.
Why did you marry a smoker when you don't smoke?
You're neat, if we ignore the smoking.
You are fun and pleasing to the eye.
And that's why I like you!
You have the answer to everything.
But you went on three blind dates,
including the one with me.
Why did you take me?
You wore the least amount of clothes.
You wore the least amount of clothes,
but clothes from Dior.
How crazy you are!
You are gentle, but sometimes you can be cruel.
If you're coming, hurry up.
I will wear very few clothes to bed.
In five minutes.
Am I dreaming?
Are you talking to me?
I sorted myself out.
Give me 10 min.
Did you pass the teacher's exam?
- I did.
- Did you?
Congratulations.
Maybe I'm late.
Thanks.
I am going to Semyeong for an academic conference.
are you ok
I am.
I heard you were a medic in the army.
I got out of the army a long time ago.
Where did you hear that?
From the old men in the park.
A young unemployed man joined the army
and came back a new man.
Were you in the park?
Should I have written you a letter?
Are paramedics allowed to receive letters?
- We get love.
- Did you get a lot of them?
FOR JOO YEO-JEONG
FROM CHEONGSONG PRISON
I don't like letters.
What brings you to Semyeong?
Do you work there?
Not yet.
I went there on business.
Is he with you?
He's been staring for a while.
I have to go.
Me too.
Just so you know...
then,
when we started playing go in the park,
it was the coldest period of my life.
But the hours with you...
they were my only constant
and the only companionship.
If I seemed warm,
you are responsible for that.
It was eating me up.
I work here.
If you are interested.
Have a good trip.
SEOUL JOO GENERAL HOSPITAL
JOO YEO-JEONG, PLASTIC SURGEON
Excuse me.
Don't you live here?
You are in apartment 301, right?
I am the owner.
Good evening.
I'm asking if you live here.
Your electricity and water bills
they are always low.
I pay my rent on time.
I know that.
But you said you wanted an apartment so badly,
and now it has been empty for months.
I'm interested in what's going on.
I haven't gotten a job in Semyeong yet.
I'm trying.
I know we shouldn't meet,
but I have a recording.
I will sit in the car.
You should have entered from the other side.
Sorry, I'll write it down for another time.
I enlarged the picture,
so the quality is not the best.
You have to watch closely.
Good.
Here, look! Here!
"Director,
why don't you sit in the front today?”
I don't get it.
"Love, you sit in the front today."
The driver is Jo Soo-hyeon?
How do you know?
It wasn't a woman.
He was on medication for erectile dysfunction.
Gender does not play a role in this
as long as it can last.
We should have focused on age.
You are serious at odd times!
What is it?
You thought I couldn't laugh
because he always beats me?
He may be beating me, but I'm happy.
Lord!
You should have told me that sooner.
- What is that?
- That you are happy.
I don't want to laugh.
Why not?
I'm afraid I will for laughs
forget what I should be doing.
I didn't remember that.
I'll be careful.
Maybe that's why he's beating me.
Don't do that!
I really like the way I am now.
I'm happy, but I don't have a chance to be happy.
Now that I've breathed, I always smile.
Don't worry, I won't drag you down.
Let's try now!
How come she and I... No.
How come we have to try?
Labor is extremely tiring.
I'm tired of trying, Yeon-jin.
Here you go.
How are you, Mr. Kim?
It's me, Dong-eun.
Who?
Sunghan High School.
I graduated in 2004.
You don't remember me?
What is your name?
Soo-hane! Hi!
Where did you come from?
Dong-eun, what are you doing here?
This is my house. This is my father.
Seriously?
How small the world is.
I was your father's student.
Do you remember me now?
Well, of course.
Mr. Kim, I'm a teacher now too.
What did you say?
about my son?
Do it again! What did you say?
Why are we here?
You should have come to Siesta.
This building was abandoned
when we were at school.
She is still like this.
Enough chit chat.
You want revenge, don't you?
That's right.
Look at her. You're not scared.
You left me out?
I can't take revenge on you. You have nothing.
Others may lose something,
but you have nothing at all.
Are you saying that to my face?
I can push you out of here.
Better watch out.
I know.
I stood here once.
Because you mistreated me.
Are you threatening me?
- At least you can be scared.
- You're asking for trouble.
- Remember So-hee?
-What?
It was said that she killed herself
when she went to a new school.
You must remember her.
Before you said, “Here comes Dong-eun,”
you must have been saying, "Here comes So-hee."
This is where So-hee fell.
But she didn't kill herself.
What the hell? I didn't do it!
I didn't kill her!
I know.
Take the money from the person who killed her.
That's my information.
Who did it?
I told you. My work is a priority.
They were not easy to find.
Everything is full of dog hair.
Ten to the root, right?
Wait.
Are you...
You gave birth to Jae-jun's child?
Only if you are too.
I'll call you when I confirm.
I didn't leave you out.
You can lose something too.
Just one.
My life.
In hand! She says the back of her hand hurts.
Sa-ra, wake up!
You have to clean up and go to the exhibition.
It's too bright.
Are you an angel?
Come on, get up.
You have a special exhibition today.
If you really have to smoke something,
take something weaker.
There are also thinner cigarettes.
Is there such a thing for drugs?
LEE SA-RE SPECIAL EXHIBITION
OBSERVATION OF THE IDEAL IN A SLEEP
I want one.
Send her to the club.
You have to pay for shipping, dear customer.
The rich are greedy.
It will all come back to me after taxes.
I'm actually doing a good deed.
That's how it goes with income tax.
You wouldn't know that
because you don't earn enough.
Sa-ra?
Hide the drink.
- Wife of Director Jang from Buil.
- I'm glad!
The pictures are beautiful.
How God gifted the artist Lee
such a lavish gift?
Amen.
She bought three paintings.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- This way.
- Good.
We need your address.
Shall we send them to your home?
Why are you so normal, artist Lee?
Next month I will receive an award.
Will you come so I don't embarrass myself?
And you, artist Lee.
Fuck it, stop it.
What prize will you get?
CEREMONY FOR GRADUATES
It hasn't changed at all.
I haven't been here since graduation.
Seriously? You haven't seen the physical education teacher?
Hye-jeong left him. He was crying.
- You haven't been to Korea?
- I didn't.
In Paris, I watched Lovers in Paris.
It took me three days to download the episode.
So much fun.
Why isn't the jerk answering?
I need something.
Myeong-oh?
He still doesn't answer today?
I need something too! Do you know anything about it?
He's probably drunk and asleep.
I have to fire that monkey.
Long time no see.
are you ok
I've seen her somewhere before.
17 years have passed
since when were all six of us together?
Five. Myeong-o is not here.
I know! Moon So-hee, right?
You always mix up names.
Moon Dong-eun and Yoon So-hee.
I heard that she worked in a factory.
What are you doing here?
You didn't graduate.
Sorry, my fond memories are hazy.
Good to see you, So-hee.
Dong-eun.
I come to this hall every so often.
But today, all the friendly faces are here.
How are you, Yeon-jin?
I love your forecasts.
On TV, you seem like a really good person.
And you?
how are you
I got a new job, so I'm working a lot.
I bought new clothes
and ate expensive sashimi.
You are the chief director of schools in Semyeong?
Congratulations.
Who are you?
Did you dig through my trash?
I had no choice.
Is your driver Jo Soo-hyeon?
Do your son and future daughter-in-law know
that they will share the inheritance
with Jo Soo-hyeon?
Are you threatening me?
Sorry.
What I am looking for is very simple.
I want to be a 1-2 class teacher
at Semyeong Elementary School.
I am qualified.
I live in Semyeong.
I quit my job at my current school.
Are you a teacher?
I am.
May I start working?
when does the new semester start?
SEMYEONG PRIMARY SCHOOL
HA YE-SOL
We will start awarding prizes immediately.
This is an award for Park Yeon-jin,
23rd class graduate.
CEREMONY FOR GRADUATES
From now on, your days will be a nightmare.
It will be provocative and frightening.
You can't stop me or remove me.
I intend to become
your very old rumor, Yeon-jin.
That, Yeon-jin!
Bravo!
You're fantastic, Yeon-jin!
End of episode 3