(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
[Tangjing]
The New Policies of Empress Dowager Xiuli.
From today on,
Biantang abolishes slavery.
The slave trade is hereby prohibited.
Yuequn Academy
is a martial arts academy for women
founded by Empress Dowager Xiuli.
It aims to provide
freed female slaves with the chance
to learn martial arts
and practical skills,
so they may have a craft to rely on.
Those who wish to learn martial arts,
please line up
at the 1st registration point.
Those who wish to learn music or tea arts,
please register at the 2nd
and 3rd points respectively.
Everyone is welcome to sign up.
I'm so tempted.
That's great.
I'll sign up!
I'll sign up too!
Hurry, I'll go too!
Count me in!
These are all memorials opposing
the abolition of slavery.
Several court princes
and vassal princes from outside
are submitting memorials
several times a day.
They are this close
to coming to the palace to make a scene.
Don't worry.
With you and Song Cheng protecting me,
they wouldn't dare.
We've hurt their interests,
so naturally they need a place
to vent their anger.
Before, I only thought
Biantang was prosperous
and its people lived in peace,
making it different from Great Yong.
I didn't expect
that this decree abolishing slavery
would expose so many acts of oppression.
Biantang
is just like this dress I'm wearing.
It looks exquisite,
but every piece of silk and thread,
every pattern and embroidery on it,
was sewn by the female slaves
in the weaving workshop.
Look at the former Crown Prince's Mansion.
It looked glamorous,
but weren't all those maids and concubines
just slaves carefully crafted
by their masters?
If their masters were unhappy,
they would still be beaten,
killed, or sold.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 24]
Flowers!
Buy a bouquet!
Go away.
Go sell them somewhere else.
No one wants your flowers here.
Wait.
Flowers!
Please, buy one.
These flowers are beautiful.
Miss,
I want a bouquet.
How much?
Linlang?
My skills are inferior.
Just kill me.
Who sent you?
No one.
I hate you so much
and want to kill you.
Why?
You killed Zhan Ziyu,
leaving my sisters and me nowhere to go.
We've been orphans since childhood.
If Zhan Ziyu hadn't bought us
and placed us
in the Crown Prince's Mansion,
we wouldn't have had a good life.
Now we have nowhere to go.
As we grow older,
we will soon lose our youth
and beauty,
and won't be able to marry again.
This is all because of you!
How was it?
Did you succeed?
I came here today
not to kill,
but to recruit workers.
Recruit?
What kind of work?
We opened a Yuequn Academy in Tangjing.
It aims to teach women martial arts,
tea arts, and other livelihood skills.
I know your abilities.
If you're willing,
you can be female teachers
at Yuequn Academy.
From then on, even without relying on men,
you can be self-reliant.
Female teachers? My foot!
Bah!
You must be tricking us
into working for free.
I'm not going to teach any skills.
We've been slaves since childhood,
learning only how to serve men
with our looks.
What do you know?
Only by relying on our looks
can we live a good life.
You can rely on your youth and beauty now.
But what about when you get old?
How many years
can you keep living in luxury?
That's why we need to find a rich husband
as soon as possible
while we are still young.
And it's best to have a child or two.
This way,
we'll have long-term support.
She's right.
Everyone has their own ambitions.
We just want to marry rich men,
even if it's just as concubines.
You always claim
that you respect what women want,
so why not respect our wishes?
Since I have ruined your lives,
I will arrange suitable husbands for you.
Here are the noblemen in Tangjing
who are of marriageable age,
in their prime, and seeking wives
or concubines.
I'm not asking for someone
incredibly handsome,
but they shouldn't look so ugly.
Are you fooling us on purpose?
Are you fooling us?
There are 930 noblemen in the capital.
Excluding those with obvious disabilities,
wife-beaters, alcoholics, and gamblers,
the remaining are these 35 men.
If any of them catches your eye,
I will arrange a meeting for you
immediately.
Actually,
we don't necessarily have to get married.
Right.
Sisters,
we women can only find a way out—
By relying on ourselves!
Are you really not going to
take another look and choose?
Thank you for your kindness, Your Majesty.
We will go to Yuequn Academy tomorrow
to find a job.
Sisters, let's go!
Wait.
This is the deed
to the restaurant Li Ce bought.
He couldn't bear to see women suffer.
If you can run this restaurant well,
it would be considered
fulfilling his wish.
It's mine!
Move! Hurry!
Move faster!
Stand up!
Young Master,
I've found out.
They say too many people died
mining black gold.
Now the civilians
inside and outside the city
are all being captured as slaves.
If a household fails to hand someone over,
they will all be taken away directly.
Stop!
Hurry up.
Queen of Lingyue?
I heard you've made a great contribution
to His Majesty recently.
Are you here to receive a reward today?
I was being presumptuous.
The black gold mine you are in charge of
has always made His Majesty worry.
I heard you haven't mined much gold,
but a lot of people have died.
Hurry up. His Majesty is waiting.
Your Majesty.
The mining of black gold
hasn't stopped day and night.
I have drafted more laborers,
but the weather in the mountains
is too cold,
and many horses have frozen to death.
That's why we haven't been able
to meet the schedule.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
If there's not enough horses,
why not use slaves?
One horse can be exchanged for 15 slaves.
The slaves in Ximeng will never die out.
If you can't bear to do it,
you can have your clansmen mine for them.
If I remember correctly,
when I conquered the Lingyue stronghold,
there were thousands of people.
Your Majesty!
The people of the Lingyue Clan
are innocent!
In the previous trip to Biantang,
you lost my entire Ximeng delegation.
You said you killed Zhuge Yue,
but you didn't bring back his body.
I let you make amends for your mistakes
by mining black gold,
but you kept missing the deadlines.
In my opinion,
you've long forgotten
your King.
[King of Lingyue]
Don't rush.
There are more here.
The King of Lingyue betrayed his people.
He deserves to die!
Your Majesty, why don't you just kill him?
Do you really want him to die?
He betrayed his clan.
He deserves it!
The neighboring Xiyi Tribe
has been occupied by King Ximeng.
Chief Xiyi was hanged
for refusing to surrender,
and the Xiyi people were wiped out.
Stay here
and wait for me to come back.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the tribes to the east
for help.
Ximeng has taken Xiyi.
We're next.
We share life and death,
and we live and die with the Lingyue Clan.
Wait for me.
I will bring reinforcements back
to save you
and the whole Lingyue Clan.
There is a waterway
30 miles east of Mount Wumu.
When we used to hunt,
we often passed by there.
If you set off from there,
a round trip will only take 3 days.
On the morning of the 4th day,
when the sun rises,
I will wait for you
at the top of Mount Wumu.
Here is a pair of green-eyed birds.
One for each of us.
I hope they can bless us
to get through this hardship.
I'll be waiting for you.
On the 4th day,
when the sun rises,
I will definitely be back.
Hurry up!
Keep up!
Be careful. Don't fall.
Hurry! They're coming!
Wait for me!
Protect the Queen!
Your Highness!
Ximeng is bypassing our defense line
and attacking from the back mountain.
The stronghold!
We can't hold the stronghold!
Why?
How did they know that path?
Your Highness.
It's... It's His Majesty.
His Majesty surrendered to King Ximeng.
He told King Ximeng about our defense.
What did you say? Who?
Impossible!
Impossible! Impossible!
His Majesty
went to the east for reinforcements.
It's only the 3rd day.
He will definitely be back on the 4th day.
This is impossible.
Impossible!
I know how cruel you are.
You can do whatever you want with me.
But I will never surrender to you.
I heard long ago
about the same-clan marriage system
in Lingyue.
The Kings and Queens of Lingyue
are from the same clan and are married.
They live together from childhood
and rule the tribe together
after they grow up.
But why do you look
so much stupider than the King of Lingyue?
He knows what
is best for his people.
He used the defense map to trade
for a way out for his people.
And by doing this,
do you want to ruin
his painstaking efforts with your own hands?
He made his own choice!
I made mine!
Good. You have backbone.
No!
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Your Highness, please save my child!
Please, Your Highness!
Save the child, Your Highness!
Your Highness, please save...
Mother!
Alright!
I agreed!
If you let them go,
I am willing to surrender to you.
Your voice is too soft.
I can't hear you.
Kneel!
Louder!
I promise you...
that if you are willing to let them go,
I will submit to you.
If he dies,
your people will think
that it was you who betrayed them.
And you will bear this crime
and live in humiliation.
My reputation
hasn't mattered for a long time.
As long as they can stay alive.
As long as it can appease your anger!
Not necessarily.
You promised me
that you would keep
the Lingyue Clan alive.
Whether your people can live
and how long they can live,
the key...
lies in you.
I know.
Many people died mining the black gold.
The people of Ximeng
have begun to resent me.
But as you know,
this is just the beginning.
To continue mining the black gold,
I need more slaves!
No,
citizens.
For Ximeng
and the black gold mine,
I have to let you
make some sacrifices.
Zhuge Yue,
I'm sorry.
Zhuge Yue!
Zhuge Yue,
where did you go?
Zhuge Yue!
Zhuge Yue
is dead.
No!
Zhuge Yue!
If Xiao Ran is quiet,
he must be up to something.
5,
15,
22,
23.
It's been 23 days.
Why is there still no news?
Logically, a round trip from Biantang
to Ximeng by fast horse
should only take
a little over half a month.
If everything goes smoothly,
he should have finished this trip
and be sitting in front of me
a long time ago.
No, there must have been an accident.
You messed up my counting herbs!
Counting what?
How many days has it been
since you last killed a patient,
or since you last developed
a lethal poison?
Such a medicine pot.
Boring.
Fang Miaomiao!
What?
I have a
super big problem
that I need your help with.
Super big?
What problem do you need my help with?
If the turtle shell faces up, I'll tell.
If it faces down, I won't.
It says to tell.
No, no. Best two out of three.
What exactly do you want to say?
I want to say...
Zhuge Yue is dying.
Zhuge Yue is dying?
What did you say?
[Tangjing]
This is the military tally
of the Xiuli Army.
The other half is with He Xiao.
When the two halves are put together,
you can mobilize the entire Xiuli Army.
I will bear your instructions in mind,
Your Majesty.
The Emperor is still young.
Many important matters in the court
will have to rely on you, Grand Secretary Liu
and General Sun.
If there's an emergency,
you can have Fang Miaomiao
go to Ximeng and send me a message.
-Yes, Your Majesty.
He Xiao.
Yes.
You and the Xiuli Army will stay here.
From now on,
Biantang is your home.
And the Xiuli Army is Biantang's army.
But if Grand Secretary Liu and General Sun
become dictatorial
and abuse their power,
you must help me keep an eye on them.
Your Majesty,
you'd better say that behind our backs.
Otherwise, we'll feel very awkward.
From now on,
I'll be counting on you two.
Stone her! Beat her!
Step back!
It's all her fault! She spread rumors,
forcing King Ximeng to mine gold
and capture slaves everywhere.
[Meng En, General of Ximeng]
Damn witch!
She offered schemes to King Ximeng,
causing the deaths of countless people!
Not only that!
Step back!
She even betrayed her own Lingyue Clan!
She deserves this today!
It's all because of you!
Beat her to death! Witch!
Beat this witch!
Bad people get what they deserve!
Karma! Karma!
Witch!
Witch! Beat her to death!
Go to hell!
Die, witch!
Stone her to death!
Witch! Witch!
She deserves it! Beat her to death!
You caused all this!
Witch!
Spreading rumors!
Beat her to death!
Get lost!
Damn witch!
This witch!
Witch!
Beat her! Witch!
Beat her to death!
She deserves it!
Witch! Serves you right!
Witch!
Heinous crimes!
Die a horrible death!
It's all karma!
Get out of the way!
I'll beat you to death!
Get lost!
Get up!
Serves you right!
Murder!
Let's go!
Oh no! The prisoner is gone!
She couldn't have gone far.
After her!
Yes!
Let's go!
I didn't expect Wang Shi'er's trick
to work.
I can't walk anymore.
You go first. Don't worry about me.
The horse is just ahead.
Come on!
Let's go!
Hurry!
Keep yourself safe.
She can't get far!
-After her!
-Let's go!
Stop!
Whether your people can live
and how long they can live,
the key...
lies in you.
You witch!
I'll kill you!
Witch!
This dagger...
was for you to protect yourself.
Who asked you to save me?
You took me,
and King Ximeng
will take his anger out on my clansmen.
I can't let them suffer for me!
Do you think you can protect them
by dying?
King Ximeng promised me
that as long as I took the blame
for mining the gold
and killing the slaves,
he would spare the Lingyue Clan.
When you agreed to surrender to him,
he also promised
to spare the Lingyue Clan.
But what actually happened?
I had no choice.
You can only protect them
if you are alive.
If you die,
they will end up buried
in the dark mines.
I didn't come here just to save you.
If you insist on dying,
I can't stop you.
Saving you today
is repaying you for your past kindness.
I will bring news of your death to Baze.
Baze?
Baze is still alive?
He traveled thousands of miles
to Tangjing to ask for my help.
He should have recovered by now.
Everyone thinks
I betrayed the Lingyue Clan.
Both the Lingyue Clan and King Ximeng
want me dead.
Great Yong and the Zhuge Clan
also think I am a traitor.
I will forever bear the shame
of betraying Qingshan Manor.
Actually, the one
who betrayed the Lingyue Clan
was King of Lingyue.
He secretly defected to King Ximeng,
causing the Lingyue Clan to be defeated.
We used to be deeply in love,
but when he betrayed our clansmen...
Zhuge Yue?
Is it the Blood on Snow acting up?
Zhuge Yue!
Come.
Let's get up first
and get out of here now.
Zhuge Yue!
Get up!
Don't!
Give it to me!
Zhuge Yue,
no.
Zhuge Yue!
This sword was for me to protect myself,
not to hurt you!
Give me some more time!
I will find the antidote!
Stop.
Go.
You, come here.
What would you like?
This one. And this one.
Alright.
Here you go.
How did you find this place?
You don't need to be nervous.
I didn't bring anyone with me.
Remember when we attacked
the Beiyu people?
I was injured, and you saved me
and brought me here.
Although I was unconscious at the time,
I vaguely remember some things.
You're not here to catch me?
You saved my life,
so I am returning the favor.
Go back with me now
and hand the person in that room
over to King Ximeng.
I will back you up and say
that this was a trap you set
to lure out Zhuge Yue.
He saved my life too.
I can't do this.
What about your clansmen?
For someone from Great Yong,
are you going to sacrifice
the entire Lingyue Clan?
Have you fallen in love with him?
What nonsense are you talking about?
The blood dove landed here.
It should be in the woods.
This is a Lingyue wood carving.
It must be here.
What are you doing?
Stop it!
If you keep fighting,
he will die for sure.
She is performing bloodletting on him.
Baze, let's go.
How is he now?
Thank you for your blood dove.
We attacked you earlier
because we misunderstood you.
Although this courtyard
is in a wild forest,
it is fully equipped.
The hunting knives and bows in the room
are also in pairs.
I just saw
the green-eyed birds
of the Lingyue Clan carved on them.
This should be the place
where you and King of Lingyue
used to rest when hunting.
If you have time to notice these,
you'd better figure out
how to save your man first.
Is that wandering doctor actually capable?
Can he really save Zhuge Yue?
You should know better than I do
that the poison of Blood on Snow
is incurable.
Unless
we get the antidote from King Ximeng.
Then there's nothing we can do.
There is a clearing behind this forest.
If you don't mind,
it can be his burial place.
Don't you want to save King of Lingyue?
I know that
he's locked in the dungeon
of King Ximeng's Palace.
I also know that
he was also poisoned by the Blood on Snow.
What do you want?
I want to know King Ximeng's weakness.
I'm sure you know how to help me.
If you want to stay here,
keep your mouth shut.
If you interfere any further,
I'll exchange your man's body
for the antidote to Blood on Snow.
Congratulations.
You will become King Ximeng's women.
Always and forever,
I
will stand by your side, Your Majesty.
No one leaves here alive tonight!
We are exposed!
Don't run!
Where is Chu Qiao?
Zhuge Yue?
All of this
is over.