(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
ظآزWandering aloneظآز
ظآزWalking far by dusk-lit streetsظآز
ظآزYour eyes are as cold as cloudsظآز
ظآزFaintly coming into viewظآز
ظآزThe city lightsظآز
ظآزLit up that single momentظآز
ظآزI can't hide or stop missing youظآز
ظآزI can't forget those momentsظآز
ظآزLosing youظآز
ظآزLike the seasons in my memoryظآز
ظآزWithout winterظآز
ظآزWalking down the long, dark streetظآز
ظآزSnow will never fall againظآز
ظآزOur old story was tornظآز
ظآزInto scattered piecesظآز
ظآزReplaying every single sceneظآز
ظآزAfter you leftظآز
ظآزAs if our documentaryظآز
ظآزLost winterظآز
ظآزThe breeze speaks of good timesظآز
ظآزPure white devotionظآز
ظآزSend out a letterظآز
ظآزCarrying my longingظآز
=The Double Game=
=Episode 3=
That's not true.
His abs are seriously solid.
Look.
Settle down, Xiao Ting.
Don't wreck our jobs too.
This one's pretty shy.
- Your friends are fun.
- Have a seat.
- It's my birthday.
- Sit, yeah.
Eat and drink up.
Let's drink!
Drink!
Sit.
Get up and dance.
Dance!
Talent Boy,
why are you sitting here alone?
Playing statue?
Can you handle them all?
I've got plenty of energy.
You're drunk.
No, I'm not.
Listen, I'm totally sober.
What's this?
Don't move.
This looks familiar.
Come on, let me see.
Let go.
Don't be so stingy. I'm just looking.
Let go, or I'll tell your husband.
Your mouth is warm.
How can it say something so cold?
I...
You can act as if my so-called husband
doesn't exist.
How irresponsible of you.
You're taking it so seriously.
Let me see what you look like.
What kind of dump is this?
Why's the room out of power?
Isn't it all lit up outside?
Three days and three nights.
- Sis.
- In the middle of the night.
Sis.
One more drink.
Hello?
What's wrong with you?
How can the club offer that?
Cancel it right now.
(Cut the power
and shut the club down at once.)
(Don't ask why.)
Careful!
(Qing)
Hello?
Wen Yan, I got some gossip for you.
Guess what happened to the models
we booked last night.
Male models?
Weren't they your friend?
How would I know that many hot guys?
Those were male models.
What?
How could you book male models?
We just shut down
their paid female companions.
No, this won't do.
Which place was it?
I'm going to report them.
Here's the real gossip.
That club cleared out
all the male models overnight.
We got the very last batch.
Lucky for them.
Enough.
No, no way.
I can't keep playing like this.
(Lin Zhi'er lured me here,)
(but the Lianxin Island deal
smells off.)
(Since I'm already here,)
(without some dirt,)
(this trip would be in vain.)
(I still need Lu Tingxiao.)
(Lianxin Island Fundraising Proposal)
Tingxiao.
Sober now?
How did you know I drank last night?
A friend tipped me off.
Last night, you were picking favorites.
That was impressive.
He must've made a mistake.
I drank alone yesterday.
What have you been busy with lately?
Is it the Lianxin Island project?
How's it going?
Why the sudden interest
in Lianxin Island?
I heard
you never cared about business.
I'm finally feeling the pressure.
Tingyu still won't settle down,
so I can only work harder and learn more
to take some weight off you.
How about I start
with Lianxin Island?
But you're a Lin, not a Lu.
Why should I trust you?
Come on.
I'm your sister-in-law,
part of the family.
You want to know about Lianxin Island?
Not a chance.
You're Jin Chanchan,
the industry's top star.
If I told you about it,
you'd expose everything
about Luzhou Group.
Something's dirty?
Even so,
as part of the family,
how could I harm our own interests?
You seemed
interested in my computer.
No.
I just thought
your screensaver looked nice.
So, you must be into me.
That's even less likely.
What are you saying?
Really?
Really.
(Why does this necklace look familiar?)
What's this?
- Don't move.
- Let me see.
(No way.)
(How could Lu Tingxiao be a male model?)
What did you do last night?
Do I need to report to you where I go?
It's so cold out.
Go and rest inside.
I didn't get any shots.
(He never touched the computer,)
(yet he could lock it remotely.)
(Could that necklace be
the control key?)
(Where did he hide the necklace?)
(Where on earth is it?)
Don't go.
I didn't mean to.
Mom!
(Jin Chanchan)
(Expos├ر: Food expired, seniors silenced)
(He actually...)
ظآزSooner or later, it's meant to beظآز
ظآزMaybe the start feels like a prank tooظآز
ظآزLove leaves you laughing through tearsظآز
ظآزMelting the lonely isle below freezingظآز
(Maybe next time.)
Forget it.
ظآزA hug that I've waited so long forظآز
ظآزMelting the lonely isle below freezingظآز
ظآزThe warmth in every breath risesظآز
Mom,
I met a girl.
She's just like you.
(Was he talking)
(about me?)
ظآزMelting the lonely isle below freezingظآز
ظآزDrifting to the edge of spaceظآز
ظآزWhat words could describeظآز
ظآزThe hug that I've waited so long forظآز
ظآزMelting the lonely isle below freezingظآز
ظآزThe warmth in every breath risesظآز
You had a high fever last night.
I was worried about you.
That's why I'm here.
Why did you come at midnight?
You knew I'd get a fever?
I had a feeling.
Is that not allowed?
The door was locked.
How did you get in?
You had a fever.
You must've forgotten to lock it.
You were burning up all night.
I stayed and took care of you.
- You...
- Lu Tingxiao, open up.
ظآزThis doorظآز
ظآزLets in the sky outsideظآز
ظآزWith a voice even lighterظآز
ظآزThan how you just greeted meظآز
ظآزI know nowظآز
ظآزWhat the chill in my body meansظآز
ظآزThe moment salt hits the woundظآز
ظآزMy heart still beats so naivelyظآز
ظآزTo completeظآز
ظآزA joy that needs no brave pretenseظآز
ظآزHow cruel sincerity can beظآز
ظآزLike a door with no keyظآز
ظآزMaybe you just passed byظآز
ظآزThe tears in my eyesظآز
ظآزYou looked like you had nothing to sayظآز
ظآزThen got so good at being coldظآز
ظآزThat's why a smile feels so preciousظآز
ظآزMaybe you just passed byظآز
ظآزThe tears burned into my heartظآز
ظآزLet's say silence was just for showظآز
ظآزEven if I've grown another yearظآز