Fictional work. Any similarity
to real names or events is coincidental.
Underage smoking is prohibited.
End of Reiwa era.
Japan suffered an overwhelming defeat
in the fourth industrial revolution
at the hands of the USA,
China, India and other countries.
In addition, the acceleration of the
declining birth rate and aging population
and a major drop in education levels
compounded Japan's deterioration.
A nuclear war broke out.
Though Japan did not become a battlefield,
refugees poured in,
and infectious diseases spread.
Furthermore, major earthquakes
hit one after another.
Meanwhile, wealth concentrated
in the hands of those ridiculed as elites,
such as politicians and capitalists.
Suffering government failure, heavy taxes,
natural disasters and famine,
the people finally rose up.
This was The Great Violent Revolution.
The nation collapsed as a state.
Within a few years, the population reduced
to less than a tenth of what it was,
and all modern culture, infrastructure
and technology were lost.
Civilization regressed
to early Meiji era levels.
A world of chaotic war
divided by military cliques began.
Then, decades later,
the three nations of Yamato, Buo and Seii
entered the Sangoku period,
fighting for hegemony.
YAMATO - EHIME DISTRICT
Show some self-restraint!
A wedding dress is completely absurd!
AOTERU MISUMI
AGE 15
I can't help myself.
It's a wedding, so I need a wedding dress!
SAKI HIGASHIMACHI
AGE 16
EPISODE 1: AN OATH FOR PEACE
Saki, that was the case
in the late Japan era.
The very end of the end too.
To begin with, the wedding dress is attire
worn in Catholic Christian weddings…
You are so hardheaded!
I'm wearing a wedding dress
because it's cute.
"Because it's cute"?
What the heck? That's not logical at all!
Hey, hey, wait! Saki!
Aoteru! Saki!
Congratulations on your marriage!
Wow! Saki looks really wonderful!
I wonder what that white clothing is.
I heard it's called a "uejingu dress."
EHIME LIBRARY
Man, I never thought
my daughter would get married
to a hardheaded,
quibbling man like you, Aoteru.
Library Director. No, Father-in-law!
It's just that I judge things based on
whether they are reasonable or not.
In the late Japan era,
weddings were held in the Christian style,
funerals in the Buddhist style,
and people visited shrines at New Year's
following the Shinto style.
In other words, Japanese people
had a close relationship with religion.
But that's not the case now.
It's completely natural
for me to stop Saki,
who has no religious beliefs whatsoever,
from wearing a wedding dress.
But then Saki goes,
"I'm wearing it because it's cute…"
That would make anyone go, "Huh?"
Library Director,
Aoteru sure does know a lot!
And he's a good talker.
Yeah, that's true.
When Aoteru's parents
died young from illness,
I started taking care of him.
He acquired literacy and gained
varied knowledge of the Japan era,
and now he's a fine agricultural officer.
Though he is at the bottom of the ladder.
All things considered,
they make a good couple.
That said,
Saki is the exact opposite of you,
quick to anger
and doesn't listen to reason.
Please take care of Saki
from here on out, Aoteru.
Yes.
A FEW DAYS LATER
He's been gone a while.
NOBUHITO HIGASHIMACHI
NAKADAI - NAKASONE
Whoa, whoa.
Saki.
I knew you would be here.
I can't believe you are doing this
on a cold-ass day like this.
A little more. Just a little more.
I like the view you can see from here.
The mountains, the sea,
the artificial land.
The factories and buildings
from the Japan era.
The paved roads and all the utility poles.
It makes me think
Japan used to be an amazing civilization.
You have always drawn maps,
ever since we were young.
TOGETHER FOREVER
R8.4.15
It's nostalgic to think about
how everyone avoided you because of that.
Not everyone. You didn't, Saki.
I just felt sorry for you.
But this map-making
has proven to be really helpful
in agricultural management.
Maybe it could help me achieve something
even greater than what I'm doing no--
Like… war, for example?
Sun Tzu, the military strategist
from ancient China…
…preached the importance
of using geography in war.
Right, right. And the genius
military advisor, Kanbei Kuroda…
…analyzed the terrain
when conquering Bitchu,
then surrounded
and flooded Takamatsu castle.
That's right!
If you put your knowledge to use,
it might be possible
to secure the borderlands
and end the Sangoku period.
The reunification of Japan
wouldn't just be a dream!
The reunification of Japan?
Aoteru, have you heard of "Toryumon"?
Mitsuhide Ryumon… He's a general
who has jurisdiction over the borderlands.
Noble and talented both in literary and
military arts, he's a well-respected man.
They say that over a thousand people visit
his house in the capital Osaka every day,
hoping to serve under him.
I think you would be able to make
the most of your resourcefulness with him.
I just want to live a normal life
with you, Saki.
That's enough for today. Let's go home.
A FEW DAYS LATER
It's so delicious!
Saki, your cooking is the best!
We harvested all those ingredients here,
so I could never have made it
if not for you.
But, man, it doesn't feel real.
While we are here farming, so many
Yamato samurai are out at war, right?
Kinda makes you feel like a disgrace.
There's nothing disgraceful about it.
To win the war,
we must have strong samurai.
What do you think you need for that?
Skill with a blade?
A competent commander?
A strong conviction!
Those are all very important,
but there's something even more important.
Food.
To provide nutritious food
to many samurai,
you must have
high agricultural productivity.
In other words,
agriculture makes the nation stronger.
I will say it over and over,
you are not disgraceful at all.
We are amazing!
-Let's eat and get back to work!
-You can't farm on an empty stomach!
-What's that?
-Look at all the people.
An imperial visit?
That means the person in the carriage
is the emperor of Yamato?
No, that's not the emperor.
LORD OF HOME AFFAIRS - DENKI TAIRA
People of Ehime, bow your heads.
This person has come from Osaka,
the capital of Yamato.
Lord Denki Taira of Home Affairs!
What do you think you are doing?
Capture him!
Hold on, now.
Right.
Dismemberment by the wheel.
-Within 30 seconds.
-What?
What?
Three, two, one.
No way! What?
Right.
Listen closely, commoners.
I am the state. Got it?
I'll be in this town until noon tomorrow,
so you best behave yourselves.
That fatso is out of his mind!
Show some self-restraint, Saki! Seriously!
What is that fatso's deal?
Lord Denki Taira of Home Affairs.
He's the highest officer of Yamato
and in control of state affairs.
The Taira clan's been a powerful clan
since before the founding of Yamato.
OSAKA
Nineteen years ago,
when his younger sister was made empress
of the former emperor Fuji II,
he was appointed lord of home affairs.
Then, Denki Taira murdered Fuji II
by poisoning him.
He backed the current emperor,
Fuji III, as the successor,
and made his own daughter the empress,
seizing full power and control.
MURDERED BY POISON
He killed the former emperor?
If he did something that insane,
why would the current emperor
give that fatso control over everything?
Out of fear.
Fear? No way, I can't accept that!
How dare he say, "I am the state"?
Are you kidding me?
He's not necessarily wrong.
Aoteru, are you saying
you agree with that fatso?
I'm not agreeing with him.
It's an established fact.
I won't let a fact like that exist.
We gotta kill that fatso.
What? Kill?
Wait, can you calm down for a second?
That's not going to bring about
any kind of fundamental change.
I respect that you have courage,
but you must learn
to control yourself at least a little!
Aoteru, it's you who must learn
to have courage.
What are they doing?
Next one!
Taxes are ¥10 per person!
If you don't have enough,
borrow it from a loan shark,
or it's 20 strikes with this stick!
1 YEN
50 SEN
Mr. Tax Collector of the Taira clan,
here is a total of ¥10.
Please accept it.
-Aren't you forgetting something?
-What?
There's a ¥2 handling fee.
So I'll need two more of these, all right?
That absolute piece of trash!
Wait, Saki!
Come tomorrow, they will leave this town.
One! Two! Three!
You have to show self-restraint!
No. I can't do that.
Eleven! Twelve! Thirteen!
What the-- Who are you, girl?
I'm Higashimachi. I'm from this town.
Then get in line.
Can you not see this family crest?
If I may most humbly say, isn't the rule
that taxes are handled by each district,
with payments being a fixed amount
collected at the end of each month?
What are you trying to say?
If you keep getting in my way, I'll--
However, how very strange
that it is still the middle of the month.
This counts as an advance payment,
right, sir?
You are a funny girl!
I'm not being funny. Answer the question.
You are a piece of trash
that's useless without your family's name.
"Piece of trash"?
I am of the Taira clan!
What the--
WORLD PEACE
Is this tax collection your own doing?
Or is it by order of that fatso?
"Fatso"? Are you referring
to the Lord of Home Affairs?
Tell me now!
I did this on my own!
Is that so?
Lineage, gender, land of origin,
skin color, appearance.
I can't stand people who think they are
superior based on such superficial things.
Your worth is something
you create with your own hands.
What's with that woman?
Forget it, let's go!
Thank you very much!
You're the late library director's
daughter!
You have grown up so much!
Are you all just fine
with getting beaten up like that?
What?
I should have stepped in.
I was all right on my own.
No. I was watching,
and it was pretty dangerous.
But it was fine in the end.
You spoke much better than I expected,
but I could have taken care of it
more peacefully.
But I used force and took care of them.
I'm glad you are safe. Really.
Easy for you to say, you just watched.
But today sure was full of surprises.
Yeah. The Taira clan is crazy.
The Tairas were one thing,
but I had no idea you were
so passionate about agriculture, Aoteru.
That was a big surprise.
No, I'm not passionate about agriculture.
I just thought about what I should do
to have a stable life with you, Saki,
and decided to get a steady job
as an agricultural officer, that's all.
So then, does that mean it's my fault
you became an agricultural officer?
No, Saki, I didn't mean it like that.
I want to know what you want to do,
Aoteru, rather than what you should do.
I still think Toryumon, the thing
I told you about the other day is…
No, I'm a civil official.
I'm unversed in war.
What do you mean, unversed?
You borrowed
The Art of War
yet again.
I realize something new
every time I read it.
But all I have is knowledge
without any real practical experience.
What is that knowledge for if you
never actually use it for a real purpose?
There's only one thing
you are lacking right now.
Courage.
If you just had courage, Aoteru,
you would be able to unify Japan,
end this Sangoku period,
and build a peaceful world.
Come on now,
what kind of a theory is that?
I truly believe that.
I guess we should go to sleep. Good night.
But I don't think
that theory is convincing at all--
Good night.
UEJINGU DRESS AND TABI
TOBACCO
Saki…
Saki?
As if she would ever be in here.
It's cold.
Blood?
It can't be…
Right, it's you, young man.
I was just about to
make them bring this to you.
Your wife's head.
"Your worth is something
you create with your own hands."
What nonsense!
She's lost her hands,
and her feet and torso too!
What's she going to do now
with just her head?
I'll kill them.
First, I'll take the tax collector's sword
and slit his throat.
Then, I'll stab Denki Taira's foul stomach
and kill him.
I'll be killed, but it doesn't matter.
Saki said it herself.
"We gotta kill that fatso."
WAIT… KILL?
Wait, just calm down for a moment.
If I did that, I'd just be
branded as a traitor and executed.
Then someone from the Taira clan
will act as regent and wield power again.
Even if I give in to my rage
and take revenge on them,
it won't bring Saki back to life.
There's just one thing
I should do right now.
That's to receive Saki's head.
There's only one thing
you are lacking right now.
UNITY OF KNOWLEDGE AND ACTION
I am an agricultural officer
by the name of Aoteru Misumi!
I have inquiries
for Lord Taira of Home Affairs
regarding the execution of my wife, Saki.
May I ask for a little bit of your time?
What? Who do you think you are?
How incredibly rude!
No, it's fine. Keep it under five minutes.
What?
Then let me inquire.
What were the charges against my wife?
Charges, right.
I had her executed
because she offended me.
Lord Taira, you say you have executed
my wife because she offended you.
Then, could you share the details
of that charge, please?
Why should the Lord of Home Affairs
need to explain himself?
All you should do is receive
the head of your idiot wife. That's all!
Please, give me the details.
She got in the way of tax collection,
and she called me "fatso."
These two reasons.
I understand.
Then, Lord Taira, were you
at the tax collection point yesterday?
No, I wasn't.
Do you still have more to say?
Yes, as you have
graciously given me five minutes to speak.
So who did you hear about this from?
What a disingenuous thing to ask!
You know that it was me!
All right, Mr. Tax Collector.
I was also there yesterday.
Firstly, in regard to my wife
getting in the way of tax collections…
That is true.
She did indeed get in your way.
Next, in regard to my wife referring
to Lord Taira as "fatso,"
that is factually inaccurate.
My wife never once used the word "fatso"
in reference to Lord Taira.
What? No, no, you are flat out lying.
Lord Taira, he's lying to you.
Allow me to repeat myself.
My wife never once used the word "fatso"
in reference to Lord Taira.
What are you rambling about?
Yesterday, this is what
my wife said to Mr. Tax Collector.
"Is this tax collection your own doing?
Or is it by order of that fatso?"
No, you said it right there!
You said "fatso"!
Whereupon Mr. Tax Collector said this.
"'Fatso'? Are you referring
to the Lord of Home Affairs?"
I did, but what about it?
It was obvious your idiot wife
was calling Lord Taira "fatso," you idiot!
Regardless of who my wife
referred to as "fatso,"
it's clear the person Mr. Tax Collector
thought of upon hearing "fatso"
was Lord Taira of Home Affairs!
In other words, my wife did not address
Lord Taira of Home Affairs as "fatso,"
but Mr. Tax Collector interpreted "fatso"
as referring to Lord Taira.
This is the fact of the matter.
That's such a trivial argument!
You must have meant to set me up
from the beginning!
Lord Taira, I'm being falsely accused!
Right, that's enough.
It's been five minutes.
Someone behead that tax collector.
Within 20 seconds.
-Yes, sir!
Lord Taira, I--
Are you satisfied?
This is not at all what I expected.
I simply explained the facts.
-Take this box to him.
-Yes.
-Now, I will take my leave.
-Wait.
What sort of feelings drove you
to come and face me?
Give me a concise answer.
Sun Tzu says,
"Those who arrive at battlefields first
and await the enemy have ease,
those who later approach the war
face hard battle."
"Thus, those who fight well
move the others
but be not moved by them."
"Those who induce the enemy
to come toward them,
do so by allowing them to find merit."
"Those who prompt the enemy
not to approach them,
do so by implying demerit."
What's that mean?
It's a passage regarding deception
from Sun Tzu's
The Art of War.
Okay, fine.
Then how do you feel right now?
Laozi says, "The journey of a thousand li
starts with a single step."
Was it all right to let him go?
Well, yeah.
He looked his wife's killer
right in the eyes
and showed not a single bit of rage.
An interesting young man.
He was talking to me,
but it was as though his eyes were looking
at something far into the future.
Well, I'm off, Saki.
Year 57 of the Yamato era. Spring.
Young man, where are you headed?
To Osaka, please.
Osaka! What are you going that far for?
To change the world.
What?
TO BE CONTINUED
Creative Supervisor
Hideo Kimura