You bastard.
I finally got you.
Say hi to the boss for me.
Jeong Gu-won.
Do Do-hee.
What do you want?
I'm…
my bodyguard's bodyguard!
Stay away.
Why is charging
always the problem for everything?
Stay away.
Get her!
Jeong Gu-won!
Do you know
how to tango?
Tango?
You must trust your partner
when you tango.
Why are you suddenly talking about tango?
Get him!
Behind you!
You morons,
why are you dancing all of a sudden?
Pull yourselves together!
What is this?!
"Rule number one for bodyguards."
"Never let her out of your sight."
"Rule number two."
"Never stray far from her."
"And rule number three."
"Never…
fall in love with her."
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I made a report.
Let's get out of here first.
Jeong Gu-won!
Jeong Gu…
The doors are closing.
What in the world…
EPISODE 5
ONLY YOU
SUNWOL FOUNDATION
What happened? Are you hurt?
Get the first aid kit!
-Let me see.
-Is someone trying to kill me?
Why is the sword so sharp?
What?
Star Jin, you're on another level indeed.
You were so in the zone
that you cut yourself
with this dull sword.
Thank you.
Manage the props better, will you?
Manage the props better!
There it is.
Forget it. I'll do it.
The show's just around the corner,
but Director Jeong couldn't care less.
But I'm here for you all the time.
-Isn't that enough?
-Of course not.
That makes sense.
Is there something going on
between him and Do Do-hee?
-What?
-He's still with her at work,
and they're always with each other.
Come on.
You know he has a heart of steel.
You've had eyes only for him
for over 20 years,
but he's never batted an eye--
Jeez.
Maybe he did bat an eye.
My point is,
his heart is as cold
as 200-year-old ice cream
that's been forgotten
at the bottom of a freezer.
It's frozen to the point
that it no longer functions properly.
He's not just good-looking
but unbelievably good-looking.
Yet for 200 years…
Yet for 200 years, he's been single.
There's a reason for that.
It's still bothering me.
I have a bad feeling about this girl.
Are there no other options
than him being her bodyguard?
That is our best option at the moment.
Don't you need a break?
This is nothing.
I'm short on time as it is.
Let's take it from the top.
Something's wrong with me.
Falling for a worthless human being?
Could it be…
because of the tattoo?
I mean…
Why would he look at me
with such contempt?
He was obsessed with holding my wrist.
Why is he suddenly acting
as if I were invisible?
Do I have to put up with this?
Was I the only one getting a vibe?
I bet he was too.
So why is he so cold all of a sudden?
Fiery one minute, cold the next.
What is he, a hot iced Americano?
I couldn't care less
whether he's hot or iced.
I'll just go my own way.
I've already been clingy enough.
SCHEDULED TOMORROW:
BLIND DATE
No, I must find out
whether he's hot or iced for me.
SUNWOL FOUNDATION
This is it.
I'll be clingy just one last time.
There's nothing wrong with me.
It's just a side effect
of losing my powers.
If he asks why I'm here,
I'll say that I was so curious
about the thugs from earlier
that I couldn't sleep.
I show up unannounced late at night.
He'll be happy to see me
if he has feelings for me.
If not, he'll be upset and annoyed.
It'll only take a second.
He can't fabricate the look in his eyes
the second he sees me.
Who are you?
What about you? Are you a thief?
I would say you're the one
who looks the part.
You don't look all that ordinary yourself.
Do Do-hee?
-You know me?
-You don't know me?
I can't believe
you don't recognize Star Jin.
Then I must be the star here.
Leave right now.
Outsiders aren't allowed in at this hour.
I'm not exactly an outsider,
so I refuse to leave.
I doubt it.
I have a special relationship
with the director here.
Jeong Gu-won?
The lights are on.
Where did he go?
He didn't seem like the academic type.
These must be just for show.
Does he collect vintage clocks as a hobby?
But why do they all look the same?
The numbers…
Nothing about him is ordinary, is it?
Who said you could go through my stuff?
Is that your diary or something?
Why so sensitive?
A cross?
Why, you pervert.
What?
Why are you half-naked?
Shouldn't you be rehearsing?
That's not what's…
Babe.
Didn't I tell you not to expose your skin
in front of other women?
-"Babe"?
-If you do this,
women will keep clinging to you
no matter how coldly you treat them.
Like fruit flies.
Cut it out and get back to rehearsing.
You always seem to act distant
when other people are around.
You're so cute.
Come down to the theater later.
I need to talk to you.
This is what you call
a "special relationship."
Who is she?
It's none of your business.
She and I almost killed
each other earlier.
I'd love to know
whose life I almost ended.
Did you show up here alone at this hour
to pry into my personal life?
No.
It's just
you took off so abruptly.
I was worried.
I just didn't want to be with you.
And yet here you are,
bothering me again.
Did I do something wrong?
-No.
-Then what's with the attitude?
I don't see why I should be nice to you.
Anything else you want to say?
I was clearly mistaken.
Sorry for bothering you.
Do Do-hee.
You couldn't have been more wrong.
Mr. Park, Do Do-hee is on her way out.
Make sure she gets home safe.
Check inside locker number 17.
You seem to be responding well
to the medication,
but let's keep monitoring your progress.
Nothing out of the ordinary, right?
It's not a big deal,
but I killed a person.
I see.
What?
Just checking if you're listening.
What a lunatic.
-Shall we?
-Sure.
I didn't know you could drink, Mr. Noh.
I can, but I've been holding back.
It must've been hard to hold back
in so many ways until now.
Thank you all for responding so quickly
regarding the audit team.
The company's stability
is our top priority.
On that note, we must soon fill the void
left behind by my mother.
I'll be counting on your help again.
Since the late chairwoman's will
was made public,
everyone seems to be welcoming
the youngest chairwoman in history.
So it's not as easy
to publicly support you.
Do-hee is like a little sister to me,
but I learn a lot from her.
She'd certainly set a good example.
But…
if we kept allowing anomalies like her,
the world would turn upside down.
The world is no longer an easy place.
Unfairness is the last thing
that people will tolerate.
Nepotism has become
such a taboo these days.
We can't do anything that wouldn't
sit well with the shareholders.
You don't seem to get my point.
Then let me spell it out.
You all recently received
a little something
from our subcontractor, right?
"The directors disbanded the audit team
formed under the chairwoman's last order
and accepted money from a subcontractor."
That may as well be a confession
to all your wrongdoings so far.
But you gave that order yourself.
Me?
You think a son
grieving his mother's passing
would do such a thing?
I didn't give or receive any money myself.
How will you prove it?
It was your greed
that led you astray, not me.
The world was never
an easy place to begin with.
You get trampled on and eaten up
without power.
There's only one way
the powerless can survive.
Siding with the most powerful.
Nothing else.
You're right.
I'm a lunatic.
About Mr. Cha.
How long did he work for you?
Almost two years
before he transferred to Mirae Group.
Did anything stand out during that time?
Not really.
How audacious of him
to pocket company funds.
It's not that he was audacious.
He was greedy.
You're actually right.
I'll go inside if you're done.
Why are you so surprised?
I didn't hear you come in.
What's Do-gyeong up to these days?
I don't know.
Nor do I want to.
Did you eat dinner?
Obviously.
It didn't come off.
CLOTHING BIN
Bravo!
Star Jin, you never disappoint.
Not even your injury could stop you.
That was amazing.
What do you think, Director Jeong?
It was good.
I kept making mistakes.
I even missed some beats.
Did you?
You finally found the time to be here,
but you can't seem to focus.
You're like an empty shell these days.
He does have an excellent-looking shell.
What more does he need?
So just stay on the beat.
Are you happy now? I'm off.
ENFORCER
ABRAXAS HAS ENTERED THE ROOM
ABRAXAS:
I DON'T SEE ANYTHING IN THE FOOTAGE
It's his doing.
The suspicious guy next to her.
He's something else.
He beat so many guys by himself.
ABRAXAS:
HE'S CLEARLY BETTER THAN YOU
THE MORE ELUSIVE YOUR PREY IS,
THE MORE SATISFACTION IT CAN GIVE YOU
HUNT YOUR PREY
AND YOUR THIRST WILL BE QUENCHED
The moment he disappears,
I'll get the job done.
QUIT
Good morning, ma'am!
Good morning indeed.
Is this what you talked about last time?
Gosh, is it just me
or did the temperature just drop in here?
Then again, it could've been worse.
If I were Ms. Do,
I would've given him the axe right away.
Ms. Do has an axe?
Yes, she does.
You're clueless, aren't you?
What do you mean I'm clueless?
People love me
because I'm perceptive and sociable.
Good for you.
I really envy you.
There's no need to envy me.
Did you have a fight?
I mean you and Ms. Do.
I saw you two
holding hands under the table
at the team dinner.
Don't worry.
I'm surprisingly an outcast here,
so your secret is safe with me.
So?
Did you have a fight?
I can't even read the newspaper in peace.
-Lock the door.
-Yes, sir.
This isn't single-origin.
How can anyone call this coffee?
This is what helps you
get through the day.
-Is that alcohol?
-Don't mention that right now.
It's instant coffee.
Why would anyone drink this crap?
This was invented to exploit workers.
There's a saying.
"Instant coffee is the only pleasure
granted by employers."
-"Pleasure"?
-Yes.
Humans exaggerate too much.
Do you all drink this
to forget that you're slaves?
I spent three years hunting for a job.
And my dream back then
was to enjoy a cup of instant coffee
in the office.
The most important part is
wearing an employee ID around your neck.
You must really be cut out to be a slave.
You wasted three years to become a slave?
There you are, Mr. Jeong.
-Mr. Jeong, Ms. Do is heading out.
-Here's some advice
from someone
with more experience than you.
Oh, shut it.
"Shut it"? You're so…
We shouldn't get paid during breaks,
should we?
Right?
Hello? Hi, how are you doing?
Is that Hassan? How's everything, Hassan?
Hassan…
Would you like a sip?
Ms. Do is heading out.
That's really something.
We're a beverage company.
Who had the audacity
to order drinks from another company?
Young people these days…
They're incredible. I admire them.
Where did he go?
Ms. Shin's gone too.
Ms. Shin.
Do Do-hee. Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
What's going on?
Ms. Do, I caught the culprit.
His head is twisted!
Is he dead?
He's not the culprit.
You got the wrong person.
Do you know him?
He's alive.
Director Jeong!
Where are you going?
Who are you? Go away!
-Director Jeong.
-Stay away.
-I said stay away.
I was just…
worried because you seemed down.
I wanted to sneak in
to see how you were doing.
I didn't want to look suspicious,
so I disguised myself as a deliveryman.
Great job.
You weren't suspicious at all.
I never imagined
they'd think I was the culprit.
Don't I exude goodness even from the back?
-Is that right?
-Yes.
Why would you
do such a pointless thing?
I'd been keeping a proper distance,
but you ruined it all!
"A proper distance"?
Right.
Come to think of it,
all of this happened because of you.
Ever since you showed me that weird movie,
The Bodyguard or whatever it's called,
something's been wrong with me.
How exactly?
My heart…
My apologies.
I hear you're with the Sunwol Foundation.
My apologies for the misunderstanding.
But if it hadn't been for
Mr. Park Fork-you acting so suspiciously--
He's with the Sunwol Foundation.
It was careless of me to use violence.
My name isn't Park Fork-you.
It's Park Bok-gyu.
Park Fork-you.
Bok-gyu.
Fuck-you.
-Is it just me?
-Yes.
My current predicament
has put her on edge.
I apologize.
Well…
Sure, I understand.
We'd like to compensate you
for both physical and mental injuries.
That won't be…
refused at all.
-That won't be necessary.
-If you say so.
But…
-I'm the one who got hit. Why--
-Zip it.
Are you okay?
Sorry? Yes, I'm fine.
Where will the meeting be held?
Right. Please follow me.
-Okay.
-All right.
Let me make something clear.
I'm not sitting back
because I'm incompetent.
I'm letting you take charge
because family comes first in crisis.
I appreciate that.
Invest in Mirae Apparel as you promised.
Or that'll be the end of it.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I thought you weren't going to make it.
Of course I made it.
I couldn't leave you here alone.
Before discussing the main agenda,
we shall take a vote on entering into
the emergency management system.
This was decided
-Already?
-to minimize confusion
following the chairwoman's passing.
The person we would like to elect
as the acting chair
is CEO Noh Suk-min of Mirae Electronics.
Let's hear from Mr. Noh.
My mother spent her entire life
building Mirae Group.
I'll do my best to restore stability
in the organization.
All directors, please vote
using the device in front of you.
CEO NOH SUK-MIN AS ACTING CHAIRMAN
IN FAVOR: 16, AGAINST: 2, ABSTENTION: 0
I declare that CEO Noh Suk-min
has been elected acting chairman
by a majority vote.
I thank you all for entrusting me
with the position of acting chairman.
I promise to lay the foundation
for the future of Mirae Group.
Let's go, Do-hee.
Just how many bodyguards do you have?
What are you so afraid of?
But then again,
the more you've sinned,
the guiltier the conscience.
It's okay, Seok-hoon.
A barking dog never bites.
It's barking out of fear.
No one's on your side.
At least no one with power.
-Su-ahn.
-Wake up, Seok-hoon.
As an investor, shouldn't you be
better at reading the situation?
She can't become chairwoman.
She has way too many enemies.
I won't let that happen,
even if it means
I'll have to give up what's mine.
Too bad.
It'll happen sooner than you think.
Do you think I'll just sit back and watch?
I'll look forward to your next move.
Why you little…
That's enough.
It would break Mother's heart
to see our family make such a scene.
-What family?
-Noh Su-ahn.
Everything's happening so fast.
We already have an acting chairman.
The situation called for it.
I'll leave the company in your care,
though it'll be brief.
Do-hee.
Haste leads to mistakes.
And marriage can change your life forever.
So take your time to find the right one.
You can leave the company to me.
That's very reassuring.
But it won't take too long.
Do send me a wedding invitation.
I insist on being there as your family.
Nice tattoo.
It looks good on you.
You got a tattoo? When?
Well, recently.
I see.
Do you have a minute?
Do-gyeong.
Everyone else came out. Where's Do Do-hee?
You know who I am, right?
I don't.
Then let me surprise you.
I don't like surprises.
I rarely pay attention to our employees,
but you caught my eye
when you turned down Do-hee's proposal
at the speed of light.
Are you interested in modeling?
I can make you big.
I shouldn't get any bigger.
Nice and brusque.
Mr. Jeong Gu-won, right?
Do-hee tells me you saved her many times.
Thank you for being there for her.
Please keep taking good care of my Do-hee.
I didn't do it for you.
And you don't need to tell me what to do.
Don't mind him.
He's equally rude to everyone.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
The two of us need to talk.
"The two of us"?
"My Do-hee"?
This is the reason
I was late to the board meeting.
"Mirae Group's financial statements"?
They're from two years ago.
I found something suspicious in there.
Two years ago, Mirae Group
purchased a ship from a firm
at a rather high price.
But the ship is nowhere to be found.
So I did some digging
and found that the firm
went under recently.
This is a textbook example
of accounting fraud.
What are they cooking up
by themselves in the car?
I'll keep digging.
They can't have cleaned up
all the evidence.
I hope you're right.
By the way,
isn't it awkward
between you and Mr. Jeong?
Why would it be? We're just working.
I'll get going.
Take care.
I'll let you know if I find anything.
Thanks, Seok-hoon.
Anything for you.
"Anything for you," my foot.
Do-hee.
Never mind. Take care.
Okay.
What's with the longing look?
-What?
-You were looking at me.
-I was?
Humans can tell
when someone's looking at them.
You're delusional.
I'm not anymore.
I won't care about whatever you do,
nor will I read anything into it.
That's good to hear.
HEAD ATTORNEY
JEONG JUN-HO
Something's definitely fishy.
Could we bring criminal charges?
To do that, you'll need solid evidence.
Going after a chaebol
could cost you your life.
Circumstantial evidence won't cut it.
We looked into the motorcycle
he was riding,
but it was undocumented and untraceable.
And the sketch
didn't hit any match in our database.
We're not making much progress.
Maybe I should act as bait.
Don't say something so scary.
I understand your concern,
but I'll make sure
you can go back to your safe daily life
as soon as possible.
SEOUL SEOCHO POLICE STATION
What did you mean by bait?
He would have to show up
in order to harm me.
That's our chance to find a clue.
You really are reckless.
I'm that desperate.
Also, I hate to admit this,
but you're an excellent bodyguard.
Ms. Do Do-hee?
Yes. Nice to meet you.
I'm Prosecutor Choi Woo-sun.
I'll do my best
as my name suggests.
We finally meet.
It's an honor.
Please have a seat.
And who might this be?
He's my bodyguard. Please understand.
No problem.
It's just common practice
for the upper class, am I right?
I'm sorry about last time.
It was for the best.
Your value peaked in the meantime.
My value?
I hear you'll be chairwoman.
Right.
I ordered for you.
You like steak and wine, right?
And you like me too, don't you?
So you're a prosecutor?
Be careful,
or I'll indict you
for stealing my heart.
Where does he even learn those lines?
Let's eat first.
I asked them to serve everything at once.
We Koreans love
a table full of food, don't we?
-Would you like to taste it?
-Sure.
I like it.
I don't drink during the day.
That's a shame.
Then let's meet after sunset next time.
I ordered some lobster
following the restaurant's recommendation.
Let me see.
Food should be treated the same as wine.
One should only take a bite
after enjoying its aroma.
Fill your nose with the aroma.
Let go.
Excuse me. I'll be right back.
What are you doing?
I shut his mouth.
I couldn't stand it anymore.
Stay out of this.
I'm not in the mood for your jokes.
Sorry about that.
-Are you okay?
-Of course.
The lobster here sure is fresh.
What are you doing later?
I have a trial to attend,
but why do you ask?
Let's register our marriage today.
You're full of spunk.
People who are meant to do great things
are certainly extraordinary.
Then…
I'll meet you at the district office
after the trial.
See you in a bit.
I can't believe
we'll be married in two hours.
Neither can I.
All right then.
Are you really going to marry
that sleazebag?
He's a prosecutor.
I need someone
who can go after the chaebol with me.
Still, you can't marry someone like him.
What do you care?
It doesn't matter who.
It's not a real marriage anyway.
Please prepare a press release.
The wedding will be held tomorrow.
You and Mr. Jeong could be our witnesses.
Says who?
Please pick out a dress for me, Ms. Shin.
Something fancy
that would look good on camera.
As for the ring…
There's no need.
I already have one from Madam Ju.
I can't stand it anymore.
Marry or divorce whoever you want
for all I care.
Just don't make that face in front of me.
Who are you to tell me what face to make?
You look as if you're being
dragged to a slaughterhouse.
Then just don't look at me.
You're right. Then I won't.
What are you doing?
I won't have to be with you
once we catch the culprit.
-What?
-Let's catch the bastard.
Pardon me,
but he seems to be
more than we can handle.
We're lucky that we even survived.
If we run into him again…
Then what?
You bunch of weaklings.
The boss would be turning in his grave.
-I'm sorry, sir!
Get lost. I can't stand the sight of you!
-We'll get lost, sir.
-Get some rest, sir.
I said get lost.
What are you two doing here?
What about the culprit?
As you said,
it takes one scumbag to deal with another.
You see this?
Bring this bastard to me right now.
Are we, the Wild Dogs, a joke to you?
Do you think I'll do as you say?
Great.
I guess I'll take it out on you.
-Jeong Gu-won.
-So you dodged.
Try and dodge this too.
What are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm paying him back.
This is all your fault.
I've been a mess
ever since you hit me on the head!
Stop it. He might die.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Fine, I'll do as you say.
It's too late.
-Give me your wrist.
-No.
Stop getting in the way.
I said stop getting in the way.
Why are you so upset?
Pull yourself together
and tell me what your problem is.
You want to know what my problem is?
You.
You're my problem.
My life was perfect until I met you.
But it's become a mess
since you came into my life.
If it weren't for you,
I'd be just fine.
Let's stop this.
I'll let you go.
You're no longer my bodyguard.
Fine, let's stop with this bodyguard crap.
I'm in danger right now.
I don't know who's after me or why.
You need your tattoo,
and I need your powers.
This is the only way
for both of us to get what we want.
Humans tend to romanticize
unnecessary and inefficient emotions
as part of being human.
I'm not going to use you
lest I end up
exploiting others' misfortunes.
My life was perfect until I met you.
But it's become a mess
since you came into my life.
I'm human.
I'm a person with emotions,
not just a charger for…
If it weren't for you,
I'd be just fine.
Let's stop this.
Thank you.
I'm sorry. Something came up.
I'll be in touch tomorrow.
No…
No!
Don't!
Please don't!
Please stop!
Please!
Jeong Gu-won.
Do Do-hee.
Do Do-hee could've really died this time.
We'll find the person behind all this.
The real culprit behind the disguised one.
So what if I kill someone?
I must know
exactly what she's going through.
And what gives you the right?
I'm the only one on her side.
What's so funny?
What could possibly be that funny?
-Are you getting jealous?
-Jealous?
I never understand why people get jealous.
Why are you swaying her now?
Just because.
I don't want Do Do-hee to die.
Subtitle translation by: Min-jin Kim