The Manipulated
Excuse me.
Are you Baek Dokyung's mother?
Yes.
Hello. My name is An Yohan.
I'm a friend of your son's.
Oh, one of his friends?
Well, nice to meet you.
The thing is, my son isn't here right now.
Ah. I just wanted to say hi.
I have a business meeting
at this restaurant.
Oh, yes, I see.
Your companions haven't arrived?
Just my husband.
We always come here
for our wedding anniversary.
He's a politician, so he's quite busy.
But moments like this
are still quite special to him.
Hmm. That's important.
Your son and your husband
came to visit my place recently.
And what is it that you do?
I operate a security consulting firm.
Well, I'm happy to know that my son
has such a wonderful friend.
I've only seen you in photos,
and I must say,
you're even more stunning in person.
Oh!
You're being polite.
Still, it's nice to hear.
-Why are you here?
-There you are.
I was keeping her company
till you arrived.
I actually need
to use the restroom.
I'll just be a minute.
Would you keep my husband company?
How did you know that I would be here?
Ah, don't you worry about that.
Besides, all I'm doing
is returning the favor.
I can track you down too, Congressman,
no matter where you are.
I'd say that makes us even.
How about you tell me
what you're doing here?
Should I?
Park Taejoong, that guy who escaped
from prison not too long ago?
He's after your son as we speak.
What?
That said, if you were to ask for my help,
I'd be willing to provide you
a security detail again.
Would you like my help?
You've allowed yourself
to become quite deluded.
I have?
You think I gave you that job
because I couldn't take care
of that guy on my own?
No, I did it because
everyone's good for something.
You clean up shit for me
after I've finished with it.
That's all that you're good for.
Wow, you're really something.
It just dawned on me
that you care more about your own pride
than you do your son's personal safety.
And now that you know,
I would proceed more carefully.
If you try to fuck me over,
you'll regret it.
Please excuse me.
I'm thinking this restaurant
just isn't for me.
Your insight is impressive
as always, Congressman.
Did he try to talk politics with you
while I was gone?
Not at all.
He gave me some valuable advice.
I would appreciate
if you reviewed my proposal.
I'd love to hear your thoughts.
Of course. I'll consider it
and get in touch with you soon.
What was that?
Uh, no, it was nothing.
He was asking me for a favor, that's all.
Then you should do it.
He says he's a friend of our son's.
You're right.
Why don't I just go ahead
and make that call right now?
Yeah, why not?
Congressman Baek...
This is his way of answering.
You shouldn't come to someone's house
without an appointment.
Where are you going, huh?
Where? Where you going?
The Manipulated
Want me to get you another beer?
No, no, I'm good.
This is enough for me.
You know, when I was younger,
I couldn't go a single day
without alcohol.
Every day I would come home
a complete mess.
Really? You?
I never would have guessed.
The day Eunbi's mother died...
I returned home drunk, as always...
and my wife started nagging me.
We had a fight, so I walked to the store.
But when I finally came back,
our whole house was on fire.
When I left in a rage,
I had thrown the cigarette I was smoking
down on the floor.
The embers must have caught on something.
My wife...
I should have gone in there
and gotten her out.
But I was so scared, I couldn't move.
The police saw me there and assumed
that I started the fire on purpose.
They said a good husband
would have gone in to save his wife.
Whenever I think about that night...
God...
I should have helped her,
but I did nothing but hesitate.
And so that's how my wife died.
I killed her.
Yongsik...
for as long as I've known you...
you have never hesitated, not once.
I know. I'm sorry.
We're gonna catch this guy
sooner or later.
I know you're working hard.
Just keep it up.
Well, that guy is impossible to read.
Can't tell if he's content
or if he really doesn't care.
I can't believe we came to Busan
and got bread instead of fish.
Ready to go?
Yeah.
You've been cooped up in here for hours.
What's keeping you so busy?
Park Taejoong's two little friends.
I have no idea why they're helping him.
What's the nature of their connection?
Maybe he paid them a lot of money.
Please. He doesn't have any money.
Huh.
Do you think they're family?
No, they're not related.
It's a guy he knew from prison
and the man's daughter.
-Hmm.
-These two lived separately for 20 years
and only reunited recently.
Actually, her father killed her mother.
Wow. That's pretty unusual.
But they don't seem
to get along with each other.
So why in the world are they
banding together for Park Taejoong?
I'm honestly pretty confused.
Oh, dear. I know how frustrated you get
when you can't solve your puzzles.
Should I stop by and ask them?
Wow.
Uh...
It's... It's time for breakfast.
That's all right.
I don't feel like eating right now.
Somebody spent time making it.
At least come and try it.
Something wrong?
Just come before the soup gets cold.
"Before the soup gets cold?"
What was that?
Why are you here?
I'm offering him food.
But I told you I'd do it.
What does it matter who tells him?
-You've got a crush!
-No way!
Didn't you tell me when you're around him,
it makes your heart ache?
Forget about that.
I'm gonna buy cigarettes.
Text me if you need anything.
-Wait, Eunbi, Eunbi!
-What?
Hurry back before the soup gets cold.
Hey, come here.
Come here. Hey!
You better come quick
or I'm gonna tell him.
That's right. We picked up a signal
from a nearby cell tower earlier.
When's backup going to arrive?
Damn it.
It's fine, you guys stay in position
until they get here.
I'm hanging up.
Welcome.
Oh, hello there.
-What are you doing?
-Miss, don't forget to take your items.
Huh?
Why isn't she taking
the stuff she paid for?
-Is this hers?
-Yes.
Excuse me.
Have you ever seen this person?
No.
Hang on.
Your cigarettes.
What's wrong with her?
What about you?
Oh, I already ate. You go ahead.
All right.
I can't promise it'll be any good.
No, it's really tasty.
Wow. When did you learn
how to cook like this?
-You must have been hungry.
-Mmm.
-There's more rice, so eat all you want.
-Sure.
It's good. Mmm.
MY DAUGHTER
Have some more.
Pick up the phone.
Why did you buy so many drinks?
The girl's cigarette money.
What?
Hey, get your hands off me! Oh!
Shit.
That's the girl we talked to at the shop!
-Damn it!
-Huh?
-Where are our guys?
-What is it?
Track the bicycle that just left the store
and follow us. Get in the car.
Ah, why isn't he answering?
That bicycle. Isn't that the one?
Oh, shit!
Jesus Christ. This is crazy.
That little shit.
Hey! Stop right there! Hey! Move the car!
Shit! I said move the car!
Wow! She got back here fast.
She must really like that guy.
-Whoa, what is it?
-Ah, shit!
What's the matter?
Be careful.
Why didn't you pick up?
The police are here.
Shit.
That little bitch.
All right, playtime's over.
What?
Hey! They're driving away!
Stop that car!
You search the house. Move it!
I got you now.
Check the trunk.
Get out!
Come here.
-Is there anyone in the back?
-No. All clear.
Is refilling washer fluid a crime or what?
Noh Yongsik, you son of a--
Hey, mister!
Give me a bottle of washer fluid.
I'm gonna fucking lose it.
I've got a question for you
and I want an answer.
Where's Park Taejoong?
I'm a little confused as to why
you're looking for Park Taejoong here.
I know you know where he is.
Tell me now. I want an answer.
If you're so well informed,
can't you find him on your own?
I know nothing about it.
If you really didn't know,
then why'd you run away, huh?
Listen, I told you last time.
I don't like running into you.
It makes me uncomfortable.
And now you're chasing after us
like we're criminals?
What are you trying to accomplish?
Hurry up and let's go.
You little--
Shit.
Jesus.
Did you search the whole house?
You sure? Check the alley.
Been seeing you a lot lately.
Noh Yongsik, would you just...
please be honest with me?
Is Park Taejoong with you guys or not?
Which Park Taejoong do you mean,
the one who ran away
after committing a horrific murder,
or the one who was falsely accused
and is now desperately
trying to clear his name?
If it's Park Taejoong the murderer,
I won't say.
Washer fluid's in.
Let's go.
Right.
What's the situation over there?
Can't you do anything?
Wait, where are they going?
No one in the house?
Then check again, damn it! Shit!
Why aren't you answering?
Just pick up the phone!
Ah, who is it?
Who is it?
Uh...
Who are you?
Hello?
Can I help you?
Did you come to see Hanbyeol?
Hanbyeol?
Oh, you mean her?
Hanbyeol!
Oh, my God!
-Are you all right?
-What's wrong?
Come on, get up!
I'll take her inside. Let's go.
I'll take her to her room.
Hey. Try to wake up. Come on.
Who are you?
And what are you doing here?
I came to see you two, but she lied
and said she didn't know where you were.
You bastard!
You don't have to worry.
She just fainted. That's all.
But thanks to you, Park Taejoong
has weaseled his way
out of yet another crisis.
-I'm gonna--
-Eunbi, wait.
Just tell us. What do you want with us?
What is Park Taejoong paying you two?
It's just...
Harboring a fugitive carries
serious consequences.
So that tells me that whatever you
received must have been considerable.
Otherwise, why do all of this?
I have no idea
what you're even talking about.
You think we were paid to do something?
There has to be something.
I asked you, who the hell are you?
Take it easy. You take care of Hanbyeol.
I'll talk to him.
Yeah, but he's asking all these
strange questions about payment.
Hey, tell us who you are!
You're Noh Eunbi, aren't you?
Honestly, I'm also curious
about this father-daughter thing.
You get back together after 20 years
and you're the best of friends?
You know this man
killed your mother, right?
-What?
-Who the fuck do you think you are?
Eunbi!
Eunbi, are you all right?
Look at you.
You've got quite a temper
and you know how to punch.
Don't tell me you're holding back.
You protecting your dad now?
You should have fought back
if you wanted to protect your mother.
Go fuck yourself, you son of a bitch!
Eunbi!
You bastard! Come here!
I'm going to ask you again.
What did you get from Park Taejoong?
Just answer the question.
Is that so hard?
You son of a bitch.
Well, this is no fun.
Since you two won't help me out, I guess
we'll just wait and see what happens.
Stop right there.
I said stop, you're not leaving, asshole!
Right.
I'm still uncertain
who's going to be the victor here.
Okay.
Oh!
Move your foot out of the way. Come on.
Shit. I was really worried
you weren't gonna show up tonight!
Whoa! Did you see his eyes?
Hey, I get it, man.
You feel like you got fucked over.
I'm giving you a chance.
It's time to pay for all your crimes.
You're crazy, man.
What did I do?
Mr. An planned that whole thing.
I wasn't responsible for that.
You know the Arleli thing?
Is that it? Yeah, Arleli.
The sculptures or whatever.
Look, I got fucked over too.
So I'm willing to let this one go.
Ah, forget it.
If you were to drop dead right now,
my life would be so much simpler.
Actually, I think this is my chance.
You're wrong.
It's my chance.
Whoa, shit! What the...
-Is that a gun?
-This guy's crazy!
Oh, fuck!
Fuck!
Hey, call more of your guys!
I'll fucking pay you! Huh?
Go wait in the car.
All your whining is getting on my nerves.
Just get the fuck out of here.
Okay.
Fuck!
Fuck you!
Does it hurt? Huh?
Oh, shit.
So you brought a nail gun?
What are you, a carpenter or something?
Hey, come here.
Ah, Jesus Christ.
Come here.
Ahh!
Wait, wait, wait.
Do it. Shoot.
Do it!
Son of a...
Hey, he's there.
He went that way!
Hurry and get him!
-Oh, shit.
-Hey, boss, are you all right?
Get your fucking hands off!
Ah, damn it!
What the hell's going on?
That motherfucker!
All he does is take my fucking money.
Shit.
Let's go.
Step on it!
Fuck! This crazy son of a bitch!
Get closer. I said get closer!
Closer! Closer!
Go, go, go, go!
Shit.
Get out of the fucking way! Damn it!
Fuck you! You're fucking--
Shoot him!
You better fucking shoot him right now.
Shit.
Die, you fucking asshole!
Fucking die!
Step on it!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Oh, shit!
Hold him down!
Give me your gun. Where's your gun?
Gun, gun! Give me the gun.
Shit!
Son of a bitch.
Fuck.
You fucking morons!
Fuck you, you son of a bitch!
Jesus. Fuck.
VOICE RECORDING
Confess.
I want to hear it from you.
I don't think so.
Why don't you just fucking kill me?
INCOMING CALL
CEO AN
What did I do?
Mr. An planned that whole thing.
I wasn't responsible for that.
I'm glad you managed
to find my little gift. Good for you.
I had faith you'd be able to do it.
2802, Mr. Vitamin.
-What exactly do you need?
-Vitamins.
Vitamins?
It was you?
In all honesty, I was hoping
you'd be the winner.
Is Baek Dokyung dead?
It looks like it.
How does it feel to finally take revenge?
I knew you had it in you,
But still, this was quite shocking.
Oh, dear. What a terrible accident.
Are you all right? Are you hurt?
You've been through a lot.
Why don't you tell me what you want?
How about five billion?
That was the prize money back then.
That's more than you could
ever make on your own.
And what do you want in return?
Ah...
Well, let's see.
What use do I have for you? Ah.
How about you work as my partner?
I have a feeling that you and I
would work quite well together.
With that kind of money,
you could do whatever you want.
I'd also restore your identity
and clear your name.
Sounds pretty good, doesn't it?
Bear in mind,
the only reason I'm making you this offer
is because I genuinely like you.
Restore everything?
Why don't you turn back time instead?
My life was destroyed because of you.
You took my friends away...
...and you got my brother killed.
Can you restore all of that?
What's the point of bringing up old news?
I'm trying to make a deal with you.
Your brother died because
you lost the bracelet. Simple as that.
Besides, I killed the guy
who killed your brother.
Your revenge should've ended after that.
But no, you keep blaming other people.
It's quite pathetic if you think about it.
What I want right now...
is to drag you down from there
and make you pay for what you've done.
Look, I think that I've made you
a pretty generous offer.
Don't waste it.
Just you wait.
I'll be coming for you next.
All right.
We'll do things your way from now on.
And the next time we meet,
we'll exchange more than just words.
He's completely consumed with revenge.
I don't usually make these visits myself.
I mean, what's the point?
All that driving back and forth
is such a waste of time.
But you're an exception, Assemblyman.
Do you want to know a secret?
When I was 16 years old,
both of my parents died.
What I mean to say is...
I killed the both of them.
They had signed this pledge
and said they would donate
all of their assets to our local temple.
And when I found out,
I felt this rage
that I just couldn't control.
When I saw the autopsy results later,
it said they'd been stabbed
130 times in total.
Crazy, right?
I'm not sure what compelled me.
But either way,
when I saw them lying in the kitchen,
I remember thinking,
"How am I gonna deal with this?"
Wouldn't you have it?
A news report came on saying a murderer
had broken out of prison
and was hiding nearby.
So I filed a report and said
this murderer killed my parents.
Two days later, that guy was shot
and killed trying to flee the police.
That's when I realized...
Oh...
I could use
this method in the future.
It was too easy.
I've never told anyone this before.
That means, Assemblyman Baek,
you have to take this to your grave.
Congratulations.
Does this thing work?
The old man
still has some regrets.
So what are you going to do next,
Park Taejoong?
The Manipulated