( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
What is this place?
What's wrong?
Oh, it's just…
How did we end up here?
We are on a trip.
What?
You're doing it again.
Want to nap some more?
You're awake?
Yes.
Where did you go at this hour?
I went to the convenience store
to get some stuff for breakfast.
You weren't here, so I was worried.
Oh, you should get more sleep.
I'm wide awake now. I'll go wash up.
What's wrong?
You seem a bit tired.
Did you not sleep well?
I just had trouble dozing off.
Get plenty of rest after work today.
I'll do that.
Drink some of this.
What's wrong?
You…
-Who are you?
You hurt me in a lot of ways.
You don't even recognize me anymore?
Ms. Seo Mi-rae, renew your subscription
to continue your date with Gu Yeong-il.
Are you leaving already?
Yes. I'm going to go home,
then go to work from there.
-I'll see you later, then.
-Okay.
GU YEONG-IL
Why did you leave so fast?
You didn't even say goodbye.
What is this?
What's wrong?
It's just…
You seem a bit tired.
Did you not sleep well?
I just had trouble dozing off.
Last night,
did something happen
while I was asleep?
You were just by yourself
because you couldn't fall asleep, right?
I saw it.
What…
You saw what?
Boyfriend on Demand.
Well, what exactly did you see?
I saw everything.
That man too.
Talk next time?
This isn't… It's not what you think.
So, things ended up this way somehow,
but please don't misunderstand.
Misunderstand?
You and Gu Yeong-il, I mean…
That man has nothing to do with you.
You know Mr. Min, right?
He asked me for some reviews,
so I ended up trying Boyfriend on Demand,
and things happened, and…
I ended up making a character, and he…
A character who looks just like me
was created by coincidence?
I know this may all seem absurd.
I mean, I thought so too.
But it really was a coincidence.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you sooner.
I just kept it from you
because it might sound weird.
All right.
Are you
disappointed in me?
To be honest,
I'm not sure how I'm feeling right now.
I guess I'll know after a while.
I WANTED TO TELL YOU THAT I LIKE YOU
PAYMENT COMPLETE
-Hey, did you--
-Are you okay?
What?
Why did you leave like that?
So you're telling me
he was the one who came to see me?
So nothing happened for real?
-No.
-And you didn't say anything?
What is there to say about us?
You rejecting me was all there was to it.
What was it like?
What do you mean?
When he saw you,
what was his reaction?
Well, he just
acted like he'd seen a ghost.
My good looks must've shocked him.
What am I going to do?
What did that man say?
He doesn't know
how he feels about this.
Damn it.
PRODUCER PARK KYEONG-NAM:
EARLIER…
SO-YEONG
Yes, So-yeong, let me get back to--
Ms. Seo, this is bad!
Huh?
Director Hwang told Ms. Yun
that her contract was terminated.
She needed someone to vent her anger on
and found the perfect target.
Ms. Yun, how can I--
-Move.
-Yes, ma'am.
She said she had nothing more to lose
and stormed out.
-Taxi! Hey!
-Please stop her.
Oh, Yun Song…
Wow, so this is what you've been up to.
That coffee sure smells amazing,
doesn't it?
Goodness, Hermès?
-Wait, that's…
-When did you become so successful?
I'm noticing a lot of things
I haven't seen before.
I'm guessing you must've made a fortune
thanks to someone!
Hey, you can't barge in here like this.
You startled me!
-Mr. Hwang!
-Dear God!
Do you think you're more startled
than someone who got axed?
-Please just put that down.
-What?
What?
Shouldn't have shown off that mug.
-Where is Ms. Yun?
-She's with Mr. Hwang.
-I won't give it to you!
-Hey, have you lost your mind?
-Let go!
-Wait!
Watch the finger!
Let go!
God, my wrist!
It wasn't that bad.
You handle that crap with such care,
but don't care that all that drawing
left me barely able to hold chopsticks.
Are authors less important to you
than a mug?
Huh?
I'll have you know
this is a workplace injury.
Do you have any idea
how much this wrist is worth?
Ms. Yun.
Seo? Where have you been all this time?
Please calm down. We can talk--
I can't put up with this crap anymore.
Let's go.
No need to stick around
with this shitty company any longer.
But…
-You can't just leave like this.
-Let go.
Let's try to convince the director--
Let go!
Ms. Yun, please!
Goodness, that temper of hers.
She really needs to get it under control.
Why are you looking at me?
What's with the grim faces?
EPISODE 10
AN UTTERLY NORMAL FUTURE
I got scratched a little.
There.
Thank you.
Shouldn't you be checking in on Ms. Yun?
Once she calms down a bit.
About what we were talking about
this morning…
You already explained everything.
Are you okay?
Did you see how she pulled
a shoulder throw on Mr. Hwang?
Stop making it a big deal.
What did I do?
What's wrong? Are you hurt? Let me see.
It's nothing.
Look at her face. This won't do.
Let's head out.
What you need is a bowl of unadon.
You're having lunch, aren't you?
I have a meeting with an author later.
Yeah? That's too bad.
Are you treating your teammates
to unadon, then?
Doors opening.
What is it?
I thought we got interrupted earlier.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes.
Look at me.
You actually made it?
Doors opening.
Well, Hwany
is waiting for me.
I'll be going now.
Okay. Bye.
Right.
I had a strange feeling.
That Park Kyeong-nam had gone back
to the man I once knew him as.
This unease.
Why does it feel so familiar?
What I need to do
is pretend everything's okay.
PRODUCER PARK KYEONG-NAM
Good luck with your meeting.
GOOD LUCK WITH YOUR MEETING!
(UNREAD)
Are you busy?
You like him that much?
When you like someone,
you go all in, no matter what happens.
That's a no-no.
How come?
It's just how relationship dynamics work.
Whoever shows their affection more
ends up getting dragged around in the end.
You're being dramatic.
Think about your past relationships.
Fine, let's say you're right.
What's wrong with getting dragged around?
I mean,
if you're cool with staring into
your phone all day, waiting for a reply,
and going, "Has he lost interest in me?
Is this a one-sided thing?"
while trembling with anxiety,
then it's okay.
Just put a curse on me, will you?
And that's how the vicious cycle goes on.
You get anxious. You get clingy.
He grows distant day by day.
This especially applies to you.
When things get a little awkward
for the first time,
you need to be extra careful.
Why?
That's when it starts to show
which one of you likes the other way more.
That's when the lord and the serf
in the relationship are determined.
Always so dramatic.
ARE YOU BUSY?
You've been moody lately.
The other day, you were grinning.
Today, you look like crap.
What are you talking about?
I'm just eating my food.
Are you busy?
I'm out to eat right--
You're seeing someone, huh?
Want me to guess who? It's too easy.
I can act like I don't know if you want.
What?
You knew?
Man, don't treat me like an NPC.
How could I not know?
I had my suspicions the moment I heard
you were working late every Friday.
You can talk to me about Ms. Seo.
Forget it. I can't talk to you about her.
What's it about?
So there is something going on.
Well…
It's just that…
What? Did she do something to upset you?
No, I wouldn't say that, but…
Are you mad?
-Are you fuming?
-No, it's not that bad.
What then, are you just sulking?
Huh?
I mean, if you're not upset or mad at her,
then you're just sulking.
I'm…
I'm sulking? Me?
Hey, it's nothing to be embarrassed about.
We all get sulky.
No, I've never sulked before.
Is that right?
Sure. Of course you haven't.
Hey.
So…
why do people normally get sulky
with someone?
ARE YOU BUSY?
(READ)
He left me on read?
PRODUCER PARK KYEONG-NAM
CALL
Don't get clingy! Don't call him
just because you're a bit worried!
That's a fast track to a rut, you know.
I'm going to bed now.
What are you so worried about?
It's not like you committed a crime.
As long as nothing happened
between you two, that's fine.
Wait.
If that man ever acts petty, tell me.
What?
Let me know if he frustrates you
or gives you a hard time.
Why?
I'll help you.
Is everything okay?
GU YEONG-IL
Okay. Good night.
OKAY GOOD NIGHT
(READ)
Why do people normally get sulky
with someone?
Because they like them.
Wow. You must really like Ms. Seo.
-Did you have break--
-Did you get some sleep?
I had breakfast.
I got some sleep.
What's going on?
He's acting somewhat cold.
Why is she avoiding my eyes?
I'll…
get going now.
Okay.
BOYFRIEND ON DEMAND
-Isn't that Yun Song?
-Yeah, that's her.
Are you here for the Karrot trade?
Oh, yes, Karrot.
Did you format this?
No.
Can you do it right now?
You've got such a kind heart, Song.
I should help you get motivated.
If it's too much trouble,
I can do it later.
I'll wire you the money.
What's your account…
Hello?
What the heck? Are you not selling it?
I'm sorry.
This is driving me crazy.
-Hey.
-What are you up to now?
You said
you've lost your appetite recently,
so I'm going to make you soup.
Are you trying to drive me crazy?
Why carrot soup, of all things?
What's wrong? It's what you like.
You almost got karroted off.
You know that?
Did I do something wrong?
Yes, you did!
I didn't have to know any of this,
but you made me find out.
You're the reason I ended up like this.
Hey, stop lashing out at me
and tell me what this is about.
I don't know.
Everyone keeps mocking me for liking you.
Mocking you?
Who is?
They are saying
things won't work out between us.
Who said that?
Everyone except you and me. All of them!
Come here.
It's okay.
Here.
-You like?
-Yeah.
Why do you like me?
You only like me
because you have to, don't you?
Why do you like me?
You're good-looking.
You're a good cook. You're nice to me.
You're cute, and you're kind.
-Then why are you being like this to me?
-You might have a hundred good qualities.
But you have one fatal flaw.
I didn't ask about my pros and cons.
I asked why you're being like this to me.
Do you hate me now?
Then what's the issue?
I asked you first. Answer me.
Tell me why you like me.
I just
like it when you're happy.
There's no other reason.
That's not what I'm asking.
What do you like about me?
Why do you like me?
Liking you
and liking you being happy,
are they different?
I'd be okay with it
even if you had 10,000 flaws.
But
if you absolutely can't stand my one flaw…
then you can leave.
Because
your happiness is what matters to me most.
Did I give you such a hard time?
It's not because of you.
It's because of me.
Who cares how others think about me
when I like you so much?
I'll stop going on Karrot.
I'm done with that now.
What's this Karrot you keep mentioning?
You don't need to know.
Eat the soup first.
It's going to get cold. You seemed hungry.
-Is it good?
-Yes.
It's good, huh?
-Yum yum.
-Yum yum, nom nom.
Yum yum, nom nom. Here.
There.
I put away all my mugs.
She might barge in again any day.
We can't let our guard down
until Yun Song has calmed down.
Sir, how could you do that
without even giving me a heads-up?
Hey, I only did that to save you
from the trouble of telling her yourself.
God, I'm hurt.
Even Mr. Min said he didn't want
to make an issue out of the plagiarism,
and the rest is just a private matter.
Did she commit a sin or something?
Until the public unrest dies down,
put her work on hold,
and focus on managing the other authors.
Putting her on hiatus would be inevitable,
but I don't agree
with terminating her contract.
Oh, that's right.
You're my boss.
Oh my, it totally slipped my mind!
Mr. Hwang!
Fine, then.
I'll reconsider it.
Put her on hiatus for now.
But I can't promise you anything.
Now please leave, ma'am.
You're making me very uncomfortable.
Going somewhere?
I need some air.
I'm going to work outside.
Why are you here by yourself?
Oh, everyone else went home.
They all went home?
Yun Song's series has been put on hold,
so Mi-rae's back to leaving work on time.
Only the team leader remains
to hold down the fort.
The nerve of those punks.
They've never once told me
they were leaving before…
You too?
Huh? You didn't go home?
No. I was working outside.
Wait, everyone went home?
Are you here by yourself?
Mm-hmm. They all left a while ago.
I haven't said anything to you guys,
but I have a lot pent up inside.
I never talk about it,
but now that you're here, Mi-rae…
For the first time since we got together,
he left work without even telling me.
What does this mean?
-I'M OFF TO A MEETING.
-OKAY.
HEADING BACK NOW
WANT SOME COOKIES?
I'M GOOD
-WHEN DOES YOUR MEETING END?
-IT JUST ENDED
-THAT WAS LONG, YOU SHOULD EAT LUNCH
-OKAY
She left work without even telling me?
He's changed.
Ever since he found out about
Boyfriend on Demand, he's changed.
She left first and didn't even text me.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO CANCEL
YOUR SUBSCRIPTION?
I'll help you patch things up
with that guy.
Back so soon?
Want a drink?
What's the problem?
Tell me what's troubling you the most.
I just
don't know what he's thinking.
Besides, I keep obsessing over
every little thing about him.
I'm glued to my phone all the time,
wondering when he'll reply.
It feels as though
my life has disappeared.
Why not just ask what he's thinking?
I can't bring myself to do that.
And you don't want to break up like this?
So, you feel that he has changed
after he found me, but you can't ask him.
At the same time, doing nothing
makes you nervous and frustrated.
Is that it?
Yes.
Then we'll have to find out
how he feels about you.
But how?
Let's go somewhere else.
Seo Mi-rae.
What is this?
Are you surprised?
Why are we at a place like this?
And what's with that outfit?
Did I make your heart flutter?
I won't get the wrong idea.
I know full well that you like that man.
Isn't it confusing when the familiar
gets mixed up with the unfamiliar?
In an unexpected situation like this,
people tend to reveal their true feelings.
The heart cannot lie.
Can you make it make sense?
Well, I'm proposing that we create
a situation that he won't expect.
Then, we'll be able to confirm
whether his heart still beats for you.
Show up at a familiar location,
but in a getup that he's unfamiliar with.
Hello.
-You look so pretty!
-Hi.
-Hello.
-What?
-She's wearing a skirt!
You look so pretty today.
Really!
Ms. Seo!
Good morning.
What's this?
What's going on?
Are you also being interviewed?
Interviewed?
I hope the trip here
wasn't too inconvenient.
I hope our article
didn't inconvenience you.
Oh well, I don't mind such things.
Webtoons Monthly is here for an interview.
All the recent articles are about Ms. Yun,
but the contest awards ceremony
and the new releases are coming up.
He's on a full charm offensive.
Please take good care of us.
Why isn't he here yet?
Who?
They're here for Mr. Hwang and--
Hey, Kyeong-nam!
No way.
Holy crap.
Hello.
Hey! Can you hurry up, please?
-Yes, sir.
-They're waiting for you, Mr. Park.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Why did she have to look so pretty today?
So much for confirming!
It only confirmed
that my heart's still alive and well.
Man, he's good.
I wasn't expecting a countermove.
I spent all that money at the salon
for nothing.
This won't do. Change of plans.
Before we confirm his heart,
let's manage yours first.
Leave your heart here.
Like the Tin Man
who was missing his heart.
Step into the mindset
of someone living without a heart.
I'm sure you'll feel a lot more relaxed
once you have no heart.
Stay put at home.
My heart isn't here.
-A bug! On your back!
-What? Me?
Oh God, get it off! Get it off me, please!
That's why today…
Please!
What was it? Goodness, that's creepy.
It's nothing.
…I won't lose my cool,
no matter what happens.
She grabbed a bug with her bare hands?
I'm sorry. The meeting ended a bit late.
Oh, it's fine.
Sorry about that.
CUSTOM-TAILORED BOYFRIEND GU YEONG-IL
Mr. Min,
what is that?
-Excuse me?
-Oh, I meant Gu Yeong-il.
Oh, this?
It was developed as a special bonus
for the users who didn't like our themes
because they were too contrived,
but it's gotten so popular
that we have a dedicated team for it now.
If it's custom-tailored,
does it cover everything?
We try to make it as close
to the user's ideal man as possible.
Personality, looks, everything.
Whoa, then he must be a perfect man.
Some say that he's definitely
a cut above a human boyfriend.
But as it turns out,
that wasn't the case for some.
Why not?
Aren't movies more fun
when you don't know the ending?
The man of your dreams has appeared,
but you already know he will like you,
and that breaks the immersion
for some people.
Besides, love is about
giving your heart to someone
when you have no idea what will come next.
And it's not like
love can simply be mimicked.
That's the hardest part.
True that!
With TMTK gone, it feels like a free win,
and I don't love that.
But has it really been canceled?
It hasn't, right?
I don't know much about it.
Setting the second male lead aside,
there's still so much left to wrap up.
There's the aunt's embezzlement
during the Cebu construction
and the affair between the chairman
and Director Song.
When does she plan on revealing all that?
Try talking to Ms. Yun.
You're a fan, so she might tell you.
A fan?
Are you insane?
I only read it to review the coloring work
So-yeong poured her heart and soul into.
About that thing earlier on…
Gu Yeong-il, was it?
Do you think So-yeong might have made one?
I'm a little curious as to
what her Gu Yeong-il would look like.
Well…
how do you think you'd feel
if he looked like you?
Me?
Come on, man!
I'd love it, of course!
That would mean I'm the man of her dreams.
Hold on a second.
He would only look like me
and be better than me in every other way.
Should I be worried?
Nah, I shouldn't be. I can beat him.
Because I like her more. That jerk
would only be pretending to like her.
How would that jerk know
how pretty and adorable So-yeong is?
Damn, talking about her
makes me miss her more.
-Hwany, I'm sorry.
-Huh?
I thought you left for the day.
Mi-rae just went to get us some snacks.
You're missing out.
Where did she go?
The café right out front.
Huh? What?
Why…
Did you run all the way here?
I just
wanted to follow my heart.
What?
To see you when I want to see you…
and hug you when I want to hug you.
Should I not do that?
Well…
Do it.
That's what I want to do too.
Are you sure about this?
There's no better person
to help us strengthen our scenarios.
I don't know about this.
She probably stays at home all day
watching dating shows and playing games.
I doubt she'll be capable of
communicating with us.
Boyfriend on Demand?
Yes.
I am Boyfriend on Demand.
This is a special case for us, too,
but we were really impressed
by your analysis of our themes.
That's why we reached out.
Ji-yeon,
what is your dream?
I'd like to review all 900 boyfriends,
then publish a book about that, and so on.
You plan on meeting all 900 of them?
Yes. I'm almost there.
Then you won't live your life?
What I mean to say is…
I'm living my life to the fullest.
You must have thought Boyfriend on Demand
is all I do. Not at all.
Then do you have other hobbies?
My hobbies?
Going on dates?
Ji-yeon!
Yes?
I didn't get to give you my card.
Thank you.
Have a safe trip home.
-Goodbye.
-Right.
Didn't see the step there.
I'm okay.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
I do look pretty good today.
What's your name?
-Hwang Ji-eun.
-Have you arrived?
Right this way.
Did you park on the ground floor?
Just a second!
Where should I put this?
-Put it there, please.
-Sure.
Family members can sit here.
The awardees have designated seats,
so please sit in the front.
Seo Mi-rae, come over here.
Say hello.
The winner of the Best Romantasy Award.
Oh, hello. I loved reading your webtoon.
Thank you.
Producer Seo here
will be managing you from now on.
You know, Yun Song's career took off
because she met this one.
-Glad to be working with you.
-The feeling's mutual.
I'll leave you two to talk.
-Come back later.
-Okay.
It's so hectic.
Did you say hello to the author?
Yes. I read her work so many times
that she didn't feel like a stranger.
I'm proud of myself too.
It'd be nice to judge together again
next year, right?
We might have a fight every day.
Put those scary eyes away.
Hey, what if someone walks in on us?
Wait. This is it.
-The storage room situation.
-Huh?
There's always this kind of scene
in every office romance series.
In the storage room,
just the two of us.
-Stop messing with me.
-Do you hate getting caught that much?
Just not at work.
Why?
Do I embarrass you?
Kyeong-nam, are the picket signs…
Kyeong-nam! Are you okay?
I knew it. Something felt off.
I should've known
my love life wouldn't end happily.
-Is he badly hurt?
-Here!
-Dong-min, go with him.
-Careful.
-Take care.
-I'll go with him.
What was that?
I mean, how did this happen?
What landed on him exactly?
-Mi-rae.
-Ms. Seo!
Mi-rae!
Hey, you there.
Get out of the way. Move aside.
Why are you getting in the way?
Come on, move!
Unbelievable. Sheesh.
Seo Mi-rae?
What's wrong?
Are you okay? It hurts a lot, doesn't it?
What's going on with you two?
What the hell?
No way!
If this is what I think it is,
I should probably leave, huh?
Are you okay?
Well…
Okay. I'll go.
-Thank you.
-Yeah, sure.
I'll keep it secret.
But you have to tell me all about it.
You have to, okay? You have to!
Does it hurt a lot?
I'm fine.
Why did you come?
You should have stayed there.
You got hurt because of me.
It was just an accident.
No.
I pushed you.
I thought something bad might happen
if people were to find out about us.
I did it because I was scared.
I'm sorry.
And
there's something else I didn't tell you.
After you found out
about Boyfriend on Demand,
I went back to Gu Yeong-il.
Why?
At first, I wanted to hear
what the two of you had talked about,
and after that…
it was because I was scared
of how much I liked you.
I thought if I liked you too much,
I might struggle with it later on.
Why do you keep thinking about the end?
Because I'm pathetic.
Right.
But I'm pathetic too.
When I saw Gu Yeong-il for the first time,
the first thing that came to mind was,
"Did she like him before she liked me?"
I wanted to grab him and ask him
about everything from start to finish,
but I couldn't because of my pride.
About that--
But it doesn't matter anymore.
I'm the one you like, after all,
however it started out.
I also get scared every day
of how I keep falling for you
more and more.
But what can I do?
You ran all the way here for me
with a runny nose.
How could I not like you?
Easy.
I'm sorry.
Can't we just
live in the moment and nothing else?
Those who don't doubt the future
and focus on the love in front of them.
That's who I draw.
I'll do that.
All of you,
just come with me to the States.
Who am I gonna have team dinners with now?
-Delicious?
-I'll miss you, sir!
Oh, that's right.
I have to check this before I leave.
I heard something strange recently, okay?
I heard that Seo Mi-rae over there
and Park Kyeong-nam
are dating.
-Yes, we--
-We--
That's ridiculous!
See? They're not dating, you bastard.
Choi Dong-min, you bastard.
You totally played me.
Those two hate each other's guts, man.
Hey, you guys,
let me say this one thing before I leave.
Don't talk behind the authors' backs
too much.
It's like shooting yourself in the foot.
The authors' success is our success.
-Over there!
-Let me drop some words of wisdom.
-Hi. Mind if we join you?
-Sure, you--
Hello!
-Hello.
-Hi.
Yun Song?
What? Am I not allowed here?
No, it's not that. I…
Just take this.
What could this be? What is…
Wait, could this be…
Wow, Yun Song!
Naemo's favorite author!
-You feel me, don't you?
-Sheesh.
-Don't cry. I might leave.
-Oh my God!
Make room, guys.
-Take a seat.
-Come over here.
-Sit.
-I want to drink from this.
-Set her place.
-Wow, this is authentic.
-It's precious.
-Looks amazing.
Don't let them touch. Be careful.
-So well-made.
-Look at him.
-We have to drink to this.
-Cheers!
Air cheers.
Hey, it looks like
you're a better drinker now.
Me?
I've been working out lately.
I go to the gym early in the morning
and hit the climber for 30 minutes.
All that exercise
must've given me a brand-new liver.
I feel invincible now.
What motivated you?
Whoa, hold on!
-I'll pick it up.
-I didn't give up.
-Why?
-What was that?
Well…
Here. Use a new one.
Okay. Thank you.
May our longing
One day bring us together
Mr. Hwang!
-Don't go!
-What are you doing?
-We can't live without you.
-Wait!
I'll be back later this year.
So don't ignore my calls,
or you'll pay the price.
-Really? You'll be coming back?
-Of course. I'll be back.
-Don't forget about us!
-I won't!
-Have a safe trip.
-And take care of your health.
I'm gonna miss you.
Try to cut down on the coffee
while you're at it.
God, Yun!
Seeing how much you care about me
makes my leaving feel so real.
How much is this thing anyway?
Hey, let's have a drink!
-Cheers!
-Love you!
-Love you all!
Hey, the company card's been unleashed!
Maybe goodbyes aren't as bad as we think.
It's been a while.
It has.
If it took you this long to come find me,
it must've gone really well
or really badly, huh?
Did it go badly?
Man, that's a shame.
Are you gonna be okay?
You might end up lonelier and more anxious
than when you were alone.
And neither one of your feelings
will stay the same forever.
That just might be.
You're okay with that?
I am.
Why's that?
That's just how people are.
We choose to set out on adventures,
despite knowing the dangers.
Hop on. It's dangerous here at night.
You know I won't get on.
Take care. Thanks for everything.
Are you really going to end this?
Ms. Seo Mi-rae, would you like
to part ways with Gu Yeong-il?
You'll manage fine, right?
Your relationship.
Just follow your heart.
Be brave even when you're afraid.
I know that too.
I remember when you were clueless.
Bye now.
YES
Kyeong-nam!
You're running again. I told you not to.
It's dangerous.
Relationships are dangerous.
Love is even more dangerous.
If you head out earlier,
you won't have to run.
You and your nagging.
But this time, I think I'll be okay.
Because it's us.
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon