(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
Chun'er.
I was betrayed by Huan Huan
and have lost control of Great Yan.
I hope you can help me
take back Great Yan.
Why should I help you?
You are nothing but an abandoned pawn now.
No matter what you think,
I will give it a try.
I can do anything,
even if it means risking my life.
Just please help me.
You've already dirtied this.
I don't want it anymore.
I am now
a mighty Princess Protector of the State.
If you want to see me,
come to the Princess's Mansion
to request an audience.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 35]
[Princess's Mansion]
Our Princess said
if you wanted to see her,
you must kneel here for 24 hours
to have the honor of entering.
Our Princess also said
she was just...
trying to scare you.
-To scare you.
She gave you 4 hours.
-Four.
Follow me.
Yan Xun.
Do you know?
I used to really like you.
But you ruined me.
I have no feelings for you now.
Why should I help you?
Chun'er.
I am powerless now.
The future of Great Yan is in danger.
If you can give me 5,000 soldiers,
I can take back Great Yan.
As long as you are willing,
I am willing to atone for everything
in the past.
Is that so?
Are you really willing
to do anything for me?
I am.
Change into these clothes.
Wait.
Change right here.
Li Yan.
Chun'er.
I miss you so much.
Li Yan.
No.
These eyebrows don't look like
he drew them at all!
Chun'er.
Chun'er!
♪ The dust in the world ♪
Chun'er.
Why?
♪ Is blown away easily by the wind ♪
Why do you treat me like this?
Chun'er.
Why didn't you tell me
♪ Who can stay calm ♪
that you are the Empress's son?
Why did you leave me to die alone?
♪ And not be scared? ♪
♪ A slight ripple ♪
Do you know that I hate you?
I hate you!
♪ Floating life hangs by a thread ♪
-Chun'er!
-I hate you!
I hate you!
Chun'er!
♪ The more pulled, the softer it gets ♪
Chun'er.
♪ Who dares to say forever? ♪
♪ Let it be ♪
You are a favored daughter of heaven,
♪ Grudges and grace
were never meant to be ♪
a noble Princess.
You shouldn't have been involved
in this conflict.
♪ Why must you take and demand so much? ♪
I didn't tell you
because I wanted to protect you.
♪ Go weaving ♪
♪ Grand and glorious excuses ♪
I wanted you
to live a life of joy,
♪ We face ♪
contentment, and good fortune.
♪ The heavy thunderstorm together ♪
♪ Even with extreme pain ♪
♪ We don't even wince ♪
I...
♪ Why in this world ♪
didn't get to...
♪ The staunchest heart
and strongest soul ♪
tell you...
anything at all.
Chun'er.
I'm here.
I didn't get to...
didn't get to...
Guards!
Chun'er, you're awake.
I specifically had someone
prepare Dew Lotus Soup.
I remember it's your favorite.
On summer afternoons,
you always have a bowl.
Hear my orders!
This witch is named Chu Qiao.
She is a criminal slave of Great Yong.
She impersonated the Faceless Saintess
and rebelled against Great Yong.
Today, in front of the Jiuyou Platform
at Jinsheng Palace,
she will be burned alive
as a public warning!
Yan Xun.
As I told you,
this place holds too many bad memories.
It would be better if you didn't come.
But you wouldn't listen
and insisted on coming.
Rest assured,
didn't you want my help?
I've already informed
His Highness the Thirteenth.
Once Chu Qiao is dead,
we will lend you a troop
of Zhenhuangcheng's imperial guards
to help you take back Great Yan.
Thank you, Princess Chun'er,
and His Highness the Thirteenth.
Yan Xun,
you lied to me.
You came to me,
not to borrow troops.
Speak.
Where is Chu Qiao locked up?
I don't know.
She's been locked in the doghouse
of the Thirteenth Prince.
The antidote for muscle-softening powder.
My name is Chu Qiao.
I was once a slave in Great Yong,
and now I am the Queen of Ximeng.
I know this Chu Qiao.
She used to be a slave in Qingshan Manor
and later defected from Great Yong.
Zhao Chun'er and Zhao Yang,
together with the witch, Jia Meng,
used the Faceless God Sect
to oppress the common people.
All their actions
were aimed at annexing Ximeng.
Is this true?
How could such a thing happen?
The current Ximeng
is a brand new world.
No one is a slave there,
and no one can recklessly trample on
the lives and dignity of others there.
Every commoner
can live fairly in this world.
Such Ximeng will not
be dependent on Great Yong,
nor will it ever associate
with Great Yong!
Ximeng has abolished slavery?
You don't know yet, do you?
I heard that many slaves
from our Great Yong
have fled to Ximeng.
These past few days,
by giving me the rabbit tail
and feeding me the lotus soup,
you treated me so well.
Was it all for today's plan?
This Jiuyou Platform
has claimed 16 souls of the Yan family.
Chu is the last important person to me
in this world.
I will never let her suffer
the slightest harm here.
Yan Xun.
Have you
never regretted it?
Just kill me.
The father of my child
has been killed by you,
and my mother also died because of you.
In this world,
I have nothing left.
Why don't you end my life
with your own hands?
This way, I will no longer have any pain
or attachments.
Chun'er.
Yan Xun.
All these things
were done by Zhao Chun'er,
including bringing in
the Faceless God Sect.
Now that the murderer is dead,
can I go?
Can't I go?
Shut up.
Quickly, save the Princess!
Holding a prince hostage is a great crime.
If there is any misunderstanding
among Ximeng, Great Yan, and Great Yong,
we can put down our weapons
and talk it out.
But if you persist in resisting,
that would mean
making an enemy of Great Yong.
Chu.
Don't believe them.
That's how they deceived
the Yan family back then.
If we let Zhao Yang go,
we will still die.
Qingshan Manor, hear my orders!
Capture the King of Great Yan
and Chu Qiao with all your might!
Who dares!
Zhuge Yue,
cooperate with me.
Let's get out of here together.
Zhuge Yue.
I gave you a choice once.
I wanted you to leave with me.
You gave up that path yourself.
Now,
I am Zhuge Yue, Chief of Qingshan Manor.
You're lying.
You only came back to Qingshan Manor
to save me.
Zhuge Yue,
let's go together.
You're wrong.
Even without you,
the blood of the Zhuge family
still flows in my veins.
I'm destined to belong to
Qingshan Manor for all my life.
There should be a clear line
between you and me.
Zhuge Yue,
this is not what you truly think.
What you truly think
is that as a member of the Zhuge family,
you don't want to become like them.
You never lived freely or comfortably
because every moment in Qingshan Manor
brought you pain and contempt!
Do you think you know me that well?
I know you,
Zhuge Yue.
I know you just as well as you know me.
Well then,
I'll tell you now.
However many blood debts
Qingshan Manor bears,
I bear them too.
In Yan Shicheng's case,
I was the one who handed the evidence
of his rebellion to His Majesty.
I knew it was fake,
and I knew what price the Yan family
would pay for it.
You don't believe me?
Then ask him.
Yan Xun,
is everything he said true?
Why did you never tell me?
Because I thought
he still had a shred of conscience.
I thought leaving you in my care
was truly a temporary measure.
But I didn't expect him to still choose
his Qingshan Manor
and the Zhuge family.
Do you really think
you can help me escape the Zhuge family?
Ridiculous.
Abolishing slavery and stopping wars?
Justice and freedom?
Open your eyes and see
who you really helped.
If you hadn't implemented
new policies in Ximeng,
Great Yong would never have had
the slightest interest
in such a barren land.
You thought you were helping
Yan Xun escape Zhenhuangcheng.
Now take a good look.
After all this,
hasn't he ended up right back here?
Yan Xun,
you are the new King of Great Yan.
Are you really willing to give up
the people of Great Yan
and your throne for a slave girl?
Chu Qiao, a criminal slave of Great Yong,
has conspired with Yan Xun,
King of Great Yan,
to rebel against Great Yong.
Qingshan Manor, listen to my command!
-Here!
Arrest them both!
-Yes!
Wait!
His Majesty has an order.
Release Empress Dowager Xiuli of Biantang
and King of Great Yan,
Yan Xun, immediately.
Young Master Zhuge,
do you just let them go
without doing anything?
They attempted to assassinate me
and Father.
This is His Majesty's order.
Don't use Father to scare me!
They deserve to die
for attempting to assassinate me!
Your Highness the Thirteenth Prince,
Biantang sent envoys
to ask His Majesty to release them.
Please consider the big picture,
and do not disobey His Majesty's will.
Fire! Fire!
An ominous sign! An ominous sign!
This is the Faceless God's punishment!
The Thirteenth Prince
has angered the Faceless God!
Is it really
the Faceless God's punishment?
Pass my orders.
Qingshan Manor spies
and imperial guard will split up.
One team to close the city gates
and put out the fire,
and the other to protect the civilians.
-Yes!
-Come, put out the fire!
-Over here!
Hurry!
Yang.
My Yang.
Your Majesty,
the Thirteenth Prince was murdered
by poison.
Why?
Zhao Che,
I know you've always coveted the throne
and seen Yang as a thorn in your side,
a thorn in your flesh.
Do you think I don't know
what you're planning?
You have talent,
and you have a strategy.
You also have wild ambitions.
Wild ambitions.
That's right.
I killed Zhao Yang.
Father.
Is this the path I wanted to take?
I entered the army at 13.
I lived a life of bloodshed.
Ten years of life and death on the border—
I never harbored any disloyal thoughts.
But you, Father,
you don't trust me,
testing me at every step
and suspecting me every day.
No matter how hard I try
or how loyal I remain,
I'm only labeled as wildly ambitious.
I only wanted to defend this country
and protect its people.
But Father,
it was you.
You forced me onto this path of no return!
I fought bloody battles
on the battlefield,
surviving 34 campaigns.
A fifth of Great Yong
was bought with my life!
I narrowly escaped death countless times.
But in the end,
all I got is your wariness,
and being trampled on by Zhao Yang,
such an absurd and incompetent person!
Yang was absurd,
but he wouldn't hurt you!
You are wrong, Father.
What you mean is,
he wouldn't hurt you, right?
Because he was simple and foolish.
Therefore,
relying heavily on him
makes you feel much safer
than relying on a capable
and accomplished son.
I fought bloody battles
on the battlefield,
fighting through mountains of swords
and seas of blood.
But Zhao Yang
was indulging in debauchery
and fighting his brothers.
Why should I
be beneath someone like him?
Today, I've rebelled,
confirming your suspicions.
I have become a traitor in your eyes.
But Father,
is everything I've done
really my fault?
Please write an edict
to make me the Crown Prince.
Here is His Majesty's edict.
From now on,
the Seventh Prince Zhao Che is appointed
as the Crown Prince.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
-Paying respects to you, Your Highness.
From this moment on,
seal the city gates immediately.
No one is allowed to leave Zhenhuangcheng.
Your Highness,
the envoys from Biantang
are still in the city.
How should we deal with them?
Execute them all.
Yes.
[Qingshan Manor]
I promised you
that if you could capture Chu Qiao,
her life or death
would be yours to decide.
But today,
you let her and Yan Xun escape.
Rest assured, Your Highness.
The captains at each gate have checked
that Yan Xun and Chu Qiao
haven't left the city.
I won't let her interfere with our plan.
If they escape back to Great Yan,
they will definitely come back
with the army of Great Yan
to attack us just like before
and start a war among Great Yan,
Biantang, and Great Yong.
When that time comes,
I'm afraid I'll have to break my promise.
Reporting, General,
the soldiers of Great Yong
have been following us.
I couldn't get any news
about Zhenhuangcheng.
We came all the way via the official road.
Several groups of troops
were heading towards Zhenhuangcheng.
Something big must have happened
in Zhenhuangcheng.
I have to go back and save Yan Xun.
Stay here and help me hold them off.
Yes.
Why is the Yong Army here?
General Huan,
should we go up and ask?
His Highness the Crown Prince
invites you to the palace.
I have been waiting here for a long time.
His Highness the Crown Prince?
Since when did Great Yong
have a Crown Prince?
General Huan, you might not know.
His Majesty has issued an official decree,
naming the Seventh Prince Zhao Che
as the Crown Prince.
Zhao Che.
The wound has been bandaged.
We don't have medicine here.
You have to endure it for a while.
That day, Zhao Yang
suddenly died on the altar.
Zhenhuangcheng is under martial law now.
The city gates are closed.
We can't leave for now.
Yan Xun,
did I make the wrong choice?
If
Zhuge Yue and I had left Ximeng,
this wouldn't be happening now.
Chu,
you used to never
speculate on things
that had already happened.
Chu,
before I met you,
I always thought
that everyone had their own destiny.
Slaves have their destiny,
heir apparents have theirs,
and princesses have theirs too.
But who made these rules?
I never thought about that.
It was you
who told me not to accept my fate
during the darkest time of my life.
You changed my destiny
and the destinies of many others,
including the people of Ximeng.
You've brought a ray of light
to this dark world.
Even if it's faint,
it's enough for many people to watch it
and keep living.
When I was little,
at every sacrifice,
I stood at the very back.
I always dreamed of getting closer
to take a close look
at the portraits and memorial tablets
of the ancestors of Great Yong.
Until today,
I can get so close
and see clearly for the first time.
Huan Huan.
We have similar backgrounds.
Neither of us had the protection
of parents since childhood.
We had to fight for everything on our own.
You surely can understand me.
I know.
Without parents' protection
and relying on yourself all the way,
it must have been extremely hard.
Huan Huan.
I've spent half my life on the battlefield
and never been attracted to a woman,
until I met you.
If you are willing
to represent the 13 tribes of Great Yan
and not make an enemy of Great Yong,
Great Yong and Great Yan
will cease fire forever.
Then the past grievances
can also be written off.
But...
Huan Huan.
I'm not someone who loves killing and war.
I hope Great Yong and Great Yan
can live in peace.
I hope even more to stand with you.
Huan Huan.
I will definitely become
the master of Zhenhuangcheng.
What is this?
This is an item
of the Great Yong royal family.
Each prince has one,
bearing his own unique pattern
and his rank.
♪ The dust in the world ♪
I give it to you.
♪ Is blown away easily by the wind ♪
Is this a love token?
♪ Who can stay calm ♪
This is the interest on that donkey.
♪ And not be scared? ♪
♪ A slight ripple ♪
♪ Floating life hangs by a thread ♪
♪ The more pulled, the softer it gets ♪
♪ Who dares to say forever? ♪
♪ Let it be ♪
Then my donkey
♪ Grudges and grace
were never meant to be ♪
is too cheap, isn't it?
♪ Why must you take and demand so much? ♪
♪ Go weaving ♪
♪ Grand and glorious excuses ♪
Huan Huan,
♪ We face ♪
I want to be with you like this forever.
♪ The heavy thunderstorm together ♪
♪ Even with extreme pain ♪
♪ We don't even wince ♪
♪ Why in this world ♪
♪ The staunchest heart
and strongest soul ♪
♪ Yield so easily to gentle warmth? ♪
♪ We once beheld ♪
♪ A mirage on earth ♪
♪ Beauty never ♪
♪ Lasts for long ♪
♪ No matter how a jade is carved ♪
♪ It's just a stone ♪
♪ It will eventually disappear ♪
Zhao Che,
I really like you.
But I was born in Great Yan,
destined to be one of them all my life.
I can't let go of Great Yan
and join Great Yong.
Let's treat last night
as a beautiful dream.
When we meet again,
you will be the Crown Prince
of Great Yong,
and I can only be General Huan
of Great Yan.
When we meet on the battlefield,
there's no need to show mercy.
You promised me before
that you wouldn't let Chu Qiao
interfere with our plan.
Eradicate the evil
and destroy the disrespectful!
If you don't leave now,
you won't be able to leave.
Then thank you, Young Master Zhuge.
You can't die without my order!
You told me
that as long as I took good care of Chu,
you would come back.
Huan Huan.
Capture the King of Great Yan immediately.