=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 7=
Let me change your dressing.
Only a minor wound.
I don't need tending.
Wan,
go get some rest first.
Then I'll head back.
Stay at Lin Mansion these days
to heal your wounds.
Commandant Xia and I are at camp.
Don't worry.
I've already seen
all of you before.
Even if you're dressed,
it won't restore your honor anyway.
No need to care
about the mortal form.
Your Grace, I didn't know you'd come.
Sorry.
When did you, Meng Wan,
and Xia Qingsheng first meet?
After I returned to Nandu from Daizhou,
we studied under Academician Yang.
That was all
after you turned 18.
How is it that every friend
and teacher you name
came into your life after that?
What were you doing before you were 18?
The master blinded by a goose
was your teacher
before 18, wasn't he?
Was the amnesiac Han Lingqiu
your friend before you were 18?
My master
was from before I turned 18,
but Han was not.
I had no friends before I was 18.
Who are you, really?
Duan Xu.
Duan Shunxi.
Your Grace,
please…
Please show mercy.
Your martial arts are superb.
Why not struggle?
Why not resist?
Before absolute power,
skill means nothing.
I can't defeat you.
Other than begging,
I have no other way.
What if I don't spare you?
You wish
to keep my skull, right?
When I reach 50,
my skull will look even finer.
Why not wait a while
until I turn 50
and devour me then?
I won't harm you.
I want to make a deal with you.
I'm listening.
The deal is simple.
I will grant
one of your wishes.
In return,
you will lend me your five senses.
One wish,
one sense.
For ten days.
During those ten days,
I will lose that sense.
That's right.
This is the limit
a mortal body can bear.
After ten days,
I will return your senses
to you.
Once you recover,
we begin the next exchange.
That means
you may ask many wishes of me,
but wishes have their limits.
They can't alter the mortal world.
For example,
you may wish for me
to save your life in battle,
but you may not wish
for me to win the war for you.
What if I do not agree?
We have come this far already.
You no longer get to refuse.
Must we speak in this position?
What is wrong with it?
You are not light;
you are quite cold.
General,
I fetched this medicine
for you.
I...
Commandant Xia.
Where are you going?
I made some food.
I'm taking it to Xu.
I just saw the General.
He's not hungry.
No need for this.
And you would know if he is hungry?
Xu has gone all day
without one hot bite.
Move. Or it'll go cold soon.
What are you doing? Xia...
This wasn't for you.
Fine.
Xia Qingsheng,
just you wait.
Miss He,
you and the General
have really ruined me.
Your Grace,
is this your first trade for the senses?
It's a trifling matter.
I paid it no mind.
So, you admit it.
You came near me
for the Deliverance.
I believe
the one who can trade with you
must be the Deliverance's master.
When the old man gave me
the sword, he said
the Deliverance
had no master for 300 years.
By that reckoning,
I am the fated one
you waited
for 300 years for.
Just a pastime on my rest day.
Don't flatter yourself.
How many years have you lived
without the five senses?
We don't need such things.
What a pity, then.
Nothing to pity.
Those are only the cravings
of you mortals.
I mean myself.
I've thought about it,
yet I can't think
of a single wish.
Your Grace,
I never make wishes.
For hundreds of years,
I've dealt with countless mortals,
yet never have I heard one
truly say,
"No need."
"I have lived well"
"and can rest in peace."
"I want nothing at all."
No exception.
Let alone you.
I never ask others
to grant my desires.
Had I not saved you today,
you'd have fallen to the Chong troops.
On the battlefield, life hangs thin.
Are you certain that without my aid,
you could escape death every time?
No matter what,
thank you for today.
General,
you are too young.
You must know fate is ever-shifting,
beyond any mortal's grasp.
Fate is ever-shifting,
but so am I.
Was the look yesterday
your true form?
I remember your robes
were exquisitely ornate,
unlike the mortals'.
If you're curious,
go dig up a few tombs
from 400 years ago.
You'll see enough.
So, you're 400 years old?
You're reluctant
to see me go, right?
So, I won't leave.
I'll sleep here tonight.
Come on, then.
I'll be unable
to sleep again.
Shall I share my pillow
with you?
In the dead of night,
with a spirit lying in your bed,
aren't you afraid?
I do feed on people, you know.
We fight over land,
till the dead blanket the fields.
We fight over cities,
till the dead fill every street.
We seize land at the cost of the living.
By that measure,
we're of the same trade.
And you said you couldn't sleep.
Foxy,
not a word from you is true.
But looking at you now,
I don't think you're so clever.
More like a rabbit.
Han.
Han,
what on earth is going on?
The General locked me up.
I don't know what's going on.
Han,
I know.
You must be innocent.
If it's hard for you
to say certain things,
tell me instead.
I'll plead with the General.
The innocent need no defense.
I trust the General.
He will clear my name.
Han,
rest easy.
With me here,
I won't let you suffer this wrong.
Xiaoxiao,
yesterday, the General
brought grain back
and distributed it again.
We're not short of food here.
Best to be prepared.
But Xiaoxiao,
don't worry.
Lin told me
that as long as we stay here,
we will not go short of food.
You seem
to be close to everyone.
You like him?
Of course.
Lin is
kind to everyone.
He also helped the General a lot,
procuring and distributing grain.
Besides the General,
he is everyone's hero too.
Xiaoxiao,
you always eat so little.
I know you can't bear to eat more,
because you save the best for me.
You even fainted from hunger before.
But Xiaoxiao,
we have enough grain now.
You needn't starve yourself anymore.
Young Master.
Young Master, this is bad.
(Ultimate Joy)
The master was caught
and brought below the city.
Young Master.
Let's go.
Xiaoxiao,
do you think Lin
might be in danger?
You want to go see?
Uncle.
- Uncle.
- Mr. Lin.
Master Lin.
Talk with the ones
on the wall.
They are
your family.
(Lin Huaide, main branch)
Jun.
I'm here.
Have you received the provisions?
They're here.
Is it enough?
Yes.
Thanks, Mr. Lin.
Jun.
Your grandfather
was once a general of Great Liang.
He fell in Yunzhou and never returned.
Your grandmother
would not flee south
of the Guanhe River.
Because of that,
your father was born.
He stayed in Shuozhou
and built up this family estate.
All these years,
we've bowed to the Chong people.
But you must remember
whose hands
claimed your forebears.
Your grandmother once said,
"If one day"
"Great Liang"
"crosses the Guanhe River
to reclaim the land,"
"though we're merchants,"
"we will give all our strength"
"and never shrink from death."
No!
Jun, listen carefully.
Hold on at all costs.
I came to see you today
to tell you this:
I'm going
to answer to your grandfather.
I will tell him
our clan didn't fail him.
Jun,
you didn't fail him.
One day, surely,
the land will return,
bringing back the golden age.
No!
Kill them.
My father
was slain the same way.
He was unarmed,
cut down like livestock.
General Duan,
was it worth it to trade
23 lives of the Lin clan
for these carts of grain?
Soon, I will take
your head
to console the 23 souls
of the Lin clan above.
Withdraw the troops.
Yes.
(Chongde Chamber)
Young Master,
you've eaten nothing
since yesterday.
The dead can't return.
(Memorial Tablet of Master Huaide)
Master Huaide
would not wish to see this.
(Memorial)
Mr. Lin,
my condolences.
(Memorial Tablet of Master Huaide)
Shuozhou is in grave peril now.
I still need your support.
For the sake of the whole city,
you must pull yourself together soon.
Mr. Lin,
I've failed the Lin clan.
General, do not blame yourself.
All men must die one day.
Uncle
was only betrayed by traitors.
Please rest assured.
I've sent men to recover
all the remains
for burial.
I heard your father died young.
Your uncle cared for you
as if he were your own father.
I know the Lin clan has suffered,
and your heart is heavy.
But right now,
I need your help.
Please agree.
What is it?
It concerns the spy who tipped off
the Chong Army
and got your uncle killed.
But I heard
you've had Captain Han…
I've locked up
Han Lingqiu.
Han Lingqiu
is from North Chong.
He claims he lost his memory,
but too much does not add up.
He lost his memory?
His martial arts style
resembles the Chong people's.
I suspect
he is a spy sent by the Chong Army.
I wish to hold a martial contest
to test his true skills.
I heard you're also
fond of martial arts
and have several skilled guests at home.
May I ask them
to come as well
and face Han Lingqiu in a match?
General,
I am but a humble merchant.
Why entrust the contest
to me?
The Lin clan is loyal.
In the whole army now,
the one I trust most
is only you.
Leave it to me.
The General wants me to fight?
I must win,
yet preserve my strength,
and not reveal it unless forced.
Why?
The General's order is just that.
Are you willing to obey?
(Zhang Mansion)
Are you there?
You've arranged
everything already.
So, you knew it all?
I had guessed most of it.
When this round is over,
we'll see how much you can guess.
You scramble for power and gain
with the same old routine.
I am long tired of watching it.
Tomorrow's show
is more than a hunt for spies.
Your Grace, do be patient,
and watch until the very end.
I will not disappoint you.
Then I'll wait and see.
Do not let me down.
(Liang)
The martial contest begins.
Contestants, enter the arena.
(Wu Junyi, Han Lingqiu)
Captain Han Lingqiu wins.
(Sun Xiu, Han Lingqiu)
(Liang)
Next contestant, enter the arena.
(Ge Tian, Han Lingqiu)
(Zhou Yi'ang, Han Lingqiu)
(Wang Shuo, Han Lingqiu)
Next contestant, enter the arena.
(Lin Mo, Han Lingqiu)
(Han Sheng, Han Lingqiu)
Captain Han Lingqiu wins.
Han,
make your move.
General,
if this keeps up,
we won't see Captain Han's skill.
I've heard that there is
a blindfolded contest
in the Jianghu.
Both sides must judge the position
by the sound of the wind.
It best shows one's martial arts.
Very well.
Anyway,
no winner is clear now.
Let's do it.
Captain Han Lingqiu wins.
Steward,
prepare cloth for blindfolds.
Yes.
The match is suspended.
Captain Han Lingqiu wins.
Han is that skilled?
What a surprise.
How is it that I
never knew this before?
Everyone,
during our time in Shuozhou,
Miss He's carriage
was attacked,
and the provisions were burned.
While seizing the grain,
we ran into an ambush,
and Master Huaide was betrayed.
All these incidents point to one thing:
There is a Chong spy
among us.
Could it really be Captain Han?
I never knew his skills
were this formidable.
Only today
have I finally confirmed
who that spy truly is.
Who is it?
What is going on?
It can't be Captain Han.
Captain Han?
Mr. Lin,
what do you say?
Perhaps I should ask you
where you've hidden
the real Lin Jun
since we entered the inner city?
Is this not Lin Jun, Mr. Lin?
Yes.
What does that mean?
General,
what do you mean by that?
You suspect I'm a spy?
It's not suspicion.
I'm certain.
Mr. Lin,
may I borrow a carriage?
You honor me, General.
It's a small matter.
Miss He's carriage was attacked.
Han Lingqiu was riding with her.
But the carriage was yours.
General Duan,
may I ease the Tabai Army's burden?
I'll send half my men
to guard the granary.
Thank you, Mr. Lin.
You know
the granary defenses,
the time of the grain raid,
and letters from Master Huaide.
When the Chong people send grain here,
they must pass through
several northern cities.
Our clan has kin in the north.
I sent carrier pigeons to them
to track the grain convoy.
And what does that prove?
I truly did not know
the All-Knowing's Blindfolded Trial
was a rule of jianghu.
Master Fifteen.
Don't come over.
Or I'll end him.
Lin,
I always took you for a real man.
Your uncle
met a grim end below the city wall.
I even felt
I had wronged the Lin clan.
Who would've thought
you were the one who sold him out?
He isn't Lin Jun.
He was only in disguise.
So, the man he sold out
wasn't his own uncle.
That's right.
I am the real Lin Jun.
He seized me
and copied my every move.
He deceived every one of you.
Perfect timing.
I had thought
Lin was a good man.
But I saw him yesterday.
Lin…
I told Xiaoxiao
about this matter.
She told me
to bring the real Lin here today.
You cur!
How dare you deceive us!
You are not leaving today.
You've lost your memory?
What does it have
to do with you?
Without your memory,
you'd be forgivable.
You should be my 17th junior brother.
Come back with me to see Mentor.
Stop talking nonsense.
I am Han Lingqiu,
Captain of Great Liang's Tabai Army.
That's my only identity.
Even if I die,
I'll never go with you.
You were once
Mentor's favorite.
Now, you can't tell right from wrong.
Even Captain Han ignores you now.
Surrender without a fight.
Fool.
As long as I have you,
they won't dare make a move.
Get a horse for me.
I'm leaving the city.
Follow my orders.
Get him a horse.
Let him leave.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪