[techno music playing]
[Morgan] Sorry, so you've just
been having sex this whole time
and just… just keeping it from us? Hmm.
I wouldn't say the whole time.
It's been, like, a year.
A year?
Oh my God. Where are you having sex,
like, in your rectory?
I'm not answering that question.
No offense 'cause you just kind of--
You really present as someone
who hasn't had sex
in a long, like, a long time.
"No offense"?
What, you want me walking around
with a big old erection all the time?
Ew, no.
Just waving it around so that you can know
that I'm having sex? No.
[Morgan] Just saying you don't seem like
you're being dicked down by a contractor.
[Nicky] Okay, cool. That's kind.
[funky music playing]
[Morgan] A year. A year of your life.
[music continues]
-[Morgan] Are you guys open or monog?
-[Nicky] Yeah.
-[Morgan] You're open.
-I'm just-- It's a revolving door of men.
-[Morgan] Oh.
-At this point. Yup.
-[Morgan] It's different for y'all.
-[Nicky] Nope, it's just a relationship.
[music ends]
[Morgan] Holy shit.
A private jet. What is going on here?
-[Morgan gasps]
-Oh, I can get those-- Okay.
Okay, well, I know we haven't exactly
been on the same page lately,
but can we just stop and enjoy the fact
that we are going to Miami
on a private jet.
-Wow.
-[pilot] Champagne, sir?
-Uh… Thank you. Thank you very much.
-Thank you. Hi.
[music resumes]
[exhales] Now you're acting like
someone who's getting laid.
Morgan, what?
Leave my sex life out of this.
[Morgan] I can't.
[Morgan] Ooh!
[guns cocking]
-[music intensifies]
-[guns loading]
Jesus Christ.
[opening theme music playing]
[music ends]
-There they are.
-[Andrei chuckles]
-[Ivan] Okay. Okay, come, my friends.
-[whispers] What the fuck, Morgan?
So, how was the car ride? Comfy?
-Yeah, yeah.
-Huh?
-The driver knew where he was going?
-Yeah, we're on the plane, so…
-Okay.
-[Morgan clears throat]
Have a seat.
Thank you.
So, we found the guy.
It's an amateur.
It should be resolved soon.
Okay, but not, like, "resolved" resolved.
We're talking just get the money,
and then it's done.
[Ivan clicks tongue]
[guns clicking]
Sorry, are we gonna talk about
who they are?
Security. Don't worry about them.
-[pilot] Doors closed. Wheels up.
-[door thuds]
-So…
-[Morgan clears throat]
-[inhales] Here we are.
-[engine starts]
Eight people responsible
for changing the face
of the central New Jersey cocaine market.
Yeah. [laughs]
[Ivan] Now all we have to do
is reassure the Brazilians
we have what it takes
to move their product.
[in Russian] To prosperity and survival!
-[men toasting in Russian]
-[laughing]
-What did he say? What was the last part?
-I don't know. Why would I know that?
[Ivan] Lady and gentlemens.
[engine powering up]
-To Miami.
-[all] Hurrah!
["Gosh" by Jamie xx playing]
♪ Hold it down ♪
♪ Oh gosh ♪
♪ Oh my gosh ♪
♪ Easy, easy ♪
[music stops abruptly]
[vehicles honking loudly]
[Morgan] Okay. Not gonna lie,
this was not the Miami I hoped for
fresh off a private jet.
Well, It's humid,
and I'm pretty sure we passed
a group of people burning a pile of books
on our way in from the airport,
so we're definitely in Florida.
[Morgan] Yeah.
[Morgan] Okay, what is going on out there?
-[Ivan yelling indistinctly]
-[car honking]
[Morgan] Okay…
[sighs heavily] This is not good.
What's not good?
The Brazilians were supposed to
meet us here 20 minutes ago.
-And? What… what… what does that mean?
-[doorbell tinkling]
It means something's not right.
Hey. [exhales]
[cheerfully] Hello, hello! Hey!
Hey.
-[Ivan clears throat]
-And?
[exhales] We're good, we're good.
Everything is good.
We just-- yeah, we have small…
change of plan. [breathes deeply]
-[in Russian] Jackass, bitches!
-[china clinking]
The Brazilians want to meet
at their house for dinner.
The plan was to meet somewhere neutral.
-I know that was the plan!
-Their house is not neutral.
Do you know what he's saying?
[Ivan] They didn't give another option!
I don't know how this is helpful.
What do you want me to do, say no?
They threatened to call off the deal.
This is not good!
I hate when they do this.
Is there something wrong
or is there nothing wrong?
What's up? Like…
You have something nice
to wear for dinner?
Define "nice." I brought an overnight bag.
I have, like, a, uh-- like,
a couple of going-out tops,
but I don't know how nice they are.
Also, should I cancel Mango's?
Feel like we're not going?
I was never going to Mango's.
What the fuck did you bring this for, huh?
Like, for if we go to a club.
-Go to a club?
-Club?
What the fuck did you think
was going on here? Huh?
Okay, go get
something expensive you can return.
I need you to look like
you could be taken seriously, okay?
["NAILS" by Noga Erez playing]
♪ Oh, look at what the cat brought in ♪
♪ It ain't smarts, baby
Just a muscle game ♪
♪ Your mouse ain't runnin'
Don't blame the wheel ♪
♪ L-loop in like, oops, I did it again ♪
♪ Now sharp your nails
All the sad ones on the meds ♪
♪ Sharp your nails
All the bad ones ♪
No security.
Oh, um, actually, no, no,
I… I… I would like to… to bring security.
Morgan, it's okay.
We'll call them if anything goes wrong.
[in Russian] They want you to stay behind.
Keep your phones on.
Open the trunk.
[Andrei speaking Russian]
[Andrei in Russian] Check this out.
[Andrei in English] Nice.
What the fuck is this?
It's fruit that looks like flowers.
Andrei, I told you to get a nice gift.
We're meeting with the Brazilian cartel.
You think they want $500 worth of fruit?
The Brazilian cartel?
Did you know that we were doing
a drug deal with the Brazilian cartel?
I didn't even know
there was a Brazilian cartel.
What? Have you never seen Sicario?
Those guys insulate their walls
with dead bodies.
Do I look like I've seen Sicario?
Look at this cellophane. The chocolate,
it's coming off. It's disgusting.
Leave it in the car.
Hey. Okay, let's go.
-[Morgan] Hey.
-[Ivan exhales]
[man in Brazilian Portuguese] Frisk them.
[Nicky] All right, wow.
-[guard] Cell phones.
-[sighs]
[tense music playing]
[Ivan] Okay. Okay.
[Ivan] Okay.
-[Morgan] Hey, listen.
-What?
-Just to be totally clear…
-Huh?
…we cannot return this expensive dress
if there's blood all over it.
Let's stick to our talking points, okay?
Now, now, if you don't have an answer
to something, don't speak.
Let us take the lead.
Just, you know, look confident.
-Like you've done this before.
-Have you done this before?
Morgan, fuck off.
[music continues]
Hey.
-[greets in Brazilian Portuguese]
-[Ivan greets in Brazilian Portuguese]
[in Brazilian Portuguese]
You can leave, they're with me.
[host in English] Forgive my friends
for the warm welcome.
[chuckles] I hope
they weren't too impolite.
-[Ivan] No, not at all, not at all. No.
-Yeah?
Well, if I knew we were dressing up,
I would have put on a jacket.
-[host] Come, let's go.
-[Ivan] Yeah, yeah.
-[host] How was the trip?
-[Ivan] It was good.
I feel ridiculous.
[funky music playing]
[host] Okay, guys,
make yourselves at home.
[Ivan] Wow.
[tense music playing]
[people speaking indistinctly]
[music ends]
Hi. Can I just get
a shot of, like, anything?
[upbeat music playing]
[Morgan sighs]
[Nicky] I feel like
that guy is staring at us,
and I just… I have this creeping suspicion
that he knows we're not legit.
Oh, um, yeah, no.
Nicky, listen, listen. [smacks lips]
-If things go south tonight…
-Uh-huh.
…I want you to know that I know
how much space I take up in our lives.
Yeah? And?
Well-- No, nothing.
I'm just, like, acknowledging the fact
that we're basically in Halloween costumes
in front of a bunch of cartel members.
And if that doesn't end well,
I have some, like,
feelings I want to release.
I don't think that's necessary.
I'm messy, and I'm rude.
I know that, okay?
I can't, like, seem to
figure my shit out. [inhales]
But these are the things
I want to get off my chest
in case this is
my last opportunity to do this.
Things I don't want to die with.
[people chattering indistinctly]
-You think we're going to die here?
-Mm.
I think that the chances of that
are higher than I did before.
-What the fuck?
-Yeah. No, but listen.
[music continues]
I forgive you, okay?
-For what? What for?
-Yeah, I forgive you for everything.
-What? But what, specifically?
-[bell chimes]
I'm trying to get to the bottom of what--
Oh, fuck.
[tense music playing]
[Nicky] Who is that?
-[Nicky] Well, that man is terrifying.
-[Morgan] He's important.
[music ends]
Well, that was fucking bone-chilling.
[dramatic music playing]
[Morgan clears throat]
[music fades]
Uh… Paolo, uh, so, thank you so much.
What the fuck is that?
Claudia, where did that come from?
Uh, yeah, yeah. It… it wasn't meant to be
paraded in front of the party like that.
It's fruit that looks like flowers.
Anyway, we have-- We have lots to discuss.
We don't talk business at a table.
-It's bad manners.
-Oh, sure.
And speaking of bad manners,
it's always nice to know in advance
who's coming for dinner.
This dude don't look like
a Turkish man from Istanbul.
[Ivan chuckles nervously]
Yeah, uh… l, uh, I apologize.
We-- we had a last-minute change of--
Well, I don't like last-minute additions
to my dessert cart.
And certainly, I don't like
last-minute additions to my dinner table.
[Ivan] Sure, sure. Um…
[Paolo] Are you going to
introduce yourselves?
-Yeah. Do you… do you want to…
-Okay.
[Nicky] Or do you want me to?
-Oh… Okay.
-You can do it.
-I-- I'll take it. Um… [clears throat]
-Okay.
-Hey, y'all. I am Morgan Dardano.
-Y'all?
-This is my brother, Nicholas Dardano…
-Uh-huh.
…and we work with Ivan and Andrei on…
-Transportation.
-Yes, transportation side of things. Um…
[Paolo] Uh, you see, I could have sworn
that you teach kids
at Glenview Elementary,
and you're a pastor
at a community church in New Jersey.
-I… I do.
-I…
[Paolo] Oh, well, then I'm confused.
Are you two handling transportation,
or are you a public servant
and a servant of God?
-[Nicky clears throat]
-Or both.
Yeah, which ultimately benefits everyone.
I mean, we fly under the radar…
-[Morgan] Mm-hmm.
-…which is your biggest asset.
And correct me if I'm wrong,
but don't you want the people
handling logistics for a… a drug…
-Can I say drugs? Drug route…
-Yeah. No judgment.
…you know, to be the last two people
that law enforcement would ever suspect?
We have clean slates
and no criminal records. So…
-I do have… I have one DUI. But…
-That doesn't…
She got it when she was 17,
and it's been wiped from her record.
-True. No points.
-Very little to do with this.
-We are an incredibly value-addition…
-Bottom line… Bottom line…
Bottom line here I think
is we want to apologize.
Okay, okay, okay. Fuck!
That's enough.
[insects chirping]
Who's hungry?
[chuckles]
[guitar music playing]
[plates clinking]
For you.
To try.
Just in case we have
some federal agents in our company.
[music ends]
-Mm-hmm. I've never done this before.
-Just do what I do.
[metal straws clinking]
[percussive music playing]
[Morgan snorts]
[clears throat, sniffs]
[Morgan clears throat]
[music ends]
[snorting]
[Morgan] Oh, wow.
It's really good.
[Nicky sniffles, exhales]
[Paolo] Tonight, we welcome you.
-[Paolo toasting in Brazilian Portuguese]
-[all toasting in Brazilian Portuguese]
[club music playing]
What do you mean, you forgive me?
What is that? I don't like
the way that makes me feel.
Oh my God, I'm sorry that you don't like
how it makes you feel, genuinely.
I think that you care about a lot
of people, and-- I'm not one of them.
Of course I care about you, Morgan.
-I do. You're my sister.
-Okay.
That's an inherently given thing.
Like, I shouldn't have to
say that out loud.
Some families do say that out loud.
Some families do.
-Some families do.
-Okay.
And sometimes I wish that you would admit
that you kind of abandoned me
when Mom and Dad were breaking up.
-Abandoned you?
-You did.
I went to seminary, Morgan.
What do you want me to do?
Why, to go be a hero?
Meanwhile, I'm at home with Mom.
She's losing her mind. Where were you?
-Nowhere to be found.
-I didn't know you needed me to check in.
I did not know that, okay?
Your two favorite words at the time
were "fuck off."
Oh, reverse psychology.
Did you ever think that maybe
that was my way of saying I need you?
That's fucked-up, Morgan. If that's how
you tell people you need them.
What am I, a mind reader?
Also, I looked up to you.
I did not know. You gave me
none of this information.
I am sorry, Morgan.
-Thank you for saying that.
-I'm sincerely apologetic.
-I'm so sorry. I… Yes, I feel so bad.
-I can tell it's coming from your heart.
I will not judge you
if you want to do that.
[chuckles] I…
Like, I… I might, but it's not gonna be
for the reasons you think it's gonna be.
Like, this has been a good medicinal tool
for us in terms of communication.
Communication-wise,
this has been really good.
Yeah, you don't have to explain it to me.
I also really love cocaine.
I understand why this is a thing.
Like, I understand why people like this.
-Yes.
-I understand why people get addicted.
You can't get addicted to it.
It's a personality thing.
There's, like, a pile of this.
Should I try, like, right in?
-I would love to see someone do that.
-That's crazy. That'd be fucking crazy.
-Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it.
-I don't want-- No. I can't.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
[snorts]
[laughs] Oh my God.
[muffled music continues]
[sniffs]
[door opens]
Sorry, there's someone in here.
[door closes]
[Nicky] Uh…
Oh, okay. All right.
Um, can I help you with something?
Well, you tell me.
You've been staring at me
all night.
[spluttering] You were staring at me,
I thought.
-Because you were staring at me.
-Okay.
Now, as a pastor who looks at men,
I thought this could be our secret.
[inhales] I think-- I think
there were some crossed wires here.
I think there might have been
a mi-- a miscommunication.
Why? You don't look at men?
Come on.
-You seem very gay to me.
-[laughs]
Well, I mean, I do look at men.
I just… I have a boyfriend, so…
Oh.
-Is kissing bad?
-Well…
-Because in Brazil…
-Mm-hmm.
…we kiss to say hello.
-And to say goodbye.
-[mouths] Oh my God.
Uh-huh.
I think I'm just… Uh…
I'm a little more concerned about
what happens after the kissing, and…
-Mmm.
-And we're not open, um…
Even though now I'm regretting
not having that conversation, but, I--
Yeah, I just… I don't think
we should kiss, uh, goodbye or hello.
-[inhales]
-So why were you staring at me?
I thought-- I thought
maybe you didn't tru-- Uh, trust me.
-Why wouldn't I trust you?
-I don't…
You know I'm not like my father, right?
Sorry, who's your father?
Paolo, you met him earlier.
We don't really get along that well.
Paolo is your father?!
-Hey, hey, hey. Shh!
-Okay. Shh.
This is a secret.
-[whispers] Don't scream like this.
-I won't.
Let's just say that my father
wouldn't be very happy
if he knew
I was in this bathroom with you.
Well, then why are we in here? [laughs]
We should probably not be in here, then.
-You're not going to tell anyone?
-No, of course not.
-Nobody knows.
-Oh.
I just want to keep it private for now.
You understand that, right?
Of course, of course.
Of course I understand that.
You know, and I'm-- I am really sorry,
Jesus, that you have to hide, um,
a part of yourself away.
That's really, really hard.
-Am I the first man you've been with?
-No, no, I fuck a lot.
Oh, okay.
It's just that I mostly fuck male models.
-Okay. Mm-hmm.
-Really tall ones, shredded.
-I fucked this dentist once.
-Oh, right.
-Super hot, had a big dick.
-That's a lot of hot people.
Just people who aren't so close
to my family.
Okay.
This is really risky.
I understand. [inhales]
Listen, if, um…
[smacks lips] If you ever need
to just… talk, you know,
I… I would be more than happy
to offer my services. [inhales]
-I appreciate that. It's a…
-[sniffles, clears throat]
It's a nice feeling knowing that,
you know, my secret is safe with you.
[Nicky] Mm-hmm.
-You're going to keep our secret?
-I will.
-Okay?
-I will, yeah.
-Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh.
-Shh. Shh.
Or else…
[Nicky grunts]
-[mimics gunshot]
-[gagging] Uh-huh.
Uh… That's funny. [laughs]
-I'm kidding.
-[laughing] I know, I know.
-Okay? Don't tell anyone.
-That's…
-Nope. Good.
-Have fun.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Holy fuck.
-Here's to this fucking night!
-[girl] Ooh!
Morgan, we gotta go home.
Oh my God. What is that?
-I don't know. I don't know.
-Can I have some?
-Uh, sure.
-Oh my God. Bye. I love you.
-Get home safe, okay?
-I love you. You too. [blows kiss]
-[Nicky] Who is that?
-[Morgan] Oh, I don't know.
[guitar chord playing]
[gravel crunching]
[Morgan sighs audibly]
Oh… Fuck, uh…
[seagulls calling]
-I'm not okay, Morgan.
-That's the cocaine.
This is what cocaine does?
Why… why… why the fuck
does anyone do cocaine?
Last night you were asking
if you could get a prescription for it.
What? When?
Can you believe this weather, huh?
It's fucking gorgeous. [laughs]
It's the perfect day
to be on the water. [laughs]
-Let's go. [laughs]
-[Nicky] Okay.
Okay, this is the Miami I'm talking about.
[Nicky] You don't feel bad at all?
[Morgan] No.
Cocaine is really good for me.
[greeting in Brazilian Portuguese]
[in English] We have
business to discuss. Please.
[Andrei] What's going on?
They're our people. They come with us.
Don't worry.
Paolo's giving them a tour of the bay.
Uh-uh-uh.
No, we're not leaving them alone.
You are the dealmakers.
You don't want to make a deal?
How can we make a deal
if Paolo's on the boat? Paolo!
I make the deals. He approves them.
[speaks Brazilian Portuguese]
[tense music playing]
[continues speaking]
Wait, what… Uh…
-What's going on?
-Where are they going?
[Paolo] Oh, they have
a deal to make. [laughs]
Where are we going, then?
To have some fun. Let's go.
Oh, no…
[men speaking Brazilian Portuguese]
[unsettling guitar riff playing]
[Paolo laughing]
[music ends]
[upbeat music playing]
[Nicky] Yeah.
Why are criminals so indirect?
Like, why is there this Kabuki theater
around just, like, telling people
what's going on?
I know. It's like, just tell us
you're taking us on a boat to kill us.
I wasn't thinking that, Morgan.
-Now that's all I'm thinking about.
-I was kidding. I was joking, okay?
But, I mean, think about it, Nicky.
What's a better place to dump a body
than on a private yacht
in the middle of the ocean?
They call Mom.
They've ID'd you by your foot.
-It's all that's left of you. [chuckles]
-Uh-huh.
I feel seasick.
[tense music playing]
[gravel crunching]
[music ends]
Where are we?
Let's go.
-Hey. Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
-Huh? What?
-Friend. Friend, what's happening?
-I said, get out.
-Okay.
-[doors slamming]
-[Ivan] Buddy.
-[Andrei] What's going on?
Can-- Can you-- Hey. Help us out here.
What's… What's happening here, huh?
[loud clanking]
Dig.
[insects chirping]
[in Brazilian Portuguese] Now.
[upbeat music playing]
[seagulls calling]
Are you ever going to ask me
why we're here?
[Morgan] Nope.
Tareq was in trouble,
and I offered to come here
in exchange for Ivan and Andrei's help.
Wait, so…
we're stuck out here
with the Brazilian cartel
to help your boyfriend?
Yeah.
I mean, I didn't know it was
the cartel at the time, but yeah.
[Morgan sighs]
And I'm really, really sorry
for getting you involved in this.
[music continues]
[Morgan sighs]
I'm sorry.
I have to end things with Max.
-What?
-[exhales loudly]
I would never do something like that
for him. We've been together 17 years.
[exhales] It's like, I've convinced myself
that there's some, uh, agenda
to your, like… goodness.
Like, it's not genuine or something,
because if it was,
then I would only feel like
a bigger piece of shit,
but there's not.
You're just… you're somehow just
a good person.
It's so annoying.
-Good person?
-Yeah.
Have you been listening to me speak?
I put us both in so much danger.
Whatever, dude. I wanted it.
You know it, I know it.
-Okay.
-Oh.
Fuck.
I think you're just coming off
of a lot of cocaine.
That wasn't a lot of cocaine.
I've done way more than that.
-Excuse me?
-Yeah, that wasn't even a lot.
Morgan, come on. That's scary.
Hey!
-[Nicky] Is he talking to me?
-I…
-Are you talking to me?
-Yes, you. Come.
What the fuck does he want from me?
[tense music playing]
[music ends]
[Andrei grunts]
[Ivan] Sir.
Sir. Look.
We can handle 100 cows a month.
One hundred-- Possibly more.
And we are slowly
inching into their territory,
so the Italians won't see it coming.
Do you want to tell us why the minister
and schoolteacher are actually here?
What? What… what… what do you mean?
We went through this last night.
-I mean--
-I'm asking for the truth.
It has nothing to do
with the Turk going missing?
[insects chirping]
No. Who told you that? No.
[in Brazilian Portuguese] For fuck's sake.
[in English] Do not fuck with me.
If there is a loose end out there,
we need to know about it.
The-- there's nothing to worry about.
Trust me.
[gun cocks]
-[Andrei shouts]
-[shovel clanking]
I took care of him!
[spits]
Yusuf ran away to Turkey.
But I had someone over there
take care of it because… [exhales sharply]
[panting] If there is a problem,
we fix it.
And I will do it again if anything else
gets in the way of our business.
[panting]
So, do we have a deal?
Or do we keep digging? [inhales deeply]
[Andrei breathing heavily]
[upbeat music playing]
[in Brazilian Portuguese] Leave us alone.
[Paolo speaking Brazilian Portuguese]
-[lock clicks]
-Do we need to lock the door? Okay.
-[Paolo] Soundproof.
-Yeah.
-Incredible, right?
-Mm.
It does look thin,
but you can't hear a thing.
-[Nicky chuckles nervously]
-Mm.
Yeah. It's a beautiful boat.
Did you… [inhales deeply]
…sail it here from Brazil or…?
Well, that would be fucking stupid.
No. Mexico.
I'm Mexican.
Oh, I'm… I'm sorry.
I thought you were… from Brazil.
No, no, no. I'm from Sinaloa.
I killed my way to Brazil.
-Just kidding.
-[chuckles nervously]
I just go where the powder blows,
as they say.
Sit.
Come here.
What do you want to drink?
I have a splitting headache,
so just water, please.
I don't like drinking alone.
There's a judgment to it. Tequila?
-Uh… Yep.
-[cork popping]
-You had fun last night?
-Mm.
Dinner plates aren't usually empty.
Sorry about that.
I had to make sure that you were serious.
Oh…
But it was good shit, huh?
Yeah, it was, uh… [sniffs]
Uh… really good shit. Very pure.
-Very nice.
-[Paolo inhales]
So,
I heard that you met my son.
I don't know who your son…
-Filipe.
-Oh.
Yeah, he has a good head of hair?
I think we might have… [inhales]
…crossed paths at the club.
We're very different, he and I.
[Nicky] Okay.
He's a homosexual.
Interesting. [inhales]
-Does he know that you know that…
-No.
Hmm.
It might be nice to… to let him know
that you know and that you're fi--
I won't be doing that.
Hm. I mean, as… as somebody
who has hidden parts of myself away,
I can tell you that, you know,
knowing that your family is on your side,
it… it means the world.
I killed my father with a butter knife.
[phone ringing]
[tense music playing]
[in Brazilian Portuguese] Heitor.
Speak.
You believe him?
Okay then.
Bye-bye.
[in English] Well,
looks like I'm not going
to have to kill you today.
[music ends]
We have a deal to make.
[clears throat, sniffs]
Okay.
-Yeah.
-[glasses clinking]
[tense music resumes]
[Paolo breathing loudly]
[gagging, gulping]
[glass clinking]
[Paolo] Good evening, everyone.
To think that there was a very real chance
that this entire team of Americans
and Russians would be shot dead.
-[men laughing]
-[Paolo] But, look at us now.
[laughs] Cheers!
-[Paolo toasting in Brazilian Portuguese]
-[men toasting, cheering]
-[Ivan speaking indistinctly]
-[glasses clinking]
-Is he joking?
-I don't know.
[Morgan breathes heavily]
[upbeat music playing]
Hey, is there any part of you
that likes this, like, what we're doing?
Absolutely not. I literally
cannot wait to get out of this.
[Morgan sighs deeply]
I think there's something wrong
with me. [smacks lips]
Morgan, there's nothing wrong
with you, okay?
You might be restless and easily bored
and stuck in a bad relationship
and, you know, likely undiagnosed ADHD.
And you should absolutely invest
in a day planner,
but there is nothing wrong with you. Okay?
[music continues]
[Morgan] Yeah. Wow.
Thank you for saying that.
Yeah, I think I really needed to, um,
hear that.
-[inhales]
-Did you do more cocaine?
No. Like one bump, two bumps.
One bump. Are you using?
-"Using"?
-[Nicky] Like, I don't know.
-Is it 1997? "I'm using"?
-[Nicky] It's like a weird…
I'm just saying.
What, suddenly you're a cokehead?
You're acting like it's, like--
Like it's meth.
You're saying it like it's meth.
-[exhales loudly]
-Well, it's something.
-That's nice.
-[music gets louder]
I just have to say,
I think that this trip has been
a lifeline for us, don't you think?
[raised voice] It's been something.
-Something nice, right?
-Yup.
I know this sounds corny.
But I've really enjoyed my time with you.
[music continues loudly]
[muffled gunshot]
-[screaming]
-[muffled gunshots]
[screaming]
-[loud gunshot]
-[Nicky screaming]
-[screaming]
-[glass breaking]
[Nicky heaving]
-[Nicky cries out]
-[Morgan gasps]
-[door closes]
-[gasping]
Holy… Holy fuck.
[gasping]
[strangled cry]
[exhales loudly]
Fuck.
[dark percussive music playing]
[music ends]