(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
10 YEARS AGO
MIN HWAL-SUNG &amp; JEON YI-GYEONG
WE WISH YOU A HAPPY MARRIAGE
We have Da-rae here.
Do we have to be at the after-party?
We can't skip it.
It's Hwal-sung's wedding.
I was the MC for the ceremony
and he also got me a golf bag.
Da-rae.
Have a fishcake.
Fishcake.
Gi Su-jong. Long time no see.
Jung Man-sik, you're here as well?
I should be here.
- It's been a while, Seon.
- Yes, hi.
You punk.
You haven't changed at all.
I haven't.
So you must be...
What's your name?
It's Da-rae. Gi Da-rae.
Da-rae, say hello.
(Hello, I am Gi Da-rae.)
- You're really quite pretty.
- Hey.
You don't have to shout.
She can read your lips.
Oh, really? Then...
Will you pour me a shot... No.
Will you pour me some soda?
Would you like some, too?
She can't drink anything sweet.
No, she can't.
Da-rae.
Let's drink.
Cheers.
They're here!
Congratulations!
You look great!
I'm almost the last of us to marry,
so I'll keep it short.
I told you not to marry too soon.
- What's he saying?
- Come on.
The last one to smile
is the true victor.
Come on, man.
Gosh, Min Hwal-sung.
Thank you for the jeers.
I'd like to thank you all for coming.
There's one thing I really must say.
My best friend Su-jong.
Stand up.
I wouldn't be here if not for you.
Thanks for hosting the ceremony.
- Are you okay?
- Darn it.
May our friendship last forever.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
Congratulations, Yi-gyeong.
To my friend Su-jong, his wife
and his daughter Da-rae.
I dedicate this song.
Eight, two, seven, eight, nine.
SHAKY FRIENDSHIP
Clap.
I know it's wrong
So why do I have feelings
For my friend's girl?
I tell myself I must stop
So why do thoughts of her
Fill my mind?
She called me without telling her man
Why does that make me feel so good?
I could be cool and just reject her
So why can't I seem to do that?
It's driving me crazy
I don't know what got into me
I'm ignoring
A long-standing friendship
Because I'm falling for a girl
It's torture, pure torment
It would be fine
If I could just give up
Why am I putting so much thought
Into something so pointless?
All together.
I'm sorry, dear friend
I deceived you for a while
The friendship I had with you so far
Must not be strong enough
I hope you understand, dear friend
Our friendship was shaky for a while
Pretend someone got jealous
Of what we had
And decided to test us
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
EPISODE 7
Well? Do you like it?
Do I even have to answer?
What are we doing here?
Seon.
Give me three years.
I'll buy this apartment
and put it in your name.
- Did you look around?
- Yes.
- Isn't it nice?
- It's lovely.
Mr. Gi, just buy it already.
- I should.
- Come over here.
This is the only apartment
of this size with this view.
- It's great.
- Right? You can see right across.
And there's easy access
to public transport.
What's going on? Is Da-rae not home?
Oh, she said she'd watch a movie
with some friends.
- You shower first.
- Okay.
Seon.
Let's shower together.
What?
Well...
It's been a while. How about...
we do it?
You're home.
Hi, Da-rae.
You go ahead
and shower.
Go shower.
FOR LEASE
CONTACT M&amp;A REALTORS
DEPUTY NAM SANG-HO
Great work.
I knew I had an eye for people.
I'll do even better in the future.
Hey.
Are you happy?
Hey, Hwal-sung.
What's going on?
Su-jong.
You ride this indoors
and bike outdoors.
Are you a professional cyclist?
Forget that. What happened?
How did you leave the hospital?
How would I know?
My eyes just snapped open.
Do you know the first person
who came to mind?
It was you.
It wasn't Yi-gyeong or my mom.
You.
So Yi-gyeong's mom died like that
and the first-floor café owner
took the fall for it all?
And Seon is clueless?
She doesn't know anything.
You colluded with Deputy Nam
to buy Mr. Kim's property?
Yes.
That Deputy Nam punk.
I heard bad things about him.
I should've been there to advise you.
Yi-gyeong helped a great deal.
Yi-gyeong?
Okay, where's my share?
Your share? What's that?
We agreed to split it.
That went out the window
the moment you called the police.
I explained.
I didn't call them.
My mother-in-law did.
You're talking your way out again.
This was your idea.
It's your mess.
You created this whole mess
and I've been through hell
trying to clean it up.
I almost died.
You killed me.
You killed me
my mother-in-law, and the café owner.
Are you a serial killer or something?
If that's your excuse,
we can go way back in history.
You're insane.
Hey, Su-jong.
You think I don't know you struggled?
That's why I came here
as soon as I woke up.
All the way here.
Let's do this, then.
We'll call my lawyer
have the contract notarized,
and split the shares.
That's reasonable, isn't it?
I don't have a say in the shares.
It belongs to a corporate body,
not any one person.
- A corporate body?
- Yes.
- Was that Deputy Nam's idea?
Darn it. What the heck?
You stupid loser.
- You can't trust him!
- Hey.
It must belong to a corporation
to be included in the redevelopment.
How much will he give you?
Ten billion won.
What the heck? Hey!
You could get
at least 30 billion out of it!
I don't believe
what this idiot has done.
Hey.
That's why people
take advantage of you.
You frustrating fool.
Yes.
I'm a loser and a doormat.
That's why I get taken advantage of.
I even lost my wife to my friend.
What are you talking about?
- You really don't know?
- What?
You slept with Seon, didn't you?
Sorry, hang on.
All that sudden shouting
gave me a headache.
It's ringing.
- I need to get back to the hospital.
- Wait.
Hwal-sung.
We need to talk.
Learn to brake and take your time.
Why did you sleep with Seon?
When did you find out?
You're asking me that right now?
Hey.
Hang on.
Didn't I gift you those clubs?
You did, punk.
Okay.
I'm sorry about Seon.
Do you want me on my knees? I can.
What if Da-rae were to find out?
And Yi-gyeong?
What does that make me, you jerk?
Hey, come on.
Calm down.
How long did you see her for?
Hey!
- You can kill someone with that.
- How many times did you screw her?
Is he dead?
Poor guy.
Move him fast.
SEJEONG-RO TRAFFIC ACCIDENT
TRUCK OVERTURNS ON UNDERPASS
TAXI-AMBULANCE COLLISION IN FIRE LANE
Su-jong, how did you find out?
I had such a weird dream last night.
Is he okay?
The MRI results show he's fine.
His blood panel
came back normal, too.
You could call it a miracle.
I've never seen anything like this.
Your husband
left the ward in secret last night
and got into a traffic accident.
He snuck out?
I ran a few tests.
He shows signs of amnesia.
I guess that's why he snuck out.
Memory loss?
The official term is TGA
or transient global amnesia.
Most patients recover in time.
By "most," you mean...
In some instances,
their memory doesn't return.
Fortunately, the collision itself
didn't cause much harm.
Come in.
Yi-gyeong.
No, sit back down.
Sit down.
Goodness.
- Wait.
- What?
Why?
You don't remember?
I really have no idea.
What's the date?
I know that we celebrated
your mother's 70th birthday.
You don't remember I was kidnapped?
Kidnapped?
What the heck has happened?
Are you all right?
Did they catch the culprit?
Hwal-sung.
It's me.
Do you remember me?
Aren't you Mr. Gi Su-jong?
Come on.
Darn you.
How could I not know you?
It's great to see you.
Your mother.
Give her a call.
I should talk to her.
Right?
What?
Is something wrong?
She passed away.
What?
What do you mean?
I'll explain later.
Explain what later?
Why would she pass away?
That doesn't make any sense.
What the...
Yi-gyeong.
Mrs. Jeon...
Doctor.
When can I go home?
My wife.
I can't let her be home alone.
I need to get out of here.
Please?
I'm sorry.
Hwal-sung woke up?
Yes, they say it's a miracle.
Didn't you say he was in a coma?
He suddenly just woke up?
That's why they call it a miracle.
But he lost his memory.
He lost his memory?
It's called transcending
global something.
Transient global amnesia.
Yes, that's it.
Does that actually exist?
Yes.
Hi, Da-rae.
Uncle Hwal-sung's awake.
He's doing okay.
(Really? That's great.)
Yes.
(Why are you two making weird faces?)
She's asking why we look off.
What?
What about us two?
(You look like
you saw something horrible.)
- No, it's fine.
- It's nothing.
Let's eat.
I have something to say.
Are you free?
- Let's eat.
- Okay.
Mrs. Jeon.
Hwal-sung's here to see you.
Your idiot son-in-law
took his time...
I took my time to visit.
The dream you failed to fulfill.
I'll make it come true for you.
So, what happened to Pyeongbukgwan?
Did you sell it
while I was unconscious?
Why do you care about that?
Your mother passed.
We should manage the assets...
Hwal-sung.
Stay in your place.
What's up with you?
We're married.
We should work together.
I get that you're distraught
because your mother's gone.
But then
if a couple were
to put their heads together
there's nothing
they can't get through.
How could I discuss with a vegetable?
You're right.
But I'm back by your side now.
Aren't you glad I'm awake?
Have some fruit.
You saw her will, didn't you?
I need your signature
regarding the inheritance.
Do I have to read every word?
No, you don't have to.
Your mother had
many different investments.
We have a few issues to handle,
such as taxes.
There are also properties
in the redevelopment area.
Yes.
INHERITOR: JEON YI-GYEONG
PROVISIONAL OWNERS:
JEON YI-GYEONG, MIN HWAL-SUNG
You take care of everything for me.
Okay.
Take care of it for us.
I'll call when it's taken care of.
You should carefully read
papers like that before signing.
You never know.
You never know what?
He worked with Mom for a long time.
I'll take care of it. Don't mind it.
I'm sure you'll take care of it.
Have some fruit.
I'll go wash my hands.
Good job, Lawyer Yang.
See you soon.
Did you read my DM?
Let's meet.
Can you keep tabs on someone for me?
Who?
My husband.
Yes, I think I'm at the right place.
Where are you?
In the third booth.
The third booth.
What's that reaction for?
Take a seat.
This is for you.
- It's fine.
- It's not fine.
Look at what I'm wearing.
So.
You look much better
now that my mother-in-law's dead.
Thank you.
No one knows you embezzled yet?
Why would you bring that up
all of a sudden?
Did you update
the inheritance documents as I said?
Yes.
Soon, they'll be put in your name.
Good.
Will this really be okay?
Of course.
Trust me. I have a plan.
Get up.
Let's take a photo as a souvenir.
Try it on.
- It suits you.
- Are you kidding me?
It's a mess.
The circuit breaker keeps tripping,
doesn't it?
It's because of the leak.
How much will the repair cost?
This is a bad case.
The water tank and breaker box
both need to be fixed.
So how much?
They're all so old.
Why are you so hesitant to answer?
It'll cost about ten.
- Ten million?
- Yes.
That's on the cheaper side.
For now
do what you can to get the lights on.
I can do the bare minimum
to solve that issue
but it can be
really dangerous later on.
Everything needs replacing.
Okay, I'll take care of that later.
Take some emergency measures for now.
It's so darn old.
Replace the whole system later, okay?
- Okay.
- Bye.
Thank you. Bye.
I don't have ten million won.
What the heck?
Gosh, you're so very busy.
What are you doing here?
- The place smells.
- What?
Is it because it's the basement?
Where are we going?
Do you have any last words?
What?
The final words you wish
to leave to your family.
I'm kidding.
Deputy Nam wants to see us.
You work with Deputy Nam?
Since when?
Jonah.
That's my name.
Do you know what it means?
Jonah.
"The bringer of misfortune."
So what?
Do you remember?
"The pain that doesn't kill you
only makes you stronger."
What does that mean?
Call me whenever you need help.
PYEONGBUKGWAN HAS
A LONG TRADITION IN SEJEONG-RO...
You're friends with him, right?
Yes, we're best friends.
We go way back.
What now?
What if he refuses to sell?
He's all talk and no action.
You don't have to worry.
Why can't I reach the daughter?
I offered extra money,
yet she still wouldn't answer.
Is this a Gen Z thing?
You must handle Pyeongbukgwan wisely.
You should let her keep her pride.
Take over Pyeongbukgwan.
Goodness.
I have the money, so persuade her.
Do your best
to let her pride stand tall.
Well, I'll require some shares.
- Shares?
- Yes.
If I convince Pyeongbukgwan
I'm taking half the shares.
I've already convinced Hanmaeum,
so if I also took Pyeongbukgwan over
it would mean I got my hands
on most of the altered zone.
So of course, I'll need more shares.
Mr. Gi, I didn't know you liked
to live life in the fast lane.
I wouldn't say that.
Sure.
I'll consider it.
Yes, do consider it.
Please excuse me.
By the way.
Are you free tomorrow?
Tomorrow? What is it?
What is this?
Are you getting married?
It's a couple's night,
so make sure you dress up.
You may go now.
Yes, okay.
You heard that punk talk, right?
This is why
you never take someone in
and show them a favor.
Get rid of him once the job is done.
Did you hear me?
I did.
I'll handle him.
Su-jong.
Do I have to go?
Yes, of course.
Why do I only have sweatsuits?
Seon, where's my suit jacket?
It's all the way in the box
under the blanket.
Is this too much? What do you think?
Hey, Seon. You look gorgeous.
Cut it out. Do I really look okay?
Darn it.
Since you're pretty,
you and Hwal-sung... Darn it.
Why are you suddenly going there?
I was randomly reminded of it.
You and Hwal-sung would...
Darn it.
Su-jong.
It's time to put it out of your mind.
Get rid of it.
Okay?
- Okay?
- Yes, fine.
Okay, let's get ready and leave.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Put it on.
LOAN HEAVEN
You're almost done.
Hey.
Seon told me about you.
How many weeks are you in?
It's a little over two months.
Take good care of yourself early on
to have a safe delivery later.
Stop by occasionally for the shots.
I'll give it to you at cost.
Hold this.
That's a vitamin.
It's on the house.
Thank you.
You can thank Seon.
Excuse me.
I have a favor to ask you.
Can I find some anesthesia?
Anesthesia?
I know you've made
a similar deal before
with someone named Min Hwal-sung.
He's my husband.
Can you do that?
OH DONG-KI
PREVIOUS CHARGES: NONE
No criminal records.
POSTMORTEM REPORT
COMMENT FROM THE EXAMINER
A FATAL GUNSHOT IN THE HEART...
BRUISES AND SIGNS OF BEATING...
THERE ARE SIGNS OF TETANUS
CAUSING NECROSIS IN THE TISSUE...
I know something is up
with Gi Su-jong.
Ju-ran.
We're done with that case.
Why are you stressing out?
You also said
Mr. Gi seemed suspicious.
But we found all the evidence.
Right?
We did find all the evidence.
You should take a few days off
and get a good rest.
Right.
Someone is out there,
looking for you.
Who?
SEOUL YONGDAEMUN POLICE STATION
I heard Mr. Min woke up.
I want to check
if this is the same drug
they used when I was kidnapped.
Is that possible?
Go ahead.
The current shares...
You're here.
You can sit over there.
Yes, okay.
Please help yourself.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
ASSETS PORTFOLIO
Please meet Mr. Gi Su-jong.
- Hello.
- Of Se-yoon Building.
He's a building owner
who has been playing a big part
in the Sejeong-ro Project.
- A great young man.
- He got Hanmaeum as well.
Please meet her.
Hello.
I'm so sorry that I couldn't make it
to your son's wedding.
Meet her. So, your son...
Why are you ignoring me?
Why?
You should be glad I ignored you.
Don't be so hard on me.
Hey, I came back from the dead.
Shouldn't you be
a little worried about me?
Sure, I'm glad you woke up.
- Were you there, Hee-ju?
- I went.
Su-jong knows about us.
Are you going to divorce him?
What's wrong with you?
If you do, let's start over together.
I mean it.
Have you lost your mind?
I heard you had amnesia.
Do you really not remember anything?
Is it that obvious?
I thought I had put on a good act.
I did it because of Su-jong.
That punk tried to kill me.
Mr. Gi is great at doing business.
Let me tell you a secret.
Su-jong was the one
who kidnapped Yi-gyeong.
He's also the one
who killed my mother-in-law.
He tried to kill me
because I caught onto everything.
So today...
We need to work together.
Why should we?
I'm going to divorce Yi-gyeong.
We'll both get divorced
and take over
the redevelopment project.
With the right plan
we can pull it off.
Hwal-sung.
Yes?
You were the kidnapper.
I already know what's going on.
I know what you
and Su-jong have done.
Okay.
There seems to be a misunderstanding.
We can discuss this later.
I bet you didn't know this.
Su-jong has something to do
with Gyun's death.
What are you talking about?
Do you remember that time
when he almost lost Se-yoon Building
in an auction?
He went around
trying to borrow money.
Do you think we can take out
another loan
against Se-yoon Building?
I've pulled all the loans I could
but you can get some more, right?
Gyun tried to help Su-jong out
and ended up like that.
Everyone in Sejeong-ro
has heard about it.
Gyun died because of Su-jong?
How can I...
I can't bring myself to say that.
Ask him yourself.
Kim Gyun?
You were at the scene
of Gyun's accident
weren't you?
Let's go, Su-jong.
Hello, friend.
- What brings you here?
- What?
I just stopped by.
What did you two talk about?
You, obviously.
It's the most fun
to talk behind someone's back
when they have stepped away
for a brief moment.
You punk. That's not even funny.
Don't call your friend a punk,
you punk.
Are you trying to hit me again?
Or trying to kill me again?
Hwal-sung.
You...
remember, right?
What?
Was there something
that I should have remembered?
Goodness, Mr. Min.
Oh, my.
Hello, Mr. Nam.
I heard you had been fatally wounded.
I've resurrected.
Mr. Min!
Goodness, Hee-ju.
It's been a while.
Did you know that Hwal-sung lied
about losing his memories?
I found out just now.
Did you really find out just now?
Are you suspicious of me?
No.
Anyway, did you call him here today?
Why would I do that?
What were you two whispering about?
Enough is enough.
Stop acting like you have
- something on me.
- What do you mean?
Look at the way you're acting.
You pry, ask, and nitpick over things
to make me feel guilty.
What do you want?
Do you want me to feel helpless?
I'm tormented too, but what can I do?
It's all in the past.
How can you be so cold?
How can you talk like that?
You just hurt me greatly.
Let's set the record straight.
I had an affair and hurt you?
What about you?
- You kidnapped your friend's wife.
- Hey!
And you...
What?
Never mind.
My life is miserable enough as it is.
So, stop messing with me.
Sir, will you let me off here
for a moment?
Darn it.
YI-GYEONG
Hello, Yi-gyeong. It's me.
I have something to say to you.
PYEONGBUKGWAN
MY DAUGHTER
WHERE ARE YOU, DAD?
I'M ON MY WAY TO YOUR BUILDING
I came out for a moment.
I'll text you later.
Hello, Yi-gyeong.
Have a seat.
Sure.
Now.
SEJEONG-RO INVESTMENT CORPORATION
So here's the thing.
The biggest office building in Asia
will be erected in this area.
And Pyeongbukgwan will have
its place on the first floor
as a representative Korean brand.
It'll be a great opportunity
to globalize the business.
I'm sure Madam Jeon
would have loved that.
Is this about Nouveau City?
The one Mr. Nam is involved in.
Yes, you've heard about it?
It's funny to hear about
Pyeongbukgwan's renewal from you.
Yi-gyeong, I...
I'll talk to him
and give you a good price
for the building.
So please give me your trust
and join the project.
Why are you trying so hard?
Because of money?
I don't know.
I guess it's because of Da-rae.
Right, Da-rae.
I'm sure she means the most to you.
The contract works for me.
But I have a question
before we proceed.
LOAN HEAVEN
Did you know about them?
DETECTIVE KOH JU-RAN
Hello, Detective.
They're the same anesthetic agent.
I'd like to open
an official investigation.
May I ask how you came to get this?
Something's going on, right?
No.
No, it's nothing like that.
Sorry?
I'll reach out to you later.
BENZODIAZEPINE WAS FOUND IN THE DRUG
Hwal-sung had bought
an anesthetic drug
at the hospital
Seon hooked me up with.
Be honest with me.
Did you two...
Yes.
We kidnapped you.
I should've told you this earlier.
I'm sorry.
Seon was involved in this
so I was quite stumped.
So you knew
they were seeing each other?
Yes.
It must've been hard.
It was.
But still
she's Da-rae's mother.
I know it's brazen of me to ask
but I don't want
Seon to end up in prison.
This was Hwal-sung's plan all along.
How intriguing.
Yi-gyeong.
Please, I'm asking you.
I know it makes no sense.
But can you please forgive her
for Da-rae's sake?
I've recently come to realize
how much Seon truly loves Da-rae.
Your child will also grow up
healthy and beautiful like you.
But the kid won't have a dad.
Just like me.
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Da-rae.
The acceptance e-mail
just came from Harvard.
MY GOSH... WHAT DO I DO?
Should we click on it together?
YES
Did you get in?
YES! WHAT ABOUT YOU?
I didn't get in.
OH NO
It's okay.
I'll get into another school.
Congratulations, Da-rae!
This is great!
THANK YOU
UNKNOWN ERROR
CLOSE THE PAGE AND RETRY
LOADING
PLEASE WAIT
Mr. Gi?
Hey, what are you doing?
You aren't allowed to drink
at a convenience store these days.
Is that so?
I have something nice at my office.
Come with me.
Okay, sure.
Yi-gyeong, I'm home.
Yi-gyeong.
I need to talk to you.
What?
I'm tired, let me just...
- Can I wash up quickly?
- No.
Right now.
Where have you been?
I had to meet someone.
I asked, where have you been?
There was an event
with the redevelopment project
so I went there.
Why?
To sell Pyeongbukgwan away?
Does anybody there
even listen to you?
Jeez.
Do you really think
I'm that dumb?
I have my own plan.
You'd be helping much more
if you didn't do anything.
Just sit around still like a stone.
I should've stayed in bed
as a vegetable.
Why did I wake up?
Sorry.
But you also are unbelievable.
You always hated your mother.
And you said her naengmyeon
tasted like mop water.
What are you trying to do now?
Be a good daughter?
Have you been cheating with Seon?
Hey.
We just met by chance and had a chat.
What about the kidnapping?
What are you talking about?
Hey.
You were much better
when you were a vegetable.
I can explain.
Get out of my house.
What do you mean, Yi-gyeong?
Get out of here!
KIM GYUN
I bet you didn't know this.
Su-jong has something to do
with Gyun's death.
Hey, Da-rae.
I WANT TO BE ALONE
IS SOMETHING GOING ON?
What's with her?
I SAID I WANT TO BE LEFT ALONE
YOU KILLED ME
MY MOTHER-IN-LAW, AND THE CAFÉ OWNER
YOU SLEPT WITH SEON, DIDN'T YOU?
KIM GYUN
Get in.
Don't make a scene around here.
Okay, so get in.
Legally speaking,
when you get divorced
the one who had an affair
is the one at fault.
That means the innocent one
is more advantageous
when we divide the assets.
I didn't have an affair
but Seon did.
What is this?
Su-jong is getting ready
to divorce you.
What?
You're about to be backstabbed.
M&amp;A REALTORS
What's going on?
Do you have trouble with your wife?
Affairs, affairs.
A wind of affairs is blowing.
Hee-ju.
Man, what time is it?
Get up.
Hee-ju.
What?
SEON
Hee-ju.
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
I really didn't do anything.
Da-rae got accepted?
You didn't know?
She received
the acceptance e-mail last night.
We oppose forced development projects
that rob private property!
- We oppose!
Some are starting to catch on.
Let's wrap this up quickly.
I got a message from Da-rae.
What is this?
This plan was put together
to take Se-yoon Building from me.
Da-rae.
Prepare yourself to divorce him.
You already know
about the crimes Su-jong committed.
You need clear evidence
to use against him.
I'll give you a hand.
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Jennifer Lim