At the start, you had my heart, oh
You are my everything
Attracted to my light, poor thing
Ugh, boring!
I can't retain, don't say my name
I'm too smart, too hard
To get caught up in…
Uh, Kitty Song-Covey, I'm on the list,
Afraid not,
No, I have to be, That's my boyfriend,
Uh-huh, I'm sure it is,
I'm not lying,
Min Ho!
Look, sorry, I can't let you in,
Especially not in that,
All the boys wanna see me
All the girls wanna be me
It ain't surprising
I'm hypnotizing
I get them so excited with a kiss
Hey, You were having a nightmare,
Yeah, I guess I was,
I love interpreting bad dreams,
Naked in front of a class?
Ooh, Losing all your teeth?
Min Ho and Eunice
Okay, it gets really dark
Well, last night, Min Ho said
but then I saw him
And they were hugging,
And not like a hello-goodbye hug,
Kitty, there's no way,
And people hug all the time,
And besides, Min Ho's a great guy,
Just trust him,
You're right, I know you're right,
Oh my God! It's Yisoo,
She wants me to meet her at the office,
- Gotta hurry! Okay…
Don't you have, like, time off the clock?
You don't get to be a fashion legend
Oh my God, this is amazing,
I didn't even know she knew my name,
Well, I'm very glad she sees you,
but you are gonna make it
My imo-halmoni's coming from Bukjeon,
This might be my last chance to have
Yes, of course,
Save me a seat, okay?
Kitty, don't spiral,
Go talk to your boyfriend,
HAVE A GREAT CHUSEOK
- Kitty! Hey, hey,
Oh, well, that's probably
or the fact that
Stop! Tell me everything!
Okay, If you must know,
- Then I'll go in with salicylic--
I don't know,
We just kind of blurted it out,
That is so romantic,
Wait, so this means you got over
in the summer with Marius?
Oh, yeah, Water under the bridge,
Marius is ancient history,
Although he did tell me last night that
I know, Intense,
Damn, does that change anything?
If it did, would I be introducing Jin
Wait, whoa! Your love life is,
I know, I'm kind of nervous,
I never introduced my mom
She's always got high standards,
Well, I'm sure when she sees
she'll be nothing but supportive,
I hope so, God, look at us,
Yes! You and me both!
See you later,
What am I going to say?
"Where were you last night?"
Oh my God!
So sorry, Eunice,
Didn't mean to… do that,
Just set you right here,
My God, that is lifelike,
Okay, this is actually weirder
Are you stalking me, Covey?
I'm actually looking
Ha-ha, very funny, Hey,
Um, how was it with Marius last night?
Yeah, about that, um…
I didn't actually end up
Because you were with Eunice?
I saw you two from my window,
Okay, the truth is…
I didn't want you
I was getting her opinion
this,
Happy Chuseok, Covey,
- The gift is actually inside the box,
It's beautiful,
I'm sorry for the white lie,
You're just such a hard person
I don't know what to say,
I think of Chuseok
It's when I started
So…
What are you doing here?
Oh, I, um…
I need your help,
Jiwon texted me and said
I'm so sorry,
Yeah, At the very least,
And my Korean is getting better, but…
All right, say no more,
Remember? Soon Ja-nim adores me,
Thank you,
Yisoo, it's such an honor to meet you,
Well, everyone has already left
To be honest, I'd usually give this task
Oh, well, Desperate times,
I can handle anything,
Good,
Ah,
Koko's sitter canceled,
I'll be back in three days,
But Koko has separation anxiety,
so don't ever leave him alone,
Keep giving him verbal affirmation,
Oh, and never make direct eye contact,
Oh, and he's vegan, Mm!
Aren't you a little angel, Koko? Mwah!
Do well!
Impress me, And who knows?
Maybe one day
Koko, Mommy's leaving! Be good,
Bye!
What are you doing? Bring down my bag,
Chop-chop!
Uh…
Oh my God!
You came,
- Welcome to BoDaeGa,
I thought of the name,
It's mine, my brother's
Wow, Bora, you've grown so much!
Yuri! Welcome!
Hello, Mr, Kim, Congratulations,
Thank you,
It's because of your family
Oh, there’s really no reason
- Okay,
- Yes!
- Huh?
You got a dog?
It's my boss's,
I had to bring him
How could you bring a dog here
We could be shut down,
Sorry, I didn't think of that, I'll go,
No, Dae, you can't uninvite her!
And he's so cute!
Don't make eye contact,
Okay, fine,
Just promise me
Of course, Of course,
- I said, "I'll do it myself,"
I snapped that ankle back into place
with my hands
I'll never forget that guy's scream,
- I'll never forget that story,
My injury was more of a sprain,
Luckily, I didn't need surgery
Huh,
Marius!
Dr, Candelaria!
Oh, you must join us, Sit,
When Quincy first came to KISS,
They were inseparable,
It was such a relief, especially after all
- Mom, please stop,
I mean, his dad used to say,
"He really puts the 'lazy'
- I'm sure it was very cute,
Well, actually, I have a photo,
- Check this,
Look at that,
- Okay, there it is,
So good,
I'm sorry,
Look at this place, It's perfect,
It has to be, My dad sank
Well, this is gonna be a huge success,
Thanks,
Min Ho! Is Eunice coming?
Ah, she's going to be spending
- Um, is everyone here?
We are?
I don't think I can handle another setup
No, no, I think you're gonna like
Ta-da! Happy Chuseok!
I convinced her to come after all,
Halmoni…
You wouldn't come home to me,
Hello,
Yes, yes,
Let's go,
What is going on?
The reason I said Halmoni couldn't come
What? Why not?
She didn't approve of me moving to Seoul,
We had a huge fight before I left
Sorry I didn't tell you,
Min Ho, why don't you tell my imo-halmoni
and how all the students love her,
As a teacher, Jiwon is so popular!
Mm,
If she had stayed in Bukjeon,
Don't they have kids there?
It would've been great
and see your face during the holidays,
If I went home,
Who?
Chung-hee? The guy she's been wanting me
because she's always trying
So, Quincy, you haven't told me
- All A's, except AP Chem, B+,
"Like an A" is not an A,
Does it really matter?
Track is not exactly a major,
He needs to start thinking
He's from Bukjeon,
lots of money, and so much land!
I mean, that's great bone structure,
What? He could have a career in modeling,
I mean, why rule out any possibilities?
Why didn't you wait to see
She's got a point, You know,
I think it's smart
Well, I think a full ride to USC
Halmoni,
Chung-Hee and I are nothing!
Marius, what are your plans
Well, I'll be interning
You know, he's always talking about
Must be nice,
Well, finally someone
I mean, you can't get into medical school
Okay, all due respect,
Q was the first person
- Jin, stop,
Your son is amazing
Oh my God, is Jin sexy?
I am beyond proud of him,
And you should be too,
I thought you'd get tired
then come back home where you belong,
I have to live my life,
My goodness,
This mandu is delicious,
Yummy,
Sorry to interrupt,
Opening a restaurant with my dad
but she never thought we could afford it,
And now we can,
But really, it's our love for her
She always believed in us, no matter what,
What better way to honor her
My mom would be so proud,
Happy Chuseok!
Mom would be so proud of you, Dad,
I will do my best,
At least someone's mom
Jiwon, I'm so sorry, This is all my fault,
No, it's not, Uh…
Halmoni's not gonna be happy
unless I follow her exact plans
I'm gonna go now,
No, uh, wait, What if I talk to her?
Like, matchmaker to matchmaker,
Kitty, you of all people
She didn't speak to her own sister
This isn't your problem to solve,
Well, so much for checking off
a traditional family Chuseok
In my experience,
You still get to cross it off your list,
Well, at least I got to spend it with you,
Min Ho!
Are you okay?
No, they followed me
That was insane, I'm gonna call my dad,
Eunice, are you okay?
Mm,
Oh my God, it's really you?
Can I get a picture with you?
Yeah, Of course,
- Kitty, would you mind?
Oh, I love your necklace, Where's it from?
- Uh, Min Ho got it for me,
It's happening, My unofficial
And I'm already sold out of these,
- Wow,
Ooh, Yuri, can I get a photo
I'd love to create a frenzy,
Fine, but his fee is crazy high,
Girl…
Wait, Oh my God, Oh my God,
Oh my God, Oh my God,
What?
Oh my God,
Ugh, You're so fired,
No, I cannot screw this up
- This night's so important for them,
He has to be here somewhere,
- You check the back, I'll check in here,
Okay, Okay,
Koko! Koko! Koko! Koko!
I tried to talk to my parents about it,
but I couldn't,
Honestly, I couldn't speak,
I have no idea how to begin to tell them,
I'm so scared
What am I going to do? I'm so scared,
No,
Listen carefully,
You're not alone, okay?
I'm responsible too,
But listen,
You can't tell anyone about this,
If anyone finds out, we're done!
It's okay,
Oh my God,
Wait, Did anyone
No, I lured him out
Oh no, You've given this gremlin
I am so sorry,
Honestly, thank you so much,
If you ever need anything,
Good to know, 'Cause I'm pretty sure
Um, will you excuse me just one second?
We need to talk,
- When did you get a dog?
Okay, I just overheard
Are you okay, Eunice?
Yeah,
Why wouldn't I be?
Okay, I think you were right all along,
Min Ho and Eunice
I know, He said she helped pick
He said whatever it is, it's big enough
Oh no, Koko, don't eat that,
Wait, Is this a…
A… pregnancy test,
A positive one,
What exactly did you hear them say?
See you back at the dorm,
Mm-hmm,
Kitty, you all right?
Is Eunice pregnant?
- How did you know?
Yes,
When did it happen? Over the summer?
I don't know, When we were in Paris,
Look, okay, no one knows, all right?
My… career would be over,
I saw you two hugging last night,
Kitty, what--
And supposedly she helped
She's never even seen it before,
Yes, I lied about--
Yes, you did lie!
You said you didn't hook up last summer,
- I didn't!
You got our friend pregnant?
Friend pregnant?
Who are you?
Kitty!
Hey, want a mocktail?
You okay? What happened?
Min Ho said that he didn't hook up with
And not just about that,
I'm so sorry,
How'd you get over
- I mean, it's not the same, but…
- Never mind,
No, Jin, wait! I…
What happened between you and Marius?
- What do you mean?
- Okay, it's not a big deal,
Jin, please, not right now,
Tell me!
It was before you came to USC,
You know what they say,
Jin, wait! Wait, don't--
Oh my God,
Oh! Oh my God, I'm so sorry,
Jin! What is wrong with you?
You?
Quin…
Jin, Jin, wait,
Jin, wait, Can we please just talk?
I thought that you told him,
I didn't think I had
- I didn't think it'd be a big deal if--
So, I guess Marius was
I don't even know why I sent that pic,
Jin loves me,
and I love him,
Marius has been playing games
Well, my doctorate
maybe there's a reason
why you're attracted to people
You know, I failed my, uh, chem final,
Yeah, I stayed in bed all week,
You never told me that,
The pressure got to me,
Being pre-med,
I mean, they never told me
I guess they were afraid
I don't always show it,
your whole life,
Even tonight?
Even tonight,
And I am so sorry
But Jin…
Jin cares more about you
And that's…
That's the kind of love you deserve,
Come here,
So, you think Min Ho and Eunice hooked up?
- He said it happened in Paris,
I'm sorry to be the one to tell you this,
I know how you feel about her,
No, I mean,
I was with Eunice
What? What are you talking about?
When the settlement came through,
my dad gave me some
So I bought a plane ticket
And Min Ho doesn't know that, Nobody does,
Did you sleep with her?
I'm sorry, It's not my business, but…
Right now, this is important,
Yes, I did,
But after we came back to school,
she started acting
Oh my God,
Min Ho is protecting her,
Protecting her? From what?
I'm sorry, I can't tell you,
But I do think you need to talk to Eunice,
I don't know,
She's too much of a big star now,
People saw one paparazzi photo
and now we're booked out for a month,
Wow, that's great news
But regarding Eunice…
sometimes things are
Whatever it is, you can tell me,
Honestly, after Paris…
I stopped having my period,
Min Ho thinks I was with Tae-Oh,
but obviously I was only with you,
If you're saying
let's do this together,
We can even get married if we need to,
No, Dae, it's not like that,
I'm not pregnant,
Are you sure?
Mm,
For a while, I thought that I was,
But that wasn't the case,
When I came home tonight,
I started my period,
I guess I was so stressed,
The paparazzi always following me,
Honestly, I was so scared,
I felt like I couldn't breathe,
Dae, I just
want to go back
Hi,
I'm sorry,
I got everything so wrong,
Why did you not just tell me the truth?
Because I gave Eunice my word,
I didn't expect my own girlfriend
I know,
I think that I spent my whole summer
watching you with all these fancy people,
and it made me question if I would
ever really fit… in your big, fancy world,
So I got in my head,
Like you did with Gigi,
You know, I get it now,
It's not that you don't trust me,
It's that you've never trusted me,
No, no, that's not true--
I've done everything…
I've given you every reason
But the problem isn't me, it's you,
We're done,
No, I…
Min Ho…
Please record your message,
LJ, I need to talk to you,
I've messed everything up,
I don't know what to do,
It's killing me
Fear is holding me down
But I wanna be sure
I will burst through the crowd
Screaming for this man
If I got this with you