Good morning, there.
Fadel, Fadel, Fadel!
You suddenly live at my pace.
Morning jogging, grocery shopping,
showing up at my burger joint,
and now frequenting the same gym?
Stop following me.
Don’t say I didn’t warn you.
Don’t you think we should just
keep it casual between you and me?
I don’t want no casual.
You’ve still got a lot to prove.
Make sure he knows he
really matters to you.
You have a meeting with
Senator Vichai at 4.30.
Right.
Then dinner with Mr. Boonterm at 7.
I’ve got all the documents prepared.
What about our important meeting?
They’re waiting in your office.
Good.
Don’t let anyone in there
until I’m done talking to them.
Yes.
Of course.
Ms. Lilly.
We need you to sign this
month’s financial report.
You want me to sign it here?
Shouldn’t you have put that on my desk?
I’m sorry.
Your new job.
Who is he, Mother?
Someone important.
He’s a big shot.
Why does he deserve this?
I see him on the news
for helping poor children
and charity.
He’s never done anything bad.
Bison, dear.
You’ve always been easily
deceived by appearance.
It’s all for show.
He acts like a saint.
But it’s just a facade
to mask all his crimes.
He’s the man behind corruptions, drugs,
human trafficking, and so much more.
It would take me forever
to list everything.
But for this kill,
you need to make it a spectacle.
They need to send a message
to the other big shots.
One more thing,
this could be dangerous.
But I believe in you two.
Of course, Mother.
But it’d be better
if you let me take a little break.
Fadel!
What’s the matter, Bison?
Do you want to stop?
Do I not pay you enough for this?
Well?
Or…
Are you seeing someone?
Well, Fadel?
Is your brother seeing someone right now?
You can tell me, love.
Well?
There’s no one, Mother.
I promise we’ll take care of this thing.
Don’t worry.
Don’t quit so soon, my dear.
Work with me.
We’re all each other’s got.
Right?
Excuse us.
I guess we’ll do it.
If you think Fadel and
Bison might not make it,
do you want me to help them out?
You’re already doing well at the office,
and you’re not as adept
on the field as they are.
You still have so much to learn.
One beer, please.
You’re always here alone.
Why not go have fun with everyone?
I’m good.
I’m having the time of my life here.
Hello. Hi.
Cheers.
Long live rock and rolls.
Oh, hey.
To think I’d run into you here.
You like heavy metal?
You don’t look the type.
You’re supposed to have fun with
your friends at a place like this.
You can’t just sit
drinking looking mysterious.
Come on.
Let’s go dance with me.
I’ve made so many new
friends already, you know?
No.
I can have a good time all by myself.
How’d that even work?
You need someone to “scream” with.
Well, whatever.
I’m here all the time anyway.
This place is so my thing.
I’ll make you scream
with me one of these days.
Bro, I need a double.'
Coming right up.
Double, it is!
Follow me, alright?
Double, huh?
Hey, I’ll be right back.
Did you know
they use heavy metal to torture prisoners
so they confess?
If I was the warden,
I wouldn’t do that.
What if it was me?
What’d you do to torture
the truth out of me?
Would you kiss…
or choke me?
You’ll know.
You look kinda sexy tonight.
Mind if I join you?
You’ve been following me.
Me?
This is the nearest onsen around here.
I’m a regular.
Maybe it’s you who’s been following me.
You’ve got a tattoo on your back?
I didn’t notice it that night.
I was busy with…
With what?
Can I see?
“If I be…”
What does it mean?
“If you piss me off,”
“careful of my fist.”
Really?
Where is that from?
It’s from one of Shakespeare’s books.
Babe is a fan.
I asked him to pick
some cool quotes for me.
This is my favorite.
It’s about bees.
“If I be waspish,”
“best beware my sting.”'
Scary.
I’m just saying that.
You know I’m actually just a baby.
You’re much scarier than I am.
I’m scary?
Look at me.
Do I look like I can hurt anyone?
But I get what you mean.
If they did me wrong,
I’d get them back.
What’d you do to them?
You want to know?
Oww, hey!
That’s what they’d get.
That’s just a sample.
But if you don’t mean me harm,
then you have nothing to be afraid of.
Stop it.
Bye.
Anything worth reporting?
Did you follow me, Cap?
Well, it’s kinda my job to follow through.
All I know right now is that
they have the same mother,
but different dads.
Continue investigating.
Better yet, get inside their house.
I’m sure there’s some leads there.
You’re asking me to
enter the tigers' lair here.
You know I could get
clawed to death, right?
You can do it.
Up your game and gain his trust.
He’ll lead you right into his house.
Trust me.
What about the big brother?
How are you dealing with him?
You sure he won’t get in your way again?
My friend is handling him.
Does your friend know they’re hitmen?
No.
I’ll give you a fair warning.
Don’t tell anyone about this.
The more people know,
the more dangerous it is.
Good morning.
If you’re here, it’s clearly a bad morning.
Hey.
Starting the day off on the wrong foot
makes the whole day bad, you know?
Do you like doing cardio?
I hate doing cardio after weight training.
It’s boring.
I’m looking for some
other form of cardio, though.
Is that all you think about all day?
Go jerk off if it bothers you so much.
I know I can do it alone.
But it burns more
calories doing it together.
Is that why you won’t leave me alone?
You want to sleep with me?
May I?
I want your body and your…
Heart.
You’re not my type.
What’s your type, then?
Tell me!
I can be that for you.
Hey!
Excuse me.
What can we get you today?
Ground pork?
We grind… the pork ourselves here.
It will sure make some good burgers.
Do you work here full-time now?
If you’re here every day,
then I’m here every day.
I’ll give you some fresh meat daily.
Oh, you don’t want it?
My meat is sweet, I tell you!
Auntie, I’ll be back.
I have to win that guy over.
Alright.
I’m rooting for you.
Do your best.
Thanks.
Welcome to Heart Burger.
Please have a seat.
Here’s the menu.
What would you like?
One cheeseburger and some water, please.
Please have a seat.
Hello.
Here’s the menu.
Come on in.
This place is a must.
- It’s cheesy and juicy.
- I’ll be back to take your order shortly.
Come on in.
It goes down easy and
agrees with your stomach.
Come on over.
Can I have a photo?
Of course.
Let’s do it.
One, two, three.
Alright. Thank you.
Come on this way.
Come here for some
juicy and cheesy burgers.
It’s a must.
Don’t miss it.
Come right in.
- You won’t regret it— - What
the hell do you think you’re doing?
I’m spreading the word about your place.
I’m doing it for free, mind you.
Stop it.
I didn’t ask you to do this.
You didn’t have to.
It’s a great strategy to attract customers.
Don’t you know how many
burger joints there are?
We gotta stand out to survive.
One more thing,
who would be able to resist
a handsome guy in a costume?
They’re here for my burgers,
not your theatrics.
Who knows?
Maybe they’re here because
the chef is so damn good-looking.
Don’t try to cozy up to me.
Why not?
Did that make you blush?
It did, didn’t it?
You’re blushing.
Take that thing off and
go back to your garage.
Why?
I said take it off.
I won’t!
I said I won’t!
No!
You hungry?
That’s so cute.
Please come on in.
Welcome.
Leave my restaurant alone.
Shouldn’t you be
cooking at a time like this
instead of telling me off?'
Your brother isn’t even here to help.
But I am.
All I ask from you is a little decency.
No.
This is my job.
I can handle it myself.
Help me up.
I can’t get up.
Help me!
Keep it dry for the time being.
Make sure you avoid water.
Here as well…
No soap on your tattoo
for the next seven days.
Of course.
Thank you.
What is this?
Are you getting lonely?
Is that why you called
me over to your studio?
Well, you said I can’t go to your place.
And since Babe is home at
night, I can’t have you over.
This is the only place
we can meet during the day.
I don’t see an issue here.
We can just book a hotel.
Hotels are for hookups.
I want to see you every day.
Who meets their boyfriend at a hotel?
I’d prefer your place.
Jumping the gun, are we?
I’m not your boyfriend.
What are you talking about?
One more thing,
I don’t think Fadel will let
you step foot inside my house.
So?
You called me over just to chat?
Mn
Look at this.
I called you over for the cat tattoo.
You left it here last time, remember?
You like it?
It’s nice.
But I don’t want a cat tattoo anymore.
I think it makes me look too cute.
I want something cool.
You can get any cuter than this?
I can barely resist you as you are.
Ow!
Do you like it rough or something?
Can you handle it?
If you like it, I can handle it.
What if I told you I’m
into… bondages and whips?
Are you the S or the M?
I prefer to be in control.
You didn’t mention that
the first night we met.
Who’d tell a total stranger
their sexual preference?
Do you trust me now, then?
Not 100%.
What do I have to do
for you to trust me 100%?
Hey.
Which table orders this?
I’ll do it.
Go away.
You’re going to both wait tables and cook?
Just stay in here.
I’ll handle the serving.
I called Bison and he’ll be here soon.
Just go.
Your customers would leave
by the time Bison is here.
Learn to accept help from people, will you?
I’ll help you.
Fine.
But go get changed into
our uniform before that.
Where is it?
Over there.
Mine will probably fit you.
Quickly.
Hey, hey, hey.
Do it in the bathroom.
Why?
This is nothing you haven’t seen before.
Getting embarrassed, are we?
Embarrassed, my ass.
This is a…
kitchen.
Oh, hey.
Your stuff sure… fits me perfectly.
Can you shut up and be quick?
Or else I’m going to change my mind.
Yeah.
Take this.
Yes, Chef.
Hurry up.
Ugh, damn it.
Here.
Sorry for the wait.
Hey.
How come they get their food before I do?
I was here first.
Yeah.
I’ve been waiting forever.
We thought the place was nice,
but the service sure is awful.
I apologize.
I’ll hurry up your order immediately.
Sorry.
Hey.
Is the food for Tables 5 and 6 ready?
They’re pissed.
I’m making it.
I’m doing it as fast as I can.
Told you I don’t need help.
I don’t need this many customers.
I don’t need money. I’m
only doing this for fun.
That can only come out of
the mouth of real millionaires.
I’m not a millionaire.
If you’re not, and you’re
only doing this for fun,
then you’re hiding something.
Are you…
What?
You’re a…
A police informant?
Definitely.
Or are you an undercover cop?
What are you investigating?
Murders?
Drugs?
Adulteries?
You can tell me.
I know everyone around here.
I’d say you watch too
many of those Fast films.
Now get out there.
If you want to help,
deal with the customers.
Keep the talking to the minimum.
What?
I’m watching you like a hawk.
Will you tell me what you like?
Well, it varies.
Something from face slapping, bondages,
to something involving some tools.
Face slapping?
How hard?
Depends on how intense the
mood takes me at the time.
Won’t you try slapping me?
What?
Why’d I do that?
I’m not in the mood for that.
Try it.
I’ll know if I can handle it
if the occasion ever arises again.
Please slap me.
Do it.
That’s it?
It doesn’t even hurt.
That turns you on?
I don’t want to hurt you.
Hey.
Don’t hold back.
Just slap me.
Who knows?
Maybe I’ll even be into it.
We could be the perfect match.
You like inflicting pain.
I like feeling pain.
Slap me.
Harder.
Hey, let’s–let’s not.
Come on. Just stop.
I said harder!
Hey, are you alright?
I’m sorry.
I told you I didn’t want to do it.
You really didn’t have to do this for me.
I think I liked it.
Anything else you want to try?
Answer, damn it.
What the hell is he busy doing?
Calling for backup?
Hell yeah.
Oh?
Your first burger for me.
Are you finally folding?
Was it because of how hard working I am?
You like me now, don’t you?
Don’t get your hopes up.
This is your wage.
My wage?
This is next to nothing.
You weren’t listening.
I told you I didn’t ask for your help.
Fine.
I’ll take it.
Go home when you’re done eating.
And take your burger suit.
Oh, the nature of man.
He will exploit you
and then throw you away.
Don’t be dramatic.
Just go home.
Don’t you just love to chase me off?
Let me finish this first.
It’s great.
Customers.
Eat and go home.
I know.
It’s really good.
Thank you.
What the hell are you doing here?
Oh?
Is that how you talk to a customer?
Your place is pretty popular.
You might do better flipping
burgers than killing people.
Just tell me what you want.
Does Mother want something from us?
No.
I just want to help out.
Who is she?
Ruerat’s secretary, Penpak.
She knows all his schedules,
keys, and passwords.
If you get to his secretary,
you get to him.
That’s it?
What do you mean by “help,” then?
Bison and I can do this much on our own.
It’s not you I’m helping.
It’s Mother.
I see.
You just want to lick her boots.
Fine.
Once we get this job done,
I’ll put in a good word for you.
So?
Are you both quitting after this one?
You said you’d quit last time, too.
But as we saw,
you ended up having nowhere to go.
Didn’t the dude you wanted
to rely on just disappear?
Why did you bring this up?
I just want you to tell your brother
how pipe dreams always end.
In this line of profession,
no one waits for you.
Are you serious about this?
Of course I am.
I doubt it will even hurt.
Are you sure?
It’s not too late to
change your mind, you know?
Look at all the tattoos I have.
This doesn’t compare to that.
How about this?
Let me know as soon as it’s too much.
Just… say your safe word.
What do you mean?
Just a word that will
let me know when to stop.
It can be anything.
Can’t I just call your name?
Bison, stop it.
Bison, please stop.
Bison.
Nope, that won’t do.
Pretty sure I’ll think
you enjoy it if you do that.
I’ll just hurt you even more.
You’re right.
How about…
Penguin?
Why penguins?
It’s just cute.
I saw a documentary on them.
They’re adorable but can be pretty vicious.
Sounds like you.
Okay, then.
Penguin it is.
Ready?
Are you okay?
It doesn’t hurt as bad
as I thought it would.
The other one, alright?
It’s not too late to back off, you know?
Bison!
Fadel.
What are you doing here?
You didn’t show up at the restaurant.
You weren’t answering my calls.
That’s how I know you’re here.
I was just getting a tattoo.
With you straddling him like that?
Go home.
We have a job to do.
I gotta go.
Let’s go.
I need to talk to him.
Fadel.
Go.
Fadel!
Go!
Hello.
I think I was pretty clear last time.
It seems you don’t remember.
I’ll give you one more fair warning…
You and your mechanic friend
should leave us alone.
Or you’re in for something serious.
Why’d you embarrass me like that?
You neglected your work.
Well?
Were you sleeping with him again?
I didn’t even get to that, Fadel!
You were kind of interrupting!
Fadel.
I don’t want to work at the restaurant.
I want to live my own life.
I don’t want to kill people
anymore, don’t you get it?
I don’t want to wait
tables at a damn burger joint.
I want a boyfriend!
I want to tell him about
myself without lying.
Think about this.
If Mother didn’t take us in, where’d we be?
We would’ve had no parents,
no house to live in, nothing!
How’d we survive like that?
And we’re supposed to do
this for the rest of our lives?
Is that what I said?
Look.
I’ll talk to Mother.
I’ll tell her this will be your last job.
But during this time,
will you just cooperate and listen to me?
Just that.
Okay?
Of course, my best big brother.
Save your goddamn sarcasm.
And if you really want
to talk to that tattooist,
just bring him to the restaurant.
I’d rather you guys
stay where I can see you.
Thanks, Fadel!
Don’t hug me.
I said he could come to the restaurant.
I didn’t say you two can date.
Well, we’re not dating anyway.
We’re just hanging out for now.
Tonight’s task.
Get some information out of
Ruerat’s secretary at a host club.
Host club?
I ain’t playing that role again.
You’re good at it.
So it’s just up your alley.
No.
You do it.
I think this one suits you.
She’s a mature woman.
I’m pretty sure she prefers
your god-sculpted face,
with a jawline so sharp
it cuts, like yours.
I don't think she likes an
adorable petite guy like me.
So, Fadel, tonight,
you’re the star.
Good evening, Ms. Pen.
How are you tonight?
See anyone you like?
Not even close.
I’ve seen them all
before and they’re boring.
Don’t you ever recruit new faces here?
Oh, Ms. Pen.
Of course, we do.
We just recruited some today,
just this afternoon, actually.
With the way they look and everything,
I’m sure they’re your type.
Well, where are they?
All you do is talk.
I’ve been disappointed by
you too many times before.
One more time, and I go somewhere else.
Oh, Ms. Pen, please calm down.
He’s here.
Why don’t you have a little drink first?
Is this one of them?
Yes, he’s just recruited today.
But he’s only pouring your drinks for now.
He’s not ready to entertain anyone.
But if you like him,
he’ll be alright keeping you company.
Come closer.
No.
Too cute.
I prefer someone rougher…
dark and brooding, you know?
Is there anyone like that here?
Someone like that?
Dark and brooding.
Oh, sure there is!
He’s exactly your type.
I’m sure you’ll like him, Ms. Pen.
Less talking, and just bring him out.
Wait a minute.
Oh, he’s hot.
Hey, Dad.
I’m just supposed to
give her the key, right?
She hasn’t paid?
Fine.
Okay.
Hey, you there.
Yes?
Where’s Ms. Ped?
I’m here with her car key.
She’s inside.
You can go in.
Thanks.
Is that enough for you?
It’s perfect.
I love it.
I’ll see you in your room.
That was humiliating as hell.
I think it kinda suits you.
Didn’t know you could dance like that.
I learned it from Magic Mike.
Stop it.
Don’t you think it’s weird, though,
that Keen just suddenly
helped us out like this?
I did at first.
But not anymore.
You know how he is.
Dude just loves getting all the credits.
He probably just wants Mother to approve
so she’d let him on the field, too.
I guess it makes sense.
Is it done?
Yeah. All done.
What about your girlfriend?
Do we just leave her here?
Girlfriend, my ass.
She ain’t my type.
Well, what is your type?
Style?
Piss off.
Just leave her like that.
They’ll just think she’s passed out drunk.
Let’s go home.
Careful not to be seen when you leave.
You go first.
I’ll leave in a bit.
See you at home.
See you, big bro.
Hey.
That was pretty hot.
You again?
Hey, don’t get the wrong idea.
I didn’t follow you.
I’m here to return the car
to the owner of this place.
I just happened to see
your sensual performance.
You’re working at a host club, too?
It’s a second job.
I get it. It pays well, right?
You need the money for
your restaurant, right?
No need to be embarrassed.
An honest job is an honest job.
With your look and your body,
of course you gotta
make some money with it.
Wait.
Don’t go. Let’s chat.
Yeah.
You’re right.
I need the money for my restaurant.
Happy now?
Yeah.
I guess owning a business isn’t easy.
I know because my dad worked
hard for his garage, too.
Do you need to get a loan or something?
I know someone.
Thanks.
But I don’t wanna be in debt.
Hey, newbie.
Where are you rushing off to?
Me?
Yeah, I’m talking to you.
Think you can steal my
regular on your first night?
Ms. Pen usually goes for me.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t know.
I’ll stay out of your way.
You can do what you always do.
Oh, you think you’re better than us?
She paid you well so now you’ll
give us your scraps or what?
Guys, guys.
Let’s be rational here.
I’m sure there are enough
clients with hefty pockets
for all of you.
Who the hell are you?
What do you have to do with this?
I’m just a good-looking pacifist.
You guys are fellow hosts,
so you gotta stick together.
I know people think
lowly of your profession,
but I totally support you.
I’m rooting for you all.
The hell are you babbling about?
I don’t need your support.
I need to let off some steam.
Get away!
Come here!
Hey, that’s not fair!
Piss off!
Get out of the way!
Get up.
No, don’t!
I surrender!
Let’s run.
Let’s get out of here!
You okay?
I am.
Go home.
Hey.
I think there’s
something shady about Fadel.
He’s suspicious.
How so?
As if I’d believe he
needs to work at a host club
to get some money for the restaurant.
Then what’s with all
that pep talk you gave him?
I was just trying to gain his trust.
I was acting stupid
so he doesn’t get suspicious of me.
But I swear something’s off.
You should have seen when he
put those guys in their places.
Damn it, man.
Those three guys sure had
their asses handed to them.
He’s gotta be some kind
of hitman, assassin, killer.
I’m sure of it.
I think you read too much into this.
Maybe he’s just multifaceted like that.
I used to steal cars, you know?
And now I’m a tattoo artist.
I dance, too.
You think too much.
You’re doing a good job.
Just wait a little longer.
Once I get inside their house,
you won’t have to hit on this guy anymore.
And you’ll get my car, as you wish.
The car isn’t a priority anymore.
I just want to find out more about him.
I hate being left in the dark.
So you’re taking my brother out tonight.
Yes.
A friend of mine just opened her own bar.
I thought I’d ask Bison to go with me.
I let you in here,
but that doesn’t mean
you’re free to take him out.
Ever since you’re in the picture,
this guy’s been slacking off at work.
I’m not that bad.
You’re not going anywhere today.
Your schedule is full.
You have dishes to wash
and trash to throw out.
You have to clean this kitchen, too.
And you think you’re free to go anywhere?
Come on, Fadel!
Can’t we switch schedules for once?
I just want to go to this bar.
That’s none of my business.
I have errands to run today.
How about…
I help you out?
You? Doing chores?
Don’t underestimate me, big brother.
I have a little brother, too, you know?
I do all the chores at home.
And I’m hygienic as
hell, I’ll have you know.
I don’t need your bragging.
It’s not a brag.
Fine.
If you finish all the tasks,
I’ll allow it.
But it’d better be spotless.
Really?
You promised?
Go.
You really don’t have to help, you know?
Fadel was clearly messing with us.
It’s alright.
I just want to show your brother
that I’m serious.
Serious, huh?
There!
Hey!
That’s dirty.
It’s dishwater, not soap, you know?
Well, you were asking for it.
The pin looks really great.
Who designed this?
I did.
You’re the best.
I want one.
Will you give me one?
No can do.
I only give this to
my special someone only.
You’re not that yet.
I’ll be your special someone one day.
Hey.
If you don’t get everything done,
and if I see even one
spot on one of the dishes,
you don’t get to go anywhere.
Yes, sir.
This place is great.
The vibe’s kinda beachy, isn’t it?
I love it.
I guessed as much from your taste.
I knew you’d like it.
We haven’t met all that long,
and you already know me that well?
I love learning about you.
Don’t do it so fast.
There’s still so many
things to learn about.
Thanks.
Try this.
It’s the house special.
My friend made this.
I don’t know if you can handle it, though.
It’s pretty damn strong.
Handle it?
You don’t know me well enough, then.
You’re saying you can hold
your liquor looking like a baby?
It’s not too late if you want
a milkshake instead, you know?
Are you challenging me?
If you dare.
I never turn down a challenge.
Winner gets something.
Name it.
If I win,
we go back to your place.
Why do you want to go to my house?
Because my house is occupied.
Babe brought his friends over tonight.
And you said Fadel won’t be home.
I’ll leave as soon as we’re done.
Okay.
Fine.
I don’t want to be a bad
example for you brother anyway.
What if I win?
What do you want?
I’ll give you anything.
If we go back to my place,
can we continue what we left
off at your studio the other day?
I’ll give you a big show.
Big… how so?
It’s a surprise.
Well?
Are you scared?
Okay.
Deal.
One more.
How about a love shot?
Hey.
SUPPORT GROUP FOR LOSS
Losses are typical.
Time will heal.
So feel free to cry it all out.
Take your time.
Is this your first time here?
We welcome you.
We are a support group for
people who have lost someone,
and people who have
not overcome their past.
This is a safe space.
You can trust us.
Would you mind taking off your sunglasses?
Everyone’s more comfortable
knowing each other’s faces.
Please introduce yourself
and tell us your story.
My story?
Something you’ve lost,
or the changing point in your life.
There is one thing.
It’s still stuck with me.
When I was a kid,
there was this one vicious
stray dog always chasing me.
But one day,
I fell down a sewer hole.
There was no one there to help me.
But believe it or not,
this dog went and got help for me.
I survived because of him.
I adopted him immediately
and I named him Boonterm.
But recently…
He fell down a sewer hole and died.
I was deeply depressed.
I don’t know what to do.
Every time I walk by a sewer hole,
I can’t help but see him.
Boonterm.
Boonterm, my boy.
It’s okay.
Boonterm.
You can take your time.
I lost a dog, too.
Wipe your tears.
Here’s some napkins.
My poor boy.
You alright?
This is nothing.
I don’t even feel it.
Wait for me on the dance floor.
I’ll bring you your drink.
Let’s dance.
Sure.
Don’t pass out.
The night is still young.
Hey.
I want the same thing,
but make one shot really strong.
The other shot…
No alcohol.
But can you make it look the same?
What are you talking about?
Just do it.
Fine.
Thanks.
Hey.
I think I’m losing this time around.
Then you’d better tell me your address
before you pass out.
Of course.
But I don’t know if I’m
up for anything tonight.
I’m just feeling so tired.
I’d say you’re still pretty good.
Hey!
Where are you taking me?
Hey, what are you doing?
I’ve been too nice to you.
Do you take other
people’s losses for a joke?
I don’t.
แ
I have my own problems.
You’re not the only one.
Stray dogs?
His name was Boonterm.
Respect him, dude.
And I found this support
group on the internet.
It was a coincidence you’re also here.
That’s it.
I don’t buy that.
I’m hitting on you
because I like you.
I want you.
Nothing more than that.
I don’t like being pursued.
If I like you, I’ll do the pursuing.
Well, then don’t you like me just a little?
No.
I don’t.
Not even a little bit?
You really want me?
Fine.
If you want it,
I’ll give it to you.
Hey, where are you going?
This ain’t no hit-and-run.
I gave you what you wanted.
What kind of man do you take me for?
I might look like I play around,
but I’m damn devoted to love.
I want to date.
Then go find someone.
Hold on.
You can’t do this to me.
Why can’t I?
We agreed on it.
You’re way too mean.
Move.
If you don’t move,
I’ll beat you.
No, you won’t.
You like me.
Hey, Fadel!
As if I’d let you nail
and bail me like that!
Hey, we’re here.
You know…
You’re the first guy I ever brought home.
Thank you.
Where’s your key?
Let’s go.
You alright?
Yeah.
Which room?
Careful.
Hey.
Where are you going?
I’m going to get you some water.
Don’t go.
I’m not that drunk.
That means…
I won.
Hey.
Give me what I asked for.
What are you gonna do?
You know…
I’ve been waiting to have fun
with someone like this for so long.
You ready?
Are you?
Ye–yeah.
Now…
We’ll finally get to do
it as more than strangers.
Hello.
I’m Bison.
The most adorable waiter at a burger joint.
I’m Kant.
I’m a tattoo artist
who loves adorable guys.
Don’t forget your safe word.
Penguin.
Keep your eyes closed.
Hope you don’t say penguin soon.
Directed by Tichakorn Phukhaotong
What are you doing?
How did you get inside my house?
Your brother was dead drunk.
I gave him a ride home.
Besides being a tattooist,
what else do you even know about him?
You have my heart now.
Take good care of it.
What do I have to do to win you over?
I know someone like you
just needs a little nudge.
So what are we?
Be my boyfriend.