WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, ETC. ARE FICTIONAL
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
WITH GUARDIANS PRESENT
ANIMALS WERE FILMED
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION AND WELFARE RULES
- No.
- Are you trying to make me mad, son?
- Honey!
- Will you stop?
I told you it's my teacher's.
Please help me.
This is Kim Wooju.
I was wondering if you went to the doctor.
Maybe I should ask him.
He has the same name.
Jingyeong, can you help me?
Someone needs medical attention.
BUS STOP
Which way are you headed?
Right.
He didn't seem like a weirdo.
I only need him briefly at the ceremony.
KIM WOOJU
CALLING
CACTUS
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
EPISODE 2
What did the doctor say?
Did you get a doctor's note?
Oh, the doctor.
[In background]
I was too busy to see one.
Are you perhaps married?
I'm sorry?
Are you a married man?
No, why?
That's a relief.
What is?
I gave it a lot of thought.
I know it's rash to say this
when we've only met once,
but you're the only one I can turn to.
Could you
be my husband?
Your... your husband?
Of course, I don't mean it for real.
You'd be my husband for one day.
I was wondering
if you could play my husband.
Is this a joke?
I thought this was
about your medical bills.
No, wait!
Sorry about that.
This isn't a joke,
and I haven't lost my mind.
It's really urgent, that's all.
It'd take at least four days
to tell you my whole story.
But my life literally depends on this.
I'll hear you out, then.
Oh, thanks.
I need a husband for a particular reason.
He has to come with me somewhere.
- Where?
- The department store.
- To shop?
- It's not that.
Uh...
Should I tell him about the prize?
I don't want word to get out.
I'll tell you the details
once you agree to help me.
Shouldn't it be the other way around?
How can I help you
without knowing when, why, and how?
I have my own life, too.
Oh, of course.
It'll be this Saturday at 3:00 p.m.
You can meet me
at Beauté Department Store.
Hmm...
All I have to do is
pretend to be your husband?
That's right.
It won't even take that long.
I'll offer compensation
that'll make your time worthwhile.
How much?
A hundred million won?
That's a bit too much.
How come?
I thought that was your base rate.
How much do you want?
A hundred million won.
Oh, that night?
Sorry about that.
I was so drunk
that I mistook you for someone else.
You still seem drunk,
judging by how you're taking me for.
You'll pay me
to play your fake husband for a day?
It's easy to picture how this will play out.
Hubby!
How dare you lock lips with my wife?
You want me to catch you in the act
and collect a settlement from a guy.
Is that it?
A settlement?
Aren't you doing this for money?
I guess you could say money is involved.
See? I knew it.
- You want to shake down some poor guy.
- What?
But look here,
aren't you too young
to be doing things like this?
Think about finding work
and earning decent money,
rather than planning a shakedown.
You have it all wrong. I...
That dirty scam of yours will never work.
I usually don't bother
with others' business,
but I can't let con artists have their way.
Saturday, 3:00 p.m.,
at Beauté Department Store?
I'll remember that.
You'll pay for it if you try anything funny.
You were never going to say yes, were you?
- No.
- Then why did you play along?
I figured it would hurt more
to have hope and then lose it.
That's mean.
- You don't even know my story.
- As if I need to know that.
I'm not kind enough
to be generous to a scammer.
Wait, hold on!
Wooju as head of the Marketing Team?
What about my Eungsoo, then?
You'll kick out someone doing good work
just to make room for Wooju
at the company?
"Kick out?" The correct term
would be a demotion.
A demotion?
That's even more annoying to hear.
So, what if you're annoyed?
He should've done better.
Sales have plummeted
since Eungsoo took over marketing.
Didn't your husband tell you?
That's because
he's only been there for a year.
Once he adjusts...
Where was he before the transfer?
He worked in planning for two years.
Two years is plenty of time to settle in.
How many projects did he ruin
during that time?
- Mom, why dredge up the past...
- Three.
That shows he's incompetent, not unlucky.
But you can't replace him with Wooju.
What would people think?
They'll claim you favor your son's child
over your daughter's.
I'm not favoring Wooju at all.
Eungsoo had the opportunity first.
I'm taking it away since he did poorly.
Mom, is this how it's going to be?
Your son and his wife are long gone,
and I'll be the one to care for you
in your old age.
You can't do this to me.
Confirm if our hangwa will be served
at the Blue House banquet
- for global business moguls.
- Yes, ma'am.
Also, get her out of my face!
- She's making me dizzy.
- Mom!
CFO JANG HANGU
What the...
Seriously?
No way.
Mom, want a bite?
It's one of our newest products,
and it's good. It'll be a huge hit.
You damn brat.
How can you be enjoying that right now?
What now? Why are you all prickly?
Grandma got under your skin again,
didn't she?
I have you to blame for that!
How aren't you annoyed
when Wooju is about to replace you?
Mom, here's the thing.
If the mountain can't be conquered,
you should try to go around it.
To me, hanging on like a damp leaf
feels like pure wisdom.
Gosh, I've got a knot in my back.
You're no damp leaf,
but more like a dog kicked to the curb.
Wake up, you brat!
If you don't have your grandma's approval,
Wooju will take everything from you.
Don't worry, Mom.
I'm not that clueless,
and I have my own plans.
I have it all figured out.
It's from that movie we enjoyed.
Remember?
As if!
What's your problem, Mom?
You said you wouldn't do that
at the office.
- As if!
- Mom, come on!
Dad, can you please stop Mom?
- Don't be like this in the office.
- Get back here.
She's in a foul mood,
so try to cheer her up.
Why didn't you say anything earlier?
She only looks down on Eungsoo more
since you don't stand up for him.
What could I have said?
This is a business we're trying to run.
You still should've butted heads with her.
"How could you be so heartless
when I've worked here for 30 years?
If you keep treating my son that way,
I'll have to put my foot down."
The situation called for it!
Nothing good comes from raising voices
among family members.
Besides, having Wooju here
will be good for Eungsoo.
Having competition helps you grow.
My goodness, you're killing me.
Can't you see how serious this is?
Quit fuming about this
and head to the sauna.
I'll book us a table for dinner
at your favorite sushi place.
- That place?
- Yes.
DAEJU GENERAL HOSPITAL
YOON JINGYEONG
WOOJU
Hey, Wooju.
When do you start work?
Tomorrow.
You'll be busier now.
Still, your grandma will be happy
to see you every day.
She couldn't visit you in the US
because she couldn't get on planes.
And you rarely flew in to see her.
I knew I could count on you
to look after her.
I can't look after her forever, though.
It's not like I'm her granddaughter-in-law.
Are you really
interested in Eungsoo?
Of course not!
That reminds me.
What happened with that woman?
The cactus lady.
She never came back.
Oh, don't worry about her.
She's perfectly fine.
Actually, no. I wouldn't say she's fine.
She must've injured her head,
not her butt.
- She's not right in the head.
- What?
Out of nowhere,
she asked me to be her husband.
What?
Does she like you?
No, she said it was for something else,
but I couldn't care less.
Ayeong!
Seriously.
- Ayeong!
- Goodness.
My goodness, come on.
I told you not to run.
Are you okay?
Let me see.
Enough with the tears,
or the tiger will come and get you.
Take it.
Goodness.
Does anything hurt?
Enough.
Enough with the tears,
or the tiger will come and get you.
Thank you.
Here.
Can you wear it yourself?
There you go. Good girl.
Let's get you on your feet.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Are you okay to walk?
No running, okay?
What was that?
A tiger?
Where did you pick that up?
Beats me.
Maybe it was my grandma.
By the way,
are key rings on backpacks
a thing these days?
Oh, stuffed toys on key rings like that?
Why? Do you want one?
Of course not.
Wait, didn't you find a toy like that
when you were little?
- I think you said someone gave it to you.
- What?
That toy you took with you
when you went to the US.
I teased you
if it was from your first crush.
Don't you remember?
What do you mean, first crush?
- Who was it from?
- I don't know.
I mean it. I don't even remember her name.
I suppose she's living
a good life somewhere.
Hold on.
Still, you can't barge in here like this
in the middle of the night.
I texted you
that the renovation begins next week.
Sir, hurry in there
and measure the sink and windows.
Sure. Sorry about this. We're coming in!
- Sorry.
- Excuse us.
Just a second.
Ma'am, please.
But...
MOM
Hey, Mom. What's up?
It's just that
since your wedding got postponed,
Sori has to book a new flight
and wanted to know the date.
Apparently, the earlier you book flights,
the cheaper they are.
Wooju's extremely busy, you see.
I'll call after discussing it with him.
By the way, how's Sori doing?
She must be doing well
at her restaurant job in the US.
You won't believe
how good her English is now.
She has no problem
talking to Americans on her own.
- Really?
- Yes.
Good for her.
It sounds like she's tied up with her job,
so tell her not to stress
about attending the wedding.
Hey, that's nonsense.
Of course, she should attend
her big sister's wedding.
Just give us a date, or at least tell us
whether it'll happen within the year.
I have a lot to prepare on my end, too.
I'll visit you soon, Mom, so let's talk then.
I have something to tell you.
As in what?
It's not something we should talk about
over the phone.
Don't tell me
you and Wooju got into a fight.
Huh?
Well, you've already registered
your marriage,
- so what's the point of fighting?
- Right.
Instead of arguing with him
about everything,
just give him what he wants.
Sometimes, losing is winning.
Got it?
Mom...
- You see...
- Excuse me.
Come on in. Meri, I have a customer.
We'll talk again some other time.
Mom.
I need to tell her the truth.
But when?
MYUNGSOONDANG
- Uncle.
- Hey.
Come on in.
Have you been well?
It's really reassuring
to have you at the office.
Is it your first time here?
I came by a few times as a kid,
but not since the offices were renovated.
A lot has changed.
You'll need to adjust quickly, Wooju,
since there's a lot for you to do.
I'll learn the ropes fast.
Think of me as your father,
and come to me with any problems.
Thanks, Uncle.
I've always been grateful
for how you've looked after me
since I was a kid.
I'm happy you think that way.
- Why don't you say hi to everyone?
- Sure.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Kim Wooju.
After completing his MBA in the US,
Team Leader Kim Wooju spent four years
at a consulting firm.
It's his first time at a Korean company,
- so help him adjust smoothly.
- Yes, sir.
- Of course.
- Sure.
You'll properly greet them later
at the team dinner.
Ms. Oh, can you give him
a full briefing on the current projects?
Bring him up to speed before the meeting.
Yes, sir.
- Hello, sir.
- Hi.
- Morning, sir.
- Morning.
- Hey, Dad.
- Hey.
I'm sure you remember
the afternoon meeting with the chairwoman.
Of course.
Are you prepared?
Sure.
PREMIUM HANGWA COLLECTION
This is the seven-piece hangwa
assortment that was introduced
at the Paris International
Dessert Fair last year.
When a K-pop artist
with 90 million followers
posted our product on social media,
the dessert went viral among zillennials.
To meet demand, we will
officially release this assortment.
Are we launching in duty-free shops first?
That's right.
With holidays approaching
in China and Japan,
the product will hit the shelves this week.
Beginning next week, it will be available
in department stores across the country.
I like the idea behind the packaging.
It's like an advent calendar.
Yes, there's joy in opening a door
to reveal the dessert inside.
The packaging received a design award
at the dessert fair.
Hold on, Ms. Oh.
Won't we face any copyright issues
with the packaging?
- Sorry?
- I'm just saying
because I remember a time limit
on the packaging design copyright
when we signed the contract last year.
Oh, that?
Sir?
6 MONTHS AGO
Let me see.
"Permanent rights to the design
versus single-use rights."
Single-use rights.
So, we will only hold the rights to it
for a month.
Yes, but the cost will be much lower.
Exactly.
Since it's only for the dessert fair,
let's keep the numbers low.
It's a one-time event anyway.
At the time, we had no plans
to release this as an official product.
So, you didn't renew the contract?
Oh dear, what if the design company
sues us for copyright infringement?
This is a delicate matter nowadays.
Isn't it the team leader's job?
I apologize.
I failed to recognize the issue.
I'll reach out to the design company
right away, extend our contract,
and handle the matter.
What a bunch of amateurs.
Wasn't this supposed to be handled
before the meeting?
Wasn't it?
I suppose only I thought that.
I apologize.
Team Leader Kim Wooju
will ensure the contract is extended.
This is a crucial matter,
so be sure nothing goes wrong.
Yes, ma'am.
Did you say 50 million won?
Fifty?
That's 10 times the original price.
Since we'll be giving up our copyright,
we'll need to account
for the opportunity cost.
Right, please give us a call.
Sure thing.
- What did they say? Are they in?
- They'll call after discussing it.
Are you really asking for 50 million won?
Of course not.
Still, I need to find out what the call
I got this morning was about.
2 HOURS AGO
Hello, this is Merry Design Studio.
Myungsoondang?
The hangwa packaging design?
Yes, that's one of our designs.
What is this about?
Myungsoondang will contact you soon.
When they do,
ask for a high price on the design.
It can even be 10 times the original price.
What?
I'm sorry, but who's this...
Hello?
I initially thought it was a prank,
but Myungsoondang called soon after.
This project was from a year ago.
I still feel we asked for too high a price,
just based on a stranger's words.
What if they call off the deal?
Change the design.
There are other design companies,
and we can redesign the packaging.
I'm afraid
it won't be that easy.
7-PIECE HANGWA ASSORTMENT
PROJECT PROGRESS REPORT
Over 150 million won
went into the pre-production
of the packaging.
Contact the CEO of the design company.
- I'll negotiate.
- Yes, sir.
The grand prize winner is.
Ms. Yoo Meri,
holder of ticket number 29710,
congratulations.
Ms. Yoo, congratulations.
BEAUTÉ CEO LEE SUNGWOO
Damn it!
What are you going to do about this?
We can't redraw the names
now that this is on NeoTube.
I'll look for a way to withdraw the prize.
Can you actually do that?
Come here a second.
How? Just how?
Don't be a crybaby.
You.
Get my shoes cleaned.
Get lost!
BEAUTÉ MANAGING DIRECTOR BAEK SANGHYEON
The mayor's extorting me.
3 MONTHS AGO
He wants one of the town houses
in exchange for approving
the department store development.
A town house?
As in a unit at Beauté Palace?
That scumbag requested
a five-million-dollar unit.
You should give in.
If construction doesn't begin this year,
delays and loan interest will cost more.
Besides, anything can happen
under a new regime.
Hey, as if I don't know that.
I can always offer him one of the units
owned by the group.
But what if my father finds out
about the laundering?
Shit, I can't handle that old man.
We'll give it away through a raffle.
Last month,
the mayor's wife's nephew got married.
The unit will be disguised as a raffle prize
during the department sale.
It's me, Mr. Kwon.
Were you able to contact Yoo Meri?
Of course, the husband must be present.
Otherwise, we'll redraw.
- Should I call them?
- And say what?
That.
I was a bit tipsy from day drinking earlier
and added a zero by mistake.
Don't. We'll wait a little longer.
I'm sure they'll call.
Will your husband
be attending the ceremony?
If he can't,
the prize will no longer be valid.
What did they say?
That was for something else.
- Songhee.
- Yes?
Don't you have an older brother
studying for the civil service exam?
I do.
- How's he doing?
- Beats me.
I haven't seen that jerk
for about two months.
Why do you ask?
Could I maybe ask him for a favor?
If he's free this weekend...
You'll pay for it if you try anything funny.
What if he comes to the ceremony?
I'll be done for if he rats me out.
- Ms. Yoo.
- Yes?
What kind of favor?
It's nothing.
I shouldn't. It's too risky.
Are you going somewhere?
There's someone I have to see.
Call me the moment
you hear from Myungsoondang.
Why hasn't Wooju been in touch?
The jerk went to Hong Kong
and turned off his phone.
Give him time.
Besides, no news is good news.
- Mom.
- Yes?
To be honest,
there's something painful
about Wooju and Meri breaking up.
What do you mean?
I can't have Meri's
green onion kimchi anymore.
The sweet stir-fried eggplant was good,
and her mom's geotjeori
was just the way I like it.
Gosh, I get cravings sometimes.
Same here.
As if her side dishes matter,
when Wooju's new girlfriend is filthy rich.
Her family owns
a few buildings in Hong Kong.
She's rich and then some.
Lucky you, Mom.
Your son will finally give you
a life of luxury.
You hated that Meri wasn't enough.
Don't even bring up that name.
SON
- It's Wooju.
- Is it Wooju?
Why is she looking for you
when she's the one who got scammed?
Of course not.
Who cares if you insisted
on getting that unit?
She always had the option to refuse.
Did she ask you for money?
Of course not.
You're not to blame,
so don't let it bother you.
And don't take Meri's calls.
I've already blocked her number.
Is Elizabeth well?
Of course.
Since she's Jenny's little sister,
we've been taking extra good care of her.
We've been feeding her
only top organic French kibble.
Let Jenny know
we're taking good care of her.
By the way, when will you be back?
- Next month.
- Next month?
What about work?
Your son
tossed in his resignation letter.
You quit your job? Why?
- Why?
- Don't worry.
Jenny's got me covered.
What now?
Oh, the bowls.
Coming!
Oh, well. That was sooner
than usual.
I haven't been able to reach Wooju.
Why do you need to contact him
when you broke up?
There's an urgent matter.
Is this about the rental scam?
Did you get in touch with him?
Yes, and he told us all about it.
But what about it?
Did your mom tell you to cling to Wooju
by any means necessary?
- What?
- I wasn't going to go this far,
but you have absolutely no shame.
You have only one parent, you're old,
and you went to a third-rate university...
She dropped out, remember?
That I didn't know.
Let me get this straight.
A college dropout dared to marry my Wooju,
who graduated from both
a prestigious high school and university?
I invested so much in him,
driving him around to his extra classes.
Meanwhile, you did nothing.
The best you could do
was rent a place to live,
but even that was only in your own name.
I didn't know about that, either.
Exactly, and I call that a scam.
The place should've been
in both your names.
The loan for the deposit
was taken out in my name, so
I'm glad you brought that up.
Since the unit is in your name,
handle the rental scam yourself
instead of troubling my Wooju.
I'm not trying to give him a hard time.
Mother, I came here today
- because I won...
- Mom.
This isn't worth our time.
Just stop, okay?
If you have a shred of conscience,
you won't bring Wooju down with you.
You registered the marriage in advance
just to trap him, you gold digger.
What did you just call me?
Talk about a bad match.
Get lost already.
If we ever meet again,
let's act like strangers.
Are you striking first?
What?
Are you worried I'll ask Wooju for money?
Don't worry. I'll deal with the debt
that's in my name.
But that's not what I
came here to talk about.
Either way,
I suppose there's no point
in telling you anymore.
Please tell Wooju
that I won't be contacting him again.
If you two happen to hear
about me, just ignore it.
I'll get going then.
I can see Wooju takes
so much after you, Mother.
Now I know where he got his audacity.
Why you...
That's hardly appropriate for a woman
from a family of educators.
If you hit me,
I'll put up posters in the neighborhood
exposing that your husband was fired
for sexually harassing his TA.
My gosh!
That bitch!
It's over now.
I tried my best.
SONGHEE
What's up?
Right now?
No, I can make it, so say so.
Sure.
Yes, Ms. Yoo. Head straight up.
Mr. Kim, the CEO
of the design company is here.
- Conference Room Two, is it?
- Yes.
Where are you headed?
To sign the contract.
With the designer?
You're hard at work even on day one.
I'm paid from the first day, aren't I?
Oh, good one.
That's a healthy approach.
You must be carrying quite a burden
on your shoulders.
Grandma's expecting results.
Meanwhile, your load is light
because you have no work.
Come on, man.
I was the team leader up until yesterday.
So, the work you're handling now
used to be what I did.
You should've taken care of this
instead of dumping it on the next person.
I dumped what on you?
That wasn't me.
I would've handled it
if I were the team leader.
It seems like I was brought in
because you couldn't.
What? What are you going on about?
Okay, fine.
If you think you can do it better,
extend the deal at the same price.
Then I'll fully recognize
your talent and competence.
- Really?
- But if you don't get the deal,
you'll leave your position.
What do you say?
We'll settle this man-to-man.
I'm in.
If you're done, can you move?
I have to go and clean up your mess.
Is that the best you can put it?
It won't be as easy as you think.
I'm a man with a plan, you see.
What's he doing here?
I must've seen wrong.
I guess I'm so stressed.
I'm starting to see things.
He's our new team leader,
and he wanted to talk to you in person.
I'm Kim Wooju.
This is my one last chance.
I'm Yoo Meri from Merry Design Studio.
I'll get straight to the point.
The price you asked for is too high.
It's well over the market average,
and most design companies could create
a design of similar level and quality.
However, if you agree to renew
the contract at the same price,
the company will offer an extra benefit.
We'll ask you to handle
the packaging design
for our latest product.
A partnership with our company
will help you build your portfolio.
Sure.
Thank you.
I'm glad we're on the same page.
On one condition, though.
Would it be all right
if Mr. Kim and I talked alone?
It's fine.
STANDARD CONTRACT FOR DESIGN SERVICES
I'll get back to work.
What's your term?
Be my husband.
Are you still set on that?
I'm making a new request,
given how our dynamic has changed.
How has it changed?
Well, before, I was the only one
who needed help,
but now you do, too, right?
If I turn down this deal,
it could cost you billions.
How can we look
for another design company
now that the packaging is done
and the promotional posters are made?
Right.
Merry Design Studio is a small business,
so we'll have to push hard
in negotiations.
That would be on our team leader.
You've already mass-produced
the packaging?
You have leverage, is that it?
It's more like I have a reason
to keep you at the table.
Consider this negotiation over.
We may lose money over this,
but it beats being implicated in fraud.
Ms. Yoo, you realize
you'll be arrested for attempted fraud
if I report you to the authorities.
I'll make that call, then.
Not so fast!
What do you mean you'll report me?
There's no reason to be mean.
Don't we all deserve
to dream and fantasize?
You openly suggested
that I commit a crime with you.
How is that just fantasizing?
But...
But... Okay, hear me out.
I lost everything in a rental scam,
but I won a five-million-dollar house.
If it were you,
would you let this chance slip away?
I just need a husband to tag along,
so wouldn't you do whatever it takes?
You won a prize?
So, that's what this is all about.
Sure.
Exactly. I won a prize, okay?
So, please...
Can you please just help me this once?
They suddenly said I have to bring
my husband to the ceremony,
but I don't have time
to find someone else.
That's too bad.
I feel for your situation,
but my conscience won't allow it.
How's it going?
You'll step down as team leader
if this deal falls through.
I'm texting to confirm our deal.
Team Leader Kim Wooju
will ensure the contract is extended.
This is a crucial matter,
so be sure nothing goes wrong.
Mr. Kim!
Look at this.
What if my elbow keeps hurting
whenever it rains?
The aftereffects of a car accident
are usually scarier.
Come on. That only happened because you...
Here. Where do I sign?
Isn't this a win-win situation?
I'm a pro at signing contracts.
MYUNGSOONDANG YOO MERI
It won't take long, so please relax.
Did you perhaps read the text I sent?
Our wedding date, address,
and the registration number.
You said all I had to do
was stand next to you.
Oh, of course.
But you never know, so...
Forget I said anything.
I'll handle all the questions.
You just stand there...
Wait for me.
Going up.
Take this.
It's a wedding band.
Sure.
These too.
In the photo I sent of Kim Wooju
to the department store,
he was wearing glasses.
Right.
You look like him.
Hold on.
How did you send a copy of an ID?
Did you fake it?
Of course not.
I had a copy of his passport,
which I sent to the travel agency
when I was booking our honeymoon.
- That's what I sent.
- I see.
Do you have any idea
how risky this scam is?
The other Kim Wooju wouldn't let this fly.
You don't have to worry about that.
Kim Wooju's the one
who's been dodging my calls,
and I won't tell anyone else about this.
I'll sell the house as soon as I get it.
I won't get caught.
Oh, just know I'll make it worth your time
once I sell the house.
I seriously promise you that.
Forget it.
I don't want black money
or anything that feels wrong.
I told you all about the situation I'm in.
I'm a victim of fraud,
and I have my mom's debt to pay.
Who in this world
doesn't have a sob story?
But not everyone scams others like you.
Of course, I want to live
by my conscience,
but the situation I'm in
is just too damn hard!
Did you just raise your voice at me?
Sorry.
A ceremony?
Wasn't the prize called off?
I'm sorry, sir.
You.
Is this what you call
handling the situation?
What now?
What will I tell my father
when he gets back?
I already informed him
that this is a social contribution event.
- A social contribution?
- You've become active on social media
to engage with zillennials.
By presenting this as an event
to support young people without homes,
the press will take an interest.
On top of that,
a positive public image could help
get the new department store approved.
Sounds good. Go with that.
Congratulations.
You're lucky to have a wife like her, sir.
Yes, sure.
It seems as though
reality hasn't sunk in yet for him.
Of course.
When we didn't hear back
from you yesterday,
we thought we had to withdraw the prize.
He just arrived in Korea this morning.
You must be tired, honey.
Right, I kind of am.
That must be why
you don't look like your photo.
You look somewhat different
from your ID photo.
He took that photo a while back,
so that must be why.
Of course.
A lot of people
don't look like their photos.
Exactly.
May I see your IDs?
You already did.
These are only copies,
and I need to check them in person.
I'm not sure if we brought them with us.
Did we?
Mine's here, but
I can see that.
That's you.
And the husband?
It's in the car.
I forgot to tell him to bring it.
I see.
Then how should we proceed?
What's your resident registration number?
- It's 960902...
- It's 960902-102463.
Our address is
Unit 101, Green Villa, 118 Hanseo-dong,
Jungmun-go, Seoul.
We registered our marriage
on Monday, January 6 of this year.
Confirmed.
When did he memorize all that?
Is he a genius?
Sir, can you confirm the press release?
Sure.
Please relax and enjoy your tea.
The CEO isn't ready quite yet.
Sure.
IN AN INTERVIEW, THE LUCKY COUPLE
PRESS RELEASE, BEAUTÉ
BEAUTÉ DEPARTMENT STORE 30TH ANNIVERSARY
COUPLE WINS FIVE-MILLION-DOLLAR UNIT
AT BEAUTÉ PALACE
Hold on.
- Sir.
- Yes?
Will this be in the press?
Of course.
An article will be released
right after the ceremony.
- I had no idea.
- An article?
- Sir.
- Yes?
Sorry, we can't have this in the news.
We don't want word to get out.
Is it because
of creditors?
- Because they could come after you?
- Right.
How did you know that?
That's why I haven't been able
to share this with others.
It's as I thought.
It's not just creditors.
You'll probably even get calls
from distant family members.
Two years ago, was it?
After winning fourth place in the lottery,
I had to buy so many people meals
just for sharing it on social media.
- You were one of them.
- That's right.
I even had to pay
for my wife's nephew's college tuition.
We appreciate your understanding.
Please don't thank me
when I have to apologize.
The article has to be released.
What? That can't happen.
But, sir, this was never the agreement.
You can't release an article
without our consent.
Here.
"The prize winner is required
to cooperate with any event publicity."
It says so right here.
Then, could you at least
let us use false names?
Sure, I'll consider that.
YOO MERI 32, KIM WOOJU 29
Put them under false names.
Can I please take this call?
The ceremony is about to begin,
so don't wander off.
Sure.
Hello?
A case of African encephalitis?
Sure.
I have a fever, and my throat hurts.
Could this be contagious?
That means other people
could get it from me.
I'm in a public space right now.
Yes, of course.
Please let me know
as soon as you have the test results.
Got it.
Honey, do you have a face mask?
I don't. Why?
One of the people I flew in with yesterday
has a case of African encephalitis.
- Goodness me.
- You've heard about it.
It's an infectious disease
that's been taking lives around the world.
- The one with the highest mortality rate.
- Right.
Jeez, this is bad.
My test results aren't back yet,
but since my coworker got it,
they want me retested...
Are you all right?
I think I'm showing symptoms.
This is terrible.
MR. KWON
Yes, Mr. Kwon.
Mr. Baek,
I have urgent news.
A case of African encephalitis?
He's not sick yet,
so make him wear a mask.
That alone isn't enough
to call off the ceremony.
Anyway, the article
about Mr. Lee matters most.
Of course, sir. I understand.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be. Shall we?
- Ma'am.
- Yes?
May I borrow this cap?
Sure.
I'll return it to you soon.
I'll take the photo in one, two, three.
One, two...
Ma'am, could you lower the flowers?
We can't see your face.
Okay, that's better.
Sir, can you lift your cap a bit?
Lower the flowers, too. Much better.
Focus the camera on Mr. Lee.
Right. Of course.
Mr. Lee, can you flash a generous smile?
Give a killer smile.
One, two, three.
One, two, three!
I'll head out first.
Thanks for today.
I was actually going to take you out
for a meal afterward...
All right.
Now that the ceremony is over,
you can collect your prize.
Right.
Here you go.
Thank you.
We want nothing but happiness
for you both.
- Right.
- Just a second.
Could you sign this form
saying you received the prize?
- Sure.
- And read the instructions on the back.
Right.
THINGS TO KNOW BEFORE SIGNING THE FORM
YOO MERI
- I'll now escort you to the town house.
- Okay.
Good.
Hold on.
Where's your husband?
Oh, he went to the hospital
to get retested.
It looks like
I'll be the only one to come with you.
Oh, I see.
Shall we get going, then?
- I see you're still here.
- Oh, right.
I was just about to leave.
Which way is the hospital?
Well...
It's in Gangnam.
That's good to hear. I'll drive you there.
No, it's fine. I can just take a cab.
We're headed in that direction anyway.
Which hospital is it?
Actually, I just got off a call
with the hospital.
My test came back negative.
I don't have to get retested.
You should come with us, then.
You'll need a tour of the town house, too.
Sure. What?
Go where?
I'm sorry.
Beauté Palace
is a luxury town house compound
created, marketed, and sold
by our own Beauté Construction.
The whole compound was designed
following feng shui principles,
said to provide good energy.
Because of that, it's now home
to political and business leaders
as well as
world-famous Korean celebrities.
You might bump into them
at the gym or cafe inside the compound.
Each unit sells for millions,
but none are on the market.
There are three complexes,
and the house you won is in Complex Two.
I see.
You said the chairman
loves kimchi from Punggukdang.
Gosh, orders were already full,
but I paid extra to skip ahead in line.
That's right.
Our hangwa?
Of course, we brought some.
That's our main goal today.
I asked them to box only the pretty ones.
Sure. Got it.
I'll call after I'm done.
But, Mom,
shouldn't Dad go, since it's the chairman
of the Association of Business Executives?
He and Dad went to the same college.
Your dad's giving you an opportunity.
He wants you to accomplish
something in your name.
Can I say I did this myself?
That's right.
I heard Wooju handled the design contract
on his first day at the office.
So, you need to do a good job, too.
Also, always keep an eye on him
to see if he's up to anything suspicious.
Sure, I'm to keep an eye on him.
Just wait until I catch him doing
something questionable.
By the way, it's really nice here.
Where am I supposed to go?
The appliances are built in,
and the place comes furnished
since it was used as a show house.
If you'd like,
we could remove them for you.
Not at all. We're grateful to have it all.
There's even a yard.
This looks like a fancy resort.
I'm glad you like it.
When are you planning to move in?
Move in?
You see, there's a chance
we might sell it right away.
It's quite far from both of our workplaces.
It's better to live closer to work.
Of course, you can sell the house.
But not right away.
THINGS TO KNOW BEFORE RECEIVING THE PRIZE
As previously informed,
the house can be transferred to
a different owner only after three months.
Until then, you can't sell it because
it technically belongs to our company.
Then, why did you give me a key earlier?
It symbolizes your right
to stay in this house.
Five years ago in England,
a similar prize event was held
for a million-pound house.
Right after receiving the prize,
the couple got divorced,
making a mockery of the event.
That's why we introduced
a three-month grace period
to demonstrate the event's sincerity.
If you get divorced during that period,
the prize will become invalid
and be withdrawn.
Three months?
Is there a problem?
No, of course not.
We have to move out
of where we're staying now
and find another place to live.
We can live here for three months
before selling it.
Also, there may be a few inspections.
Inspections?
It's only a formality,
but our inspector will call you
before visiting.
But in your case, that won't be necessary
since I'll see you every day.
- Sorry?
- What?
I'm one of the residents here.
What? You live here, too?
Which house is yours?
The one across the street.
That...
- Over there?
- That one?
It's been lonely with the house empty,
and I'm thrilled to have new neighbors.
That's great.
You can take a look around later on.
For now, I'll show you
the community center and walking trail.
We'll meet out front in 20 minutes.
I'll go and get changed.
- Sure.
- Right.
Then...
THINGS TO KNOW BEFORE RECEIVING THE PRIZE
Seriously.
What do you mean you'll move in here?
Do you want to get caught?
You see,
I need to move out by the end of this week
and have nowhere to go.
But don't worry too much.
He may live across the street,
but I doubt I'll see him often.
He just said he was thrilled
to have new neighbors.
He could come by every morning
and suggest we work out together.
Then,
I'll say you're on a business trip.
Will you say that every time?
That's even more suspicious.
Why not just say
I spend months at sea fishing
or that I'm a pilot?
That's a great idea.
What?
How is that a good idea?
What can we do, then?
If you have any good suggestions,
I'm all ears.
Why are you turning to me for ideas?
This is your mess to clean up.
So much for this being a one-time thing.
I shouldn't have believed you.
What now?
The guy across the street
will be watching us.
I'm sorry.
I'll make sure you're not bothered by this.
How can I not be worried?
An article with our photo was published.
Now that I'm involved,
I'll also get in trouble if we get caught.
Don't think about living here.
Things will get worse if we're caught.
Then, where am I supposed to live?
Stay at a dry sauna for all I care.
CACTUS
TEAM LEADER KIM WOOJU
Officail Website : kissasian.be  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Hello?
I'm sorry I yelled at you earlier,
but if you were in my shoes...
Excuse me, can you help us?
Where's Complex Three...
Wooju, is that you?
Wooju?
Hello?
Mr. Kim?
Where are you right now?
Auntie.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I'm here to see a friend.
What? A friend? What friend?
Just a friend.
Anyway, what brings you two here?
We're here to see the chairman of...
We're here to see someone we know.
It's nothing important.
You're already out.
- I'll see you around.
- Sure.
Hey, did you say
the walking trail was that way?
- It is.
- Right.
What about your wife?
Sorry?
His wife?
CACTUS
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
- Who were those people?
- My relatives.
The winner was announced.
The winner is
I'd love for you
to be my granddaughter-in-law.
I'll trust you've got my back
and make my move on him.
Looks like you could be
getting what you want
by pretending it's for wedding photos.
What was that look just now?
Does your husband actually live here?
Translated by Hyelim Park