♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my playful charm♪
♪Just to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for you♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
Hurry up and throw all her stuff out.
What a jinx.
(Liu Qin, Jiang Niannian's stepmother)
Jiang Feng!
That little burden isn't dead.
She's back to settle the score.
=Episode 2=
=You're Not Getting Rid of Me Again!=
Xiaodi still is still missing.
None of you are leaving!
Niannian.
- You cursed woman, killed three husbands.
- Let's talk this out.
Good that Jiang Xiaodi went missing,
or you'd get him killed someday.
If anything happens to Xiaodi,
I will make you pay!
Jiang Feng.
Jiang Xiaodi is your own son.
He's missing now.
We don't even know if he's alive.
Are you even human?
What bad luck
to have such a son.
Pitifully,
we signed an organ donation agreement
for that burden.
We thought we could
get some compensation money,
earn him some "good karma" for his next life.
What are you doing?
Put it down.
- Put it down, Niannian.
- Put down the knife.
(Jiang Feng, Jiang Niannian's Father)
Be good.
Put it down.
If anything happens to Xiaodi,
I'll kill you!
Niannian, put it down.
Jiang.
Mr. Song, you're finally here.
Don't come any closer.
Take her back with you.
Do whatever you want.
I'm...
I'm calling the police.
Go ahead.
You animals.
Mr. Song, take her away.
Take her away.
- Take her.
- Got it.
Take her away,
and the debt I owe you
is settled.
You little brat.
Let go of me!
- Let go.
- Let her go.
♪Chasing through the shadows♪
♪We'll still find our castle♪
♪Gonna win the battle♪
Are you hurt?
You...
Why are you here?
Don't be scared.
I'm here.
Who are you?
Listen,
this woman
is mine today.
Gambling debts,
identity fraud to open accounts,
that's enough to send you both to prison.
(Borrower: Jiang Feng)
Who exactly are you?
Jiang Niannian.
Are you really going
to team up with an outsider
to send your own dad to jail?
Jiang Niannian is the one to blame!
She seduces rich men with her looks.
She killed her husband for money.
Shut up.
You better remember this.
She's with me.
(I knew it.)
(Rich boys)
(love playing the hero.)
Let go of me.
Thank you.
Come with me.
I'll take care of all this.
I don't need that.
In this world,
I can rely on no one.
Could you please leave my home?
This house has already been mortgaged.
Lock the door.
What are you doing?
Now let's calculate
how much you still owe me.
Let go of me.
No.
Let go!
You...
Her parents
signed the IOU.
I have it.
She has to pay for them.
Even at the police station,
you'll have to admit it.
I will take her with me.
How much do you want?
Fine.
If you'd hooked up with a rich man earlier,
would your parents have sold the house
and you to pay the debt?
Take your things and get out.
Go.
I don't have a home anymore anyway.
Anywhere is the same.
Niannian.
I don't need your pity.
I'll give you a home.
Thank you.
Ye Lang.
Meeting you
is the greatest luck of my life.
(What a sucker.)
(He helped me get rid of that trouble)
(and brought me big money.)
(What a blessing.)
You know what?
Aside from my mom,
you're the only one this good to me.
You're drunk.
I'm not drunk.
I know I shouldn't be so impulsive.
But I'm just really happy today.
I just want to drink a little more.
You're really drunk.
Where are we going next?
Where do you want to go?
As long as I'm with you,
I'll go wherever
you take me.
No rush.
Go take a shower first.
I've prepared a surprise for you.
♪I'm the sun♪
♪Lift me up♪
♪Leave the past♪
♪There to rot♪
♪I'm breaking up all the memories♪
♪Because I am moving on♪
♪But I♪
♪Won't forget♪
♪Where I came from♪
Really top quality.
My money
was well spent.
The agent said
you're pretty skilled.
The...
agent?
Yeah.
That young lady
said she "checked the goods."
Why so shy now?
In a bit,
I need you to try harder, okay?
Hey, where'd you go?
(Transfer received: RMB 200,000)
That rich lady looked loaded,
dripping in gold and jewelry.
If I weren't rushing to find Xiaodi,
with Ye Lang's looks,
I could've sold him for even more.
Sorry,
my "dead" husband.
Whether you're truly innocent
or just pretending,
I'm not playing sweet romance
with you anymore.
The city's largest business conglomerate,
the Li Group,
is holding a press conference today.
This is the first press conference
since the death of its president...
(Miss Jiang, we've searched the whole city.)
(There's still no sign of your brother.)
Keep searching.
I'll transfer the money soon.
Jiang Niannian,
you still dare to come here?
You've delayed payments multiple times.
You're already blacklisted by us.
Pay up.
Use my card.
This card doesn't even have a number on it.
Trying to fool me again?
Run it and you'll know.
Believe me now?
I never default on debts.
You've still been treating my brother
despite all the overdue payments,
I really appreciate it.
You should find your brother soon.
He's been missing for days.
Given his condition,
he may not have much time left.
Try other hospitals or even funeral homes.
Alive or not, you need an answer.
(Hacking into the hospital firewall)
(will be faster.)
(Manlong City Medical Chain Archive)
(This is it.)
(No Permission)
(The Li Group has just integrated
national medical resources,)
(and will establish a connected)
(medical archive network
for Manlong residents.)
(To enter the national medical market,)
(they've prepared everything.)
(As long as I can get into the Li family,)
(I can definitely
use the information network)
(to find Xiaodi.)
(Breaking news.)
(The late former president
of the Li Group...)
(Cracking In Progress)
(Young Master Ye Lang,)
- (showed up at the press conference)
- Ye Lang? Wasn't he dead?
- (An illegitimate son, but highly valued...)
- Oh my, how is he back?
- (He previously faked his death...)
- Mr. Ye, please answer us.
- (Maybe it was internal family conflict...)
- How have you come back from the dead?
(Second Young Master Li Hong's bid for power
has failed.)
Are you back to fight for the family assets?
Please answer the question.
How could it be him?
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪