(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
Our plan is approching.
Still, you have to be careful.
Because Weiling are not someone you get close to easily.
And far more ruthless than one might assume.
You know how far I've come.
I've planned my whole life.
The one who ruined my life.
I'll make sure they lose everything they love.
I'll make them feel every bit of pain.
And every ounce of loneliness.
Just as I was.
Weiling's W EMPIRE
Is already publicly listed.
It's a giant that has dominated
The developer market for years.
Arguably the industry leader.
Handling only high-profile clients
Known for projects worth hundreds of millions
I think a new company like ours would struggle to compete.
What's wrong with you?
We haven't even competed yet.
Already thinking about loosing?
That was not what I meant.
I'm just saying that to win over them is not easy.
I don't have the strength.
If you don't have the strength.
Then use strategy
Who said that to win a war.
You must need only a troop of soldiers
Victory comes by planning the right strategy.
Alright, If you say so.
Then I'll celebrate our victory now.
Shall we go tonight?
Pardon?
It's not even started yet.
Going to party already?
Well, today is my birthday.
Isn't it should be a girls night?
Please join me tonight.
There is a new jazz bar
I'll drive you over
It's a hidden gems
No, it would be crowded
Party here, there's no limits.
You can listen to jazz all night long.
How many bottles of wine you want?
I'll pay for it.
That's not what I want.
We're so good-looking
We must show it to the world.
Come on
Just celebrating my birthday.
I don't want to be on my own.
That's sad.
Petra Corporation is currently establishing a new business division.
It will be a global hospitality group focused on luxury hotels and resorts
Designed to embody warmth, a sense of family.
And deliver an elevated level of luxury.
That surpasses conventional hotel standards.
Petra intends to launch its flagship.
Cornerstone Hotel in Bangkok.
They are particularly interested.
In the Suan Phiman area.
Where our company, W Empire.
Already owns and manages multiple developments.
If we are able to form a joint investment with Petra.
It is projected to generate long-term revenue of approximately
500 to 800 million baht annually.
Who is overseeing this project?
Mr. Kevin Lee, the youngest heir of Petra Corporation's founder, Mrs. Petra Lee.
Mr. Kevin the one who was recently appointed CEO?
That's correct
Then there shouldn't be any issues. I know him well enough.
But with someone like him this may require a more discreet approach.
However, we are not the only option.
Who else is competing with us?
Petra is also considering another location.
The Lan Arun district.
The developer currently dominating that area.
Is a company called AList.
AList.
They've been making waves.
They've only been around for a few years.
Yet they've already secured multiple prime districts.
Still, I don't see it as a real threat.
For a project of this scale
Petra wouldn't entrust it to a newcomer.
In the end, they'll choose us
Arisa Kunnavee.
AI.
There are so many people.
Here you are, Boss.
You're my guest tonight.
I'll take a good care of you.
Wait, let me ask you something.
Don't you have any other friends?
Why did you drag me here?
For the past few months I was glued to you.
All of my friends were tired of having me
So you have to stay with me instead.
Let's go.
Be careful.
The night hasn't even begun.
Well...
Let's party.
What?
People here are rather straightforward, aren't they?
Their gaze makes it obvious.
Come on.
Look how gorgeous you are.
Obviously, everyone will look at you.
I'm going to find a table.
Please order yourself a cocktail.
Order some for me also.
I'll have a glass of Pinklady.
Don't forget you still owe me a cocktail.
Wait.
Don't tell me that you brought me over just to pay?
That's right.
For real?
I'll have one Martini
And a Pinklady
Excuse me.
Was that your girlfriend?
No, she's my friend.
So I have a chance right?
I'm Waii.
I'm Arisa.
If you don't mind.
Let's have fun together.
I'm here alone.
I'm so lonely.
Just come.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Hey!
Hey you!
My back is aching.
Why does a life as a musician is so tough
What do you mean?
You chose it yourself.
I can't help you.
And I told you.
It's not easy to be a pianist
I know.
But you're the one making me play it 4 hours straight.
My life isn't worthless...
I have expences to carry.
Hey, you're the one begging me to work here.
Which I don't get it.
Why do you want to have a nine to five lifestyle.
Make a living like me.
Look at me.
I don't even know that this bar
Will last until the end of the year or not.
If I were you, I will enjoy every moment in life.
I can do whatever I want without thinking much.
Are you sure?
I don't feel lucky at all.
Whatever, it is what it is.
I love to play the piano.
I can make some money by being an pianist.
Being a musician, sounds so luxurious.
But in reality, it's just a job.
Not a fast track to be rich or famous.
That's why my mom doesn't want me to become one.
Hey, or should I stop playing?
I don't want to play it anymore.
It's tiring.
What's up, my dear friend?
What do you think about it.
Should I stop playing piano?
What should I do?
Should I stop playing?
If so, think it this way.
If you don't play piano.
What else you can choose to do in your life.
Sometimes these feelings come to remind you.
How much you love what you're doing.
Because there are many people
Whose duty and responsibility make them unable to follow their dreams.
I think if your life have a choice.
You should choose to do what you love.
Don't let anyone control your life.
Excuse me.
Where did my friend go?
She left quite a while ago.
Already left?
Why didn't you tell me.
You kept me grumbling for a while.
Well...
It was rather enjoyable to listen to.
Enjoyable enough to start giving advice too, I suppose?
I guess you felt a little sorry for someone that so lost isn't.
But either way.
Thank you.
Your advice really helped me.
You're not a life coach, are you?
Or are you secretly trying to sell me a course?
No, not at all.
I'm just here to hang out.
I was only teasing.
I hope it helped.
It helped more than you know.
Lyla! Are you done?
Time to go, hurry!
You're not leaving yet, right?
You'll still be here?
Please wait for me. I finish work at midnight.
I'd like to have a proper conversation with you.
I'll be back.
Please wait for me.
Wow
I only ordered two drinks.
Well, if the boss is treating, I might as well make the most of it.
Happy birthday to me, boss.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Let's take a break.
Let yourself be carried away by the paino, played by our stunning artist.
This is her space.
Ms. Lyla.
Alright. I need the original draft by tonight.
I'm waiting for confirmation.
Prepare the post.
That was so much fun.
Thank you.
Are you sure you're okay? Look at you.
Boss.
I'm fine.
You should head inside.
Go put that beauty of yours to good use.
I don't think you're okay. Let me drive you home.
No, no, no, boss.
I'm perfectly fine.
You should take some time for yourself too.
Work hard, play harder…right, boss?
And how exactly are you getting home?
Please, just go inside. I'll be fine.
There's my ride. I'll head off now.
Hey! Are you really okay? / Happy birthday, boss!
It's your birthday, you silly girl.
Watch your step.
Just go, driver.
What the hell is this.
Just follow the map.
No need to talk. Just drive.
Go, go, go!
Hey! You got into the wrong car. I'm not your driver.
Hey! Don't you dare throw up in my car.
I won't.
What kind of situation is this
Hey, pull yourself together.
Just follow the map.
Sonata Condo.
If it's that place, I don't need a map.
Hey, I told you
I'm not a taxi.
Get out.
Hey! Wake up! Where are your friends?
Happy birthday to you.
Oh great, wishing me a happy birthday?
If I leave her like this, something bad could happen.
What should I do
I'll just consider it helping another woman.
Were you looking for me?
You told me to wait, didn't you?
You're too easy to fool.
Be careful, you might become a scammer's next victim.
So you had me wait just for fun?
What a waste of time.
Wait!
I'm Lyla.
I'm glad you waited for me.
I'm Arisa.
And since you made me wait I hope it was worth it.
I don't know if it was worth it.
I just wanted to repay you.
Repay me for what? I only gave you simple advice.
You could've asked ChatGPT.
It would've said the same thing.
I guess...
ChatGPT isn't as good-looking as you.
Come on, let's go. I'm hungry.
Go where? I thought we were going to have a deep talk.
We can deep talk while eating something deep-fried.
Sounds perfect, doesn't it?
Let's go.
No, I don't eat late at night.
Come on.
Just skip it for a day.
Consider tonight a special night.
Where you don't have to follow the rules.
Come on, I'm starving.
Hey! Wait!
Does your workplace do not let you eat?
Why do you look so hungry?
They do.
But right before performances.
I get nervous so I can't really eat.
So.
Have you been playing the piano for a long time?
To be honest.
My mother had me learn since I was a child.
But professionally only for a few months.
But I didn't do it for a living.
The money isn't that great.
Here, have some.
What about you? What do you do?
Me?
I'm a photographer.
A photographer?
Do you shoot people?
Landscapes?
Or pets? Something like that?
Well, actaully everything that you've mentioned. People, animals, scenery
But I prefer photographing people.
They have stories that were far more interesting.
Then am I interesting enough to be your model?
Maybe like this.
Or like this.
Or even like this.
What do you think? Am I good enough?
Am I?
Not yet.
I don't know you well enough.
So I don't know how interesting you are.
That's a bit harsh.
So what kind of person is interesting to you?
Someone interesting.
Doesn't need to try.
Just being themselves.
That's enough.
Just being themselves?
You said it yourself.
Let's keep eating.
Excuse me, complimentary fortune cookies from the house. Please, make a wish.
That's cute.
You should try.
No thanks.
Come on just try.
I wish you both a good luck.
Do you think it'll come true?
Whether it does or not just try it.
What does yours say? Let me see.
Hey, let me see!
Fortunes telling should not be shared. Else it would never comes true.
Not always.
Share it.
I'll show you mine.
No, I don't need to know yours either.
So stingy.
They have new things today.
Do you come here often?
Quite often. Mostly after work.
It's relaxing and cheap too.
We should come together again sometime.
Who would go out with you again?
Once is enough.
Fine. Once it is.
Then let's make tonight count.
There's so much stuff here.
The atmosphere really nice too.
Hey.
Look over there.
That kid plays beautifully.
But no one's watching.
Looks like he's been playing all night.
Do you want to help him?
I have some cash.
You want it?
No thanks.
I think I have a better way.
“Let me move a little closer, just a little closer…
This small heart of mine longs to care for you…
Like a true love…”
... I wish to be your one and only"
Thank you.
If you enjoyed that, please don't forget to support him as well.
Were you secretly taking photos of me?
Not secretly.
I meant to.
So does that mean I'm interesting to you now?
Besides singing and playing music.
What else can you do?
A lot. But you'll need time to find out.
So just tonight isn't enough.
Let's go over there.
Wait.
At night is beautiful too.
Look at those lights.
No wonder you like coming here.
It's peaceful.
Hey!
What?
Come here. Quick!
Stay here.
Come on!
Hey!
Hurry up!
Wait!
Are you okay?
I'm not. My feet hurt. Why did you bring me here?
Let's go back home.
Wait!
Stay a little longer.
I don't often have someone to talk to like this.
Are you that lonely?
I grew up alone.
Not
many friends. me.
No one really pays attention to me.
It feels like I'm alone in this world.
I understand that loneliness.
I've felt it my whole life.
That's why I had to find a purpose.
Something that makes my life worth living.
I don't know what you've been through.
But it must have been hard.
Even though we've only known each other for a few hours.
But I know you'll get through it.
What are you doing?
You'll see.
I've finally become someone interesting to you.
And tonight, neither of us has to be alone anymore.
Lyla.
I think I should head home.
Wait! Already?
What's wrong with you?
You kissed me.
And now you're leaving?
I have some work tomorrow.
Goodbye.
Hey! Wait!
Hey!
Are you really leaving me here?
Industry insiders all know.
This is the first step for anyone who wants to become Petra's partner.
Whoever secures the highlight piece at the auction.
Will undoubtedly capture the attention of Petra's CEO.
Miss Key!
Pardon?
Are you feeling alright?
Or did you celebrate a little too hard with Ai last night?
No. I'm fine.
I was just going through what you've said.
So, that means our only real competitor is W Empire.
But their credibility is significantly stronger than ours.
Then, if we win the highlight item,
We'll gain leverage when pitching the project, isn't?
Yes indeed.
Boss, someone is here asking to see you.
Who? I didn't schedule any appointments today.
It's the pianist from the jazz bar.
Turn her away. Tell her that I'm unavailable.
Yes, boss.
Who was it?
Just a stranger.
It's not important.
So, she's here, isn't she?
Yes madame.
That's alright.
I'll come back tomorrow.
Please let her know.
That people should take responsibility for what they've done.
What did she do?
She'll understand.
Hey!
Boss, she's here again. She's been coming back and forth for days now.
It's fine. She'll stop eventually once she gets tired.
"This chance may never come again don't let it slip away."
Boss, perhaps you should go see her?
How did you know I was here?
Your keychain on your camera bag.
You claim to be just a photographer.
But in reality, you own a racing circuit.
So?
I'm not obligated to tell you everything.
Especially not to someone I've only known for one night.
And what of it? We've met just one night
Does that mean you don't have to take responsibility for what you did?
Responsible for what?
You were the one who said you wanted a special night.
A “special night”?
You kissed me and left me alone in the park.
That might just be the worst memory I have.
So what is it that you want?
I want to know you better.
You wouldn't be able to handle someone like me.
Do you even know me well enough to say that?
What makes you think I can't handle you?
Are you sure about that?
Then don't cry.
So how are you holding up?
This? Easy.
Is it at least a little challenging?
A little.
Are those tears?
Nonesense.
You've gone pale.
You're about to faint, and you're still acting tough.
Want some inhaler?
No need.
I told you I'm not easily afraid.
Do you believe me now?
Are you really okay?
Let me ask you something honestly.
That night.
Did you actually feel nothing for me?
Because if you don't.
I won't bother you again.
Just don't lie.
Maybe… a little.
That's why I ran away.
Ran away for what then?
Why not give yourself a chance to be happy?
Don't you want to share the loneliness with me anymore?
Am I good now?
I can ride in your race car without throwing up.
You're the best.
But if you're not feeling well, you don't have to push yourself.
I know.
I just want to step into your world a little more.
It takes a lot for you to let someone in.
Thank you for trying.
But I like you more just the way you are.
Bright and a little mischievous.
The kind of person who tricked me into a date on the very first night.
Well, when I like someone.
I must have a plan.
But my world isn't meant to be entered.
It's far darker than you'd expect
My world isn't as simple as you might think.
It only started to feel better when I met you
You're my first girlfriend, you know that right?
Girlfriend? Already?
It's only been three months.
Why not?
Time doesn't matter as much as feelings do.
Are we doing this or not?
Should we?
You still need to ask?
I endured all that dizziness riding with you.
If we're not dating after this, I'm going to lose it.
Oh really?
I'm dead serious.
Then we're official.
But you have to promise me first.
That you'll stay like this in my arms forever.
Hold me tight, for as long as you want.
I promise, I won't throw a tantrum again.
Such a hot temper girl.
You've been like that since day one.
For the past three months
You've grown quite close relationship to that woman, haven't you?
Someone special?
It's nothing, Uncle Mek.
Just a friend.
The auction is approaching.
I don't want you to be distracted
Because...
We've come too far to turn back now.
Don't worry.
I've been waiting for this moment for my entire life.
And nothing will be able to stop me.
I certainly hope so.
I won't disturb you any further.
You're lucky of having me as your daughter
If not, your home would not be this clean
Dad.
I think I found who makes me smile
But don't be upset dad, you will always come first in my heart.
She can take second or maybe one and a half
I'll have to excuse myself
We need to talk.
Mom, what do you want from me.
Isn't sending money all you've ever done?
How many time does I need to tell you
Is to protect you
Have you ever asked me once.
That this is the type of protection I need?
Lalin.
I understand.
Why you're upset.
But eveything that I've done.
Is to make sure we're safe.
If something horrible happens to you.
And ends up like your father.
Then how does I supposed to live.
In mother's line of business, it's all enemies, no allies.
It's nothing but people lurking, ready to strike at any moment.
You were young.
I was new also.
Staying with me is too risky.
You always have excuses.
All you care is your business.
To you, I'm just something that gets in the ways.
You never been a burden.
You are, and always will be, the most valuable part in my life.
Lalin.
I think it's time that we can comeback and be like other families.
I'm certain.
That nobody can hurt us anymore.
You've glown too.
Come home.
You don't need to pretend to be Lyla anymore, Lalin.
I'll give you anything you want.
Please forgive me.
Today's auction highlight is the Moonriver necklace.
It's the necklace that Mrs. Petra Lee, the founder of Petra corporation.
Has specially ordered for her daughter before being purposed to become the CEO.
Unfortunately, she passed away by an accident.
What is our budget for today's auction.
20 millions.
Then push the limits.
Show them that we're not afraid.
Excuse me.
Hello, Ms. Weiling.
Hello, Mr. Kevin.
Thailand's number one real estate magnate.
Thank you for honoring us with your presence.
Oh please, I'm just a businesswoman.
I have no intention of competing with anyone.
No need to worry.
You remain to be our first choice.
Thank you for your trust.
Still, we should arrange a private meeting.
Of course.
Hello, Ms. Alisa.
Hello.
Thank you for attending my auction.
The honor is mine. This is quite a grand event.
Ms. Weiling, have you met.
Ms. Alisa, the owner of AList.
The rising developer everyone's been talking about.
A pleasure to meet you.
Likewise, Ms. Weiling.
You've been such an inspiration to me.
Thank you.
Mr. Kevin, the auction is about to begin.
Alright. I have to excuse to prepare for the auction.
Let's find some time to talk later.
I heard AList hasn't been around for long.
Yet you've already secured multiple projects in Lan Arun.
Quite impressive just like the rumors say.
Well...
Clients are simply looking for something new.
And AList delivers what they can't find elsewhere.
That's why they trust us.
That's the nature of something new.
But whether it lasts or not. We'll have to see.
In the end, the market will decide.
Where each of us truly belongs.
Because if you overreach.
You may lose everything.
I've seen many fall that way.
Are you okay?
Let me do the job.
You better rest.
Leave it to me.
I'm sorry.
Hey you.
Sorry?
When you're not drunk.
You looks different.
Excuse me.
Do we know eachother?
You get on the wrong car. I'm not a taxi driver.
You are...
I need to get this close in order to reminds you who I am?
By the way...
What are you doing here?
Giving ride to whom.
Why do you have a camera with you today?
I'm a news reporter
Not a driver.
And who are you?
Is your name Ramyong?
Are you going to be drunk again tonight?
What Ramyong?
My name is Ai.
But whatever your name is.
When you're drunk, take care of yourself.
Don't be other people burden.
You got it?
Welcome to Petra Corporation's charity auction.
First thing first, I need to thanks all of you for attending today's auction.
However.
Tonight is not merely an auction.
But a presentation of priceless family heirlooms.
Which every piece belongs to my family.
Each piece carries a story.
Especially the love of a mother for her children.
And tonight, I hope these treasures.
Will find owners who truly appreciate their value.
And are willing to carry those stories forward.
Let the auction begin.
We going to start off with the first piece.
Which is this painting.
Let's begin.
2 millions.
2 million.
2.5 millions.
5 millions.
10 millions.
Anyone wants to bid any higher?
For this wonderful painting.
10 millions going once.
10 millions going twice.
And 10 millions. Sold.
Congratulations!
Up next.
Let go of me!
The pleasure of revenge.
Is not to see your enemy die
It's about watching tham suffer while they're still alive
Let go of me!
For this piece of land, 15 millions going once.
15 millions going twice.
And 15 millions. Sold.
And the final piece of tonight.
The Moon River necklace.
The one of one piece.
Commissioned by Mrs. Petra
For her daughter who passed away.
It is a symbol of a mother's love
Beyond any price.
This necklace is a symbol.
Of hope, love and sacrifice.
And this is the first time that this necklace will be up to auction.
Starting biding at 5 million baht.
Are you ready?
Yes madame.
6 millions
6 millions.
7 millions
7 millions baht from W Empire
8 millions
10 millions
12 millions.
18 millions
18 millions from W Empire.
Anyone willing to give any higher?
20 millions.
25 millions.
Anybody willing to give more than 25 millions?
25 millions going once.
25 millions going twice.
And 25 millions goin-
30 millions.
We cannot go higher than this.
30 millions going once.
30 millions going twice.
And 30 millions. Sold.
The Moon River necklace goes to Ms. Alisa of AList.
Moon River is not merely jewelry.
It holds deep meaning for us.
And the fact that you've won it.
Has made me begin to see AList's true potential.
AList is always ready.
I hope we'll have the opportunity to work together soon.
Anytime.
Some of you may have heard that I have a daughter.
Though no one has ever seen her.
This is Lalin, my only daughter.
When I heard the story of Moon River.
I couldn't help but think of my own.
A mother waiting for the day her child returns.
I understand that feeling of separation all too well.
Moon River was never meant for just anyone.
It represents a mother's love
Who would do anything for her child.
To give them a place to return to.
On the day they choose to come home.
Only a mother could truly understand this feeling, Mrs. Petra.