=No Doubt In Us=
(Adapted from the Manman comic No Doubt in Us)
=Episode 5=
(Star-Gazing Pavilion)
So, our bodies swapped
because Dada's witchcraft
was used on us?
You never know what will happen.
According to this ancient book,
this witchcraft is used
only to kill people involved.
Rarely does it go awry.
But your yin-yang reversal
caused the swap.
Pity we only found the first volume.
It only records
how to cast this witchcraft.
To lift it, we need to find
the second volume.
Don't tell me we have to go to Dada.
I have a way to search for it.
But before that,
both of you have to endure this
for a while longer.
Who is the caster's target, me or you?
We have to do something.
As long as we pretend to be fine,
the caster will think
their scheme remains hidden.
Once we find the second volume,
I'll slowly reel the caster in.
With the war ongoing,
we can't afford more chaos.
You're so thoughtful.
I'm eager to see
what tricks they'll pull.
Are you talking about me?
What did I miss? Looks like a nice chat.
Why not share it with me?
We were talking about an ancient book.
You want it?
Well, if you want it,
as your adorable brother,
I'll personally get it for you.
But my power alone is limited.
Can I look for it outside
with the Grand Preceptor?
I think you want
to corrupt the Grand Preceptor.
Jinyun.
Please, Jinyun.
Allow me to tell a fortune
for Your Highness.
On wealth?
On romance.
No.
I have my brother, my mother, and money.
That's all I want.
Our plan failed.
Who'd have thought
that an uneducated Empress
would see through our scheme?
The Empress is a remarkable woman.
I'd be disappointed if she hadn't.
Sadly, you lost a key pawn for nothing.
Isn't that a pity?
If not for our grand plan,
why would I
make a distant relative my niece?
Who knew the fool would use an heir
to replace the current Empress?
Utterly useless.
Don't worry.
As long as we're players in this game,
I can revive even the dead.
Let me see.
How could you be so careless?
You kept staring at me!
How could I concentrate?
If you weren't looking at me,
how'd you know I was watching?
You...
Report!
Your Majesty,
General Xu Jun returned gravely wounded!
Like my father, he never leaves
the battle for minor wounds.
As he returned,
he must be critically injured.
I'm going to see him!
Xu Yu, you can't.
As the Emperor, it's inappropriate.
I'll go instead.
But...
Xu Jun is also my brother by right.
You're injured. Skip the formalities.
That's inappropriate.
Greetings, Your Grace.
How were you so badly wounded?
No worries.
I'm quite fine.
Is the northern front stable?
Why did I get no messages
from you for so long?
A subject must hold his tongue.
Contacting the harem is overstepping.
Don't worry.
I'm glad to fight alongside Father.
But you're alone in the harem.
You're suffering a lot, aren't you?
Duo.
Xu Duo!
Why won't you call me Duo?
Duo.
Come! You rarely came back. Let me see
if you've neglected your training.
Duo.
I've been unwell lately.
Yu, what's wrong with you?
Are you alright? What's wrong?
I'm pregnant.
So, I'm going to be an uncle!
If it's a boy,
I'll teach him martial arts.
I'll make him the world's best!
If it is a boy,
he will be the imperial heir,
destined to be Crown Prince!
No need for you to teach.
It is very necessary.
His Majesty doesn't know martial arts.
That's why military power gets divided
among those old men.
Duo.
That's such a hurtful thing to say.
Yu.
Jun.
I'm often away leading troops,
but I'm not foolish.
Your pregnancy should be joyous.
But the harem is even more dangerous
than the battlefield.
Moreover, His Majesty doesn't favor you.
From now on, act with extreme caution.
Don't bring trouble upon yourself.
(Is it well known
that I don't favor Xu Yu?)
As long as you're discreet, modest,
and don't oppose His Majesty,
you and your child, even if unfavored,
will be protected
by our family for life.
I've heard that the Marquis of Zhenbei
is acting suspiciously.
He may attempt to harm His Majesty
during the autumn hunt.
When you return to the palace,
warn His Majesty
to stay vigilant
and not to fall into his trap.
Duo, aren't you worried about me?
Their target is His Majesty.
Besides, as subjects,
we're loyal to our sovereign.
Father taught us that.
(Knowing I don't favor Xu Yu,
they remain loyal to the sovereign.)
Xiao Jinyun is too weak.
He needs to exercise more.
Your Majesty.
Who are you calling weak?
How is my big brother?
He's fine.
Did you ask about my father and Duo?
They're well too.
They're just worried
about you suffering here.
Don't worry. You've been good lately.
Your Majesty, what happened to your arm?
It's nothing. Duo just patted me.
And then he shook me
until my head nearly came off.
He even wanted to spar.
Didn't you give yourself away?
I was clever enough
to claim you're pregnant.
Naturally, he couldn't force me
to spar again.
Pregnant?
Your Majesty, how could you say that?
If they believe it,
where will I get a child?
Then let's actually have one.
Your Majesty.
Soft armor?
This is great protective gear.
Jun gave this to you?
Actually, your father let Jun
give it to you.
They all care about you.
I also miss my father.
By the way,
Duo mentioned something else.
The autumn hunt is coming up.
Autumn hunt?
So I can ride horses?
Sure. Since you're using my body now,
you can hunt freely and enjoy yourself.
No, wait.
You are too weak.
To avoid embarrassing myself,
I have to practice riding and archery.
Someone! Prepare my horse.
Who are you calling weak? You...
So heavy.
(Hunting Ground)
It's time.
Your Majesty,
please commence the autumn hunt.
Since it's an autumn hunt,
we should pursue live prey.
It's the same as the archery targets
on the training field, isn't it?
Your Majesty, your safety matters.
You can't be too careful.
Release it.
Yes.
We've never heard of Your Majesty
practicing riding or archery.
What if...
What? You doubt me?
I wouldn't dare.
Prince Ning can't come due to illness.
He privately instructed me
to protect Your Majesty.
Please think twice, Your Majesty.
My decision is final. No more words.
- May Your Majesty have swift victory.
Giddy up!
♪Parting clouds to get the waxing moon♪
♪Brewing a pot of bygone years♪
♪Chill flame, window shade,
console my grieving soul♪
♪Drunk through lifetimes
with no dreams returned♪
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
♪Returning to drift
through the mortal world♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪