- You poisoned us!
- You're right!
I placed the ice!
I did that because she warned me
that Madam Violet will harm you!
That was the only way to save her
without drawing suspicion
from Madam Violet.
How do I know if I could trust you?
Yes.
I know I was a bitch to you sometimes.
Sometimes?
But I also want to get
out of this hellhole.
I don't eat spinach.
Just try it.
One bite.
Ace...
Huh?
Are you okay?
Supremo
are you okay?
Thank you for the lunch.
Zein.
Are you...
allergic to spinach?
Stupid!
You put Supremo in danger!
You're such an idiot!
Stupid!
What should we do to her?
Tie her up and punish her!
Right!
Tie her up!
Zein!
I promise you.
They will pay for what they did.
Black Blood Gang and Devil God Warrior.
Memorize these faces!
Next week
they’ll be your target.
Happy hunting!
Help!
Help us!
Are they afraid of me?
Are they angry?
Are they disgusted by me?
Do I really deserve this treatment?
Please.
Nurse Cha, please.
Something's wrong with Supremo.
Stupid!
You were so careless!
Why don't you try thinking for once?
Zein!
More!
Goodbye, Zein Shion.
Zein!
What do you think you're doing?
Untie her!
All of you
take my command.
Nobody leaves this hall.
This is an order
from the highest
Supreme Student Government President.
Understood?
Didn't I say move?
Don't ever cross their boundary.
I said move and get out of my sight.
We can't do anything!
They're all heartless!
Animals!
You're just like them!
You're a monster!
You believe me, right?
Do you?
Do you believe in me, right?
I didn't want to do it.
Are you going to help us or not?
Go on.
Try me.
Angelica!
Stop it!
Enough!
They will never forgive me.
I understand if they won't.
What happened to you was my fault.
- No amount of apology can change that...
- Zein.
What are you talking about?
The students...
they're avoiding me.
I think that’s just their way
of showing respect to the Queen.
A lot has changed when
you were unconscious.
The campus security has doubled
and all who were involved in hurting you
are being punished.
Supremo
what's their punishment?
I think it's better if you don't know.
I think it's too much.
Another thing
Roxane isn't the queen of HU anymore.
It's you now, Zein.
Huh?
How?
I have to do it to them
to give you more respect.
Now they won't be able
to touch you so easily.
Another thing.
Matthew Hart
is the new king.
You seem happy, huh?
I'll be back.
I need to see Matt.
- I haven't...
- You're not leaving me.
Understood?
I'm the Queen.
And you know that
I don’t give a damn.
Why do you keep focusing on Matt?
Duh.
Of course he's my friend.
And I had a crush on him first.
But I'm the one you love.
Are you sure?
Why, Zein?
Am I wrong?
- Help me!
- Angelica?
Angelica...
Help...
Nicky!
I can't disobey my own decree.
Stand!
Don't worry.
I told them not to put poison on the nail.
Please!
Have mercy on her!
Please, Supremo! Please help her.
Please.
You'll live.
Supremo, please.
Why are you being like this?
Help her!
Wait for me.
Stand up.
Come on!
This is too much, Ace.
Have you heard of Supremo's punishment
to the ones who hurt you?
I have.
How do you feel about that?
I honestly don't know
how I should feel about it.
Stock room.
Third cabinet.
Faculty.
Load sheets.
That's why they're all afraid of me.
Because of Supremo's punishment.
I hope he won't be harmed because of this.
Are you happy now?
From being a newbie
to becoming his secretary.
And now you're fourth in the ranks.
Now, you're the queen?
Aren't you too greedy?
You have everything!
And you still want Supremo?
Can’t you see?
While you're beside him
he gets weaker.
You're making him weaker!
You're a burden to him!
I know!
Do you think that makes me happy, huh?
If Supremo is having a hard time
I have a hard time too.
But everything is your fault!
If you didn't push your way into his life
you wouldn't be having a hard time now.
Both of you wouldn't be
having a hard time right now.
Do you think I chose to fall for him?
Do you really think that?
It was all an accident!
You won't get out of here even if you die!
Angelica...
- Angelica!
- Do you really think
I would give up after
getting punished?
I don't care how many nails
are stabbed through my body.
- Or how many cuts I get.
- Angelica!
Why are you doing this!?
I'll endure everything to protect Supremo.
Do you think I wanted that to happen?
If you really love him
stop hurting him.
Do you think I wanted to hurt him?
Angelica?
Angelica!
Please!
Angelica, open the door!
Please
Angelica!
Angelica, please!
I'm not afraid of the dark.
I prefer the dark more than daylight.
In the dark, I can mask everything.
I can cry,
I can be weak.
But in daylight, I'm forced to be strong.
I need to face reality.
You're ruining everything!
What did I ever do to you?
You didn't do anything
and you won't do anything
besides leaving Supremo alone.
You know the rules, Supremo.
You should have just punished her!
Ms. Kath is right.
You'll lose your authority.
I can live without this position.
What is really your relationship
with Ms. Shion, Supremo?
She's my secretary.
I need to protect her.
And that's understandable.
But your position is on the line here!
We’re just concerned, Supremo.
We don't want you to get hurt.
I don't care.
I don't want to lose her.
I need her.
I know that you're aware
of the consequences
of you helping them, Supremo.
I will give them the exemption.
You tell them that they can breathe
for now.
Lux started out this way.
I am nothing like him.
I need to choose when I get out of here.
I can't remain in the middle of this.
I need to choose a side and live with that.
Zein?
Zein!
Are you okay?
Who did this to you?
Zein?
It's okay. You can answer later.
Let's get you to the clinic.
Zein?
Zein...
I
Ace Craige
will be your shield
your bulletproof vest
and your knight.
I can't fight anymore, Ace.
You don't have to.
I will fight for you.
Always remember
I'll always be here for you.
I promise.
I will never abandon you.
What is it?
What do you mean?
Really?
You really don't know?
Mia is she serious?
Too bad.
What a waste.
Are you sure you don't know, Zein?
Stop it.
I don't know what you're on about.
We won't tell you.
She really doesn't know.
Come on, guys.
Please
I have to get some things from my locker.
Oh, okay.
See you around.
See you.
Someone's blushing.
Guys, stop it.
So what were you talking about?
Someone's blushing.
What is it?
You're annoying.
Vanessa!
Zein, look.
Supremo's there.
There you are Dave and Jerome.
I'm glad you're both here.
Can you tell these two off.
They're keeping secrets from me.
Oh, you don't know?
What is it?
She says she doesn't know, Jerome.
Look at me, Zein.
“You really don't know?”
You know
you're all the same.
- So annoying.
- Look at her.
Someone's mad.
Roxane is a target too, right?
Have you seen her?
She's dead when I see her.
Isn't that her?
Hoy.
You are not helping.
What's with today?
So you're keeping secrets from me too?
I hate you.
Find a new owner.
Sorry. I need space.
Let me be on my own for a bit.
You know.
I really don't want to
think of you like this
but are you turning insane?
I want to be alone, Supremo.
You want me to leave you?
Yes, please.
No.
Why do you look so annoyed?
Can you give me space please?
I don't want you to be collateral damage.
Do you want to get punched?
Can you do it?
Feel better?
What was that?
That was my
hug capsule.
Hug cap what?
Let's just say
a Supremo's hug is the most
effective medicine ever.
It can ease any kind of pain.
So if you ever need more
just run to me.
Always.
Okay?
Can I have one more then?
You're at risk for overdose.
That's okay.
It can cause addiction.
That's okay too.
I don't think you can handle it.
What's your plan for Sunday, Supremo?
Ms. Shion?
Do you have plans for Supremo?
Supremo.
If you want anything specific done
on Sunday, let us know.
We will give you anything you want.
Really?
Anything I want?
Well
what if I want you guys
to leave me alone?
Supremo.
I knew it.
You guys can't give me the
thing I want the most.
Stop playing around.
Don't be complacent, President Ace.
You should be grateful that
you still have your position.
Thank you, then.
If the other found out that
you saved Secretary Shion
from her punishment.
The ones you've punished
will rally against you.
You are being unfair.
Could you please stop
talking about this topic?
Ms. Shion is right here.
It's better she's aware of the
inconveniences you have now because of her.
Oh fuck.
Don’t listen, please.
This is not a joke!
I just want Secretary Shion to be aware!
This is for the both you!
What can I do to save Supremo?
Limit yourself.
Supremo is forbidden to have
relationships with anyone.
The President must not show
any sign of weakness.
Stay aware from Supremo.
Ms. Shion is not going anywhere.
And I don't care what
will happen to me.
So Zein should have been
punished long ago?
She was saved by Supremo.
That’s just so unfair!
Roxane...
What will the public's reaction be
if they knew about Supremo's favoritism?
And what are you
doing here, Ms. Allister?
Don’t you dare mess
with the SSG Officers.
Oh, I dare.
I fucking dare.
Both of you.
Supremo.
Do you have a relationship
with Secretary Shion?
Yes.
Wow.
The president and the secretary?
What a plot twist.
Not surprised
knowing you, Zein Shion.
You’re a bitch!
Call her a bitch one more time!
Do you know the reason why
the former Supremo vanished?
The same reason why
Ace Craige will be deposed.
What now?
Are you ready for the backlash
once I tell the whole university
about your secret?
Zein...
Please.
Don't do this.
Stand up.
Please.
I'm begging you.
Please don't do it.
Too late, Queen Zein.
And you
you will lose everything.
This is all your fault!
Come on, let's go.
Don't you dare leave me.
But it's the only way
to save you from this.
I can live without this position
but I can't live without you.
Yes, you can!
You've lived for so long without me
and you'll be able to do it again!
Yes, I was alive but I wasn't living.
Don't you understand?
For the longest time I’ve been here.
I never felt alive.
It’s like.
It's like when I met you.
I felt human again.
Because of you I felt alive again.
Like I finally learned how to breathe.
We need to set each other free.
It’s for the best.
Fuck that, Zein.
You're all I have.
Please don't take this away from me.
I need you more than what I have.
You deserve what you earned.
I don't want to be the reason
you lose everything.
Darling, don't do this.
Officail Main Site [www.kisskh.xyz]
Please?
It would be your gift to me.
My birthday is coming.
You have my heart.
Please don't leave me.
I love you more than myself
and everything that I have.
So please...
don't leave me hanging, darling.
Supremo, stop it.
♪ Will a kiss ♪
♪ grant me your affection? ♪
♪ Do you know ♪
♪ the nights beside you
still linger in my mind. ♪
♪ My only wish ♪
♪ please grant it even only in my dreams. ♪
♪ I’ll take this as a chance. ♪
♪ To give you all the time that you need. ♪
♪ Darling ♪
♪ how beautiful it is to love you. ♪
♪ I will wait for your return. ♪
♪ I’ll always be here. ♪
♪ Darling ♪
♪ how beautiful it is to love you. ♪
♪ I’ll always be here for you. ♪
Darling, I want to scream.
Don't.
I really hope you stop me
because I don’t think I
can hold it back anymore.
I want to tell everyone
how I feel about you.
Darling.
I love you
more than myself
and everything that I have.
Never ever leave me, darling.
What a scene.
Can we stop with the theatrics?
Glad to see you're still alive.
Oh well, Supremo.
You just made the biggest
mistake of your life.
You should've killed me.
That's the symbol of-
I'm going to count to three.
One...
Two...
Darling.
Let's eat?
What do you want to eat?
I'm late for class.
So tomorrow, then?
What happens tomorrow?
Oh come on, Zein.
You can't fool me.
Okay, fine.
But I don't have a gift prepared.
I want you.
And only you.
I'm already late for class.
I am dead serious.
Nothing matters if you're not beside me.
Zein...
Darling?
I want everyone to see us dancing together.
It's one of my biggest dreams.
Come on
make that dream come true for me.
Tomorrow.
You left it earlier.
Thank you, Zein.
You're not going to the party.
Who's going to stop me?
We will.
Hold her tight.
- Let me go!
- Stop squirming!
What will you do to her?
That's our business.
I can lend you our headquarters.
Stop moving!
I'm worried about her
staying with your members.
Sometimes
- they lack finesse.
- Make her shut up.
Huh? Excuse me?
Aren't you the one who set
her free during Bloody Night?
Shut up.
It's just a suggestion.
We don't need your opinion.
We can handle her.
Unless
you have a different agenda?
Relax.
Fine.
You said you can handle it.
What's his problem?
That's nothing.
Don't mind him.
Why are you doing this?
For his sake.
Love has no place in this hell.
Love is just a poison.
Fuck!
Poison?
Fuck.
Just shup up, okay?
Poison?
If love really is poison...
when will the both of you die?
Well, sad to say
this isn't love, my dear.
Hold her.
Let's go, Nicky.
We need to hide before anyone sees.
I know. Stop telling me what to do.
Hold her properly.
I'm already holding her.
Tighter!
Fucking poison.
I'm doing it.
Do you think i'm fucking stupid?
Can't you just help me?
Don't hurt her!
Matt!
- Matt!
- We won't hurt her if she cooperates.
- We'll keep her safe and hidden.
Help me.
Unless you have a better plan?
Matt!
Aren't you going to help me?
I won't.
You won't be able to
attend Supremo's birthday.
You'll ruin his dream.
You'll hurt the person
who loves you the most.
He'll wait for nothing.
I got this.
Do you know why I called you here?
Because I can always rely on you.
You're not like the others.
We can see your worth.
I need you to do one last thing.
There's a war coming.
And no one must know about it.
Devil God Warrior and Black Blood Gang
will remain blind about this.
And you're going to
make sure of this.
Can we rely on you?
Don't you want to
get out of this place?
To see your parents again?
To be with them again?
I'm the only one who
can give that to you.
has the power.
You chose the right guy, Madam Violet.
Good boy.
He's waiting for me.
It's better for both of you
if you don't go to the party.
Why are all of you
against our relationship?
Supremo is planning to reveal everything.
He's going to scream out loud
how much he loves you.
If they're pushing through with it
I'll handle Supremo.
You know the rules.
The SSG President is not supposed
to get involved with anyone.
Having feelings for someone
won't do you any good in this place.
It'll just be your weakness.
You'll find the one for you.
Why? Is there another Zein Shion?
If you walk ten steps away from me
just forget everything
that happened between us.
Loving each other
was enough.