[Fenglinwan]
[Two years ago]
Who do you think you are?
You're not drinking the toast I propose?
Zhao,
I'll drink with you.
Rong had antibiotics today.
Here.
What?
Scared you?
Come on, drink.
Drink.
Let's drink.
You two drink it all up.
Okay.
Who do you think you are?
Have you forgotten how,
in order to get the project,
you gave your girlfriend
to me?
We can be considered relatives.
Zhao,
what are you doing?
Let's talk outside.
Let's go.
Calm down.
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 23]
Bro.
Do you know what I'm here for?
What are you here for?
To get money.
Who is your boss?
It's you, Rong.
You're quite stubborn.
If my boss is not you,
who else could it be?
Who ordered you to do this?
Who do you think?
I'm asking you!
Rong,
I didn't dare to touch any of your money.
It's...
Louder!
Mr. Zhou!
Catch him!
Don't move.
You too.
Hurry up.
Hello, Chief Zhang.
When will you arrive?
Almost there.
Come on. Push harder. Come on!
Hurry!
Push harder!
Who drove?
Young man.
We meet again.
If you dare to shoot, I'll kill him.
Young man,
what do you want?
Let my bro go.
Give me
the 1.5 million in your house
and I'll return you your phone.
Otherwise...
Scared now?
Chief.
Was that a gunshot?
Where is my phone?
Rong.
I'll go tend my wound.
Rong, the...
Police!
Put the gun down!
Back off!
Put the gun down.
You put it down.
Put it down.
Put it down!
Put it down, please.
Put it down.
Stop pretending.
Everyone,
your boss is here.
The mastermind behind the whole conspiracy—
what are you looking at? It's you.
Whose boss is he?
My boss.
Our boss.
How did you know?
When Lu Zheng died,
you were at Sanjiangkou, right?
You must've heard something.
You came here
on an irregular transfer.
You kept a
close eye on me
since you arrived here.
I told you the report letter was fake;
why are you still after me?
Did I offend you?
I smashed
this phone myself!
Why did it suddenly appear?
Who has such technical support?
Putting an undercover
like him by my side—
who could be so good at scheming?
You had him and Ms. Li
create a fake car accident.
Who can get the support
of the traffic police like this?
You had him introduce Ms. Li to me.
Yet she had to appear
on the day I was making my deals.
Rong.
If she hadn't covered them,
these two idiots
wouldn't have stolen from me.
With just the two of us.
We can steal from you.
Your triad
has reunited here
now.
Shouldn't you, the mastermind,
appear now too?
Well...
Your analysis is good.
Stop.
If my guess is right,
Zhu Yifei
is someone on your side too, right?
Well...
How did you
find out about that?
We are not under him.
Yes, yes, we are!
Shut up!
Chief Zhang,
let me ask you a few questions.
Explain it properly
and we can talk about the rest.
Sure.
Go ahead.
What's with
the phone?
♪ Doubt ♪
It's easy for the police
to find a phone.
What about the video inside?
That's nothing difficult
♪ Doubt ♪
for the police,
right?
You had me deal with Zhu Yifei,
but called it off suddenly—why?
♪ Doubt, doubt the doubt ♪
You know why yourself!
Say it!
You did it for the East New Town?
East New Town, yes.
Fang Yong said
he wanted to give it to someone else—
he was referring to you, right?
Fang Yong?
Yes!
I've been building an empire here
for half my life
and here you are, ruining it
just a few days after arriving!
Zhang Yi'ang, I...
♪ He is ♪
Mr. Zhou, aim properly!
♪ Too cunning but like a joke ♪
Mr. Zhou!
I can only repay your teachings
with my death!
♪ Ha ha ha ♪
♪ He ♪
Li Qian!
I...
Chief!
I didn't...
Sit down.
I'll be fine
after laying down for a while.
I'll be fine.
Chief.
Call an ambulance.
It's...
quite cold.
Chief.
Chief?
Hang in there.
We're almost at the hospital.
Don't sleep.
Chief, don't sleep.
[Human Organs]
Don't sleep!
[Lung] [Heart] [Stomach]
[Pancreas] [Kidney] [Appendicitis]
Don't sleep!
Captain Wang.
Where Chief Zhang's shot—
that's a dangerous spot.
Screw off.
Chief Zhang.
Is there anyone
we need to notify in your family?
No.
It's not that serious.
It's just a reflected bullet.
Wang,
you're making me nervous.
You lot...
Is there enough time?
Enough time for a meeting.
I'm afraid it's not.
Doctor,
please think of a way, okay?
I don't think I'll die yet.
Who told you you're going to die?
Don't hide it from him now.
He was shot
at where his vital organs are.
Who told you that?
You did.
You said he wouldn't have time
for a meeting—
what does that mean?
We're dating.
We had plans for our parents to meet
this afternoon.
But now that we're out on an emergency,
we will be delayed.
A life is at stake here,
okay?
You are doctors.
You have to be careful with your words.
The patient's condition is very stable.
Yes.
Ar-Ae you sure?
Are you the doctor or am I the doctor?
Once he gets the bullet out of him
when he arrives at the hospital,
we can get down from the bed in 1 day
and be discharged in 3 days.
You two,
if you keep scaring him, get off.
You...
Captain Wang.
Thank you.
Sorry about that.
It's okay.
Put your phone away.
Okay.
You're fine. Don't worry.
[Ambulance]
[Emergency]
Come, give me a hand. Be careful.
Wait.
Stop, stop.
What happened?
We didn't catch Huo Zheng.
He has been with Zhu Yifei for many years
and their relationship runs deep.
I'm afraid he'll take revenge on you.
I've increased
the security of the hospital.
Revenge?
Zhu Yifei fell off
the cliff himself.
I didn't push him.
Revenge...
Take the people away.
Go find Huo Zheng.
Are you two done talking?
What if?
What if what?
I'm a police.
I'm not afraid of him.
Let him come.
Even on the surgical bed,
I can handle him with one hand.
-All right, all right.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
Listen to me.
Slowly.
Lift it up.
Slowly!
Be careful!
Slowly.
Go find Huo Zheng.
Yes!
Team 1 and Team 2, get in!
[Emergency]
The police arrested someone.
That cultural dealer
drove off the cliff and died.
I heard the leader
was Chief Zhang from the Municipal Bureau.
Uncle.
I will get your revenge.
What's going on?
Raise your arms.
Turn around.
Go.
Next.
Here.
Turn around. Next.
Here. Go.
Open your bag.
Next.
Go.
Hey.
Why are you cutting the queue?
Exactly.
Raise your arms.
Okay. Next.
Hurry up.
Raise your arms.
I've been
coughing for a week.
Turn around.
Is it pneumonia?
Go see the doctor quickly.
Next.
Raise your arms.
Whose bag is this?
Mine.
What's wrong?
What happened?
What about this knife?
That's not mine.
I didn't put this in.
Tell the truth.
Hey.
Look at the state I'm in.
Why should I carry a knife?
I'm calling the police.
Don't, I have an exam this afternoon.
Take him away.
Hey!
What are you doing?
I really have an exam this afternoon.
I'll be late!
[4th floor]
[Surgery Room]
Don't be nervous.
I'm not nervous.
Starting now, count to 10.
When?
Now.
One....
That's fast.
That was a normal dosage.
Okay.
Where's this from?
Someone tried to bring
a knife in at the security check.
They stopped him.
Huo Zheng?
No.
Someone's trying to cause trouble?
He insisted the knife wasn't his.
If not his,
did someone put it in his bag?
Could it be
Huo Zheng has sneaked in
and is trying to distract us?
Li Qian.
You two stay here.
Okay.
Get the SWAT back.
Yes.
The rest of you, follow me.
No matter what it is,
don't let your guard down.
Hurry!
[Infusion Room]
Check over there.
Follow me.
Okay.
[Please keep quiet]
You go this way.
Okay.
[Please keep quiet] [Infusion Room]
Hou Shengjie's skin test result is out.
I'll be right there.
[Infusion Room]
Hou Shengjie, right?
You're not allergic to penicillin,
are you?
I am.
The test result shows
you're not allergic to penicillin.
Are you allergic or not?
No.
I'll verify again.
Hou Shengjie,
you're not not allergic to penicillin,
right?
Don't move.
Stop looking.
Go keep an eye on the surgery room.
Wait for the SWAT.
Done.
What?
The SWAT is here.
They're searching them one by one.
Don't make too much noise.
Don't scare the patients.
One, two, three.
[Surgery Room]
Doctor!
How is it?
The surgery went well.
[Entrance Access Card]
Don't worry.
Just treat it
as an ordinary appendicitis surgery.
But it's not a minor trauma.
So Chief Zhang's all right?
He's fine.
He'll come out
when the anesthesia wears off.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
It's fine now.
Well...
We still can't go in, it seems.
Two...
Captain Wang!
Captain Wang.
A doctor was knocked out in the toilet.
His surgical uniform was stolen.
Open the door!
How did you... get in?
What are you doing?
This is the surgery room.
Where is Zhang Yi'ang?
Tell me, where is he?
I...
will kill you...
to avenge... avenge...
Uncle Yifei.
You scoundrel.
Try it if you dare.
Don't try me.
♪ Throw a toy to
that bunch of brokers in town ♪
I...
will do it...
♪ There's a strange, hazy feeling ♪
♪ Waiting for me to make sense of it ♪
♪ Worshippers hiding in the smoke,
just beyond reach ♪
♪ They are all guests ♪
♪ Be patient and wait ♪
You...
You really dealt with him with one hand.
Comrade Fang Yong,
there are some things
we have to ask.
Please come with us.
Okay.
How is it?
Tell me.
Good news and bad news—
what do you want to hear first?
The phone has been cracked.
In one of
Lang Bowen's past phones,
there is a video Lang Bowen filmed
during Chief Lu's accident.
That video proved that
Lang Bowen is just a witness.
He can't be the murderer
who killed Chief Lu.
Is this the good news or bad news?
The bad news.
What about the good news?
The bad news is not over yet.
Tell me.
What were you going to do today?
Rong said he couldn't leave today.
He asked me to make a deal for him.
It was all arranged by Hu Jianren.
I don't know anything else.
What deal?
I don't know.
I'm Mr. Zhou's employee.
I went because he asked me to.
You didn't ask what for?
I ask Zhou Rong?
He wouldn't
have me do something illegal.
I didn't do something illegal either.
I don't know
why I was arrested.
You really don't know?
I don't.
I've always been
an upright person.
I will never accept your insult.
Watch your attitude.
Kill me!
Still refusing to speak?
I'm itchy.
I'm itching.
Just kill me—
I will feel better!
Did you give him allergy injection?
Yes.
But the doctor said
it would take at least half an hour.
Let me scratch!
Stop flailing around. You won't die.
Let me ask you.
What's going on
between Zhu Yifei, Zhou Rong, and you?
I want to see Zhang Yi'ang.
I'll only speak to him.
Answer whatever's asked!
This is not the place for you
to raise requests!
Tell me about the night
Ye Jian was killed.
I've told you everything.
I really don't know.
Lu Yibo.
Look at the situation you're in.
Still not talking?
If you don't believe me,
there's nothing I can do either.
What Xiaofei?
I don't know him.
Someone saw you together.
Do you have evidence?
You want evidence?
Half a year ago,
a car accident
at a Sanjiangkou intersection.
The victim is
Deputy Chief of
the Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau,
Lu Zheng.
Your phone
filmed
the whole accident.
You don't remember?
Three days after Chief Lu's accident,
Rong Cheng transferred 30 million yuan
project fee to Otto.
Slander.
This is a complete slander.
You can check my bank.
See how much money
I have on my account.
It's meaningless to waste time.
Answer the questions.
I want to see...
[Yi'ang.]
That's a long bad news.
What about the good news?
Luckily there's Fang Chao and Liu Zhi.
We were the perpetrators
of the provincial capital explosion case.
It wasn't us.
We also robbed the Land Rover.
We both don't know how to drive.
Why should we steal his car?
I subdued that dude
immediately.
Don't believe that bastard.
Nothing he says is true.
But, just one thing—
we didn't kill that dude
who drove the Land Rover.
My bro
has never lied in his life.
He did
choked to his own death.
The phone deal with Zhou Rong this time—
my brother lured him away
to have him get 20 million.
Then he changed it to 5 million.
At the end he charged
straight to his house
to get 15 million.
What a pity.
With your bro's IQ,
he can't make up such nosense.
You were the one
who came up with the ideas, right?
Officer.
Well...
Can I get a reduced sentence
for reporting a corrupt official?
That's Yu Yueran's calligraphy—
how much's that worth?
It's fake.
Is this fake too?
A Yuan Qinghua.
Tripod cauldron with Chih-dragon handles.
How much is it?
This painting too.
It's from when Qi Baishi was young.
How much would that be?
And the bed next door—
do you dare to sleep on it?
Fang Yong told Zhou Rong
to trade for the East New Town project
with bianzhong.
Good.
Very good.
It'll be easier with this statement.
Zhang,
why did get down...
I-I'm fine.
Hearing good news,
the wound doesn't hurt that much anymore.
Don't be too old fashioned.
Moving around more
is the best way to recover.
Look.
I'm walking.
Look at me.
Look...
Chief Zhang.
It's nothing.
It's okay.
Turn around.
Let's go another round.
That's enough.
I can do it!
Come.
Turn around.
Slowly.
Yi'ang.
-Who—
-Yi'ang!
Chief Qi.
Wh-Why
are you already walking?
Here, here.
I need to get used to it.
You're being ridiculous.
Seriously.
Lie down.
I'm fine. Seriously.
Move.
Lie down.
Here.
Be careful.
-I'm fine.
-Slowly.
Slowly.
Be careful.
See.
-It's okay. Come on.
-Here.
Okay.
He wouldn't listen to me.
See?
Sit, Chief Qi. Sit.
Sit, Captain Wang. Sit.
Take it easy.
How was the interrogation?
How did it go?
Not good.
Not good.?
The others went fine,
but Zhou Rong—
every time we asked him something,
he asked to see you.
Zhou Rong still thinks
you were trying try harm him.
This should be
why he wants to see you.
I do want to see him.
Let's go!
Where are you going?
I'm fine!
Chief Qi said
I can be discharged.
Right, Chief Qi?
Take me to the 4th floor first.
♪ Doubt ♪
Hu Jianren
was sentenced to a year
for assault.
Zhou Rong went to Chief Lu
♪ Doubt ♪
to help ease this situation.
But Chief Lu insists on his principles.
We suspect that
he held a grudge against Chief Lu,
so he hired Lang Bowen to kill him.
♪ Doubt, doubt the doubt ♪
Also,
why were two deals
going on at the same time yesterday?
Why didn't Zhou Rong show up?
This is a mess.
Yi'ang,
do you think you can do anything?
No matter how cunning a hunter is,
they're no match for a fox.
I think he got that saying wrong.
Focus on the road.
I'll leave the rest
to you.
Chief Qi, don't worry.
Please go ahead.
Okay.
I'm heading back to my office first.
Chief Zhang,
you have a way to make Zhou Rong speak?
I don't for now.
But you just said—
I can't say I have nothing for now
to my boss.
Be careful.
Captain Wang!
Captain Wang, it's me!
Where do you think this is?
A bar?
Take it back.
Brother Wang,
please help.
Yibo can't sleep at night
if he doesn't drink a little.
He can fall asleep when
he has a peace of mind.
Also,
you can call me by my name—
Captain Wang's good too.
Don't call me Brother Wang.
Where did the brother come from?
You are not allowed to give gifts, okay?
Got it.
How is Yibo now?
I can't tell you.
Captain Wang.
I know Yibo
wouldn't dare to say anything.
This is really not on him.
He's afraid of Zhou Rong.
It's useless to tell me this.
We follow the law.
[Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau]
Zhou Rong, come out.
Chief Zhang
is finally showing his face?
How did you know?
Weird.
No one told him.
How did he know
that it's Chief Zhang interrogating him?
Officer.
Excuse me.
What's the weather like tomorrow?
Will it rain?
Will the winds be strong?
I left my laundry outside.
Help me check it up.
Help me
remove this needle.
Don't you have to go back to the hospital
to get your injection later?
I'd look weak like this.
Pull it out.
Take it.
Two, one. Go.
You're here, Chief Zhang.
How is your injury?
I'm fine.
I just lost my appendix.
You know I'm injured,
yet you insisted on seeing me.
I'm injured too.
I wasn't allowed to lie down.
Then let's quickly
clear things up.
I'll try my best
to get you
the best results.
If we wrap this up quickly,
you can go to bed
early.
Think I'm a kid?
Best
results?
Make two death penalties
into one?
Why are you so eager to see me then?
Be honest.
You planted so many people
around me—
what's your purpose?
To obey the law.
Drop the act!
Sanjiangkou
is all yours now, right?
Your purpose is to
end me.
Zhou Rong.
The interrogation room is not
is not a place for you to talk nonsense.
I'm sorry.
I forgot...
I forgot this is
the public security bureau.
I can't talk like that, right?
Understandable.
The characteristics of his illness
is
suspicion
and he easily gets angry.
We can
have a
peaceful discussion
as patients.
Yes.
We're in the same boat.
Otherwise, why would our first meeting
be in the hospital?
No.
Our illnesses are different—
mine's an external one,
and your is an internal one.
Look.
I got
[Seek the truth; act according to the law]
the psychiatrist on the 4th floor
to prescribe this for you.
[Be fair and civilized in law enforcement]
This is the medicine your normally take
to calm yourself down, right?
Have you taken your medication today?
Yes.
Okay, let me help unravel it for you.
In May the year before last,
there was a fight
in Fenglinwan.
Hu Jianren was sentenced
to a year in prison
for assault.
This case
was concluded by Chief Lu.
Half a year ago,
Chief Lu retired.
The story of your destruction
has then begun.
Chief Lu
has mentioned how unethical enterprises
conspire with law enforcement staff
to get benefits
at various press conferences.
Those were all about you, right?
Why are you smirking?
You...
I understand.
You left a mark
in the public security records—
you were worried
that it'd affect your business.
You were also worried that
you would lose your status
in Sanjiangkou
and you got angry.
Did you make those threats
because of these?
Offering 30 million
for Lu Zheng's life.
Am I right?
I killed him
to avenge my brother.
He locked Hu up for a whole year.
I went to beg him myself.
He didn't give me any respect at all.
Chief Lu!
Chief Lu.
That must've been tiring.
You had to climb so many steps—
why didn't they install an elevator?
I'm Zhou Rong from Rongcheng Real Estate.
I wanted to look for you at your office,
but...
I was afraid it would bring bad influence
to your reputation.
Right?
So...
Why does he have to give you respect?
Locking Hu Jianren up
is by the law.
No one
can change it.
There was something worse.
Lu,
after you retire,
who do you think
should take over you?
How is Ye?
Lu Zheng
hindered Ye Jian's future.
Ye Jian was a good cop, right?
He never took a penny from me.
He never did anything for me.
He was held back because of Lu Zheng!
Ye Jian was indeed a good policeman.
We all know that.
But I want to know
who told you
Lu Zheng was against Ye Jian?
He never once did.
Cheif Qi told me about this.
He is a talent.
We should send him out to learn.
It's a pity for him
to stay in Sanjiangkou.
You mean I...
By killing Lu Zheng,
I held Ye Jian back too?
I didn't mean that. I...
Lu Zheng's death
has nothing to do with you.
Lu Zheng's death was an accident.
We didn't have any evidence
at first.
But this is interesting.
We haven't done anything
coming to Sanjiangkou—
all we saw were you lot
running up and down
trying to cover the murder evidence.
I-It was quite ridiculous.
Well...
Wait.
Th-The evidence in the phone
i-is fake?
Lang Bowen w-was messing with me?
Lang Bowen filmed the crime scene
with his phone.
But it was also a coincidence
that he filmed it.
All he did was bring this phone to you
to cheat a huge sum of money
from you.
Then I...
I wasted my time with those two idiots.
I can also tell you
Du Cong is not someone I planted.
Neither is Fang Chao and Liu Zhi.
I didn't arrange for Officer Li
to go to your house either.
W-Wait.
That's not what you said yesterday.
What should I believe,
Zhang Yi'ang?
I didn't do
these things, then.
I won't admit it now.
You can believe whatever you want.
If you didn't do these,
then let's talk about
what you've done before.
Speculating cultural relics
and illegal arms possession.
In order to get the East New Town project,
you bribed officials
and assaulted the police.
You did these, right?
There's also Hu Jianren
trying to get kickbacks,
Du Cong using the company car
for his own use,
Lu Yibo reporting his private life
being a mess...
All right, stop right there.
They are ungrateful!
Trying to get me from behind my back.
No one is trying to get you.
But you were
indeed dragged down by someone.
You, yourself.
Chief.
The rest will be easy.
Interrogate them seperately.
Okay.
[Interrogation Rooms]
Chief.
I'm fine.
Captain Wang!
Zhou Qi wants to see you.
Why is she still here?
I'll go take a look.
Okay.
Chief Zhang,
don't make it difficult for me.
I really don't know anything.
Because you reported Zhou Rong,
yet Zhou Rong chose to forgive you,
you decided to do the trade for him
to make up for your mistake?
Am I right?
Let me tell you the latest news:
Zhou Rong confessed to everything.
Chief.
You...
Excuse me. Wait up.
What happened?
Zhou Qi is here.
She provided an important clue.
Before Lu Yibo went for the deal,
he asked her...
To go look for Lang Bowen directly.
Lu Yibo confessed everything.
What did you say?
Chief.
-Chief.
-You...
Excuse me. Wait up.
Hu Jianren confessed.
What did he say?
He basically evidenced
what Zhou Rong said.
He said Captain Ye's death
has nothing to do with them.
They also told us
how they killed Xiaofei.
Help me up.
We'll go interrogate Lang Bowen right now.
Sorry.
What did you say just now?
You need to stay in bed.
I'll go interrogate them first.