Defend us in battle.
Be our protection against
the wickedness and snares of Satan.
Cast into hell
Satan and all the evil spirits.
Trust in the mercy of the Lord
and confess your sins honestly. Amen.
Amen.
I…
saw the devil.
Blinded by greed,
I stopped at nothing
as if I were possessed by the devil.
And someone tried to stop me.
He said
he would reveal…
my wrongdoings to the world.
I assumed
he was trying to bring me down
out of envy…
EPISODE 13 THE PAST, THE ORIGINAL SIN
I really enjoyed the performance.
I finally understand why you're so obsessed with tradition.
About the human version of you…
Seo Yi-sun.
That was my name.
I like it.
What happened to him in the end?
He took his own life.
He did it
so that he wouldn't go to heaven.
He didn't want to go anyway.
Nor did he deserve to.
I feel sorry for him.
By the way, you lied through your teeth.
You said it was neither a happy nor a sad ending
but an ordinary and insignificant ending.
This time,
I'll make it a happy ending.
A firefly?
Yes.
Our reunion
after all this time
might be
my second chance.
This time,
I'll never make you miserable.
Why are you out here today?
I need some peace and quiet once in a while.
Does watching humans give you peace?
It can both hurt you
and give you peace.
There are two sides to every coin.
I don't want to repeat my unfortunate past with Do-hee.
What am I to do?
Are you asking me for help?
No, you're not going to help me anyway.
I'm just…
asking your opinion.
It wouldn't be called a misfortune
if it were preventable.
You really are no help.
I thought you didn't need my help.
Happiness has no meaning without misfortune.
Humans wouldn't appreciate happiness if they had it all the time.
You talk as if misfortune has some great value.
But it's utterly useless.
Human lives are too short,
even just for happiness.
Happiness
can sometimes be poisonous.
Wake up, Do-hee.
Five more minutes.
Let's have some homemade food like you wanted.
Homemade food?
So where's the homemade food?
Close your eyes for a second.
Just for a second.
What is this?
You remembered that I wanted homemade food.
Of course.
I never forget anything you say.
Hubby.
It looks so good.
-Shall we? -Sure.
But before that, drink some water.
Hold on. I'll go brush my teeth.
I'll be right back. Don't start without me.
Wait for me!
But go ahead and drink the water!
It's already December.
Time flies.
From the blind date to the wedding…
It all seems like a lifetime ago.
I know.
It's been an eventful year.
Come to think of it,
this will be our first Christmas together.
Then again, you dislike Christmas.
That's not true.
I like it now.
I like anything you like.
I'm so looking forward to our first Christmas.
This calls for some Christmas music.
Why is the traffic so slow?
There must've been an accident.
Do-hee.
Yeah?
What were we talking about?
Christmas.
Right.
Let's listen to something else.
Thank you.
Drink up.
It's perfect for this time of day.
That wakes me right up.
So this is new.
I'm surprised you wanted to see me.
It's because you know Do-hee better than anyone else.
Is something up with her?
We saw a car accident on our way to work.
I think
that reminded her of her parents' accident.
I want to make her happy at all times,
but she always seems…
to feel guilty about being happy.
It could be guilt
or anxiety.
She once said
that the few years she spent with her parents
before they passed away
had been the happiest time of her life.
Her life turned miserable at the peak of happiness.
It could be that happiness scares her.
Did she move in with Ju Cheon-suk right after the accident?
No, she lived with one relative after another for a while.
Her relatives would take her in for her inheritance and insurance money,
only to abandon her when the money ran dry.
When I first met her,
she was like a porcupine.
She was extremely wary of everyone, thinking she might be left alone again.
Aunt Cheon-suk was the one who opened Do-hee's heart,
but Do-hee lost her as well.
Catching her killer kept Do-hee preoccupied for a while.
But the old wound…
must be acting up again now.
Come in.
It's time for the meeting.
Okay.
We're planning a promotional event
to maximize awareness
of Mirae F&amp;B's new product
and actively attract customers.
-Ms. Choi? -Yes.
As for the location,
we're considering gyms, marathons, university festivals, and such.
Any other options?
These are all so obvious.
I want somewhere new and trendy.
How about
Sunwol Theater?
The place run by Director Jeong?
Have you heard of the term "trendy traditions"?
Traditional culture is all the rage now.
Ms. Jin's performance is the talk of the town as well.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Who's Ms. Jin?
She's the one who showed up here
after Mr. Jeong's near-fatal attack.
She even hugged him in front of everyone.
You made a fuss,
saying it was more fun than Love and War, remember?
What are you talking about? I never said that.
I'm sorry.
I like the idea.
Let's collaborate with Sunwol Theater.
-Ms. Do. -Yes?
Ms. Shin will coordinate things.
Okay.
-Ms. Do. -Yes?
Her life turned miserable at the peak of happiness.
It could be that happiness scares her.
-Gu-won! -Hey.
Is it okay if I hold a promotional event
for my company's new product at Sunwol Theater?
Whatever you want, Do-hee.
Don't say that.
I'm making an official offer,
so please officially consider it as the Executive Director.
Then I give my official approval.
Great.
Now, my company's marketing team
is going to send over a proposal.
Here it is.
-Take a look. -Okay.
Let me give you a brief explanation first.
We'll check on the performance schedule and decide on the date…
I'm concerned.
When things get tough,
Do-hee tends to push herself.
It's her way of suppressing her emotions.
Please stay by her side and make sure
she doesn't push herself too hard.
MIRAE GROUP CORP.
MIRAE FOUNDATION
"Industrial Accident Compensation Committee"?
It was established by Chairwoman Ju and was unprecedented in Korea back then.
It greatly improved the company's image after the industrial accident
and thus holds great symbolic value.
It's out of date now.
Disband it.
The stockholders who believe in Chairwoman Ju's management philosophy
will oppose it strongly.
My mother is dead.
So is the world she created.
Have at least 30% of our full-time workers to be switched to part-time.
I want each affiliate to submit their restructuring plans.
You didn't
live the way your father wanted.
That's why you're being punished.
Calm down!
It's your turn now.
Mom?
Dad?
Where are you?
Where did you go?
Where did you go without me?
Dad?
Gu-won?
They all left without me.
They left me here alone.
It's my fault.
I'm responsible.
Do-hee.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Then…
why has everyone left?
Why have they left me here alone?
They didn't leave you.
It's just…
that you can't see them for a while.
Does that mean
I can see them again?
Of course.
Should we go see them now?
Let's go.
Why is that one so big?
Because it's going on top.
Is it?
Do-hee.
You're up.
Mom.
Dad.
Hurry over here.
Or else you won't get any presents.
Madam Ju.
We need you for the star, Do-hee.
Come here.
Go ahead.
It's finally finished.
Should we have some cake now?
Gu-won.
I wish I could truly return them to you.
But this is…
all I can do for you.
Why can't I untangle it?
How come it gets more tangled the harder I try?
What the…
What are you doing?
You're up.
A Christmas tree?
Yes.
But it's harder than it looks.
Why don't you use your powers?
I just felt like decorating it with you.
Decorating's the fun part.
Actually, I had a dream about Christmas last night.
Really?
How was it?
I was so happy
that I didn't want to wake up.
I should make you even happier.
Try it.
It's finally untangled.
Whatever.
I'll just use my powers.
I'll help you.
We still have time.
You're right.
But don't you think the tree looks nice as is?
It's not a Christmas tree yet. It's just a tree.
-It's just a tree? -Yes.
You're right again.
That's piping hot.
My lips!
Drink some water.
FOR DO-HEE
-What's this? -It's a present.
Do I look pretty?
Very.
I could've driven to work myself.
I should protect my man.
Then let me give you a ride to work tomorrow.
No, thanks.
Right.
As you know,
I've failed at marriage once.
So I don't feel comfortable being open about my relationship
with my colleagues.
You didn't fail at marriage.
You succeeded in getting a divorce.
Also,
I understand you no matter what.
Bok-gyu.
Lotus roots are in season, so I made lotus root rice today.
Please don't skip your meals even if you're busy.
You really know
how to move me.
I'm even more moved
by the fact that you're moved
by these little things.
Bok-gyu.
We're here.
Already?
Drive safely.
The drive to the theater is just way too short.
I wish it took a lot longer to…
Ms. Shin! Your lunch box!
Ms. Shin!
Take your lunch box!
Take your lunch box, Ms. Shin!
-Ms. Shin! -He's so cute.
No, that's not it!
Did you run a marathon or something?
I envy you.
FREE TASTING AT SUNWOL THEATER
You can move from place to place at the snap of a finger.
That hits the spot.
What happened to your car that you've barely paid for?
Did you see all the articles about our performance?
"The birth of an overwhelmingly refreshing experience."
"A breathtaking performance full of life."
To think I planned this amazing performance.
I'm so proud of myself
I should drink some more
I'll take these too
What's that?
What are you drinking?
I'm taking good care of myself these days.
That's how I stay attractive.
Do you like Ms. Shin that much?
I've always dreamed of dating a kind woman.
But she's not kind at all.
Exactly.
When it comes to true love, your preferences mean nothing.
But guess what her first name is.
Da-jeong, as in kind.
We're meant to be.
You said you were a shining solo.
Mirae F&amp;B wants to collaborate with us.
You can take care of it.
Don't even think of bothering me.
I don't even have enough time to be happy with Do-hee!
What do you think you actually do for a living?
Being Do-hee's husband.
Are you going to Mirae F&amp;B later?
Take this, then.
Is this a lunch box?
You didn't have to.
It's for Ms. Shin.
Are you sending me on an errand?
All I want you to do is drop it off on the way.
I don't want to.
Then I'll have to go there myself.
I'd love to see her one more time.
Here I come, Ms. Shin!
I heard
about your past life
and how you and Do Do-hee got entangled.
Knowing that I stood no chance at getting between you two
somehow puts me at ease.
Don't worry.
I won't tell Do Do-hee.
Do you still want to leave Korea?
Yes.
If it's because of me,
I'm okay now.
It's not because of you, but me.
My love
is poisonous to you.
Ms. Jin!
I'm coming!
I'll be leaving soon.
So do come to work more often.
I loved your performance.
You were great.
Tell me something I don't know.
Who in the world did this?
MIRAE F&amp;B
Let's see here.
I'll do a reading on my social life today.
My goodness!
I thought it was Ms. Do again.
Can you see the future with these?
Not so much as the future,
but an inch ahead of you.
Let's do it!
How much is it?
Do you charge a lot?
This one. No!
You and Ms. Do
really are a match made in heaven.
This one.
It's the Lovers.
These two people
look familiar.
They're Adam and Eve from the Bible.
Behind them is the forbidden fruit from the Garden of Eden.
The forbidden fruit?
This card
symbolizes the completion of love.
In other words,
a bed of roses.
A bed of roses?
A bed of roses.
Come to think of it,
I've never given Do-hee any flowers.
Just my luck.
Time for a break?
Ma'am,
I can't teach your kids.
You're the leading authority on successor training.
If you can't teach them, who can?
-Who can? -I'm sorry.
Who can…
Who else?
I will.
"A new leadership paradigm is needed
in this rapidly changing business environment."
-"Servant leadership is one example." -Stop it.
"Servant leadership…"
-"Servant leadership -I said stop it.
-is based on respect for humanity -Move.
-and each member of the group." -Come on.
-"A servant leader -I said move.
-considers each individual as a leader…" -Knock it off already.
Hey!
Austin! Justin!
Let go.
Stay absolutely still.
Or else I'll make you regret it.
"They integrate and empathize with the members…"
NOH SUK-MIN
Hi, Suk-min.
I'm in the middle of giving successor training to Austin and Justin.
Yes. What?
Dinner?
NOH SUK-MIN
Yes?
Are you free this evening, Do-hee?
Why do you ask?
I'm planning a family gathering so we can comfort one another.
Let's have dinner together.
Bring Mr. Jeong along.
I have plans today.
Then should we pick another day?
Please give me a chance for my mother's sake.
We're family, after all.
Send me the money, damn it!
It's a sure bet this time.
Do you need help?
I think I can help you.
Are you a loan shark or something?
I have a higher status than that.
Way higher. Significantly higher, in fact.
-Are you from the bank? -Forget it.
Answer me one question.
What kind of life have you been living?
What are you playing at now?
It's unlikely, but I want to make sure you aren't a good person.
Consider it a loan approval process.
What are you babbling about?
You must think I'm some pushover you can screw over,
but I've been in and out of prison all my life!
Great!
You're more than qualified!
I'm a demon.
Make a deal with me, and I'll grant your wish.
My wish?
Can it be anything?
I can't kill or resurrect people.
Nor can I turn back time or meddle with natural disasters.
Other than that, I can do anything you want.
But it comes with a price.
I knew it.
Still, it's simple.
Your soul must go to hell after ten years.
That's it. What do you say?
Ten years is a long time.
Let's do it.
-As foolish as expected. -What?
You made the right choice.
What's with your hand?
Some kind of magic?
Don't mind it.
It'll be fine once you sign.
It's that bastard, sir.
Who are you to fool around on my turf?
Boss!
My hand is on fire. Want a deal?
-No! -Anyone want a deal?
No?
Hurry up and sign!
Hey, hurry up!
I always knew you were no average Joe,
but a demon?
A demon?
That's badass, boss!
-That's badass, boss! -That's badass, boss!
I didn't know you'd be so thrilled.
Anyway, what were you guys doing back there?
We dabble in financial business.
As loan sharks?
I thought someone was intruding on our turf,
so I was going to teach him a lesson.
But it turned out to be you conducting this incredible ritual.
How could you not let us know you were such an extraordinary being?
We'll follow you to hell, boss!
-We'll follow you, boss! -We'll follow you, boss!
Do you even know what hell is like?
Suit yourselves then.
But first, leave the underworld
and take on a lawful occupation.
Then I'll accept you.
You all are such a hassle.
I'm taking these.
Take care, boss.
-Take care, boss! -Take care, boss!
Leave…
Leave the underworld?
Give me every flower that symbolizes happiness.
Good.
That was natural.
-Mr. Park? -Yes?
I mean, you're mistaken.
You're obviously him.
Hold on.
I came to the wrong place.
What's with him?
What are you doing here, Bok-gyu?
How come everyone knows it's me?
How could I not?
I recognize my man from a mile away.
You're embarrassing me.
Here, your lunch box.
I took it with me by mistake.
You really didn't have to.
-Yes, I'll do that. -All right.
What's this feeling of déjà vu?
Mr. Park!
You frustrate me to no end!
-What? -Seriously,
you lack common sense
and manners!
I hate your guts!
Guess what? I hate you even more!
Oh no, you didn't!
How can you be so cold?
It's not that I'm cold.
It's that you're too hot!
Please don't get us wrong.
We are having a fight.
Obviously.
Are you really?
I don't know what happened,
but please calm down and talk--
Forget it!
It's impossible to talk to him.
How can someone lack warmth so completely?
You should let it go, Mr. Park.
That's just the way she is.
What do you mean?
I'd say she's pretty reasonable.
I guess she is.
By the way, is that a lunch box?
Yes, it is.
You really didn't have to.
Thank you.
-No, I mean… -Goodness.
Thank you for this.
You're one generous man, Mr. Park.
Even my mom wouldn't do this.
-Thank you. -Thank you.
Nice!
It's not for you.
I don't think I can make it today.
Come in.
What are those?
What's the occasion?
Today is a very special day.
It's not our 100th day together or our wedding anniversary.
Nor is it my birthday.
So what's today?
It's one of the countless happy days we'll be spending together.
If I'm with you,
every day calls for a celebration.
Your words are so sweet
that they could give me cavities.
I brought all the happiness in the world to you.
This flower here symbolizes happiness.
This one symbolizes eternal happiness.
This one means happiness that is meant to be.
Happiness that's been lost and found.
And this one…
I love you, Jeong Gu-won.
I love you too.
Come here.
-Do you like it? -Of course.
What does this one symbolize?
That one…
Let me see.
It's not here.
-The red one… -I knew it a minute ago.
WITHOUT POWERS, THE BODY OF A DEMON IS NO DIFFERENT FROM THAT OF A HUMAN
A DEMON'S POWERS COME FROM THE BRANDING ON THEIR BODY
I thought you were oblivious, but were you only pretending?
How do you know the passcode to my safe?
Just how much do you know?
Perfect.
Do we have to go?
Noh Suk-min will be acting all friendly,
and I have a weaker stomach than you think.
I can't avoid him forever.
I'm not the avoidant type either.
Also,
what do I have to fear when you're with me?
Then…
let me know if you feel sick.
Don't just put up with it.
The only thing in the world that I'm not good at
is putting up with things.
Really?
That's my girl.
-Should we get going? -Let's go.
Thank you all for coming on such short notice.
Don't mention it. Of course we should come.
Having you all gathered here
brings back memories. It's nice.
If only Mom could be here.
I'm sure she's in heaven.
She was baptized too.
Now that I've taken over her position,
I keep thinking about her.
You feel lonelier the higher you climb.
Imagine how lonely she must've been.
She wasn't lonely because of her position
but because she kept even her children at arm's length.
I wonder why she was so cold to us
while she favored someone else's child.
Blood isn't everything, Su-ahn.
People who see eye to eye and care about each other can be family.
Are you defending her because you're also a Ju?
You can say that because you're not her child.
It wasn't easy to live as Chairwoman Ju Cheon-suk's child.
Our mother may be gone,
but the rest of us should leave any grudges and misunderstandings behind.
Sure, I'm not one to hold a grudge.
The perpetrator usually doesn't hold a grudge.
Perpetrator?
You talk as if I've done something.
That's a victim mentality.
That's because I am a victim.
So?
Are you saying you're just an innocent victim?
Every time I tried to get the upper hand, you turned the tables on me.
That's enough.
We're not here to fight.
Also, past mistakes are still mistakes.
Apologize, Su-ahn.
Suk-min!
Su-ahn.
I'm sorry.
Fine.
I admit my past mistakes.
Honey,
can you get us more wine?
Sure.
How's work, Suk-min?
As you all know,
our stockholders are quite conservative.
They may have looked up to Mother as the founder,
but they'll try to find fault with everything I do.
In light of that,
I need your full support.
You have my full support, Suk-min.
Here's my point.
How about you all
transfer your shares to me?
So that's what this was about.
It'd cost a fortune to buy all of our shares though.
I'm sorry, but my answer is no.
But as long as you make the right choices,
you'll have my support.
What's right and wrong is subjective.
That's why I need my shares.
We might not always see eye to eye.
Thank you for the meal.
You haven't given me an answer.
This is my answer.
Let me ask you something.
Did you really not know what Do-gyeong was up to?
Or did you just turn a blind eye?
You're out of line.
I just lost both my mother and son.
From the way you act,
I can't tell you're grieving.
Family gatherings never end well.
I hope you'll make the right choices.
I'll also…
give it some thought.
-Su-ahn. -Yeah?
My kindness ends today.
You put up with him pretty well back there.
You could tell?
Didn't you leave to avoid punching him in the face?
You know everything about me now.
But I still know so little about you.
I could really use that demon manual.
When it comes to me, what you see is what you get.
I'm a flawless being with special powers.
That's my man.
I think my stomach's upset.
I want to order in some fried chicken.
You just said your stomach was upset.
-How about some beer? -I approve.
-You do? -Yes.
Okay.
Let's do it.
-How's the speed for you? -Just hold my hand.
INDUSTRIAL ACCIDENT COMPENSATION COMMITTEE
How can I help you?
A whistleblower came forward about fraudulent use of funds.
That's absurd.
-Go ahead. -Yes, sir.
Hello, Ju Seok-hoon speaking.
What?
What you ordered will be completed by the end of the month.
This requires an official board meeting!
That'll be all.
Is this why you wanted all our shares?
Terminating the compensation committee and full-time contracts?
This isn't right!
I'm just doing business.
This isn't business, but murder!
Listen.
This may look like a smart move now, but it'll only do damage in the long run.
Don't try to pass off your personal beliefs as facts.
I'll tell the press and persuade the stockholders.
I'll do everything in my power to stop you.
Inform the board of the motion to dismiss CEO Ju Seok-hoon.
Let's find out
who has more power.
Feet off the desk.
I already cleaned over there!
Go do your job as Do Do-hee's husband instead of hanging out here.
I'm here to see Ga-young
because she's leaving soon.
I guess you do care about your human companion.
Stop it! This is a new outfit!
By the way, aren't you getting that demon manual back?
No. Who cares about a book full of threats?
Still, you should.
Missing manuals can halve secondhand prices.
Stop treating me like some home appliance!
But I still know so little about you.
I could really use that demon manual.
Are you done being angry?
I'm going to get that manual back.
I knew you'd give in in the end.
Hi, Seok-hoon.
Do-hee.
Suk-min has revealed his true colors.
Cut off her communication with the outside
and keep her hospitalized until further notice.
Yes, sir.
I've handled your orders about your wife, sir.
You can't enter, ma'am!
Is this your management style?
Pushing things through with the support of the directors on your side?
Madam Ju prioritized
balancing profits and social responsibility.
-How could you throw that away-- -You seem to
really look up to my mother.
I know why you're doing this.
You want to surpass Madam Ju.
Do you think you can keep up with her this way?
No.
This only proves that you can't even compare to her.
How much longer are you planning to stay in her shadow?
Accept it, Do-hee.
My mother's world has come to an end.
I've cracked my way out of the egg.
It's Gi Kwang-chul's phone.
TO ABRAXAS
Abraxas.
"The bird fights its way out of the egg."
"To be born,
one must first destroy a world."
The world you have destroyed…
is Ju Cheon-suk.
This is your problem.
If you had stayed out of it, everyone would've been safe.
But you always cause trouble by never letting anything go.
If not for you,
we wouldn't have ended up here.
Why do you have to go this far?
To avenge dear Madam Ju Cheon-suk?
I suppose she's like a god to you.
How could you…
How could you kill your own mother?
That old woman was the devil.
The reason I ended up like this
is your precious Almighty Ju.
I was a sinner even before I committed any sins.
She dumped her sins on me, her own child,
and went so far as to blame my blood!
Why?
Because the more worthless I seemed, the more she stood out.
I always thought you were good at nothing,
but there's one thing you're good at.
Blaming others.
Let's test and see how far your steadfast faith can go.
You should be thanking me.
I took revenge on her for you.
What?
You think your parents died in an accident.
But that's not true.
They were killed by Ju Cheon-suk,
whom you relied on the most.
Your Almighty Ju, whom you trusted completely,
was the one who killed your parents.
It's all done.
That's much better.
But the water pressure is so low here.
Fancy seeing you here.
What a coincidence.
Have you been following me?
No way.
I just had to use the bathroom.
You don't seem surprised.
All right.
I have a question for you,
so this is great.
Noh Do-gyeong
took something important from me.
It's a green hardcover book.
Have you seen it?
No, I'm afraid not.
Did Noh Suk-min do that?
I just
burned myself while cooking.
I don't really care how it really happened.
But…
it seems like your hell has just begun.
Let me know if you find the book.
Who knows?
That might be…
your ticket out of hell.
I'm off.
Bullshit.
You really expect me to believe that?
I was there on the day your parents died.
The company is at a crossroads.
An investment offer this big doesn't come by so often!
You leave me no choice.
I'll expose everything.
How dare you blackmail me?
What do you want?
Is it money?
You're the one who quit the company and took off.
What gives you the right?
This is my company.
You didn't build it alone.
It was built on the blood, sweat, and tears
of everyone who works here!
-Honey. -Wait and see.
It won't go as you want.
Furious, my mother drove after your parents' car,
and you know what happened next.
Boom!
Mirae Electronics grew into Mirae Group after that.
You could say your parents' blood laid the foundation.
I don't believe it.
My mother used to believe in nothing, let alone have any religion.
But she started going to confession day in and day out after their death!
Why do you think?
What was she so desperate to wash away?
Just what was she so afraid of?
All the favors and affection she showered on you
were actually her ticket to heaven.
No.
That's a lie.
You're lying!
Then ask her yourself.
Whether she's in heaven or hell,
go ask her yourself!
It's all his doing!
Noh Suk-min killed both his mother and Do-gyeong!
He was also the one who tried to kill Do Do-hee.
Noh Suk-min, that bastard,
is the devil.
There is one piece of evidence Noh Suk-min failed to get rid of.
How did you gather all this information without him knowing?
Is it true? Did my brother really kill my mother?
Is it true that Ju Cheon-suk killed Do-hee's parents?
Wait and see. It won't go as you want.
After what I've been through to build this company…
This has to be made public.
How dare you try to destroy my company?
I'll stop you if it's the last thing I do.
I can tell you're desperate for something.
Do you want me to grant your wish?
Subtitle translation by: Min-jin Kim