[Disclaimer:
All depicted events are fictional
[and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
No.
It can't end like this.
Wake up, Grandma.
I'm ready.
Please send me to him, Master.
Please don't go, Khem.
Please stay with me.
I have no one left, Khem.
Peem,
I truly thank you for everything.
You let me experience a kind of love.
But from now on,
I'll find my own way,
so no one else gets hurt because of me.
Is everyone okay?
That was close, man.
- That was damn close.
- Are you alright?
How did it even fall?
Whoa,
you look
as if you were cursed.
Better stop by Gangnam Clinic sometime.
What are they looking at?
Can you
see him?
Hey,
are you okay?
- Did you get hurt?
- What happened?
Are you alright?
- You okay?
- Are you hurt?
Don't pile on him.
He's already freaked out.
- We're just worried.
Hey, hey.
Freshmen,
return to the base
if you've got nothing to do.
Don't slack off.
Come on, bro,
the sign you set up
almost crushed my friend's head.
Talking back?
Do squat jumps
as many times as your year of entry.
What?
Just do what we say.
Excuse me.
I'll take the punishment for everyone.
I'll do it.
I talked back.
You wanna do it, huh?
Then do it, both of you.
One,
two,
- Louder!
- Three,
four.
[Welcome, FAA 2022 freshmen
to the art side!
[May 25-27, all day at the square,
see you!]
So that's why you've been acting weird.
Everyone's been talking about you
since the first day.
When I was in elementary school,
my parents got called in a lot.
The teachers thought
something might be wrong with me.
I mean,
I barely talked to anyone,
and sometimes I got scared
even when nothing was there.
I've been through the same.
My dad was so afraid
I wouldn't have any friends.
So,
is the ghost that attacked you
connected to the curse
you told me about?
I
Don't know, Jet, but I guess
ghosts are just like us.
Some are good, and some are bad.
I'll help you.
I'm the number one disciple
of the country's top shaman.
Look.
Sacred rice grains,
holy water,
and a talisman cloth.
I've got it all.
Thanks a lot, Jet.
We only met today,
but it feels like
I've known you for a long time.
That's good.
I can feel
that you
are gonna bring good things into my life.
Well, obviously.
This is just our first day.
Come on.
First day or ten years,
you're my friend now.
I'll never let my friend suffer.
Thanks, Jet.
Yeah.
From now on,
you need to tell me everything,
ghosts, people, whatever.
If I can help, I will.
Don't keep it to yourself.
Yeah.
And don't dump me.
It's not easy
to find a friend who also sees ghosts!
I know,
but I'll dump you for now.
I gotta go.
Alright, then.
Khem!
You promised
you'd never dump me.
I'm sorry, Jet,
but you love Grandma Si,
Thong, and Ake.
I...
Don't you think I love you, too?
You think
I'll hate you after all this?
I don't know, Jet.
I even hate myself.
I can't bear losing anyone again.
So you're
handling this by leaving us?
It's not your fault, Khem,
but it's Ramphueng's.
If you leave,
that means she wins.
Please, Jet.
Ever since you met me,
I've always caused you trouble.
From the first day,
when you said I'd bring you good things.
I have not.
I have not, Jet.
That's not true.
Coming to this camp together
is a good thing, isn't it?
You met Master.
We met Charn.
We've been through so much together.
Don't you think that's a good thing, too?
I've never had a friend in my life,
but helping someone,
protecting them,
and knowing they can count on me...
It makes me feel so appreciated.
Whatever,
I won't let you leave.
But if you're actually leaving,
I'll cling to the train to come with you.
Me, too.
I've been willing to go through
everything with you,
even though we just met,
because you mean a lot to us, Khem.
Officail Website : kissasian.be
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
But
the villagers have already lost enough.
We won't go back there, then.
Let's all go to Bangkok.
I've packed everything.
Wherever you go,
we'll go with you.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry
that I put you through all this.
Right,
when I said I'd cling to the train,
I was joking.
We'll catch a flight.
I'll cover the tickets.
Let's take the plane.
Thanks, Jet.
I'll sleep on the floor.
You guys can take the bed.
Come on,
no need to feel bad anymore.
I'll sleep on the floor.
In fact,
you should take the bed,
and Jet and I can be at ease.
That's
what Master gave you.
You made it a necklace now?
We each have one, then.
Got anything?
What'd she say?
Well,
she's an atheist,
so she doesn't want a shrine
in front of the dorm.
I asked to set it up on the rooftop,
and she was fine with it
as long as it didn't cause any trouble.
It should be ready in three days.
Anyway,
are you sure you can handle this
without your master?
He's already lost so much for me.
What now?
One sec.
What's their problem?
Hello?
What?
Gosh, no more revisions.
Can you stop calling me, too?
Hey,
my brother's about to get killed
by a ghost.
I'm serious. Who would joke about that?
Yeah.
If he doesn't make it,
I'll blame you instead of the ghost.
Yes.
Go ahead, cancel it. I don't care.
Khem's birthday is in seven days.
As soon as June 5 ends,
he'll turn 21.
If he makes it until then,
the curse will be lifted.
Come on.
Let's give our all.
Jane, come on.
Time to cheer ourselves up.
What's this?
What do I need to say?
Charn's prepared it.
One, two, three...
- Khemjira must survive!
How about taking a break
until it's past your birthday?
Whoa,
even you want him to skip his classes?
Don't worry.
I'm in the same section as him
for every class.
I won't let him out of my sight.
Let me be a student for one more day,
just in case.
So, I won't regret it
if I never get the chance again.
Don't say that.
Forget it.
Don't move!
Are you okay, Khem?
Khem,
are you alright?
I think you should stay in your room
until your birthday.
Don't be afraid, Khem.
Jet and I will take turns staying with you.
Give me an update.
What?
All good.
The target is safe.
Passing the duty to Bodyguard No. 2!
Hey,
I'm No. 1!
Passing the duty to Bodyguard No. 1
from Bodyguard No. 0!
You won't let me win, huh?
Take care of yourself, Charn.
See you later.
I offer this food
to pass merit
to all wandering spirits.
During this time,
I kindly ask that none of you
enter this dwelling.
If you do,
Ramphueng might
take control of your mind.
How about writing them an essay?
Just tell them
you'll do a big offering later.
I just gave them a warning.
I don't think
they'd want anyone
controlling their minds.
Come on,
I'll purify you
before we go up.
Hey...
Here.
Now it's my turn.
If you want to take your turn,
make it quick.
♫ The one who makes my dreams come true, ♫
♫ The one in my heart, baby, it's you ♫
♫ It's you I've been longing for, ♫
♫ The one I've always adored ♫
♫ Right by my side, it's truly you ♫
♫ It's you I want, nothing more ♫
♫ From now on, you'll be my all ♫
Will you ever stop, huh?
Purify me, too.
Okay, Miss Jane.
No need to be so formal.
Just call me Jane.
Okay, Jane.
Are you guys done?
I made you some noodles.
Aw,
as if you could read my mind.
You should join us, Jane.
Let some tom yum freshen you up.
That's perfect.
I was looking for something
to balance out the sweetness.
I have a room ready for you downstairs
in case you need some water
I've got an urgent matter
and need to go now.
Yes, Father.
There's nothing to fear.
All my friends are with me.
After my birthday,
I'll bring them to meet you.
That's great.
Is Master there with you, too?
Master...
He's performing a ritual
to keep the wandering spirits away.
He'll also ward off
bad luck for me tomorrow.
Knowing that
someone is looking after you,
I feel at ease.
You don't need to worry, Father.
I'm doing well.
Alright, I won't bother you now.
Relax
and get some rest, Khem.
I'm tired.
Help me do it.
- Wait up.
- What?
May this lantern
rise up to the Heaven of Tavatimsa,
offering homage to the Buddha's relics
and the Chulamani Chedi.
May all of Khem's misfortunes
and karmic debts
drift away from his life tonight.
Sadhu.
Focus your mind.
If you want to say a prayer, do so now.
If you can really hear us,
please show mercy
and protect the three of us.
And if anything happens,
please guide me as you have before.
Just two more hours until midnight.
Don't worry, Khem.
We're not letting our guard down.
We're going to recite the Itipiso
108 times tonight.
In the meantime, you should just rest
and wake up
for your birthday cake tomorrow.
Thank you.
Even when you're about to die,
you still won't say goodbye
to your friend, huh?
Khemjira.
I gave you time,
hoping to see a dramatic farewell.
But your friends don't even know
that I
have been inside your mind all along.
I have a room ready for you downstairs
I've got an urgent matter
and need to go now.
Take care of yourself, Charn.
See you later.
Don't move!
Are you okay, Khem?
Keep your hope alive.
Cherish it until your final breath
before I shatter it completely.
Stay focused.
It's almost over.
Khemjira...
Jet,
wake up now!
What?
Jet,
Khem's gone.
Shit!
Wait.
What?
He didn't leave the building.
What? Where is he?
Up there.
- Khem!
Khem!
Khem...
Khem,
get a hold of yourself.
Let my friend go,
or I'll end you.
Khem...
Khem, hey.
No.
I'm taking him with me.
Khem...
Khem!
If you're still here,
please reveal yourself to me.
The vision I revealed to you
will come true tomorrow night.
For what reason
are you helping me, my lord?
I am repaying the debt I owe you.
I have done nothing to deserve it.
Not in this lifetime,
but you bestowed a deed of great virtue
over a thousand years ago.
Phuchong Nagaraja,
you have committed three transgressions.
You have stolen the sacred weapon
from the vault of treasures
and used it to slay Chimphli, the Garuda.
Though he had slain your son first,
your retribution was far too great.
For that reason,
by the supreme power of that weapon,
your deed
troubled all that lives within Himavanta
and brought about
the loss of countless lives.
I am ready to bear my guilt
and make amends across all lifetimes.
You shall no longer make amends
in any other lifetime.
Your soul shall be shattered
and forbidden from lingering
in any cycle of rebirth.
Be gone. Fade into the void.
Hold, mighty lord.
Phuchagin,
what brings you here?
Some truths have not yet been told.
Who are you?
I am Phuchagin.
I too guard the vault of treasures
of the Underworld,
and I am the cause of this matter.
What is it you say?
Do not lie.
I bore a personal grudge
against the Garuda.
When I saw my kin
driven mad
by the loss of his beloved son,
I devised a scheme,
urging him to steal the weapon and use it
to wipe the Garuda from the world.
Why would you lie?
All that I have said is true.
I am deeply ashamed
to witness my elder kin
bear the punishment alone.
Please reconsider
his punishment once more.
Phuchong,
do not defend me.
What is it you intend?
Why involve yourself in this matter?
Your son had lived righteously,
and he has been reborn
in the Nimmanarati Heaven.
If your soul remains,
you shall meet your son again one day.
But if you do this,
you
may be cast back
into the cycle of rebirth.
Then so be it.
I am tired of a life
spent only guarding these treasures.
Phuchagin,
do you swear
that what you have spoken is true?
I vow every word is so.
If that is so,
I shall review the punishment once more.
I will send the two of you
to the world of mortals.
Phuchong Nagaraja,
you shall dwell in the deep forest,
with nothing
but a cavern in which to coil.
Your powers shall be stripped.
You shall become a mere black serpent
and begin your cultivation anew.
And you, Phuchagin,
for you are the root of this matter,
in every lifetime henceforth
you shall be born a mere mortal,
destined to struggle and toil,
to sacrifice yourself
and do good for many,
that you may atone for the loss
you have wrought.
I will bear the punishment, mighty lord.
Farewell for now,
my kin.
I can't accept this, my lord.
This weapon belonged to you.
I merely returned it to you
as I believe it is time
for it to be returned to its owner.
You still worry for your kin, do you?
Officail Website : kissasian.be
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
I
I know his words were only to save you.
Who would not know
the fame of Phuchagin Nagaraja,
beloved by all?
How could he bear a grudge
against the Garuda?
If that is so,
why have you given him such punishment?
I could feel, deep within,
that he yearns for love,
the love that cannot be attained
should he remain merely a guardian
of the Underworld treasures.
Keep this.
Let it be your choice what course to take.
As for Phuchagin,
for he gave his life to save you,
I have granted him a blessing:
in every lifetime,
he shall be cherished
by both mortals and gods.
If you are to use it, think carefully,
for it carries
the power of the sacred weapon,
belonging to the guardian
of the Underworld treasures.
The human body you inhabit
is not meant to endure such might.
This is all I can offer
in return for your deed.
Beyond this,
your fate depends upon your own karma.
I wish you luck.
Kachen,
I need your help.
And then our voices say:
May fortune come.
This is an auspicious day.
Together we gather, together we pray.
The venerable shaman
declares it a blessed day.
It's a day of fortune, a day of light.
With the offerings adorned with delight,
we now summon the vital force
through this rite:
May your vital force come forth.
May your 32 parts come together.
May your 92 parts gather.
May all reside within your body forever.
As you can see,
even without Grandma Si,
we, villagers,
can summon the vital force ourselves.
There's one thing.
I want to tell you.
It's not just you who cares for us.
Everyone in the village
cares for you, too.
♫ May your vital force come to me ♫
♫ In my arms, where you should be, ♫
♫ Come to the one who loves you tenderly ♫
May you be safe, Master.
- Have a safe trip.
- Wishing you a safe journey, Master.
May you always be protected.
- Stay strong and healthy.
- We love you, Master.
The apartment you're going to
is quite old and in poor condition, Master.
If you need to be around there,
we have a VIP suite in our hotel chain
ready for you, Master.
That's not necessary.
But Young Master asked me
to give you the best accommodation.
This is enough.
Tell him to come to me
as soon as he arrives.
Yes, Master.
Khem!
Khem...
Are you tired yet?
Ready to give up now?
The longer you linger,
the more you'll suffer.
I wonder how much more you can endure.
Don't give up just yet.
I'll take you back, Khem.
Khem!
Khem,
can you hear me?
Peem!
Where are you?
Don't give up now.
Come.
The more, the merrier.
No need to wait for tomorrow.
Tonight can be your end.
Have you seen
the full extent of my power?
By day, disaster will follow you.
By night,
nightmares will haunt you endlessly.
Staying on will bring only suffering.
Not only you,
but everyone around you
will suffer.
Decide, Khemjira.
Choose.
You can end everything here,
in this dream,
and leave peacefully
without ever facing loss again.
What do you say?
What is your choice?
I've
given up.
Don't give up, Khem.
You finally came.
You don't know when to quit, do you?
This is your dream.
You can stop it anytime.
Focus.
Cast out everything you did not let in.
I offered you an easy way,
yet you did not take it.
From now on,
you'll find no mercy from me.
Khem...
Are you hurt?
Why did you come after me?
Please let me go.
I've given up.
No, you can't.
I don't wanna live anymore.
No, Khem.
You need to live,
for your friends,
for your parents,
and for me.
We must stay together in this life.
Trust me, Khem.
No matter what happens,
we'll find our way back to each other.
♫ Just one glance, and I could feel ♫
♫ A vow long hidden, suddenly revealed, ♫
♫ Leading our souls in a destined appeal ♫
♫ To meet once more with a bond to seal ♫
♫ It's more than love at first sight, ♫
♫ But a bond through every life ♫
♫ Our destinies cross again in this life ♫
♫ You'll be my last, my eternal light, ♫
♫ From now until the end of time ♫
♫ Whether it's a dream or it's true, ♫
♫ My heart forever stays with you ♫
♫ No force shall tear our souls in two ♫
♫ I love you through and through ♫
♫ Even if the world ceases to move, ♫
♫ These words will still be true, ♫
♫ I love you ♫
♫ It's more than love at first sight, ♫
♫ But a bond through every life ♫
♫ Our destinies cross again in this life ♫
♫ You'll be my last, my eternal light, ♫
♫ From now until the end of time ♫
♫ Whether it's a dream or it's true, ♫
♫ My heart forever stays with you ♫
♫ No force shall tear our souls in two ♫
♫ I love you through and through ♫
♫ Even if the world ceases to move, ♫
♫ These words will still be true, ♫
♫ I love you ♫
Khem...
Jet!
Let's
go for a walk
again, shall we?
No deities dwell in this shrine,
so it's not a spirit shrine
but rather a gate
linking to Ramphueng's realm.
She hid through this gate,
so you couldn't sense her presence.
She's been inside Khem's mind all along.
I didn't want to worry you.
I've seen the vision.
If I hadn't come here today,
tonight, Khem...
But you're here now.
Perhaps we can rest easy now, right?
We can't yet.
Ramphueng will do something.
Until now,
we've only been defending ourselves,
but we won't do that again from now on.
Do you have a plan, Master?
What's your plan?
Tell us now.
We can do anything.
Let's wait until everyone's here.
Wait, so it's not everyone yet?
Who's left?
You've got a phone, Master?
If that's your phone,
that means...
Yeah.
Come in.
Why this one, of all people, Master?
Kachen!
Anything you need,
just tell me, bro.
Ramphueng won't hear anything
we say in this room.
I'll go over the whole plan just once.
I was hoping you'd have a plan.
Don't fail me,
or every last one of you
will be wiped out tonight.
You don't need to
bear all of this alone anymore.
No, Charn.
Come, Ramphueng.
Let's end this.
Soon, you will see what I can do.
♫ The one who makes my dreams come true, ♫
♫ The one in my heart, baby, it's you ♫
♫ It's you I've been longing for, ♫
♫ The one I've always adored ♫
♫ Right by my side, it's truly you ♫
♫ Clearly, my heart beats just for you ♫
♫ It's you I want, nothing more ♫
♫ From now on, you'll be my all ♫