I'm not embarrassed
Don't hit eight.
That hat is a hit
child
already
All
I don't care
Kai
Kai is okay
Hey Kaikai
What happened?
yeah
Aiya
A little disturbing
picture
That might be it
The rustle of love
sells pure
dissatisfied heart
Isn't it an arrhythmia?
So far
work and play
Looks like you're
busier than ever
As expected, I see it often.
oh dear
It's okay if it's an arrhythmia.
current situation
No matter if I sleep or
wake up, there is no reply.
No pulse
But I'm not disappointed
What are you talking about?
Don't worry about your illness
Hello Kai-kun
picture
Louis
Okay, I'll go right away
I'm sorry, but what
should I do next?
everything is adjustable
As expected
I'm going now
Wait for me
Kai
It seems like I
can't see the stars
Today is
Fuma-san
Ray
Kai is
Where I just slept
Because I have to wake you up
First, let's talk about
the situation here.
Listen, Fuma-san.
Kai
I got lightheaded at school.
Just fall down
In hospital diagnosis
Caused by lack of sleep
and excessive stress
I was told it was a fatal fever.
stress
Member of the school
festival executive committee
Even though it's
already difficult
Doctor who cares
more than anyone else
Because I have a strong
sense of responsibility
It seems like I was
carrying too many things.
Even though I was by your side
I'm of no help
I'm the same too
I still have a fever
to the doctor
You should actually
be hospitalized.
It is said that
picture
But that is
I don't like it because it
makes my parents worry.
To me
Do the committee work
that you cannot do yourself.
I want you to do
something instead.
That's what I say
How friendly are you?
yeah
So this
You can trust me
of course
promise
don't do anything to your friend
Kai
When Fuma-san is talking
It's kind of
interesting, isn't it?
picture
What is that?
I beg him
If I were to play, I
would be so worried.
It's so strange to me
don't go
I'm going to see what's wrong
A lot of sweat
I'm not going, so
let's wipe my body.
Please don't let me go
Are you okay
i am here
I won't let anyone hurt me
I don't want to dream
like that anymore
dream
tell me
Kai
which germany
Are you making
me feel like this?
dad
picture
Why should I laugh?
being mistaken for my father
curse your father
I felt like
Why are you so cute
even though you're sick?
why always
You have eyes asking for help
What I can do
be
yeah
change the sheets
wipe your body
This is my first time caring
for someone this much.
It's my first time
I can swear
No good
I promised Ray
Let's choose
yeah
oh
Did you wake up?
A child who loves seduction
meaningless
picture
I don't remember
You held me all night
I'm like that
How long have you
endured that temptation?
a
committee work
Ray is doing it instead.
I have to rest now
But it's not
Wait a minute
this
present
I don't need it
I want to know
why it's around me
I don't want to know
Sunflowers face the sky
Even if I can't become the sun
Remember when you see sunflowers
The wind always envelops the sky
What I'm watching over
Too sharp
here we go
The stubborn, selfish and
grumpy response is over.
I'll make dinner
Please take your medicine
and go back to sleep.
yeah
Kumonin
lounge air
Temperatures soar this
morning due to low pressure
Be careful of
strong gusts of wind
So today's first song
sunflower
barely half
Don't be too stubborn
I'll be in trouble
if I even fall down.
Yeah
thank you
That's still a huge amount
Until this kind of work
I was trying to
do it all by myself
Kai is having a hard time
Not too spicy
Because you don't say that
I
I wish I realized it sooner
What's in your heart
Sometimes I don't even know
After realizing
Let's do our best to
support each other
Fuma would probably
be doing the same by now.
Fuma-san
I wonder if I'm being
chased out by a monster.
picture
That guy
When it comes to myself
very clumsy
Then why don't we run to Fuma?
I hope you can get through it
Ray
If you are worried about someone
picture
That's right
we are
I got through it just fine
Not yet
Still 1/5
There are more than twice this
amount of materials in the car.
it was
long way to go
but
If you get over it
There's nothing good about it
Let's check it quickly
Thank you for waiting
please
I've never made it for my
younger brother or sister either.
Probably transcendental
Because it's already better
It's time to go home
It’s wider than one night
Use it up and get rid of it.
I was nursing her all night.
As soon as it turns
into a pear, say goodbye
I'm brazen though
my heart is delicate
what do you want
You should know
I won't give it to you
i won't sleep with you anymore
no matter what you do
I can't give you what you want
I see.
Then you don't understand.
I definitely wanted
to sleep with Kai.
But that information is too old
What I want now is
Just don't ignore it
I want you to answer
the phone sometimes
And sometimes reply
Don't run away
even if I see your face
And important things
Please let me woo you
This is all I ask
I'll pull it today
but
Be prepared when you recover
Even if I'm pushed
I'm not interested
Come to think of it
There's some
jelly in the fridge.
Try it out
I don't owe anything
Thank you very much
I won't let you escape this time
you can't catch me
sorry
Because I can rely on Kai
I was pushing too
hard on everything.
I'm a senior
I'm sorry too
You always help me
Kai
Today I'm just sitting
picture
First, rest, second, rapidly.
Let's all go to work
work and work
It's luggage.
That can't be true
Kai's hard work so far
Everyone is moving now
thank you
I'm sure you'll succeed
honey
Sorry, I forgot something.
There's nothing
left behind, right?
It's still a little hot
Okay, rest here.
You came to stop me
For Kai
I won't stop if it's important
but
I want a reward for
coming to pick me up
A cute smile is enough
one
teeth
two
Shah
shoe
Big brother is noisy
Even if I tell you to go
home, you won't go home.
Then sit quietly
wonderful
I understand the
heart of my future lover
yeah
It's a joke
Yeah
Pyun
cold
It only looks like three lines
Why did you write it on my hand?
showed ownership
super figure
What is the
architecture department?
Fuma-san
no matter what is written
your owner is
You're the only one
Even if I do this much
I'm not even a
little embarrassed
At all
I want to change clothes
You can borrow room clothes.
one more time
Have you become a fool?
you are now
I was waiting for a kiss
teeth
sleep on the floor
A servant?
I came here on my own.
I can't help it
sleeping in the same bed
What kind of
relationship is that?
Even after I go to sleep
Don't come up to bed
How untrustworthy is it?
The past is when
I was a playboy.
After sleeping with Kai
I haven't laid my
hands on anyone
I'm not stupid
just once
twice
Understood
I'll tell you the truth
Just three times,
I swear no more
at least
I haven't seen anyone
for the past two months.
Understood
I'll listen this time
This time too
anytime
I'm the one who wins
There's nothing I can do
I have no choice but to lose
good night
what are you watching
palm reading
Look at mine too
love luck
It's rapidly increasing
Seriously
Annoying
that
I have too much time and money
oh dear
Enough to feed Kai
for the rest of his life.
I didn't ask for it
I have to eat
Because I don't
really feel well.
you can do it yourself
this situation
I think my brother would
laugh at me if he saw me
Are you good friends?
I want to know
My younger brother is in
his third year of university.
My sister is one year old
We get along well though
Both of them are strong,
persistent, and pushy.
My brother has a headache
It's me who has a headache
It's exactly like that
The best three brothers?
Kai is your brother
only child
due to parents' divorce
living with my father
lively home
I can't really imagine
Well then
I'll let you meet my
brother next time.
forget the meaning of loneliness
separately
I'm not lonely
I've lived alone
since high school.
Is that so?
Right next to my
relatives' villa school
Commuting to
school is super easy
Tai-kun
that
Stop it
You can smell it
It seems contrived
shellfish
The shellfish is ready.
Fuma-san
It's already disappearing
What should I do?
Fuma-san
Oh no
How to write better
There's more than just practice.
I started painting after taking
university entrance exams.
Huh?
Before that
Living alone at the age of 15
A bad semester where you
can do whatever you want
Looks like this
I was a problem
child in high school
Hey then
That's when I got
my chest pierced.
It was getting pretty close
That's right
sorry
I had an assignment for today.
a little bit
I'll go home first
Better than eating alone
It was delicious today
Thank you for the meal
Hi Kai-kun
It's been a long time
Looks like you're doing well
flower
spark
fire
don't go