I'll use your identity
to pay back the insults to my family
a hundredfold.
Just use this Key of Fate,
go to the home of someone
of the same sex and age as you,
and eat a meal there.
Then you will Exchange Lives
with him.
His wealth,
his power,
and his parents and lover
will all become yours.
Let go!
I'm sorry.
Sheng Yuanzhou!
What did you do to Zhang Xiaobei?
I really did Exchange Lives with him.
Zhang Xiaobei.
Your Sis getting photographed like that
only proves she's stupid.
If she wanted to go from rags to riches,
she had to pay the price.
Sheng Yuanzhou!
You dared to bully my Sis!
I won't let you get away with this!
The moment she took off her clothes,
she should've known
she was nothing but a plaything.
I'm warning you.
Be smart.
Drop this whole thing about your Sis.
Don't ask for trouble.
Throw him out!
Is there any justice left in this world?
You've gone too far!
Let's go, Sis.
Xiaobei.
This is a gift for you.
Sis...
I've already found a new job.
Try it on, hurry.
I...
Okay, okay, okay.
Thanks, Sis.
My new job is being a secretary
for your classmate Sheng Yuanzhou.
Not bad, right?
His family runs a huge corporation.
Sis!
Sheng Yuanzhou!
I won't let you get away with this!
Honey!
Xiaobei! Xiaobei!
Mom!
Honey!
The patient is in critical condition now.
Anything could happen at any moment.
She needs surgery immediately.
How much will the surgery cost?
About 100,000 yuan.
100,000...
Where are you going?
To raise money for your mom.
Where are you going to get the money?
I...
I'll sell my blood, my kidney.
There has to be a way to get the money.
Even if it costs me my life,
I have to save your mom.
Dad...
I'm begging you.
Please stop making things worse for us.
If you hadn't played the futures market,
and opened a restaurant,
would our family be in this mess?
I can't just
stand by and watch your mom die!
Sir...
Xiaobei.
I have money.
Dad, why won't my credit card work?
I froze it.
I thought you had a spine.
I set you up with
such a great marriage with the Shengs,
and you dared reject them to their face.
You insisted on being with that poor boy,
and wanted to use my money to feed trash.
Not a chance.
Without money,
you'll come crawling back sooner or later.
Dad, I...
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
You were helping me in the first place.
About the surgery fee,
don't worry about it anymore.
Don't forget,
I still have
an AI project that's almost finished.
A lot of companies
are already discussing investments with me.
I'll earn the money soon.
Where were you?
I...
I went to an employee's funeral.
Why would you go to a place like that?
I...
To deliver the condolence payment.
She was a company employee, after all.
I was wrong.
Where did you go wrong?
I...
I mishandled Zhang Xiaoyu's situation.
Wrong.
You were wrong to be afraid.
Cowering and hesitating...
How will you ever achieve great things?
If someone like her dies, so what?
That worthless life isn't worth a thing.
Don't waste your energy
on a worthless life like that.
Put away your useless sympathy.
Do what you're supposed to do.
Yes.
Get up.
The AI project you provided recently
is quite impressive.
Did you develop it?
No.
No, I didn't.
Whether you developed it or not,
claim it as your own.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Keep up the good work.
You are my son, after all.
Hello, Mr. Han.
Let me explain it to you in detail again.
Hello, I'm Zhang Xiaobei.
That project I told you about last time...
Hello?
Mr. Xu, didn't you say last time
about the AI project I developed,
that you were really interested?
We...
To be honest with you,
it's not that I'm not interested,
I just don't dare to be.
Prosperity Group's Young Master spoke.
He's taking your project, no matter what.
If anyone dares invest in your project,
they're going against the Sheng family.
Now,
no one dares touch your project anymore.
Prosperity Group, Sheng Yuanzhou.
So please don't make things hard for me.
As a young entrepreneur,
I've always put people first
and actively given back to society.
We have created many jobs
for this city.
I hope
we can live up to our group's name
and bring this city lasting prosperity.
Some people are born
with the wind at their back,
getting whatever they wish for,
and having everything they could want.
But others
struggle like hell
and end up with nothing.
Ma'am.
I don't have any money.
I've only got food.
Here, you can have this to eat.
If you want money,
go ask someone else.
Young man.
If I gave you
a chance to Exchange Lives with someone,
would you take it?
Exchange Lives?
Just use this Key of Fate,
go to the home of someone
of the same sex and age as you,
and eat a meal with this Key of Fate.
and you will Exchange Lives with him.
His wealth and power,
and his parents and lover
will all become yours.
Young Master Sheng, it's our fault.
We'll drag him out right now.
Where'd this filthy beggar come from?
Get the hell out, now!
Don't ruin Young Master Sheng's fun.
Watch your mouth.
He's my college classmate.
He's a true man of talent.
Only Young Master Sheng is a man of wealth.
You're such a money-grubber.
You filthy beggar,
how dare you snatch food?
Mr. Zhang, what took you so long?
We've been waiting forever.
Mr. Zhang,
your outfit today
is so... unique.
Is that this year's trendy distressed look?
Who are you?
Why are you sitting in Mr. Zhang's seat?
Get the hell out, now!
You got the seat all dirty.
Sorry, I... I didn't mean to.
I'm sorry.
Sheng Yuanzhou, look at you now.
This one. Here.
Okay.