"Episode 5"
Good morning.
My darling.
How about we go on
a date after breakfast?
Mhm.
Ever ridden a motorcycle before?
Ever ridden on the back?
No.
Mhm.
So this is your first time?
Hop on.
Arashi, hurry up.
It should suit you.
How is it?
It's cute.
Wait, I mean the shirt.
- Every piece suits Rei, right? - Mhm.
That's what I thought.
Arashi is so cute!
Alright, let's take a picture.
It's weird.
You’re being too nice today.
I just want to spoil you.
I’ll turn into a no good person!
Go ahead.
I’ll whip you back into shape.
Geez!
Rei?
And Arashi-senpai too.
Holding hands.
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love-"
Do you have something to tell me?
Umm...
I...
I’m dating Arashi-senpai!
Yeah, I can see.
Also that you've been in love
with Arashi-senpai for quite a while.
Even when you were hitting on Rinka,
you didn’t seem that serious.
Kai!
Was it hard for you to admit, Rei,
because Arashi-senpai is a guy?
For me,
as long as Rei is happy,
I’m okay with it.
Kai...
I love you!
Look at the person next to you first.
I’m not jealous.
I know Kai is an important friend
to Rei.
But I do have a question
for Rei’s dear friend.
Who’s Rinka?
Fuma, over here.
I finally found you.
He's my boy.
My apologies.
Can we talk for a moment?
Do you know that this is
a dangerous place where outsiders
are not allowed to enter?
Anyone who sneaks in
doesn’t leave unscathed.
What should I do?
Depends on the offer,
but if I get to choose...
You understand, right?
What you need to trade
to get out of here.
Just kidding.
Not everyone could resist
someone as cute as you,
but luckily I can.
Don't come to such a dangerous...
I will do whatever you want.
No kissing.
Tsk.
Why is he here?
Fuma wanted to see Kai.
He told me that on race day,
when you got separated from Rei,
he helped you leave the venue.
At that time,
I was so desperate that
my memory was a little fuzzy.
Let me introduce you again.
Fuma-san is Arashi-senpai’s
best friend and a racer.
And his name is...
Kai, right?
Leaving already?
I’ve fulfilled my obligation.
I have no reason to stay.
Cold, aren’t you?
You were so cute just a moment ago.
At least give me
your contact information.
At least give me your name!
Oh, Fuma-san,
you came to return something
Kai forgot, right?
Ah, yeah. I left it in the car.
Want to come with me to get it?
Rei doesn’t know, does he?
- I’ll be right back. - Mhm.
They seem to get along well.
That face of his...
Did I forget something?
Hey, tell me your phone number.
Don't you like me at all?
Yeah.
If you want to play,
please play with others.
If I wanted to play with someone else,
I wouldn’t be here.
Listen. I have no interest in
playing with you.
No matter how persistent you are,
my answer is no.
Okay, I give up this matter.
I'm glad you understand.
That time was then,
and now is now.
Let's start from the beginning.
I still don't know your birthday
or blood type.
I don't know your favorite food, movies,
and most importantly,
Are you dating someone?
- Do you really want to know? - Yeah.
Ask me when you are born again.
Did you understand?
Did you get that, Kai-kun?
Kai-kun.
I’m going to start courting you now.
Are you mad about Rinka?
No, it's nothing.
Good to hear.
More importantly,
you told your best friend
about our relationship,
I'm glad.
Why?
Did you think I wouldn't tell him?
I wondered if you’d be scared
your friend would see you differently.
I was scared.
Falling for a guy all of a sudden.
But
I was going to tell Kai anyway,
because he is my precious friend.
Give me Kai's phone number!
Everyone’s awful.
Even he is the same.
He’ll just toss me aside
when he gets bored.
You’re listening to Love in the Air.
Everyone, how are you this morning?
Today’s topic is,
‘How to forget someone you want to forget.’
Someone using the name
Heartbreaking Fireworks
says
"If you live earnestly day by day,
you’ll naturally forget."
I see,
Heartbreaking Fireworks
is so devoted to your life.
Next up, someone named
The Canary That Can’t Sing says
"If you want to forget, work"
"Push yourself to the limit
until the pain becomes numb."
Oh dear, that sounds unhealthy.
And finally,
Snowman in Summer's
answer is interesting,
"You don't have to forget."
"The more you try to forget,
the more you remember."
In order to forget someone
you want to forget,
what methods do you have?
(Unknown: How are you?)
Alright, the next agenda item
is the T-shirt design.
That's already decided.
We're going with this.
I came up with it myself.
Isn’t this kind of outdated?
The color scheme is off too.
What’s wrong with it?
Look!
This and this.
100 points.
- You know, right?
- Stop doing this to your juniors.
- You don't understand. Give it a try.
- No way. It's lame.
- You don't understand. - It's so lame.
- This is so good.
- I don't see anything good about it.
- Look at this design. Ever seen it?
- I can't take it.
(Unknown: Let’s meet again)
- Never, right?
- But the color isn't right.
- The color? It looks good.
- Both of you, calm down.
I’ll come up with a compromise
by tomorrow, okay?
How is it lame? "Connection?"
- What's "Connection?" - "Connection?"
"Connection."
Hello.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Huh?
Spare trash bags?
Bottom drawer in the kitchen.
Dad, did you have dinner?
There’s soup in the freezer
from the other day.
Make sure you eat some vegetables too.
Yes. Bye.
Let’s leave it here for tonight.
Why?
Sorry.
I’ll make it up to you next time.
Geez.
You’d better call me.
Got it.
Good morning.
I came here because you
didn't give me a reply.
I knew it was you who
sent me that annoying mail.
Annoying? That’s harsh.
It is annoying.
I’m here because I want
to know more about you.
From this distance, I can’t even
tell the color of your eyes.
What color are they?
Why don't you wear glasses?
That wouldn’t help.
Love makes me blind.
Kai-kun.
I love you.
You okay?
You look pale.
I just didn’t get enough sleep.
I'm off.
- I’m sorry. - Do you know why I’m mad?
Because...
I gave Fuma-san your phone number?
Yeah.
- Can I stand up now? - No.
Sit there until you’ve reflected enough.
I promise to guard your number
with my life from now on!
Nope.
- Don't I look pitiful? - Not at all.
Ugh...
(I’m sending you some care.)
( I’m worried about your
health. Make sure to eat properly.)
(From Fuma)
The determination
of...
wind?
How lame.
Here are your documents.
Hey, do you know what flowers
are popular among young people?
Usually you send roses, right?
Who do you send them to?
These aren't flowers
for business partners.
Then why don't you choose flowers that
fit the image of the recipient?
That's it.
Sexy, fragile,
sometimes mysterious.
But I'd like to send bright flowers.
The kind that makes you smile.
Do you smoke?
No.
Hey, you're being rude to your seniors.
Take a hit.
Isn't that right?
Kurosaki-san!
Hey, greet him properly.
You...
What’s your name?
Kai-kun,
I love you.
I also
love you too, Kurosaki-san.
Kai, what’s wrong?
You look dead.
That...
You already told Kurosaki-san
to stop doing that.
He's unrelated.
I did it to myself.
Hey!
Hold him!
Kurosaki-san!
Help me. I beg you!
Please stop!
Help me!
I beg you!
Kurosaki-san!
You love me, right?
I don't need a boring toy.
Huh?
I’m tired of you.
Help me!
When will I forget?
Someone, please...
Help me.
Why did we come so early in the morning?
And why do I have to be part of it?
Kai?
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
Ah, there you are, Kai!
Can you kick this guy out
of the committee already?
Huh? I just pointed out
an error in the document.
Aren't you embarrassed
to make such a big fuss?
I'm not making a big fuss.
- Yes, you are. - What do you know?
Kai, do something!
Be quiet!
Kai, are you listening?
- Hey. - Who are you talking to?
Ugh.
- Enough. - You're being too loud.
Everything...
I don’t care anymore.
I’m so sorry!
Don't worry about it.
- Hey! - Kai!
- Kai! - Hey, Kai!
- Kai! - Kai, are you okay?
Don't touch him yet.
“Not Just the Rain,
but the Storm Approaches”
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love-"
Kai.
Is it too sweet?
Kai-kun.
Calling him like that might be nice.
Why don't you wear glasses?
Kai.