♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 7=
(It's him.)
(Commander.)
(Wanhua Pavilion.)
(I must follow him inside.)
(The Commander is too upright)
(to visit such a place.)
(It's my chance to shake him off.)
(Wanhua Pavilion)
Mr. Zhang.
We've been waiting.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Upstairs, please.
Alright.
Mr. Wang.
I've missed you so much.
The girls are ready.
Have a great time.
Alright.
Serve our young master well.
Do come again.
Let me keep you company.
I haven't seen you in ages.
Have fun. Drink plenty.
Alright.
Young master, long time no see.
Yunyan.
Entertain the young master.
No problem.
You look new here.
Is this your first visit?
Yeah.
New experience.
Please show me around.
We have the best girls here.
Check out the new ones.
Miss.
Shall we go upstairs?
What's the rush, young master?
The night is short.
Let's not waste it.
Alright.
Young master.
Isn't that
the fortune teller we met
returning from Que City?
Why is he here?
Here.
See?
Isn't she nice?
Bro,
fate led us to meet.
I know some fortune-telling.
Would you like
to get a divination?
Bro.
Have you recently
suffered bloodshed?
Looks like I'm right.
Just a minor injury.
No big deal.
Bro.
That's not right.
Minor injury matters too.
It may cause serious trouble
if left untreated.
For example,
it may hinder your moves in battles.
That
could be fatal.
But don't worry
too much, bro.
Consider yourself lucky.
You met me today.
I have some medicine here.
This elixir
stops the pain and bleeding.
Take this
to strengthen vitality.
Thank you, my friend.
No problem.
Yingxiang.
Farewell.
Sir.
Coming.
Check please.
Five coins in total.
Okay, thanks.
Young master.
Does he really know divination?
I highly doubt it.
He sniffed it out.
Let's go.
He might be
telling fortunes here.
Isn't it nice here?
Look around.
And
look at them.
They're new girls.
Come on.
Let me show you my room.
Miss.
What's that room for?
That room?
That's where dancers practice.
Then they perform
at noble banquets.
Young master.
The night is too short.
Hurry.
Come on.
Wait here.
I'll fetch wine.
Just a moment.
(Dancers?)
(Perform?)
Hurry.
(Good thing I wore this veil.)
(He doesn't recognize me.)
Why hasn't it started yet?
I've waited forever.
When will it start?
I came just to see Miss Sun.
Start already.
Will you start?
Take care, Mr. Zhang.
What should I do?
Miss Sun isn't feeling well.
She hasn't changed yet.
Go on the stage
and buy us some time.
Hurry.
Nice figure.
Are you going to sing?
What are you waiting for?
Dance.
Just dance.
Just a second.
Dance.
Come on, we're waiting.
Start dancing.
The carriage is ready.
Let's go.
(Never mind.)
(Let me get through this first)
(to avoid being caught.)
(Since Ding Yi)
(is disguised as Sun Xiangfu's servant,)
(I'll see what to do)
(in the Sun Mansion.)
Young master.
May I borrow your sword?
Bravo.
Nice!
Sword dance.
Alright!
Isn't that nice?
Bravo!
Bravo.
A woman disguised as a man.
Interesting.
Nice!
(Commander?)
(He actually came in.)
Step down.
Off the stage.
(Oh no.)
(I lost the rhythm.)
Bravo!
Nice!
Thank you for the flower.
A flower
for a beauty.
(It's him.)
Bravo.
(This woman)
(has sheer audacity.)
How was that?
Wasn't it great?
(That was close.)
(I knew)
(Xiao Jue wouldn't)
(recognize me in this attire.)
Mr. Chu.
Long time no see.
Masterful flute work.
Thank you for your praise.
But
I didn't expect to see you here.
What a small world.
This way.
What are you doing?
Let me go.
Hurry. Bring her back.
Hurry.
Bring her back.
Let me go.
Catch her! Hurry.
Bring her back.
Don't let her get away.
Grab her.
Hurry.
Get her back.
Don't let her get away.
Tie her up.
Somebody help.
Young Master Sun's men
will be here shortly.
Do her makeup.
Hurry up.
Drink some more.
It's been a year
since we parted in Yaojing.
Now we met in Yezhou.
The court knows
that Yezhou Garrison faces
supply shortages.
I came
by decree to resolve this matter.
So the inspector they sent
is you.
Thank you for your hard work.
We should thank you
for training
the recruits in Yezhou.
I'm just holding
a nominal position.
Besides,
I don't know anyone in Yezhou
to do my job as the inspector.
I hardly deserve
any praise.
Oh, right.
Have you met Magistrate Sun yet?
My nephew insisted
on touring Yezhou.
So I came a few days earlier.
Could you please
keep it a secret?
What a coincidence.
I also came
a few days earlier
to learn a few things about Yezhou.
No business talks
since we're here for fun.
I've long heard of the snowscapes
of Yezhou Garrison.
Extend your stay and you'll surely
get to see it.
Do visit again.
Upstairs, please.
Leaving so soon, Mr. Wang.
Young master,
don't you like
any of the girls?
You're leaving so soon.
Young master.
(He Yan crosses paths)
(with Chu Zhao.)
(And he's so focused on He Yan.)
(Could it be)
(that they know each other?)
It's getting late.
I have to go.
Presumably,
our next meeting
will be at the Sun Mansion.
Take care.
Let's go.
Sorry, I'm starving.
This isn't my usual manner.
It's fine. Just eat.
Talk over food.
Where were we?
Wedding escape.
Yeah, wedding escape.
My name is Song Taotao.
I ran away from home.
I was passing through Yezhou
when I got abducted.
Thankfully, you saved me.
(Song Taotao?)
He Yan is studying
at Xianchang Academy now.
Nobody has discovered the truth.
Good to know.
He Yan is 15 now.
We must arrange for his marriage
before he reaches 18.
(Marriage?)
(I'm not a man.)
(How do I get married?)
(Once I'm engaged,)
(who will be "He Rufei"?)
The daughter
of the Chief Imperial Physician,
Song Taotao.
She seems like a perfect match
for He Yan.
We can form a marital alliance.
(I will never)
(get engaged to Miss Song.)
(Not only that,)
(I will never)
(marry any woman,)
(so as not to ruin her life.)
(Isn't she the one who almost)
(became my fiancée?)
(Fate truly connects us.)
Why are you looking at me like that?
It's nothing.
So, who abducted you?
I don't know.
I ran into him the moment I arrived.
His lackeys called him
Young Master Sun.
He called me pretty,
asked me to be his mistress,
and tried to assault me.
So I stabbed his arm
with my hairpin.
You may look frail,
but you have a fiery temper.
But I didn't expect
that I couldn't
get rid of them.
I could have run away
if I had been careful.
It sounds like you know
how to defend yourself.
What are those?
This is datura
for sedation and anesthesia.
This is arisaema
for calming convulsions.
This withered flower
is rhododendron molle
for blood circulation and pain relief.
These sliced pieces
are aconite.
- They dispel cold and relieve pain.
- Wait.
All these herbs
are poisonous, right?
Yeah.
Maybe
they'll come in handy later.
Not really. Put them away.
Anyway,
this "Young Master Sun"
could be the son of Yezhou Magistrate
Sun Xiangfu.
That complicates things.
Sir,
I'm Song Taotao.
I'll repay
your kindness
when I return to Yaojing.
Hero,
what's your name?
I'm flattered.
My name...
My name is Cheng...
Hurry.
They just won't leave us alone.
I underestimated them.
You're from the capital
and don't sound local.
They must have guessed
we'd come to an inn.
Forget it.
We're on their turf, after all.
Stay here.
I'll handle it.
In that case,
it's kind of my turf, too.
I'm quite capable.
You're not local, either.
Helping me may get you
into serious trouble.
Others didn't dare help me.
Why are you helping me?
Because
you're a woman.
(And so am I.)
Hurry up.
Move.
Go.
And you.
Move.
Hurry.
Out.
Move.
Go.
(Sun Ling, son of Sun Xiangfu)
Out.
Stop dawdling.
Faster.
Get going.
Go.
Hurry up.
Why is that door
closed?
Let's check it.
Let's go.
Open the door.
Open up.
Coming.
Hurry up.
It's so late. What's going on?
Step aside.
Search thoroughly.
Young master.
Put this on.
It's chilly.
Search carefully.
Mr. Sun.
She's not here.
It's so late.
Who said you could
just barge into my room?
This is ridiculous.
Do I need permission
to go anywhere
in Yezhou?
Keep your eyes sharp.
Inspect them.
Understood.
Looking similar.
What's your name?
Cheng Lisu.
Raise your head.
Hey, you.
Sir.
Don't cross the line.
So it turns out
that the assassin who abducted
my concubine
is you.
Guards.
Arrest
both of them.
Understood.
It's fine.
Move.
Mr. Sun.
I suggest you
think twice before arresting me.
Do you know
who my uncle is?
- Who's your uncle?
My uncle
is appointed by His Majesty
as General Fengyun
and Right Army Commander.
Xiao Jue.
How about that?
Still arresting me?
Did you hear that?
Who's his uncle again?
You brat.
If Xiao Jue is your uncle,
get him here.
He's your uncle. So what?
So ridiculous.
Today I'll make you beg
for death
in front of him.
Really?
Try your luck.
See?
That's my uncle.
Let go.
Huaijin.
Come on, who are you?
Didn't you hear?
Has General Fengyun
arrived?
We haven't heard.
How dare you fool
falsely claim official titles?
You
abducted my family member.
You're courting death.
Ouch.
It hurts.
Ling.
Father.
Who did this to you?
(Sun Xiangfu, Yezhou Magistrate)
Guards. He...
Young master.
Commander?
Commander.
I failed to welcome you
properly.
I beg for your forgiveness.
Why is Magistrate Sun
begging for forgiveness?
Your son was quite domineering
upstairs earlier.
First, he tried to abduct my servant,
then he threatened to kill me.
He even said
he'd make me beg for death
in front of my uncle.
W-What...
You're begging for forgiveness?
Seriously.
We're terrified.
Right?
Uncle?
Commander,
I failed to discipline my son.
He didn't know who you were
and offended you
and...
Cheng.
Mr. Cheng.
I sincerely...
I-I...
Come here.
Get over here.
Lower.
Father.
He hit me.
He hit you?
You should avenge me.
Avenge you?
I'll beat you to death.
You're asking for this.
Why are you hitting me?
You want me
to avenge you?
I don't even know
if I'll survive this.
Avenge you?
How about this?
I will
break my son's legs
as an apology.
What do you think?
My mother has aged.
And this is
my only son.
If he dies,
our family line ends with me.
Please
punish me instead
and spare my son.
Please.
Mr. Sun.
Your son doesn't have to recognize me.
But the inspector is on his way here.
If your son
mistakes the inspector
for an impostor,
then he may
have to die for it.
It won't happen.
I assure you.
Thank you, Commander.
Get up.
Let's go.
Come back.
Where are you going?
This way.
Let's go.
Faster.
Get moving.
Hurry.
We're off.
Sun Ling was abusing his power.
What a disgrace.
If I hadn't...
Anyway,
I ran into Miss Song on the street
and brought her here.
I did this to promote
your reputation
as a people's hero, Commander.
I don't need that.
I think
we should take Miss Song
with us.
If she stays in Yezhou,
Sun Ling will surely retaliate.
You rescued her.
You'll handle it.
Mr. Xiao.
I'm Song Taotao.
Miss Song.
You know each other?
I'm engaged
to Mr. Xiao...
What?
Mr. Xiao's nephew.
Miss Song,
don't leave sentences half-finished.
Wait.
Commander.
How many nephews do you have?
Wedding escape.
Engagement.
Y-You're...
You're Cheng Lisu's...
I'm Cheng Lisu's so-called
fiancée.
(I joined the army)
(to escape marriage.)
(Then Song Taotao)
(got engaged to Cheng Lisu.)
(Both of them fled.)
(How strange is fate.)
(It's a cycle.)
Mr. Xiao,
can you take me
to Yezhou Garrison?
I won't cause any trouble.
Are you sure about that?
Your fiancé
is right there.
I'm looking for him.
You've been
impersonating Cheng Lisu, right?
The real Cheng Lisu
couldn't fight at all.
I bet it's hard
to impersonate him.
In that case,
stay with us for now.
You saved Miss Song.
You'll handle it.
Me?
She's your nephew's fiancée.
That's not true.
You heard her.
I lost my luggage and money
because of
those hooligans.
Could you
front my room payment?
I'll repay double...
No.
Tenfold.
(Sun Mansion)
Why did you have to provoke
the living God of Death?
Come on.
He's just a military officer.
Father, why are you so timid?
"Just a military officer"?
When he followed
Xiao Zhongwu west,
he dared to behead the eldest son
of the censor.
Minister Xu
brought this case
to His Majesty.
And what happened?
Minister Xu had to swallow his losses.
If he actually kills you,
what do you think
I could do?
Absolutely nothing.
He...
He's that powerful?
Then,
what should we do?
Take it easy.
I've had a trap ready for a long time,
waiting to spring it.
Don't worry, son.
I'll make sure
you're avenged.
Father,
I know you're the best.
But for now,
keep your head down.
Get rid of
the stuff
you buried.
This box.
I'll take some too.
Cheng Lisu and I
never got along.
But my father,
who's Cheng Lusu's master,
suddenly got a wild idea
of getting us married.
His family actually approved.
I was planning to run away.
But he actually
beat me to it.
It's a total
humiliation.
So, I came here
to get him home
and cancel the engagement.
You don't like Mr. Cheng?
I think he's quite admirable.
Good-looking,
well-born,
and a brilliant doctor.
I bet he has
many admirers
in Yaojing.
In medicine,
the heart guides,
the hands follow.
But look at him.
Instead of helping people,
he's buttering up
the imperial consorts and princesses.
So spineless.
I despise him.
You're much better.
Well...
It's not a fair comparison.
Candies.
Is this osmanthus-flavored?
Yeah.
That's right.
Even blind,
aim to be
the most special of all.
This osmanthus candy
is the last piece left in the world.
Though inedible now,
it remains sweet.
I won't know
until I taste it.
Though
bitter at first taste,
its core holds
enduring sweetness.
Have it.
I once had
an osmanthus candy.
Not so sweet.
Even a bit bitter.
But it was the best
osmanthus candy in the world.
Someone also
loves osmanthus candies.
One packet please.
Alright.
Is it
for me?
Want some?
Buy your own.
This is a gift.
There you go.
It's ready.
Keep the change.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Another girl's gone missing.
It keeps happening
over these years.
They're nowhere to be found.
It's tragic.
They say that
Young Master Sun
abducts pretty girls every now and then.
Nobody reported it?
His father
is the Magistrate.
Actually,
once an eyewitness
and the victim's family reported it.
But both of them
were beaten half to death
and thrown out.
After that,
nobody dared step forward.
The other girls
weren't as lucky as you.
Don't worry.
I'll protect you.
I know
you'll always look out for me.
Let's go.
Can't anyone do something
about Young Master Sun?
Commander.
I was thinking about you while shopping
with Miss Song.
I bought you osmanthus candies.
Try some.
Take them away.
Why?
They're really sweet.
I don't eat sweets.
But you clearly...
I clearly what?
Putting loaches in my shoes.
These candies got dirty.
Don't eat those.
Should I buy you new ones?
No need. Go to class.
You're just
looking down on my cheap gifts.
Fine,
keep them for Mr. Feinu.
He won't eat them, either.
You...
Commander.
The inspector made his appearance.
So, Sun Xiangfu
will invite us to his mansion today.
Get ready.
We're going today?
He's invited us.
The inspector
will likely be there too.
Commander.
Are you worried about me?
Stop talking
and think about
how to maintain your cover.
Cheng Lisu is
a renowned noble in Yaojing.
And you...
In Yaojing,
someone like me
could at least
rival Mr. Cheng, if not stand equal
to you.
Otherwise,
why did Miss Song
only remind me to be careful,
and not you?
(Sun Mansion)
What an honor to have you here.
My warmest welcome.
This is the inspector,
Mr. Chu Zhao.
Commander Xiao.
Long time no see.
Mr. Chu.
(It's him?)
(He's the inspector?)
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪