( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
STILL SHINING
You two must have looked
inside the test room.
Did it have a clock?
It didn't.
I'm sure they'll tell you the time,
but just in case,
make sure you two bring watches.
I'll pick you up at 7:00 a.m. tomorrow,
so come to the bus stop.
-Don't be late.
-Okay.
Go to bed early,
make sure you eat breakfast,
and don't forget your packed lunch.
And your exam ID slip. That's crucial.
-Yes, sir.
-Okay.
-Get a good night's sleep.
Hello?
Well, that…
You mean the paperwork?
Let's meet at 6:50 a.m. tomorrow.
If you go in the room…
The second drawer on the right.
Okay. Sleep tight.
It's there? I told you.
Okay, I got it.
Okay, bye.
You didn't have to wait outside.
Hello, Mr. Mu.
You've gone above and beyond to help
right up until the day before the exam.
-We're really grateful.
-Not at all.
It's my pleasure.
Sir, Tae-seo needs a wristwatch,
but mine's digital.
Do you have an analog one?
This one's over 40 years old.
It's fine as long as it works.
Is that so?
Give me your hand.
Put it on now,
so you don't forget.
You two did a great job looking after him.
You did far more for him.
Did you sleep well?
Yeah, better than I thought I would.
I thought I'd be too nervous to sleep.
I think knowing you'd be taking
the exam in the next room
made me feel at ease.
Did you wait long? You must've been cold.
I'm hot.
My dad said it's always cold
in Korea on exam day.
I want to wear it.
Like this?
No.
Wrap it round and around,
and then tie it.
My goal is to get into a school
as close to you as possible.
If I can't get into one in Seoul,
then at least one nearby.
Please let us both
achieve our goals today.
I think
this will help me do well.
Give me something too.
Anything of yours.
I have something.
YEONWOO HIGH SCHOOL
YEON TAE-SEO
My lucky charm.
EXAM ROOM 6
STILL SHINING
The exam's over!
Am I the only happy one?
It's over!
Tae-seo, let's go see the Hangang River.
We've seen the ocean,
so we need to go there.
But the time…
Come on. We can make it.
One second.
I only have 7,000 won.
Let's go next time.
I didn't use my allowance
since I was studying with you.
You helped me save it,
so I should spend it with you.
Come on, let's take the train.
Not the train.
Let's see the river
from Dongseoul Bus Terminal.
Can you see it from there?
Yeah, the Hangang River is close
to Gangbyeon Station.
We'll see the river,
leave from Gangbyeon Station,
take the last train from Cheongnyangni,
and arrive early tomorrow morning.
Why are we taking the train back?
The train takes around six hours…
so we can be together for longer.
Genius.
What can we do with 7,000 won?
Buy me noodles from a tent bar.
My dad said the noodles
in Seoul tent bars are really good.
Okay.
-Want to go there?
-Okay.
Here are your noodles.
-Thank you.
It's familiar, but it's delicious.
I love noodles.
And every time, my dad would say
that when my mom was pregnant with me,
she'd always crave these noodles.
I'd always wondered what they tasted like.
I know.
I'm always talking
about my mom when I come to Seoul.
I don't miss her though.
Does she live here?
No, she lives abroad.
But I don't know where.
I never asked.
I'm sure she's doing well somewhere.
Somewhere that has nothing to do with me.
We can take the subway
at 10:00 p.m., so don't rush.
What about the Hangang River?
You can see it from the station.
Not from the station.
I want to see it up close.
We better eat quickly.
The Hangang River's right in front of me.
This is my first time.
Me too.
-Let's get a bit closer.
-Wait.
You're…
going to be cold.
Wrap it round…
and around,
and then tie it.
What about you? Aren't you cold?
I can…
just wear this.
It's a historic day.
I saw both the ocean
and the Hangang River.
I have to remember this day.
Yeon Tae-seo.
I just found my dream.
Living on my own.
Living away from my dad.
This counts as a dream
because it's only possible
if my dad gets better.
If he's not doing well,
I can't even consider it.
My dream is for my dad to get well
so I can become independent.
How about you?
Me?
Mine is…
If yours is independence,
mine is self-reliance.
I don't have a "from."
That's really amazing.
What do you mean?
Because I know
you'll achieve that like it's nothing.
From what I've seen,
you're good at doing things on your own.
-I am?
-Yeah.
I don't like doing things by myself,
but you're really good at it.
I've never seen you hang out with people.
You're fine on your own.
It's kind of amazing.
Then again,
I bet things will be different
when you go to college.
I wonder what else will change about you.
I doubt anything will change.
Want to go a bit further?
Yeah. Do we have time?
No, we don't.
Let's go.
We have to go.
Come on, we'll be late.
We walked way too far to see the river.
Hold on.
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
I burned off all the noodles.
Come on, we're late.
Let's go.
Run.
This morning at the bus stop,
I was watching you arrive.
Where we'll be,
what we'll be doing,
and with whom.
I wondered which of these three
would be decided by today's exam.
Then,
could this be the last time
we're headed
in the same direction?
It's not certain yet,
but things will change
when we're at different schools, right?
No.
Distance only mattered
when text messages didn't exist.
If we can still send texts,
no place is too far.
We can text from anywhere.
Exactly.
Texting works everywhere.
Even Yeonwoo has great service.
Would texting not work somewhere
really remote in another country?
Unless we're in different worlds,
we can still text.
Different worlds…
That's my mom and me.
Same.
There's something that only applies to us.
Because it's you and me.
You and I are going to try really hard
to spend time together.
We'll make every effort.
You like me that much?
Of course.
If I hadn't been this sure,
I wouldn't have even tried.
Even when I had…
no room in my life to like someone,
these feelings still grew.
I want to be with you.
-Shall we?
-Yeah.
Shall we?
Where should I go?
Over there?
Your room is nice.
Yeah.
Let me…
I can do it.
Hold on.
Sorry.
Eun-a, are you home?
Is that your dad?
Eun-a.
Yeah, Dad!
I'm home.
I'm going to wash up and go to bed.
Are you going to school tomorrow?
I have to, but I can go late.
Good night, Dad.
Okay, well done today.
Get some rest.
I'm proud of you, my girl.
Thanks.
Is he gone?
No.
Actually, I have a huge secret.
I was too embarrassed to tell you.
I was so hot I thought I'd die.
I kept thinking about my thermals
as I took off my coat.
It wasn't even that cold today,
but my dad insisted.
This is so embarrassing.
Why did it have to be floral?
What?
I think it's cute.
You've always done well,
so let's just figure out where to go.
Go think about it.
Okay. Thank you.
Off you go.
My gosh.
Mo Eun-a, well done. You did a good job.
Thank you.
You did really well considering
you only started studying half a year ago.
Really.
If you'd started a year earlier,
we could've tried
the regional admissions track.
It's a shame.
Now, let's see.
DECEMBER
DEPARTMENT OF MECHANICAL ENGINEERING
YOUR APPLICATION HAS BEEN SUBMITTED
All done.
I feel so glad
to have it submitted quickly.
The results come out on February 4th, so…
Just kick back and relax.
Yeah, it's beautiful.
Eun-a.
Merry early Christmas.
The guests are here.
Yeah, I'm all done.
Thanks to your help,
I'm officially on the concierge team now.
Thank you so much.
I heard you specifically asked
to work with only me.
Because you're good.
I think having to deal with
a different person each time
bothers Seon-gyu a bit.
He seemed to struggle with it.
So it's a win-win.
You haven't had dinner yet, right?
You eat this one,
and please take the other one to Eun-a.
Whenever the guests are here,
she never comes out of her room.
How did you feel when you submitted it?
Mr. Mu did it for me.
He clicked the "Submit" button too.
He clicked it for you?
I didn't ask him to,
but it was just easier for him to do it.
I'd be too nervous to click it myself.
Do adults always have to deal
with stressful things like this?
Why am I always so nervous and scared?
MY APPLICATIONS
If you're done, I'll click it now.
I'm going to submit it.
Mr. Mu, wait.
-No, you've done more than enough.
-Please just wait.
-I can't wait anymore.
-Wait, hold on!
It's Christmas today.
Can I just pray one time?
I should get up to do it.
It's okay. Just pray.
-This gave me a bad feeling.
-Go on, just pray.
Hopefully, we can make it home today.
Dear Santa,
I really want to go to college.
JANUARY
Oh, my god!
Why are you hiding in the corner?
It's so dark.
-You should've turned the lights on.
-No…
I'm fine.
Please come over here.
One thing's for sure.
We always have plenty to eat at our house.
Enjoy your meal.
We need the one you just swiped tonight,
so take any of these instead.
Okay.
Happy New Year.
My first day as a 20-year-old
with Yeon Tae-seo.
We don't have any glasses.
It's sweet.
It's pretty tasty.
It's not alcohol.
It is alcohol.
Let's go.
Eun-a!
Be quiet.
FEBRUARY
All right, shall we toast?
Congratulations.
He made it to Hanguk National University
from this tiny village. Congratulations.
You're too kind.
It's all thanks to Mr. Mu here.
I didn't do much.
He achieved it all on his own.
So did Mr. Mo's daughter not get in?
No, she's still waiting.
There's a first round of results,
then a second, and even a third.
The results come out in batches.
So it's a little complicated.
Gosh, you didn't have to.
Have some of this, Mr. Mu.
-Congratulations.
-Great job.
Thank you.
So, Mr. Mu.
Explain it properly so I can understand.
Well, there is
an additional enrollment period,
and the results don't finish
coming out until late February.
What on earth does that mean?
It must be killing Eun-a
to wait for the results.
Right.
This is my first time.
On the Sea Train?
THIS IS THE SEA TRAIN
It only runs during the day
and follows the coastline.
It takes an hour and 40 minutes
from Gangneung to Samcheok,
so if we go there and come back…
We can be together
for around three and a half hours.
Yeah.
When I was little,
my mom worked here for a bit.
I wanted to become
a Sea Train driver back then.
I guess it looked kind of cool.
That's nice.
What did you want to tell me
all the way out here?
I have to go to Seoul soon.
When I was living in Seoul,
I had a friend called Hyeong-seok.
And his dad runs a study center.
He let me use it for free
and helped me out a lot.
He asked if I could do
some tutoring starting in February.
I'd been putting it off,
but I think I really have to go now.
Right.
You should go.
And your entrance ceremony?
Is Hui-seo joining you later?
He can't go.
He can't do long journeys yet.
He must be upset.
Do you have a place to stay?
Yeah, the study center office has a bed.
How can you sleep in an office?
That's so sad.
That's nothing.
You must be more sad
waiting for your results.
Me? Well…
One of the three schools I applied to
is at least close to you,
but my chances of getting in are low.
One is halfway between
here and Seoul, but it's not certain.
The last one is in Gangneung.
Mr. Mu said it's a good school,
and the program is good there.
But…
it's really far from you.
Having to wait for over a month
is making me anxious and uncertain.
It's been dragging on for so long
that I can't believe
February is already ending.
It feels endless.
It's definitely going to end.
I hope so.
An end that really feels like one.
I hope it's a clean end.
Wait.
This isn't much, but take it.
I'm fine. I have money.
Buy yourself something to wear.
Your grandma seemed to feel bad
we couldn't buy you something to wear
to your entrance ceremony.
We can't afford to buy you a suit,
but at least buy yourself a coat.
Something that's nice and formal.
You'll need to dress up
quite often while in the city.
Here. Buy one for yourself.
Thank you.
From scholarships to tutoring,
you're doing everything on your own.
We feel terrible.
I'll visit often.
There's no need. You should be studying.
You'll only waste money.
Just make sure you call Hui-seo.
I thought he'd be grumpy
about missing your entrance ceremony,
but he's been quiet.
At least the ceremony doesn't fall
on the same day as your parents' memorial.
It's the first one.
I'll go pay my respects.
Stay at home with Hui-seo.
All right.
Go on, then.
Okay.
WAITING AREA (TICKETS)
Are you taking the express bus to Seoul?
Eun-a.
I was waiting right here.
I thought you'd be taking the train.
I'm such a klutz.
I just…
I know you told me not to,
but I'd feel bad if I didn't see you off.
I'll take you there.
I bought two tickets, so we can just go.
Don't be ridiculous.
How can you make me let you go home alone?
You can let it happen today.
Seriously, it's fine.
Let's get off at the next stop.
I can't bear to watch you go back alone.
I'll take you home and…
So you can go alone, but I can't?
That's nonsense. It's fine.
It's already been an hour.
We don't have time.
How long are you going to keep this up?
LOG IN
PLAYLIST
This is my account.
If I'm using it, it'll say,
"Currently streaming."
We can use it together.
We'll listen to it at the same time.
Then,
it'll feel like we're together.
It'll feel like we're together.
Feeling like we're together
counts as being together.
I like that.
What else is there
to make us feel together?
Sharing the photos we take?
Let's take one now.
Smile.
Sir, how long will it take?
One hour.
What?
You should go.
Let's part here. It's your first lesson.
Eun-a.
This is a lot
harder than I expected.
I can't do it.
I can.
Come on, I can't let you go back alone.
You can. Just like this.
I might end up at a college near you,
or I might not.
I don't know what will happen.
My life is always so uncertain.
Anyway, we'll have to keep doing this,
but if you feel bad or guilty,
it'll be hard to see each other.
This is driving me crazy.
I'll…
I'll do my best for us.
Okay.
Oh, my god.
What?
What is it?
I got in.
What?
GANGNEUNG WONKYEONG UNIVERSITY
No way! I got in!
See? I got in because I was with you!
Oh, my god. But it's a bit far from you.
That's not what matters right now!
Congratulations!
-You really earned this.
-Oh, my god. I'm so happy.
MARCH
-It's nice.
-Nice and clean.
You must be his roommate.
I hope you two get along well.
-The bed here's so soft.
-Sweetie, don't sit there.
Why not? Come try it too, Mom.
This is nice.
Hui-seo…
I'll bring him over when he's a bit older.
Don't worry about him.
And don't worry about Grandma and Grandpa.
I'll take care of everyone.
I almost forgot.
I'm attending the college
you wanted me to go to, Mom.
You would've been so happy
to see me there.
Mom.
Dad.
Can I sit here?
Sure.
I'm Park Na-ri.
I'm Mo Eun-a.
Hey, your student number
is right after mine.
What a coincidence.
I'm from Seoul. You?
I live nearby. Twenty minutes by bus.
-Twenty minutes?
-Yeah.
No way! We have the same elective too?
No way! Come sit here.
What's that?
-Want to pick one?
-They're so cute.
-This one.
-Sure.
-Here.
-Thanks.
This class is called
Creative Engineering Design.
This class will give you the opportunity
to reflect on what lies
beyond the machines.
Great machines are made
when you understand
both their function and value.
What you need for this class
is your mathematical ability
and a brain that's capable of thinking.
The rest you will learn
in this class today.
Did you always want to study
early childhood education?
Yeah, because I like kids.
But teaching's not really for me.
It's not what I expected.
I picked this place for the major,
but now, I'm not so sure.
But it's so nice to see the ocean.
This was worth skipping class.
I know.
I heard the vending machine coffee
was good here.
SORI MARKET
-Want to go?
-Let's go.
We're already really close.
I'm exploring Gangneung thanks to her.
I'll take you around
the next time you're here.
Okay.
I have matching stickers with Na-ri,
but I don't have
anything matching with you.
What do you want to do?
I have a great idea.
What if I make stickers with my drawings?
The same vegetable stickers
for our different classes.
Tell me your classes.
I'll draw something for each one.
I'm really good.
Engineering Mathematics.
Kidney beans.
It's extremely hard to pick them out.
They're hard to pick out? Then…
APRIL
-Kim Na-rae.
-Here.
Kim Ji-ho.
Ji-ho?
-Mo Eun-a.
-Here.
Park Na-ri.
Right, Na-ri took a leave of absence.
It's only been a month,
and someone's already taking time off.
-Park Seo-yeon.
-Here.
-Song A-yeong.
PLAYLIST
TAE-SEO
Have the flowers bloomed in Seoul yet?
It's crazy here.
Send me a photo
of the flowers at your school too.
And a selfie of you in front of them too.
I miss you, Tae-seo.
-Hello.
I'll go to school after tutoring
and send it to you.
His tutoring session usually takes
about two hours, so…
Call me when you're done tutoring, okay?
What time do you finish?
WHAT TIME DO YOU FINISH?
I have two tutoring sessions today,
so if I go straight to school after,
it should be around 10:00 p.m.
One ticket to Gangneung, please.
Gangneung?
That'll be 10,600 won.
Dad.
You never ask me to pick you up.
I didn't want to go alone.
Are we going out for a night stroll?
Where should we go? Let's go for sashimi.
I'm tired.
What should we eat?
Is there something you'd like to eat?
I'm up for anything.
Should we ask Eun-a?
Eun-a, is there anything you want to eat?
Eun-a, are you asleep?
She must be really tired.
Just let her sleep.
But we haven't gone out
together in forever.
It'd be nice if we could talk while we go.
I had no idea they'd bloomed so much.
Should I call you?
Is everything okay?
I was just wandering and thought of you.
I can leave in the morning this weekend.
Let's meet up early.
I want to go to Seoul.
It's my turn to go.
I'll come to you.
No, I'll go to you.
Spend your time on yourself.
Don't waste it.
Hello, Hyeong-seok? Yeah.
Your time is precious too.
I'll go to you.
My time right now is just passing by,
but yours is time you need to use
toward your goals.
They're different.
No more dark photos.
I miss you, Tae-seo.
A lot.
This is nice.
Did you miss me?
Of course.
MAY
Every time I take out a cigarette,
you appear.
It's almost scary.
It's fun working at a hotel, isn't it?
I feel good
whenever I see the hotel staff.
Then, try it out.
A lot of local young people
work part-time at our hotel.
Taking time off from school?
What would I be taking time off for?
I don't want to try things out
without a goal
just because everyone else is.
So annoying.
I mean, I know you're in college,
but it's not even vacation time
and you're not at school.
You've been here all day today
and riding your bike the past two days.
You're the first one to ask.
I skipped school all week and slacked off,
but no one's ever asked.
No one from school reached out.
And my dad didn't ask why I wasn't going.
I guess no one really cares.
Thanks for asking.
I'm not going to school
because I don't feel like going.
If you're going to
do college half-heartedly,
you might as well take time off
and try something else.
Don't you want to be independent?
In your current situation,
I doubt your dad would notice
you're not going to school.
If I were you,
I'd be thinking about moving out.
That came out of nowhere. What situation?
Just go pick up your guests.
It was a lunch reservation,
but it'll be dinner time soon.
So-hyeon made
a surprise announcement today.
I can't really ruin the mood.
Announcement?
-You two look great together.
-I'm so happy for you.
Congratulations.
-Congratulations.
-I'll bring out some more wine.
-All right.
Cheers.
You're here just in time.
Your dad announced
they're getting married.
You should congratulate them.
What about the Unit 610 guy?
It took you long enough to ask.
I'll end things with him.
You're only ending it now?
Seon-gyu knows everything.
He said he'd tell me
once he figured things out,
so I hadn't been able to end things.
Eun-a.
Love doesn't happen in perfect order.
No wonder why
you always have a guy around.
There's never a break with you.
-Watch what you say.
-You watch it.
How dare you two-time my dad?
Seon-gyu is the one I have feelings for.
The one in Unit 610 knows that too.
I've never deceived or misled anyone.
So you're saying you'll live
however you want
and everyone else
has to just deal with it?
And my dad just accepted that nonsense?
What do you take my dad for?
He's a good person, but someone like you…
This is the last time.
I'll let your insults slide today,
but after this,
not a chance.
Mo Eun-a.
Mo Eun-a!
Let go.
You should congratulate them.
You're startling our guests.
Take this and go back inside.
You're so damn good at your job.
Aren't you a little old to be so worked up
over your dad's relationship?
You should focus on your own life.
I'll try to find you a job.
I can't promise it'll help though.
It tends to stop or flip over
on steep inclines.
Could the weight distribution be off?
How about switching to a two-wheel design?
Are you busy?
I'm in my professor's lab.
It's only for grad students,
but the TA let me in,
so it's my first time here.
It's pretty cool.
You sound busy. What time do you finish?
What is it? If it's urgent,
I can call you right now.
You should be majoring in flattery.
Honestly. We'll continue this in a bit.
-Never mind. I'll catch you later.
-Yes, Professor.
The professor likes supreme pizza.
-Could I go use the restroom?
-Yeah, sure.
Professor, please have some.
Did you know?
Apparently, you can see Namsan
from anywhere in Seoul.
So from now on, your name is Namsan.
Yeon Namsan.
I guess I'm still stuck in uncertainty.
Where are you?
The wetlands.
No. I'm actually at the bus stop now.
TAE-SEO
You're in Seoul, right?
While I was wandering,
I was going to buy some makeup
and get a bowl of noodles.
You have important things going on.
Don't waste your time.
I have plenty of time,
so I'll drop by again.
Don't be ridiculous.
Nothing matters more
than us being together.
Tae-seo, I really want to see you.
I'm on my way.
You don't know where I am.
Hang on.
I have one more stop.
I'm almost there.
GANGBYEON STATION
I can hear Yeon Tae-seo coming.
I'm done wandering.
STILL SHINING
You were really going through it
before you did your military duty.
I hate goodbyes.
For 10 years, I'd forgotten.
They were gone.
Eun-a…
You haven't heard from her, have you?
Let's stop…
with the worries and everything else.
I thought of you.
I had hoped to see you at least once.
Subtitle translation by: Hyesoo Lee