(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
STILL SHINING
IN MOURNING
MO SEON-GYU
JULY 2016
Back when all I had to give
was my heart…
IM A-SOL, IM JI-SOL, KIM EUN-SU,
KIM A-RA, LEE CHAE-WON
MAEUM STUDY CENTER
The desperate wish
to convey how I felt any way I could.
Yeon Tae-seo!
Here.
Did my feelings
reach them properly?
STILL SHINING
STAY YOUNGWON
Where are you?
Get away from there, Tae-seo.
So where are you?
Where is your exact location?
That guy already left.
He's gone, so stop worrying.
Who says I'm worried?
What are you doing here at this hour?
What about you? Who's that girl?
You came all the way
from Gangneung together,
casually swapped drivers,
and then just went your separate ways.
What kind of relationship is it
to be so casual?
That's nice of her.
You two must've talked a lot
on the way here.
It really was nice of her,
but don't offer
to buy her a meal to repay her.
Did you end up meeting him?
No.
Did you see Park So-hyeon?
She just turned up yesterday
and said she'd take care of
my Tongyeong problem.
But when I went to her room at dawn,
I heard Seong-chan's voice
and rushed out in surprise.
And in the middle of all that,
I saw you get out of that woman's car
and wondered who she was
and what's going on.
That's all.
I don't know what those two are up to.
As long as you didn't run into him,
it's fine.
Your expression says otherwise.
The surgery was yesterday,
so it's been a day now, right?
Tomorrow will be the second day.
So she'll wake up tomorrow.
It'll take two or three days.
Grandpa, I'm here.
I see. You came.
By the way, I spoke to A-sol.
I told her to get a meal out of you,
but she wants something else.
Like what?
I'm sure she'll tell you herself.
You should eat before you go.
I'll prepare the food.
Do you know how?
Yes.
The house feels empty.
YEON CHANG-SIK
Grandpa.
I think I'll have to make the rice again.
CALLS
EUN-A
Visiting hours are open now.
Let's shoot the inserts first.
Have the cameras set up in the yard.
-And then, check the actors' blocking.
-Yes, sir.
The restroom's at the end
of the hallway on the right.
Hello, sir.
Yes, they're here.
They know this place better than I do.
There's not much for me to help them with.
Then I'll head out early today.
This is the revised contract. Take a look.
You need to check everything,
so get down here now.
Now we can finally rest easy.
Yeah, it's the second floor.
I'll be waiting outside.
Okay, I'm almost there.
This way.
I mean, does this dead wood
produce oil or something?
It just doesn't make any sense.
I followed what I saw online.
I sanded it, oiled it, and did everything.
It's been over a year,
but the oil's still coming out.
It won't dry.
It'll have to be sanded again.
Is this desk being used?
It's my dad's.
What do I need to get ready?
Nothing.
Are you done checking?
Yeah.
Let's grab a bite downstairs.
I haven't eaten yet today.
Must be tough going back and forth
to the hospital while working.
I used my vacation days
to free up time next week.
When do you need it done by?
He says he'll come back
to work next month,
but it's always "next month."
When I see him in March, he says April.
When it's November, he says December.
He's with my mom
at my sister's house in Gapyeong.
He has lung cancer.
But he's holding up quite well.
I think he'll keep living there.
I'm saying you can take your time.
Seriously, taking your brother
to Gangneung wasn't any trouble at all.
I quit my job working for a good company
in their tax department.
Then, I took on my dad's work to help him,
only to get swamped.
Now my dad says he's found a new life
and settled in Gapyeong with my mom.
I'm the only one left at home,
and I was thinking, "What am I doing?"
Then, I ended up seeing the ocean.
It wasn't planned,
and it was only for a brief moment,
but it still washed away months of stress.
So I liked it.
Hi, Eun-a.
It's my girlfriend.
What is it?
I figured you'd be back in Seoul by now.
Right now, I…
Ma'am, can we have more kimchi?
Sure.
It sounds like you're eating.
Enjoy your lunch.
-I'll call you back.
-Okay.
So… this keeps bothering me
every time I see you.
It's about me giving you my name tag.
There are different ways to interpret it.
To say "I like you," I'd put in just mine.
But there were several, right?
I wanted to show you some support.
My feelings at the time were
sympathy 40%,
respect 30%,
and liking you around 30%.
No, wait.
It was 50, 30, and 20.
Or was it 40, 40, and 20?
Or 30?
I must've looked really pitiful.
Well, you don't now.
I was really proud to see
how well you were doing.
Remember the desk you used?
Seat One by the entrance?
I used to sit there all the time too.
It was easy to concentrate
when I sat there.
I thought, "Someone endured far worse
and still made it through."
You were my motivation.
I wanted you to have a good life.
Anyway, I'm just saying
that's what it was.
It's just in case
you were wondering if I still liked you.
It kept bothering me.
I had something
to take care of in Tongyeong,
so I had to leave in a hurry.
I'll come straight back
after checking some paperwork.
It won't take even 30 minutes.
I'll call you when I'm back in Seoul.
TONGYEONG BUS TERMINAL
Show me.
What's the rush? You can read it there.
It's been revised
with the correct business type.
The dates are the same.
You can run it as planned
until March 20th.
Just sign it.
Are you…
Are you angry right now?
It's all been settled.
Just like that?
How does this make sense?
If it were this easy,
why did I spend months…
How can Park So-hyeon appear
and make this all possible?
LEASE AGREEMENT
Why now?
They apparently took in guests
while you were away in Seoul.
All your stuff was still there,
so they're clearly crazy.
They probably thought letting guests
sleep there was the end of it.
They got complaints
and demands for refunds.
They knew something was wrong,
and then Park So-hyeon turned up.
You're the one who told her, right?
What matters is that it's all settled now.
And you told her
to ask Na-yeong where I was.
Those scumbags backed down, okay?
Who cares about Park So-hyeon right now?
Let's not do this, okay?
What's there to think about?
That's your opinion, not mine.
No wonder why Park So-hyeon
rushed over here in a panic.
When I left this place,
I didn't leave the door open.
Eun-a, I really don't understand you.
What you…
Give me a second.
I thought you'd be excited
when this was all resolved.
I thought you'd come running.
Did I get Park So-hyeon involved?
I did, but so what?
We have to deal with it, don't we?
Giving up is also an option.
What kind of nonsense…
Eun-a, you put so much
care and effort into that place.
Now you can have it all back.
What exactly is the problem?
Is this something to be mad about?
There's nothing for you in Seoul.
What's there to even think about?
No matter how much care,
effort, and love you put in,
you can't hold onto it forever.
Are you taking a jab at me?
I'm not thinking the slightest bit
about getting back together with you.
We're business partners.
I won't say this again.
If we sign the contract like this,
you won't get any compensation.
Just check its condition.
Only you know what it was like before.
Then, decide whether you want
bookings or not.
Close the door.
It's exactly the same.
It's not like you were gone for that long.
Even my keychain's still on.
You go in first.
That's not where the sofa goes.
It's already become so shabby.
All the handles are broken, and…
Write it up and email it to me.
Get in. I'll drop you off
at the bus terminal.
No, I just need to hurry.
I'm off.
What's the rush?
You don't even have
guests there from today.
That place Park So-hyeon stayed at
isn't somewhere to work long-term.
I'll handle it.
You've barely even lived in Seoul.
You never cared about it before,
so why are you suddenly so hung up on it?
I didn't change my mind while I was there.
I made up my mind here and left.
I made the decision here.
I had to drink with those scumbags
like nothing happened,
and my mind was a mess too.
I almost lost it a few times.
But we're taking back what's ours.
Why are you running away?
You don't have to take bookings right now,
so just think it through
and come back.
Eun-a, I told you I'd drop you off.
Geez, she's so stubborn.
That's not possible.
EUN-A
OKAY, HAVE A SAFE TRIP AND CALL ME LATER
Hi, Hui-seo.
Tae-seo.
It's definitely two or three days, right?
Today's the second day,
so she'll wake up tomorrow, right?
Right?
I'll be there tomorrow.
You came home exhausted,
and your girlfriend's right here.
Are you getting all emotional?
You smell sweaty.
-What's that?
-You haven't eaten yet, right?
I got some sandwiches
in case you were hungry.
Thanks.
The sandwiches here are good.
You're right. It's really soft.
-You should eat too.
-Okay.
It's nice to be eating together.
I think so too.
I had no idea,
but Park So-hyeon knows
the person who blindsided me.
I thought it was hopeless,
but it was resolved,
and they sent over a contract.
So I went over there to check it.
What happens now if it's been resolved?
Nothing's going to change.
I'll keep working where I was working,
and I've found a place to live.
I just need to move in on the set date.
I can only run that place
for just a few more months anyway.
Does that…
Does that Seong-chan guy
have something to do with your guesthouse?
He introduced that spot to me.
It turns out he only knew about it
through Park So-hyeon as well.
We're partners,
but he's busy working at a hotel,
so I basically ran it by myself.
Does he live in Tongyeong?
No, he lives in Geoje
at the hotel residence hall.
You don't need to worry about him.
I'm just worried for your safety.
You don't usually see someone
being chased in a train station.
I know, but…
that guesthouse doesn't
automatically equal him.
It's not like that.
It might be mentioned now and then,
but I can't have you
take it that way every time.
It was originally an empty house.
It was like I'd brought
a dying plant back to life.
I felt proud,
and it was fulfilling.
So I have unexpected competition.
I said a proper farewell
to your competition today.
Have you…
ever considered going back to Yeonwoo?
I haven't.
Yeonwoo was the first place I ruled out.
What about you?
I have to go.
You'll be going close then.
You said before that you want to keep
your distance because they're precious.
My grandparents and Hui-seo
are precious to me,
so I want to help them from a distance.
When I'm too close, I burn out easily.
I didn't know what you meant at the time,
but that's what Yeonwoo is like to me.
It's precious to me, but it hurts.
Where will I end up after Tongyeong?
What do you think?
If you're asking for my opinion
about your future,
can I…
take it that I'm a part of it?
Instead of just your future,
I'll take it as our future.
And that's what I'll think about.
Can I do that?
Is factoring me in
going to help?
You already have a lot on your mind,
but will that really help?
Yeah.
That's nice.
Now I have something I can do for you.
Let's do that then.
Let's give it some thought.
Thank you. Have a nice trip.
Sorry, I just need to take this call.
Sure.
Hello?
Yes, how have you been?
Ga-on's family canceled before,
but they're coming as planned.
If you don't have time,
I'll make it work just for them,
so send me your manual.
BYEONNWI OPERATIONS MANUAL
ROOM AMENITIES
It's simple.
I'll do what needs to be done,
ask him to help out, and then come back.
I don't need to make Tae-seo worry.
I can handle this myself.
MO SEON-GYU
Who's there?
The cleaning's done.
I also sent you the manual just in case.
Don't do breakfast.
They'll understand
if you explain it to them.
Tell me about breakfast.
I'll give it a go.
You can't do it.
I just steam some vegetables,
blend some juice, and toast some bread.
That's all, isn't it?
We have to do it for Ga-on's family.
The steamer is…
I'll get it out for you.
Hey, where's that thing?
That tiny little serving table?
I'll give you that as well.
Then I better wash the cauldron.
I used to do it all the time.
And that.
What is it?
Your stuff from the kitchen.
I haven't cleaned the room yet.
You do it and take your things.
-Are you coming back?
-I'm saying you should take your stuff.
Why bother moving my stuff
if you're not even coming back?
I'm already busy juggling two jobs.
You can move my stuff out for good
when you're sure about coming back.
I don't even have much stuff here.
Maybe some clothes from our three months.
Seong-chan.
Can you manage things here?
I said I'd handle Ga-on's booking.
You need time anyway
to wrap things up in Seoul.
Wait, from now on?
Rather than leave it empty,
take at least one booking a month.
Take more if you can handle it.
You know which guests come every season.
Just do it until the lease is up.
I want you to run it.
You tell me to move out my stuff
but want me to take bookings.
Figure out what you want to do first.
You're going back to the hotel, right?
I'll get off here.
TONGYEONG BUS TERMINAL
Look at us. What are we even doing?
Grandpa, let me do that.
Go sleep at home.
-Stop that. Give it here.
-Never.
We need to be smart about this.
When Grandma wakes up,
that's when the real trouble starts.
She'll wake up
before I can leave the hospital.
-We need a rotation.
-I can take time off too.
No way. It'll just complicate things.
Your schedule's all over the place.
Hyang-gi worked something out.
But you and I have to take turns
to come every day, Grandpa.
It's going to test our endurance.
So right now,
while Grandma's still in the hospital,
you should rest at home, Grandpa.
And Tae-seo,
make sure you keep talking to Grandma.
Just staring at her
won't help her wake up.
I washed this just now
in the bathroom with hot water.
Grandma can't stand anything dirty.
She'll hate it
if she sees dirt under her nails.
THE DIFFERENT APPEALS
OF DRIVING SUBWAYS AND TRAINS
I FIRST CONSIDERED CHANGING JOBS
BECAUSE OF THE ROUTES
Visitors can come in now.
Okay.
Grandma.
I…
So…
My expiration date…
I think I can decide on my own
when that will be.
Hae-jin, it's me.
Can you cover for me just for today?
I just need to handle
the front desk, right?
You owe me a big, fancy dinner.
All set.
AN OPEN SPACE SURROUNDED BY NATURE
A PLACE TO REST BENEATH SUNLIGHT
FILTERING THROUGH THE TREES
Goodbye.
MO SEON-GYU
Dad.
I dreamed, built,
and accomplished a lot in this place.
You saw all that, right?
Then that's all I need.
TAEYONG EXPRESS
TONGYEONG BUS TERMINAL
There's a lost item in Car 2-4.
What are you doing here?
I missed you too much.
Did something happen?
We can see each other when we want to.
That counts as something for us.
Tae-seo.
This is the right place.
This place is what's real.
What is she, a helpful elf or something?
How foolish.
She's seriously not coming back?
The left side looks a little off.
Let's adjust it a tiny bit.
Yes, right away.
We have to clear the back area anyway.
Let's do it later.
Jeong-min, please help out with this.
Clean up over there.
Got it.
Can you try calling the actor?
Where's the props department?
So…
basically,
I originally had a job lined up.
It was a place run by someone I know,
but it looks like
they won't be able to open this year.
They acted like
they were going to open any day now.
I can't believe it either.
You mean…
Just for this month.
I need to look for a place too.
Try to hold out somehow
just until the end of this month.
Okay?
I'll get it sorted out by then.
Want help finding
a temporary place to stay?
Anyway,
it's not really for me to say,
and I thought it'd be better
to find my replacement soon
so I didn't say anything.
But the owner here has no interest
in running a guesthouse.
After this shoot,
they'll have another pop-up here.
You're only here
to open and close the doors.
I need to do at least that.
I promise you,
this place will be closing soon.
You should start
looking for a hotel job now.
A place to stay and a job…
I need to find everything again.
Well…
I mean…
That's one way to look at it.
I'm sorry.
If you're sure,
we should close this place.
I can contact Ga-on's family.
And I'll clear this place out myself.
Clear out…
Now I'm feeling awake.
KTC RAILWAY LAWS AND REGULATIONS
Including blood pressure,
her vitals are stable.
Her intracranial pressure
is stabilizing too.
If she's still stable in the morning,
we can move her into a regular room
within the next two days.
MART
Goodness, you came all the way from Seoul.
What happened?
My wife is getting better.
Goodness, what a relief.
That's great.
It is.
-I'll grab a bottle of soju.
-Sure.
Let's go.
Here, this is some kimchi stew.
Heat it for him.
Do you have rice?
Leave it. We have rice.
-Go on now.
-Thank you.
Sure. Get going.
-Bye.
-Take care.
Did you ever have a drink with your dad?
No.
Just have one glass.
I'm glad I'm at least still here
to pour you a drink.
Grandpa.
Did you know
I wanted to drive trains as a child?
I wanted to drive the Sea Train,
because when I was little, I saw Mom…
working there.
Once I pass the tests and interview,
I can choose my region.
I'm thinking Gangneung
or somewhere along the east coast.
Leave it all to Hui-seo.
He'll be out of the hospital soon.
He said he'd look after your grandma
in the hospital
until the day she's discharged.
That's his motivation to get better,
so just let him do it.
Hui-seo…
needs to help someone
to become confident and healthier.
Just hang on for a few more days,
and before you know it,
everything will go back to the way it was.
You won't even remember it
once this is all over.
Don't forget to see Jin-su.
He's been worried sick.
Don't you dare come here.
I can even go to the bathroom on my own.
I've got amazing recovery skills.
I'll admit that.
-Get some rest.
-Okay, bye.
Yeonwoo's been ruled out.
Seoul or…
Tongyeong
and the east coast.
EUN-A
STAY BYEONNWI
"Byeonnwi"?
FOR RESERVATIONS AND INQUIRIES,
CLICK THE LINK BELOW
REPOSTED
-Hey, you came.
-Hi.
So about Hui-seo…
I'm never taking Hui-seo anywhere again.
He was tense the whole way there.
I still get chills thinking about it.
Anyway, I'm really sorry.
No, Hui-seo finally worked up the courage,
and you helped him.
Hey, on my way home,
I saw the last house lit up.
It's been dark until now.
Who are…
You…
It's you, right?
There.
I should stop telling Eun-a
to come live here.
There's a lot that needs work.
It's been left empty for too long.
Eun-a shouldn't come back here.
It's in good condition.
It just needs a bit of cleaning.
It'd take at least a month
to clean this place.
I even bought these instant coffee sticks
so I can make some
for elderly folks passing by.
But nobody passed by.
Then again,
they wouldn't have come inside anyway.
In Tongyeong,
there's a guesthouse Eun-a used to run.
I'd only ever heard about it,
but when I finally went there
a few days ago…
Goodness.
It reminded me of this house
even though she didn't take
even a spoon from this place.
It made me think of Seon-gyu.
It was precious to her,
but those scumbags put her through a lot.
You haven't seen her in a while, right?
You two were unbelievable.
So was I.
Why did I think I could lecture you?
This is the address.
The one next door is her house.
But it's basically the same place.
She receives packages at this one.
The guesthouse is called Byeonnwi.
It's so hard to pronounce.
"Byeonnwi."
Apparently, it means
"sunlight filtering through small gaps."
Like the light that comes in
at an angle into the shade.
That one ray of light.
It's like how cats find spots like that
and curl up there even in the dark.
It's warm.
That's what that place is like.
Eun-a found her way there.
You should visit.
Once it's behind you, you can be friends.
She'll be glad.
EUN-A'S GUESTHOUSE
Seon-gyu used to pick flowers
every morning.
He'd stick them in random cups
and leave them around the house.
Eun-a does exactly the same.
Gosh, where is my head?
Hey, don't keep standing there.
Grab a chair and sit down.
-Do you want a drink?
-No, I'm fine.
Right, okay.
I'm getting carried away.
How's Hui-seo? Is he well?
I'm going to go.
Why are you acting like I have the plague?
Everyone here hates me.
All because I should've stayed
right by Seon-gyu's side,
but I was gone for a moment.
Take care.
You've grown up nicely.
I'll lock the gate.
It wasn't for a moment.
You went to Hawaii.
Even though you knew
you weren't supposed to leave him alone.
I went home.
Hawaii is my home. Didn't you know that?
I went back for the first time in years.
I checked 500 times.
He was completely fine.
Depression? Not even a hint of it.
He was completely fine
even without taking his medicine.
I never even imagined it.
I had my own selfish reasons too.
When I heard that Eun-a and my mom
were having a great time,
I wanted to be there too.
In that corridor over there,
there's a photo of Eun-a.
My mom actually sent me pictures of her
even though my mom
hardly ever contacts me.
She must've adored Eun-a that much.
I had it printed and put it there.
Whenever Seon-gyu saw that photo,
he would smile.
I left, believing in that photo.
Honestly…
After breaking up with you in December,
Eun-a went to intern in Hawaii.
She kept wavering about going
and then finally did.
We broke up in December?
Around December. It was then.
Still, just in case,
I asked Seong-chan
to look in on him every day,
without fail.
That Seong-chan person.
Was he really that trustworthy?
I had known him for a long time.
I see.
Did you hear how Eun-a was doing
through this Seong-chan person?
More or less.
Eun-a must have kept him close
because he was updating you
on how she was doing.
It sounds like she thought
she would do at least that much for you.
That's something Eun-a would do.
Her? I'm not so sure.
You haven't seen her at all, right?
Look.
This is last year.
This is her guesthouse.
I was sent this as soon as it opened.
This is from three years ago.
This is 2020.
This is 2019.
Seong-chan sent them to me.
He knew that I missed her.
These were all…
-taken by that Seong-chan person?
-Yes.
They dated for a brief while
and then broke up.
They're not a good match.
He isolates her from everyone.
But Eun-a loves being around people.
That guy from the station,
her business partner,
her link with Park So-hyeon,
and the person she dated for three months
were all the same person.
In the past decade of Eun-a's life…
he was the only one present.
Rule Tongyeong out as well.
Don't go there.
STILL SHINING
Subtitle translation by: Hyesoo Lee