=Eight Hundred=
=Episode 8=
(The Miscalculation)
(40 minutes ago.
People's Public Security)
Do you recognize him?
I'm not really familiar with him.
Look closely.
He looks like
the guy who bought
a lottery ticket at my place.
What did you do on October 1?
October 1?
I went to the city.
What were you doing there?
It was China's National Day.
The city was crowded and lively.
Did you enter any lucky draws that day?
I did.
I won a set of
some commemorative coins.
Where are the coins?
I lost them.
When did you lose them?
I don't know, I just can't find them.
What time does your lottery shop close?
11:00 PM.
Take a look at this ticket.
Was this issued from your shop?
I sold it.
What's wrong?
This ticket was printed
at 3:00 AM on October 2.
I remember now.
That night,
someone knocked on the door
and insisted on buying one.
It seems to be
the person in the photo.
(Peidun Cough Syrup)
This
was found in your shop.
Tell us what's going on.
This isn't mine.
Susu left it at my place.
Yu Susu?
Why didn't you mention this before?
Officer,
this is illegal stuff.
How would I dare to say anything?
I know I was wrong.
Please show me some leniency.
Zhang Mei,
listen carefully.
I'm letting you speak,
and it means
that I'm giving you a chance.
If we are the ones who have to say it,
then the nature of this changes.
Understand?
Think it over carefully.
We can give you one more chance.
Tell us,
what is your relationship
with Ma Heping?
And with Yu Susu,
what relationship is that?
Something happened.
Stay put.
What's the situation?
Hui called. He said
Huo Kaiming kidnapped him.
He wants us to release Cai.
- Did he say where?
- No.
The call was forcibly cut off.
Lin, pull up Huo Kaiming's photo.
- Print 20 copies.
- Yes, ma'am.
Alright, according to the action plan,
divide the area into four groups.
Go find Huo Kaiming.
Big guy, stay here and wait for a call.
The rest of you, move out!
Mr. Chen.
Songge.
What's wrong?
Chen Hui and I were at the photo studio.
Huo Kaiming showed up,
shoved him into a car,
and took him away.
Where did they go?
The north crossing.
The north crossing! Quick!
Master, look!
Oh, no.
Quick!
Careful, Director Chen.
Hui!
Hui.
- Hui.
- Hui!
Hui.
- Hui.
- Careful, Director Chen.
Wake up!
Come on, Limin.
Give me a hand!
Hurry!
Master, let me.
Come here.
Put his head over there.
Head over there.
Easy now.
- Hui!
Wake up!
Director Chen, look, there's blood here.
It must be Huo Kaiming's.
He couldn't have gone far.
Huo Kaiming ran this way.
Limin, get Hui to the hospital.
Right. Let's go.
Come on.
One, two, three...
Lift!
- Careful, Limin.
- I've got him.
- You okay?
- I'm fine, Master.
Why did the blood trail stop?
Blood.
Look here.
He jumped onto the train from here.
Make way!
Go, Mrs. Chen.
Hui, hang in there!
Hui, hurry!
Open the door!
Mrs. Chen.
BP is dropping, 80 over 50.
Pupils are dilated.
No pulse.
Get the family to sign the consent.
Yes.
Keep up the compressions.
Epinephrine 2 mg IV push once.
Purple flames.
You filthy drug dealers...
I'm going to burn you all to death!
You and the sickly weakling
are all going to die.
Kneel!
Where's your skill now?
Chen Hui, you're useless.
Who can you protect?
Coward!
Who can you even protect?
(Songge,)
(I'm so tired.)
Where were you?
You just got here.
Chen Hui.
Chen Hui, wake up.
I still want to take Songge
to the ends of the earth.
Chen Hui!
We have a pulse!
Sinus rhythm is restored.
Doctor! How is he, Doctor?
You're the family?
How is he?
How is he, Doctor?
The patient
is out of immediate danger.
However, he hasn't fully
regained consciousness.
Alright?
We still need to perform
some further tests on him.
Don't worry.
We'll transfer him to a ward later.
- He's out of danger, right?
- He'll be okay.
- Thank you, Doctor.
- You're welcome.
Thank you, Doctor.
It's okay now. He's out of danger.
- Everything is fine.
- It's okay.
There, there. Don't cry.
Everything's okay.
Let me do it.
I'll do it.
You rest.
I can... I can do it.
Don't cry.
Our son will be fine.
He'll be fine.
Don't cry.
Songge,
eat something first.
Come on.
Go and eat first.
Based on our examination,
the patient suffered severe head trauma.
There is a blood clot in his brain.
This is the reason
he remains in a coma.
As for whether he will wake up,
it depends
on how his body absorbs the clot.
(Efficient and Pragmatic,
Fair and Honest)
(Fengyang Town Police Station)
Take these over as well.
Okay.
Director Chen.
Director Chen, what are you doing here?
How is Hui?
He hasn't woken up yet.
How about you guys?
Well,
we conducted a search
of Huo Kaiming's house.
We found 76 bottles
of Peidun Cough Syrup under his bed.
This matches our theory of the case.
Huo Kaiming should be the source
(Peidun Cough Syrup)
of the cough syrup trafficking.
Ma Heping broke his rules
and sold the bottled medicine to Cai.
Huo Kaiming found out
and wanted to kill Cai
and Ma Heping to silence them.
But Huo Kaiming kidnapped Hui
to negotiate with the police...
This will end with both sides destroyed.
It doesn't look like a silencing.
What about the glycerin in his car?
Any results?
We checked.
He bought it a few nights ago
behind the Commercial Building.
The sales assistant recognized
his photo immediately.
Where is Chief Liu?
Back at the municipal PSB to report.
Oh, one more thing,
Master.
The lab report for the bloodstains
in Huo Kaiming's car is out.
Besides the blood
Songge spilled that day,
they also found traces belonging to
Yu Susu and Lu Yuan.
That means we have
all the evidence for the murders.
Now we just wait to bring him in.
Don't you worry.
We've already faxed Huo Kaiming's
composite sketch to the municipal PSB.
The municipal PSB should be applying
to the provincial PSB for a warrant now.
Alright, come here.
Let me say a few words.
You all have been
exhausted these past few days.
Those who just
came on shift this morning
will form two teams
to continue searching for Huo Kaiming
along the railway line.
Except for those on duty,
everyone else
should go back and get some rest.
Get your energy back.
We'll talk more this afternoon.
- Sound good?
- Yes, sir.
Come on, thank Director Chen.
- Thank you, Director Chen.
You come with me to interrogate Cai.
Again?
What do you mean by "again"?
I just feel like
this Huo Kaiming
doesn't seem like the source.
If he really killed
Yu Susu
and Lu Yuan
and then burned the bodies,
what was the motive?
Why would he do that?
Hurry up.
There are two things I can tell you.
As of now,
we have gathered
a vast amount of evidence against you,
proving that you
illegally possessed contraband.
Second,
we found a large amount of blood
in Huo Kaiming's car.
It belongs to Yu Susu.
In other words, Huo Kaiming
murdered Yu Susu
and then burned the body.
A few days ago,
he also took a hostage,
Chen Hui.
The condition he set for the exchange
was that we must
hand you over to him.
I don't know what your relationship is
with this Huo Kaiming,
but for the sake of this matter,
he has already killed two people
and is still on the run.
I'd say this man
has completely lost it.
Zhang Mei,
do you have anything else to confess?
If you don't want to talk, forget it.
Right, your daughter came
to bring you some bedding.
But according to the rules,
personal items are not allowed here.
So I had her take it back.
With the hunt for Huo Kaiming lately,
we've all been quite busy
and didn't get a chance to tell you.
That's all.
Director Chen,
you must protect my daughter.
Huo Kaiming
has gone crazy now.
He is very likely
to go find my daughter.
Protecting the lives
and property of the people
is our duty as police officers.
But
Fengyang is a small place,
so you should know
the police force at this station
is quite limited.
If you want me
to specifically assign officers
to protect your daughter,
you'll have to give me
a solid reason,
right?
I...
Hard to say?
Is it hard to say,
or are you not allowed to say?
If you don't speak up,
there's nothing I can do.
Director Chen...
I'll talk.
I will tell you
everything I know.
But Director Chen, you must promise
that after I tell you,
you will protect my daughter.
You can't let Huo Kaiming
harm my daughter.
Go ahead.
Give us the details.
Two years ago,
my husband and I
came to Fengyang.
To earn more money,
he went to work in an illegal coal pit.
Not long after he started,
his hands
and his feet
started to feel weak.
We went to see a doctor.
The doctor said it was because
his muscle tension was high,
so he prescribed him some medicine.
Later,
people at the pit were drinking
Peidun Cough Syrup.
They said that after drinking it,
their whole body felt comfortable.
My husband
also started drinking it with them.
When he first started,
the effect
was very good.
But one day,
while he was down in the shaft,
he suddenly died.
Afterward, I went specifically
to ask the doctor.
The doctor said
that the cough syrup
and the muscle medicine
would cause
a reaction if taken together.
It could kill someone.
Because of this incident, the mine
paid me over 300,000 yuan.
I used that money
to take over the lottery shop.
Now, tell me,
what exactly is your relationship
with Huo Kaiming?
Well,
after running
the lottery shop for a while,
I felt
that making money was too slow.
So I went back
to my hometown in Yunchuan
and scouted two girls.
One was Jiao Yuqin,
and the other was Yu Susu.
I told them both
to go to the illegal coal pits
and find
men with no family to marry.
Then, we'd look for a chance
to stage an accident
so we could collect
the compensation money.
(Yu Susu, Jiao Yuqin, Death Benefit Brides)
I was afraid
someone might investigate this later,
so I also had them
swap their ID cards.
So you're saying
the real identity
of the victim at Beimianling
is Jiao Yuqin.
The real Yu Susu
was with Huo Kaiming
at the time last year.
We gave him cough syrup
and the medication for muscle tension.
But
we never expected
that Huo Kaiming wouldn't die.
But then I thought,
since Yu Susu
had already taken her cut and gone home,
and no one could find her,
there
shouldn't be any trouble.
Fine.
Tell us
about the deceased "Yu Susu",
who is actually Jiao Yuqin.
Jiao Yuqin
wasn't like Yu Susu.
She liked to mess around everywhere.
Even after
I introduced her to Zhu Qiang,
she was still hooking up with
a small business owner
with the surname Chi.
Last year,
the bottled Peidun Cough Syrup
was no longer available, right?
I thought we'd just let it go
and stop having her do it.
Then, one day,
Ma Heping
showed up at my shop.
Come on in and take cover.
It's fine.
The rain came on suddenly.
It'll pass soon.
Hurry, get inside.
Don't let the child catch a cold.
Dad,
I want some water.
Okay.
Here.
From then on,
I purposefully got close to Ma Heping.
Come out.
There's no one.
It gets cold late at night.
Put your clothes on properly.
Okay.
It's fine.
I'm sorry.
My daughter works at a cabaret.
Sometimes when business is slow,
she comes home early.
By the way,
you must not forget
those cough syrup bottles,
don't lose them.
Don't worry,
I've got it.
You're so silly.
Right.
Then, I'll head back now.
Go on then.
Wait a second.
I'll print a lottery ticket for you.
Who knows, you might get lucky?
Why
did you want to buy the bottled
cough syrup?
I thought the bottled kind
looked more like legitimate medicine.
The ones packed in tube popsicles
look very suspicious.
What drug did the fake Yu Susu
give to Zhu Qiang?
Last time,
since Huo Kaiming didn't die,
we switched the drug for Zhu Qiang.
I'd read the instructions
on the cough syrup bottle.
It said it shouldn't be taken
with stomach medicine.
Then,
I had her secretly swap
Zhu Qiang's stomach medicine.
Did you give the commemorative coin
on the fake Yu Susu
and the one on Ma Heping's son
to them?
Yes, I did.
Well,
on the night of October 1,
didn't Ma Heping come by again
to bring me a few bottles
of that cough syrup?
He left in the early morning on the 2nd.
I gave him one.
Jiao Yuqin,
the one who posed as Yu Susu,
came to my place at noon on the 2nd
to pick up the cough syrup.
She saw the other one
and said she loved it very much.
So I gave it to her.
How did Huo Kaiming know
the fake Yu Susu was working with you?
I really don't know that.
I really don't,
Director Chen.
I've already told you
everything I know.
I swear. You have to promise me
that you will protect my daughter.
If Huo Kaiming can't kill me,
he will go after my daughter.
Truly,
Director Chen.
I only have one child left now.
I have no other family.
Director Chen,
please.
You have to help me protect my daughter.
You can't let Huo Kaiming kill her.
Don't worry about that.
Now, please provide us
with the real identities
of Yu Susu and Jiao Yuqin,
all right?
All right.
(Investigation and Inquiry Record)
If that's the case,
Huo Kaiming was once
(Huo Kaiming)
one of Cai's targets.
He nearly lost his life.
And Yu Susu and Cai
are both targets of his revenge.
Right.
He has a motive for revenge.
(Huo Kaiming)
But he was harmed by the cough syrup.
That means, before
Huo Kaiming was targeted,
(Contraband)
someone in Fengyang was already
selling the cough syrup.
Looking at it this way,
he likely isn't the source
of the syrup trade.
This must have something to do
with the scarred woman.
(Scarred woman? Height about 165 cm,
masked, scar on the left eye corner)
Have you checked
Huo Kaiming's social circle?
Limin is on it.
Huo Kaiming
usually didn't have
any close friends.
His neighbors also say
they never saw
any woman around him.
It's just that for now, we can't confirm
the relationship
between the scarred woman
and Huo Kaiming.
The provincial PSB
has issued a warrant for Huo Kaiming.
Once he's caught,
everything will become clear.
Right.
Colleagues from the municipal PSB
will come this afternoon
for the evidence handover.
Once the evidence
is at the municipal PSB,
we'll investigate further
to see if there are any new leads.
Good.
How is Hui doing?
He hasn't woken up yet.
(Jiangbin Municipal People's Hospital)
Mrs. Chen,
let me do it.
It's okay.
Let me.
Mrs. Chen,
you haven't had
a good rest these past two days.
Don't push yourself too hard.
I'm fine.
If I spend more time with Hui every day,
maybe he'll wake up.
Mrs. Chen.
Mrs. Chen, please stop crying.
If you keep crying like this,
your body really won't hold up.
Didn't the doctor say
that the blood clot in Chen Hui's brain
is getting smaller?
Maybe
he'll wake up very soon.
You're right.
He will.
He'll wake up.
He definitely will.
Chen Hui.
Mrs. Chen.
Chen Hui!
Hui.
Songge, quick!
I'll call the doctor.
- Get the doctor!
- Doctor!
Doctor!
Hui.
Hui, you're awake!
Drink some.
Hui.
Hui, listen to me.
Hui is awake?
Mr. Chen.
Hui,
you're awake?
Mr. Chen,
after Chen Hui woke up,
he hasn't said a word.
He doesn't recognize anyone.
How can this be?
Hui.
Hui...
Hui, what's wrong?
Hui,
look at who I am.
I'm your father.
Call me, Hui.
What's wrong with you?
Say something.
I'm your father.
Dad.
Call me!
- Hui.
- Mr. Chen, calm down.
Speak to me.
What's...
What's wrong with you?
Hui, you...
You...
Speak to me.
What happened to him?
Hui.
(Radiation hazard.
Do not enter when light is on)
Doctor,
how is my son?
The blood clot
in his brain is disappearing.
Pupil dilation
and knee reflexes are all normal.
In this situation, I don't think
it's due to a physical lesion.
Then, what else could be the cause?
It should be a psychological issue.
Before the patient fell into a coma,
had he suffered some kind of trauma?
I suppose so.
Then, that's it.
It's just as I thought.
So, for this psychological issue,
which hospital should we go to?
In this case,
I don't think staying in the hospital
will help much.
Don't put the patient
through any more stress.
Let him rest quietly at home.
Staying in a place where the patient
feels safe
will be helpful for his recovery.
(Nurse Station)
Hongbing,
you don't think Hui will...
Don't think like that.
We've never done
anything to be ashamed of.
Hui will get better.
Don't worry.
Hi there,
are you his family members?
Yes.
You should pay more attention.
He's been urinating all along the way.
I'm sorry.
- Clean this up, quickly.
- I'm sorry.
I'll clean it up right away.
I'll go find a mop.
- Mrs. Chen, I'll go with you.
- Okay.
Slow down.
Okay.
There, that's better.
When you were little,
I never even changed your diapers.
Are you blaming me
and insisting that I
make it up to you now?
Is that it?
Alright.
For you,
I would do anything.
Don't you want to be with Songge?
I'll talk to your mother.
I'm going to make sure
both of you
are happy for a lifetime.
But you have to promise me
that you will get better.
Get better soon.
I'm taking you home.
Songge,
stop working.
You've been at it for two days.
It's okay, Mrs. Chen. I'm almost done.
It's fine. I'll do it later.
Mrs. Chen,
I want to take Hui
to the roller skating rink.
He set that place up himself.
I think going there
might help his condition.
Alright.
I hope Hui gets better soon.
Go and come back quickly.
Okay.
Grandpa,
I'm taking Hui out now.
Are you leaving?
Just for a bit. They'll be back soon.
- We're off, Mrs. Chen.
- Okay. Be careful out there.
Bye, Grandpa.
Take it slow.
Chen Hui,
do you remember when we first opened,
how we skated together?
♪You ask what is outside the window♪
♪You ask what color the light is♪
♪You say hope is a dancing bubble♪
♪So colorful and free♪
♪Yet popping at a single touch♪
♪So I hope this world protects me♪
♪Just like when we
were innocent children♪
♪Back then, the distance was in sight♪
♪The road had no end♪
Chen Hui.
Songge.
♪And there would surely be a future♪
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
♪Memories tucked in an old pocket♪
♪Wind whistling through empty sleeves♪
♪Just pretend
you're holding my hand again♪
I thought if I brought you here,
you would remember everything.
Chen Hui.
Chen Hui, please get better, okay?
Please get better soon, okay?
Songge.
Chen Hui.
I was faking it.