=No Doubt In Us=
(Adapted from the Manman comic No Doubt in Us)
=Episode 1=
(Chongzheng Hall, Chen Empire)
(Xiao Jinyun, Emperor)
Long live the Emperor!
(Xu Yu, Empress)
Mountain-River Cleaver!
(The List of Concubine Candidates)
On borders south and north,
beacons rise on all sides.
Plague in the East Sea.
Drought in Liangyuan.
Banditry in Lingnan.
The state's in peril.
The ministers do not think
of the people and the state.
They only care about my harem.
What business is it of theirs
how many I marry?
Skyward Thrust!
Xu Yu.
Your Majesty.
Why wasn't his arrival announced?
Xu Yu,
how dare you
hand over the Empress's Seal!
Isn't that what you wished for?
After all, you never truly
wanted me to be Empress.
You...
If you're frail, you shouldn't keep
running out to catch a chill.
So according to you,
I am a burden to you.
Good.
Since you lead such a leisurely life,
I'll give you something to do.
Eunuch Qin.
Draft the list of concubine candidates.
Alright. It's not like
I haven't done it before.
As long as Your Majesty
trusts my judgment.
Choose me!
Choose me, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Choose me!
Your Majesty, look at me!
Your Majesty!
The eight concubine candidates
are all talented and virtuous.
They'd never lead you astray.
If you do not indulge in women,
it'll be more beneficial for the court.
I think it's unnecessary.
Your Majesty!
No need.
With your judgment,
you'll make a mockery
of the concubine selection.
Your harem is filled
with countless beauties.
How many more do you need?
The concubine selection
is for the balance of the court.
Since when does Chen Empire need women
in the harem to stabilize the court?
Xu Yu.
Enough.
Whatever I do is wrong anyway.
No matter what I do,
Your Majesty will never trust me.
Then simply let Consort Zhao
manage the harem.
So I'm not in the way
of you producing heirs.
Do you really not care?
I don't care.
Fine.
Pass the order.
Consort Zhao will take
the Empress's Seal and run the harem.
Yes.
You...
I...
The Empress's Seal
(Zhao Qiluo)
matches my attire best.
Exactly.
In my opinion,
the Empress's Seal in your hands
(Beauty Liang)
is brighter than in the Empress's hands.
Now that the seal is in your hands,
(Lady Tao)
even the palace seems brighter.
The Empress's Seal
should be held by someone
capable and dignified.
Look.
I can even tolerate that belly of yours.
Consort Zhao, you're right.
Merely transferring the seal
does not demonstrate your ability
to manage the harem.
I have over 100 account books here.
I cannot manage them all.
But I believe you can.
Your Majesty,
you are deliberately
making things difficult for me.
Unless
you can't read the account books?
Then the seal...
Who said Her Highness can't?
She's intelligent
and exceedingly learned.
Managing these account books
is effortless for her.
Not to mention a hundred.
Even if it's a thousand,
Her Highness can handle them with ease.
Right, Your Highness?
If you don't know
how to speak, then don't.
Of course.
- I...
- I'm done on my part.
I'll take my leave.
Wait.
Now the Empress's Seal is in my hands.
I have authority over the harem.
It is against the rules for you
to carry a sword in the palace.
Someone!
Disarm her sword immediately.
- Yes.
Your Majesty!
Why such panic?
Her Majesty and Consort Zhao
are quarreling again.
I heard Her Majesty even drew her sword.
You want my sword?
You'll have to defeat me first.
Xu Yu.
Your Majesty.
Her Majesty wants to kill me.
Please help me.
Xu Yu,
come with me.
Your Majesty.
You're out of favor again.
But I'm still the Empress.
You enjoy exclusive favor,
yet where's the heir
to ease His Majesty's worries?
Xu Yu,
you're just a general's daughter.
My father is the Grand Chancellor.
Why should I fear you?
Xu Yu.
Should Your Majesty reprimand me,
just say it outright.
After all, you scold me indiscriminately
time and again.
Court factions are imbalanced.
Grand Chancellor Zhao,
the top civil official, holds sway.
If you harm Zhao Qiluo now,
I...
(I can hardly guarantee your safety.)
You'd feel heartbroken.
I understand.
Your sword-carved wooden head
could never understand.
Shame on you as Empress.
Then I dare ask Your Majesty.
Do I look like the Empress to you now?
What do you mean?
Every time you visit me,
you either scold me for others' sake
or reprimand me over palace affairs.
How do others view me?
Have you considered my feelings?
So you mean
you resent my entrusting
the Empress's Seal to Consort Zhao?
Have you ever devoted
half that sword-swinging passion
to managing the imperial harem?
Then just strip me of my title
and cast me out of the palace
to make way for Zhao Qiluo.
Xu Yu,
do you wish to leave me so badly?
Isn't this exactly what you want?
Xu Yu!
Get away.
Xiao Jinyun!
Someone! Help!
(Fengyi Palace)
Their Majesties fell into the water!
Why am I in Fengyi Palace?
(This is Xiao Jinyun's study?)
(I've actually become Xiao Jinyun?)
Why is this growing here?
Your Majesty.
I heard Her Majesty
pushed you into the water.
I was so worried.
Stay away from me.
Please let me check if you're hurt.
D-Don't touch me.
Your Majesty.
(Empress Dowager)
Shall we summon Physician Jiang again?
No.
Your Majesty,
what's wrong?
I'm Qiluo.
Don't you adore me most?
His Majesty seems too traumatized
to recognize me.
Your Majesty.
His Majesty is shocked.
He should rest properly.
I'll confront Xu Yu.
You go.
I'll go too.
You go as well.
(They're going to confront me?)
(Wait.)
(I've become Xiao Jinyun.)
(Then doesn't that mean Xiao Jinyun)
(is me?)
♪Parting clouds
to pluck the waxing moon♪
♪Brewing a pot of bygone years♪
♪Chill flame, window shade,
console my grieving soul♪
♪Drunk through lifetimes
with no dreams returned♪
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
♪Returning to drift
through the mortal world♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪