♪Wandering alone♪
♪Walking far by dusk-lit streets♪
♪Your eyes are as cold as clouds♪
♪Faintly coming into view♪
♪The city lights♪
♪Lit up that single moment♪
♪I can't hide or stop missing you♪
♪I can't forget those moments♪
♪Losing you♪
♪Like the seasons in my memory♪
♪Without winter♪
♪Walking down the long, dark street♪
♪Snow will never fall again♪
♪Our old story was torn♪
♪Into scattered pieces♪
♪Replaying every single scene♪
♪After you left♪
♪As if our documentary♪
♪Lost winter♪
♪The breeze speaks of good times♪
♪Pure white devotion♪
♪Send out a letter♪
♪Carrying my longing♪
=The Double Game=
=Episode 7=
I didn't mean to.
I'd better head back first.
You held and touched me,
and you want to leave?
I was only trying to help you.
Help me?
Were you helping me
look for this?
How could that be?
I don't even know what that is.
It looks pretty nice.
It's the key
to my phone and laptop.
Really?
That's amazing.
But what's the point of me opening
your phone and laptop?
I can't read any of it.
Yeah.
I don't think what you're doing
is what Lin Zhi'er would do.
I'm even wondering
if you really are her.
Of course, I am.
So, when you were touching
and hugging me,
did you mistake me for Lu Tingyu?
How is that possible?
What kind of joke is that?
Actually, I don't mind
if you see me as your husband.
You... Lu Tingxiao,
if you keep this up,
I'll go all the way with you.
What are you doing?
Didn't you say you'd go all the way?
Is that not enough?
I can do it again.
No more, no more.
No more.
We're closed.
Leave.
Fei Yifan.
Long time no see.
Jin Chanchan,
you ruined my pool hall.
I was just looking for you.
We can settle that later.
I'm here today
to ask about the fundraising scheme.
What's that got to do with you?
Wait.
That woman acting shady that day
was you after all.
That's right.
It was me.
Let's put our issues aside first.
Your priority now
is to get back
the money in the project, right?
If I can help you
and all the investors
get the money back,
will you work with me?
You?
What could you do?
Everyone knows Luzhou Group
bleeds people dry.
I'm Jin Chanchan.
I expose the dirt.
You know
what I'm capable of.
Once this is over,
I'll clear up the pool hall mix-up.
Okay.
I'll trust you one more time.
Tell me everything
you know
about Lianxin Island.
Don't miss a single detail.
Lianxin Island
used to be a small island
near the mainland.
The fishermen
fished for a living.
Around the turn of the millennium,
a man came
and persuaded the villagers
to raise funds by investing with land,
saying they'd all prosper together.
Was it Lu Jianchuan?
No.
It was Lin Youqiang of Linhai Group.
That guy had no money.
He sold most of the shares
to Lu Jianchuan.
Lu Jianchuan
was very lucky.
After taking over the property,
he'd never made a move.
And this land
kept going up every year.
Later,
he bought several nearby islets
in one go
and put them together.
So,
this was the old Lianxin Island resort.
A heart-shaped island.
Pretty romantic.
Just a developer's gimmick.
Lianxin Island was spread out
and irregularly shaped.
It took land reclamation
to make it into this heart shape.
That must've taken a lot of reclamation.
Something's indeed off.
He broke it into pieces.
Broke it into pieces?
Check the public notice.
Total reclamation tops 400 hectares.
But Luzhou Group and Linhai Group
used cover names
to split it into 18 subprojects
under 27 hectares each.
Under 27 hectares?
Is there a reason for that?
Any reclamation project
under 27 hectares
only needs local approval.
But anything over 27 hectares needs
National Oceanic Administration review.
The process is much stricter.
For a project as big as this one,
it'd never get through.
So, you're saying...
Luzhou Group split the reclamation plan
to dodge national approval on purpose.
That's a serious violation.
(Love Is Timeless like Pearls.
Pearl Bay)
Yan.
You're still up this late?
Here, have some fruit.
Aunt Hui, you read my mind.
Is this Lianxin Island?
Aunt Hui,
you know Lianxin Island?
I'm actually from Lianxin Island.
Why didn't you mention it before?
Then do you know
about the Lianxin Island project?
Do you know Lin Youqiang?
This one.
I do.
I know all about it.
Back then,
Lin Youqiang came to the island,
dressed all polished,
and fell
for the Village Chief's daughter,
saying he'd marry her.
Lin Youqiang told the Village Chief
they should team up on development.
If the islanders put up their land,
they'd get houses for free
and get paid to build them,
and later, there'd be dividends.
The Village Chief liked the idea,
and besides,
Lin was about to be his son-in-law.
So, he trusted Lin
and got the islanders to sign.
But in fact, Lin Youqiang
was a fraud.
He was a real lowlife.
He had no money for development.
Once he got the land,
he turned around
and sold most of the shares
to another man.
Was it Lu Jianchuan?
Right.
It's Lu Jianchuan.
I heard
he used to be a poor nobody,
then married a rich girl,
and became wealthy.
After Lu Jianchuan joined us,
he kept making excuses
to stall the project.
Later, we found out
he wanted higher land prices.
What a shady businessman.
After Lin Youqiang got the land,
he showed his true colors
and broke up
with the Village Chief's daughter.
Actually, he dumped her.
The village land wasn't developed,
the islanders had nowhere to live,
and the land couldn't be used either.
Everyone started making a scene.
The Village Chief
went to ask him to end the contract.
Only then did he find out
he'd been tricked
into signing a full 50-year deal.
The land couldn't be recovered,
and the money was gone.
The Village Chief felt
he had let everyone down,
so he took his own life.
Aunt Hui,
were you close to the Village Chief?
He once helped me a lot.
When I saw all this,
I just couldn't accept it.
Why is it
that good people suffer so much
while people
like Lu Jianchuan
and Lin Youqiang
are living better than ever
with the land and money by deceit?
They'll pay for this.
Have some fruit.
(Lu Jianchuan and Lin Youqiang)
(are even worse than I imagined.)
(I'll expose all their wrongdoing.)
(Speak for the Voiceless,
Empower the Powerless)
♪This door♪
♪Lets in the sky outside♪
♪With a voice even lighter♪
♪Than how you just greeted me♪
♪I know now♪
♪What the chill in my body means♪
♪The moment salt hits the wound♪
♪My heart still beats so naively♪
♪To complete♪
♪A joy that needs no brave pretense♪
♪How cruel sincerity can be♪
♪Like a door with no key♪
♪Maybe you just passed by♪
♪The tears in my eyes♪
♪You looked like you had nothing to say♪
♪Then got so good at being cold♪
♪That's why a smile feels so precious♪
♪Maybe you just passed by♪
♪The tears burned into my heart♪
♪Let's say silence was just for show♪
♪Even if I've grown another year♪