Jay-jay. Are you feeling okay?
You don't need to resort
to fighting all the time.
But… if you really have to… Go!
- If that's what you have to.
- Are you sure?
Is it really okay?
Yes!
Your nose is so red!
You look stupid!
You better stop mocking me.
This was all your fault.
- Come with us.
- Yeah, let's go.
Do you think I've forgotten
what you did to me?
Childish!
- Childish?
- Ouch!
I'm getting really pissed at you!
This hurts a lot!
I'm asking you a serious question.
If I end up looking like Voldemort,
you should pay to fix my nose...
Don't move.
Do it properly.
Hold still.
I cannot believe Kiko.
And he won't shut up about
that new transferee, Jay-jay.
She's not even that pretty.
Who's the ugly one again?
[girls screaming]
Give me back my bag!
What are you gonna do to my bag?
The chocolate will melt!
Chocolate?
I'm getting really annoyed at you all!
- Get her bag!
- Jay-jay!
You have guts.
Who do you think you are?
I have a message to Freya.
Can you deliver it?
It's us who have a message for you.
Beat it.
Dude, get up!
Fight!
What?
Did you die over there?
What would you do without me?
Wow... So cocky.
Jay...
Are you okay?
Yeah.
We got to go.
You go ahead. I'll follow in a while.
We gotta go now!
Tss.
Suit yourself.
I should post you on Social Media.
Caption it with "Ungentlemanly!"
You move like a turtle.
If only his personality
was as pretty as his face.
I might get bashed, though.
Jay!
Where are they?!
Where's Keifer?
He already left.
Find him.
Where are you hurt?
Behind you!
What are you doing?
It'll take too long if I don't carry you.
There's something
different about Yuri today.
He seems nice.
Far from the Yuri that
I've always clashed with.
Can I ask you a favor?
Take the fall for this
incident with Section D.
If you're wondering why...
Because Keifer can't be
implicated in anymore trouble.
Fine.
I'll take the fall.
[thunder rumbles]
What the fuck?
Why is the King of Assholes ignoring me,
after he helped with those demons?
Guys, guys.
There's an announcement in the group chat.
Classes are suspended.
Most of the students went home already.
[boys cheering]
Aries, can I ride back home with you?
- Ci-N wanna share a ride?
- Let's go.
Jay, we're going ahead.
Bye, Jay.
Wake up bro.
You're staying?
Maybe you enjoy being alone here.
Hey... wait.
Tss.
What are you scoffing for?
When you scoff like that,
you're kinda like Keifer.
I just scoffed and I'm already like Keifer?
Aren't you too obsessed with him?
Hey!
What the hell?
I'm sorry.
Just go home.
Yuri... are you related to Keifer?
No. Why?
You have the same attitude.
As if you're possessed.
Possessed?
- That's the term you chose?
- Uh-huh.
Tss.
Whatever.
See! You're practically the same!
Hey, wait up!
Keifer 2.0! Wait a minute!
Stupid comparison.
You know it's my first
time taking this shortcut.
Why won't you wait for me, Keifer 2.0?
So I'm Keifer 2.0 huh?
Let's see how you can handle this!
How do I cross now?!
Swim!
[Jay-jay screams]
Mud! It got on my shoes!
I'm stuck in the mud! Please help me!
I'm gonna die here!
Quicksand! Quicksand, help!
I'm gonna die! I'm really gonna die!
Gosh, it's so muddy!
Hold this.
Why did you come back?
You look so stupid.
Here, hold this.
Just admit you were
bugged by your conscience.
Hold it!
Alright.
Wait, what are you gonna do?
I'll carry you.
Stupid.
Where?
Where's the cow?
On the count of three...
Ready.
One.
Two.
Three.
[Yuri screams]
[Jay-jay screams]
I'm sorry. Are you hurt?
No, but we have to get up now.
It's so disgusting.
Oh no, I didn't mean it! Sorry!
[Yuri groans in pain]
I'm really sorry.
Just...
Just don't move, okay?
Why are you walking funny?
You'll never understand.
Can it get any worse?!
This is Aries' fault.
What the hell.
Let's go.
Huh?
I'm not asking for your help.
Come on, get in. So we're even.
Works for me.
Here. Wear this.
You might die due to the cold.
All set?
Yeah. Thanks.
- Put on your seatbelt.
- Oh, yeah. Sorry.
Jay?
Wake up. We're here.
Where are we?
The roads to your place
are all flooded, that's why…
I thought it's better for us
to stay here at our place first.
Let's go.
To my place?
How did you know the way to my place?
I didn't even tell you where I live.
Uh... Ci-N told me.
I still don't know the exact address,
but you were sleeping like a baby.
I didn't want to wake you up.
Oh.
Alright.
Good afternoon.
Wait…
Where exactly are we?
This is not a house. It's a building!
I know.
This is where I live.
Really?
Mr. Hanamitchi, do you need anything?
No, thank you.
Let's go.
Hey!
Are you seriously saying
this is where you live?
Big time Mr. Hanamitchi.
Woah… this is massive.
Are you for real? This is not a joke?
[Jay-jay gasps]
You have elevators in your house?!
That's so cool.
Even Section E's building
doesn't have one of these.
Thank you.
Well, when you think about it,
we're in a building anyway.
Let's go.
Come in.
[in Japanese]
Welcome Home, Young Master.
What was that?
They call you "Young Master?"
Mind your own business.
I just brought you here
because I didn't have a choice.
You're so cranky.
I also didn't have a choice.
Sit down.
Are you sure?
I'm still dripping…
Sit.
Are you sure? If this couch gets ruined
I don't have money to replace it.
Young Master, your
grandfather is looking for you.
Tss.
Tell him to go back to Japan.
You jerk. Learn how to respect your elders.
Was hitting my head necessary?
I'll take a shower first.
Don't tell him I'm with someone.
Let's go.
Huh?
Let's go!
Take it off now.
What?!
My jacket. Take it off.
I'll have it washed.
Ahh.
I thought you were...
Take a bath.
Just find something you can wear.
How about you?
I'll shower in the guest room.
You want us to go together?
Hmm?
What I mean is, I'll use the guest room
so you'll feel comfortable here.
Alright.
Thank you.
That bath was nice.
Oh?
Where is my bag?
Well, I don't think it's
gonna get lost in here.
Wait... what's the view like up here?
Let's go see it.
Ouch...
Wow!
So beautiful!
Woah...
You can see everything up here.
The lights are so pretty.
How can you even sleep here?
It's so nice to look at.
So beautiful...
Wow, you can see everything here.
So pretty.
Enjoying the view?
Oh.
Don't you have any other color to wear?
We look like we're in a dance group.
You're the one borrowing my clothes,
but you have the nerve to compain.
The maid took my dirty clothes.
I was gonna head out, actually.
But how can I step out
in these baggy clothes?
You can wear it for now.
It's gonna be quick to clean.
There's a dryer here.
The rain stopped.
But the streets may still be flooded.
Unbelievable...
You're so rich.
You own this whole building.
Who had this building constructed?
The Old Man.
He wants to feel like...
He's not far away from his hometown.
That's why he had this built.
Hmm.
But where are your parents?
In Japan.
They're running our business there.
Why don't I hear you speak Japanese
if you're Japanese?
I'm in the Philippines, right?
Why would I speak Japanese here?
Is this really your hair color?
It probably isn't, right?
But it suits you.
Maybe you're imitating
Sakuragi from Slam Dunk.
Maybe...
Are you related?
You're both called Hanamitchi.
Sakuragi's not even real.
Ah.
You're right.
You know what, I take back what I said.
You're different from Keifer.
What do you mean?
You're easier to approach and talk to.
I like it better when you're like this.
Young Master. Your
grandfather is calling for you.
Just wait for me here.
He wants your friend to join you.
Yuri,
Who is this girl?
Speak in Tagalog.
We're in the Philippines.
Who is this girl with you?
Why did you bring her here?
Are you going to sleep already?
What are you gonna do?
We're having a sleepover.
Just us two.
What the hell!
She's my classmate.
We got caught in the rain. Got drenched.
So I brought her here.
A classmate?
Don't lie to me, Yuri.
It's the first time you
brought a girl home.
What is your name?
I'm Jasper Jean Mariano.
Jay-jay for short.
Who are your parents?
I'm not acquainted with any Mariano.
Ahh...
I don't know who my father is.
My mother, however...
She lives with the Fernandez clan.
Fernandez?
You're related to Michael Angelo Fernandez?
Fer Corp's new CEO?
Yes. He's my cousin.
Hey!
I thought I was late.
Not yet.
How are you and your grandfather?
It's nothing to worrry about.
What's funny?
Nothing. I just remembered
what you were doing there yesterday.
How was it again? When you were
clenching your legs like this.
- See? You remembered it too.
- "Crazy!"
Was it really painful? As in?
From 1 to 10? Was it 9?
Because it looked like
you were in real pain.
You're pushing it.
And your face became so flushed!
What was your face again like?
Just tell me. 1 to 10.
Why won't you let the topic go, Jay-jay?
Come on, 1 to 10?
Spill it! Maybe it's up to 20
that's why your face got all contorted.
Hey!
Hey, why are you ignoring me?
Hi, Jay-jay.
Move over.
Where were you?
At home. Where else?
What's up with the two of you?
Ahh. Jay-jay was stranded at our place.
At your place? How?
What do you mean how?
It rained, and then...
We went to our place
and got stranded there.
One more time.
But don't worry.
Nothing changed.
Your plan is still intact.
Jasper Jean Mariano?
And Mark Keifer Watson.
Come with me to the Guidance Office.
[students teasing]
You're in trouble.
[students continue teasing]
Ma'am, we were just hanging out in the gym.
When Jay suddenly went to us.
We asked her what she's doing there.
And we told her to go.
That's right, Ma'am.
We were suddenly attacked by that girl!
We tried fighting her off, but...
She's a girl.
We can't just hurt her.
We tried stopping her amidst
the flurry of her kicks and punches.
But then...
Keifer arrived and did this to us.
Is there something funny Miss Mariano?
Are all of these true?
Ma'am.
Not all he said was true.
Yes, we were in a fight.
But it was their fault in the first place.
He was the first to throw a punch.
Yeah. And then he fell on his face.
This one started it.
And this one also tripped.
That's not true at all!
Ma'am, that's not the truth.
It's true! It's true!
[students bickering]
So who's at fault here?
It's Keifer!
Keifer,
I'm so tired of your shenanigans.
I already warned you about it.
One more offense and you're expelled.
I thought you already learned your lesson
after what you did at the canteen.
You know it will be difficult to defend you
from the school board this time.
I hope...
Can I ask you a favor?
Take the fall for the
incident with Section D.
If you're wondering why...
Because Keifer can't be implicated
in any more trouble.
What's your defense, Mr. Watson?
Stop it!
It's not Keifer's fault.
I was the one who started it.
It was me alone.
These jerks are just ashamed
to admit they lost to a girl.
Miss Mariano, what are you talking about?
I'm telling you that it
was my fault, Ma'am.
I wasn't just caught in it.
I actually attacked these
students from Section D.
You're aware of my records
from my old school, right?
Miss Mariano...
This is serious.
You can be expelled.
You'll expel me for this incident, Ma'am?
That is why, if you are tying
to cover up for Mr. Watson,
this should stop now.
But it's true.
It was all my fault.
Okay.
Then call your guardian.
Now.
Are you sure about what you're doing?
You're welcome.
Don't blame me for it.
You helped me, didn't you?
If you know you're gonna be
expelled for it, why did you do it?
No particular reason.
Do you want to get expelled?
I knew it.
Should I retract my statement?
If you want to... it's okay.
No need.
It really was my fault anyway.
Jay-jay!
What the hell did you do this time?
Unbelievable!
Promise?
Promise, my ass.
You're lucky I was
able to pull some strings.
But now, do you know you lost your chance
to transfer to another section?
Of course you know it.
Or maybe not.
I don't know.
You don't know.
You weren't expelled,
but the school guidance will monitor you
just like Keifer and Yuri.
You know Yuri?
Don't fucking change the topic.
You promised you won't
get into fights anymore.
But fuck, I forgot.
Promises are meant to be broken.
What would Mom say?
Auntie?
And even Grandma.
And then there's Dad!
I should probably chain you to Aries,
so he can keep an eye on you.
I pulled strings to get
you into this school.
Ending, another record.
What's your plan?
Nothing of course.
I already fixed it for you.
Jay-jay.
I hope you are aware of the
repercussions of your actions.
I'm sorry, Angelo.
I know you're covering up for Keifer.
Why?
Is he doing something to you?
Is he threatening you?
No, Angelo.
Then tell me the truth.
I know that Keifer.
It's true!
He actually helped me out.
I'm sorry...
Alright.
Let's just eat together.
Where you do you want to eat?
It's okay, Angelo. I'll eat at home.
No, let's go.
Sir, we have an urgent
meeting in 10 minutes.
You are needed at the office,
There's just an issue with the Macao team.
Can you make it Sir?
Okay, got it.
I'll go now.
Thank you, sir. We scheduled it
without you because it's urgent.
Okay.
I'll be there.
I'm also still working on
the Hanamitchi appointment schedule, sir.
Close it immediately.
Jay-jay. I don't think we can go after all.
I have an urgent meeting to attend.
It's alright, Angelo.
I'm sorry. You're so busy
but you still went and helped me.
Alright. How about this?
I know you're hungry.
So I'll just drop you off at the
nearest mall. You can eat there.
It's fine, Angelo.
Really?
But you gotta eat. You're skin and bones.
But promise me.
Don't give us any more trouble.
Okay?
Avoid getting involved in fights.
Your studies is what's important.
Yes, Angelo. I promise.
Alright.
Here. Buy whatever you want.
You know how to use a credit card?
Yes.
Thank you, Angelo.
Okay.
Mom, I'll just meet up with Ella.
Okay. Take care of yourself.
Oh. Hello, Auntie.
Jay-jay.
You went on a shopping spree?
And a new bike to boot.
Oh, yeah. So you don't
have to bring me to school.
How did you afford all that?
Angelo let me borrow his credit card.
He told me to buy whatever I want.
And you abused it.
How did you and Angelo see each other?
I was suspended.
You got suspended and then went shopping?
I'm sorry...
But I bought the bike so
I can get to school easier.
It was the only thing I bought for myself.
All of these, I bought for you.
Bought with someone else's money?
Jay...
next time, ask permission properly.
I'm sorry, Auntie.
But Aries was right.
I was suspended, and then
I spent Angelo's money as if it was mine.
Why did you get suspended, by the way?
They started it! I was
just defending myself!
- Remember, you told me to.
- Alright!
It's okay. I understand.
But be careful.
Okay, Auntie.
Oh. Look at this, Auntie. It's so pretty.
- Is this mine?
- Yes, it's for you!
Oh my gosh, really?
- It's lovely, right?
- Wow!
Young master.
Hey.
Yuri.
What is this, a celebration
for your suspension?
Let's just drink.
Let's celebrate Jayjay
going along with our plan.
What happened?
Nothing.
Why did she take the blame at the
Guidance Office? What did you tell her?
I don't know.
The risk for expulsion paid off.
Or maybe, she's returning
the favor because...
I helped her fight those
boys from Section D.
Is it worth it?
If she didn't take the fall,
you could have been expelled.
But she took the blame, right?
And if it's against Aries,
it will all be worth it.
Now that we've tested
Jay-jay's loyalty to Section E,
We can use her against him.
Loyalty to Section E...
Or loyalty to you?
Why?
How about you?
You're doing things on your own.
You still haven't answered
why she was stranded at your place.
I have nothing to explain, right?
It rained.
It just happened.
It probably helped our cause.
She did that little favor I asked of her.
All your faults...
she took the blame for it.
Without you even saying a thing to her.
I don't know.
It's just that you guys were laughing
when you entered the classroom.
Aren't we getting her loyalty?
It's party time!
[boys cheering]
Yes, sir!
- Yes, sir!
- Yuri, Keifer.
- Let's get drunk!
- Let's go.
Unlimited shots tonight,
bro. Unlimited shots!
Unli shots tonight.
Let's shot, dude!
Shot, shot, shot!
Let's go!
Alright, guys. Everyone. Wait up.
That one's vodka, bro.
Hey, listen. Listen, listen.
- Guys, guys, guys.
- Yo, he said listen.
Let's toast.
To Jay-jay.
And the downfall of Aries.
Cheers!
So bro, what's the plan?
How are we gonna use Jay-jay against Aries?
Well...
I've noticed how protective Aries
gets when Jay-jay gets hurt.
You saw how he acted
during that PE class, right?
- Yeah, that's right.
- It's a weak spot.
They're family.
We can use her against him.
So you're actually saying
na we're gonna hurt her?
What do you mean "hurt?"
I'm gonna make her fall in love with me.
That sounds new.
And when she thinks I can protect her...
Aries won't stand a chance.
Then...
We can use her.
To destroy him.
Woah. That's fire bro, huh.
Dope.
It's getting spicy! Nice one.
What should I be doing?
I'll make her fall for me.
Dude...
It's all about the big gestures.
With girls...
They love the corny stuff.
The cheesier, the better.
They get butterflies.
I'm an expert at that.
You know, last week...
Hey, listen up! Last week, I had a date...
She got giddy at my corny
jokes and cheesy lines.
I swear to God, it worked.
You're just naturally corny.
What are you talking about?
But it really works!
No, no.
I know, I know.
Become a knight in shining armor.
Set up a fake problem,
and then save her and become her hero.
- Gotta flex your muscles, bro!
- Yeah!
Or! Or!
What is it this time?!
Buy her a bouquet of flowers.
- You really are corny.
- Nice, nice, nice.
Then put it in her bag.
I swear to God.
She'll get butterflies.
I swear.
Give me more ideas!
I have one.
Listen...
Put some sexual tension between
the two of you when you're together.
Only when you're alone with each other.
Or use the push-and-pull method.
Yeah, that's a great idea! I know that one!
- That's not what he meant!
- Oh, sorry.
What I mean by that is be sweet to her...
then pull back from time to time.
I swear, she won't be
able to get enough of you!
She'll go crazy for you.
It works.
I'm manipulative.
What else? Give me.
Suggestions, boys. Suggestions.
I was thinking...
maybe instead of just pretending...
What if... we doing
something really nice for her?
Show her we're on her side.
Right?
Simp!
[boys teasing]
- That's embarrassing.
- You're so corny.
No, no.
He's actually right.
I'll make her fall for me.
And then I'll break her heart.
Ohhh.
I told you, guys.
You're really on fire, bro.
Actually, bro.
I read somewhere that it's
"the little things that matter."
Like cleaning her
table or fixing her chair.
Bro, things like that get noticed more.
Sometimes, it difficult
to put things into words, right?
Just like you!
[boys teasing]
Cheers.
Let's get drunk tonight, boys!
Yeah, unli shots!
[Boys chattering]
Jay-jay!
Jay!
[Ci-N and David cheering]
- It's Jay-jay, bro!
- Jay-jay!
We miss you, Jay!
You're so pretty today, Jay.
Can I borrow money?
Did these jerks eat something funny today?
Why are they so friendly to me?
Missed you.
Am I seeing things right?
The King of Assholes, smiling at me?
What's he doing here?
Hey.
What a mess.
- Give that to me.
- Oh... Ouch, it hurts.
My wallet is hurting.
- Your wallet?
- Yeah.
[groaning]
This seat's taken.
Find another one.
What's your problem?
Sit with me.
Come.
Huh?
Thanks.
Get that off.
Hey! Who's there?!
Ay!
Don't tell Aries that I'm here.
Oh... can you say this?
"Ella is a bitch."
Ella is a bitch.
Oh! Confirmed!
It was Freya who said it, not you.
Why are you with her?
Mica?
Uh-uh-uh!
Stay there!
You must be 10 feet away from Mica.
Step back! Step back!
Move some more! Over there!
She can't stay here.
Are you out of your mind?
I can't let Section D
have their way with Mica!
We can't meddle in their mess.
Jay-jay?
I just wanted to ask you a favor.
Don't let Calix get closer to Mica anymore.
Why?
I'm horrible...
I'm such a jerk!
Hey!
What's wrong?
We're doing a 500-meter run today, okay?
Catch me!
What is wrong with you?
Spin her around until
her face turns violet!