(Uilhan Brewery)
(1. Malting, 2. Malt milling,
3. Mash tun, 4. Hopping)
(Kim Se Jeong)
(Highly passionate, highly sensitive)
(Lee Jong Won)
(Shin Do Hyun)
(Baek Sung Chul)
(Uilhan Brewery)
(Naro Beer)
(Brewing Love)
(This is a work of fiction.) (Scenes with
child actors and animals were filmed...)
(under production guidelines
along with experts.)
(Episode 12)
Some things in this
world can be messed with...
while some things in this world are sacred.
Together should've been
off-limits from beginning to end.
That's right.
What you did was wrong.
Yong Ju.
I sense a murderous vibe.
I'll get going.
Unbelievable.
Do you have to go?
Maybe I should go instead.
This is my specialty.
I'm not stopping you since
you're not one to be stopped,
but stay safe.
You'll get an earful from me
if you return home with bruises.
- Got it? - Sure.
I'll be back soon.
This is the office of the
business that Baekmok Liquor hired...
to write malicious comments online?
They terrorize people online,
so who am I to sit out
the crack down on terror?
I didn't know that such a business existed.
How did you find out about this place?
Min Ju's ex-girlfriend...
is the team leader of
Baekmok's marketing team.
Did you hit her?
- I bet you did. - Don't be ridiculous.
She spilled the beans
the second Min Ju asked.
It put me in a combative
mood, and I love it.
Min Ju will be waiting,
so let's get this over with.
But I'm a pacifist.
Who are you? How are you here?
We're from Baekmok Liquor.
We recently came to you with a job.
One that involved tarnishing
Jisang Liquor's reputation.
Oh, right. You're a client of ours.
Did you read what we spread online?
We dragged its new beer through the mud.
Another attack from us tomorrow...
will be the final nail in the coffin.
Is that so?
I never said you could enter.
Boys, show them.
What the...
Hold on a second.
This isn't for me.
I'm not as flexible as I used to be.
I'm off to see Min Ju!
I'm off to see Ah Reum!
I shouldn't have let her leave.
I should've made her stay.
Darn, this is too much.
When will she be home?
What took you so long?
Hold on. Weren't you injured? Let me see.
I'm fine. I didn't get hurt.
I, for one, am great at keeping promises.
Don't wear this again.
Got it?
If that's what you want.
(Brewing Love)
(Together Marketing Strategy)
Our task at hand...
is to resuscitate Together...
which has lost the trust of the people.
First, we begin with a sincere apology.
(Jisang Liquor's Public Apology)
("Together" will be
recalled and then relaunched!)
(As an apology, the price will be lowered!)
Then, we offer clean compensation.
We'll reduce the profit margin...
and provide beer of high
quality at a lower price.
So how can we prove that
our beer is of high quality?
(Together Marketing Strategy)
They used the media, so we should too.
(Jisang Liquor's Together)
(Wins Gold Award at
International Blind Beer Contest!)
There's the Gold Award we won.
After planting expectations...
in consumers who have turned their backs,
we will make sure the
beer is easily accessible.
Restaurants, bars,
convenience stores, and retail shops.
Together must be where
people can find them.
Our goal for this project is to
sell all the beer manufactured.
I was the top salesperson
at the Busan office.
Put your faith in me and follow my lead.
- Come on! - Sure.
As you know, the Liquor Tax
Act prohibits manufacturers...
from directly selling their
products to small businesses.
That's why wholesalers
act as a bridge between us.
In other words, to sell
all our manufactured beer,
wholesalers must buy everything we have.
You came, sir.
Yong Ju, I see you
went all out on this one.
I'm ready for battle, so I
hope you think fondly of us.
Nice. I love the attitude.
- You can trust me on this. - Sure.
All right. Let's head inside.
He's the chairman...
of the National Liquor
Wholesalers Association.
With him are the chairmen
of provincial associations.
It's not a stretch to say...
that they move all the liquor in Korea.
How we sell Together to them today...
will mark its success or failure.
Then, let us begin.
Hello.
We thank everyone who have come...
to the launching event of
Jisang Liquor's new beer.
First, we'll hear from the chairman...
of the National Liquor
Wholesalers Association...
who blessed us with his presence today.
Goodness.
Please don't.
I'm not one to give speeches.
(VIP guests)
Well, I'll say this one thing.
I vouch for that lady
standing in front of you today.
Her beer will be stellar.
Let's help her sell all of them.
After you taste it, of course.
- When will we get to taste it?
- In just a moment.
(Jisang Liquor)
Greetings.
I am Yoon Min Ju, the
brewmaster of Together.
The concept behind our new beer
is a beer that you can select.
Rather than beer that makes you drunk,
this is beer that you select.
The flavour, the colour,
and the alcohol by volume.
Select beer according to
your preference with Together.
Select yours right this instant.
(VIP guests)
It was fun to choose.
All right.
The beer you can select. For Together!
- Cheers. - Cheers.
(Jisang Liquor)
I love the smell.
Isn't it great?
- That's incredible.
- These flavours are clean.
- I'm amazed. - No way.
- I can't believe it. - My gosh.
This has a chance of selling well.
I absolutely loved it.
Great job!
- Can we have another bottle?
- That was nice.
Gosh, that's good.
I appreciate everything you did today, sir.
I've now paid off all my debt.
Here. How about a handshake?
There.
(A few weeks later)
Honey, what do you want to drink?
- Beer? - Sounds good.
With this beer, you can
choose the flavours and its ABV.
- Then... - Yes?
I want the one that is stronger.
I'll have the 11 percent Together.
Eleven percent?
- Are you sure about that? - Of course.
Ma'am, we'll have the 5
percent and 11 percent Together.
Sure.
- Excuse me. - Yes?
We'll have 2 bottles of Together 9...
- and a Together 11. - Sure.
- We'll have two more.
- Sure. Just a second.
Let's gather if you're done
researching the market share.
Congratulations on fully selling
the first batch of Together!
- Cheers. - Nice!
(Ddobong Fried Chicken)
I don't think we ordered enough.
- Can we have the menu? - Wait.
This is more than enough.
Not when there are this many people.
- Have this. - Are you good?
- Is it good? - Yes!
- It's good. - Right?
- Yes. - No way.
Look at these generous portions.
Fried chicken and beer
go together the best.
Could there be more to happiness?
Yong Ju, there's still the
most important task left.
The Busan office.
- It won't close. - Of course not.
The branch manager of the Busan office...
will be at the head office tomorrow.
I will have the director
finalize our agreement.
Don't you worry.
I'm finally going back to Busan.
You're coming too,
right? Of course you will.
That was some hard work we did.
Cheers, everyone!
Cheers.
- Cheers. - Right.
Cheers!
Let me see. Why aren't you in a good mood?
What? I'm totally fine.
I know it was rough, Yong Ju.
The others did all the heavy lifting.
Nothing's cooler...
than telling yourself
that you did a great job.
- Is that so? - Yes.
Good work.
You did great, Chae Yong Ju.
Come here.
You did great.
I did great.
(Jisang Liquor)
Could the air be more refreshing
at the office these days?
Maybe it's because I don't
have to see Director Yeom.
No, wait.
Maybe it's because Together is
seeing an upward trend in sales.
I owe this all to you, Yong Ju.
That was fine work from my beloved junior.
- Who is he calling his junior? - What?
- Sir. - Yes?
It's about time you dealt with
the closing of the Busan office.
Will you keep our doors
open like you promised?
Come on. Of course. I'm a man of my word.
I already informed the company president,
and he's well aware of
the good work Ms. Chae did.
So don't you worry about a thing.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
I have one more favour to ask.
- Shoot. - Assistant Manager Kang Beom.
Could he be reassigned to the Busan office?
Why?
Wouldn't it be nice
for him to work with you?
Don't tell me...
you're also going back to Busan.
Absolutely not.
You're now Ms. Chae of
the Marketing Team here.
You're one of my people.
We have so much to do...
Isn't that something
Ms. Chae should decide?
I'll believe that this
matter will be handled well...
and head back to Busan.
Then...
I'll show him out.
Do you have some time to spare?
Of course.
- Can we talk? - Sure thing.
Come on.
How does it feel to have
sold all the beer? Good?
Yes, I guess.
I thought I'd be over the moon,
but the emotions hit me more calmly.
I did everything I could and that was it.
Of course.
Remember when you came to
our office for a job interview?
Do you know why I hired you
when experience in the military...
was all that you had on your resume?
Beats me. I had always
been curious about that.
No one seemed as desperate as you did.
Others said they'd do their best...
and work hard.
But do you know what you said to me?
You said you'd get the
job done no matter what.
You said doing your best
was always there by default...
and that there was no
choice when it came to...
making something happen or not.
The only option was to make it happen.
That...
was how desperate you were.
To be honest,
I used you.
Back then, I needed someone who
was really desperate, like you.
So, Yong Ju.
From now on, you can do
anything and everything you want.
In life, there comes a time...
when you feel like you
can leave with no regrets.
When you feel like
you've given your all here,
you'll embark on a new journey.
You can leave and find a new path.
If you realize that you
were really happy here,
you can always come back.
So, try to find that new path.
Not something you have
to do out of desperation.
I want to see you...
doing something that makes your heart sing.
Thank you, sir.
But...
I'm worried about Beom.
He followed me and
moved to Seoul, you know.
I should stay by his side
until he can transfer to Busan...
I object.
What? Beom.
Hey, you scared us. When did you get here?
Yong Ju.
I like you.
- What? - My goodness, Beom.
What's with you? We're
family here. This is awkward.
I respect you and like you.
It's both.
Well, I'm not confessing
my feelings to you...
to try and come between you
and Mr. Yoon like a weasel.
I wish the two of you
nothing but happiness.
That's why I'm telling you how I feel.
As for Mr. Yoon, I admit
that he's a real catch.
So, I give up with no hard feelings.
As if they'd let you
meddle in their relationship.
Come on, sir.
I'm supposed to look very
cool as I'm saying this now.
My goodness.
As of today, I'm done...
being glued to you.
I can take care of myself,
so just...
do what you need to do.
I'm sorry, Beom.
Actually, no.
Thank you, Beom.
Hearing you call my name like
that makes my heart flutter.
Anyway, I'm off.
My gosh, Beom.
Are you crying?
I'm off too.
Wait, Beom!
Is there anything you want to eat?
Really?
I think you're worried about something.
Is it that obvious?
I catch these things very quickly.
Do you know what Mr. Nam said to me today?
He said I could go ahead
and do what I wanted.
I swore loyalty to Jisang
Liquor for the rest of my life.
When I heard him say that
I could leave the company...
How should I put this?
I felt...
You know, strangely enough...
You felt okay?
Yes.
I did.
I guess...
I've really given my all.
So, I guess you've made up your mind.
Yes.
But I'm not sure if this
is the right thing to do.
I've made up my mind for now,
but I might have a
change of heart tomorrow.
I suppose there's a
right time for everything.
I should've let myself
be passionately in love...
and encouraged myself to really
figure out what I wanted to do.
I feel lost like a teenager.
I never felt this way
even when I was a teen.
It's a good thing that
you're going through this.
I think this is the right
time for you to go through this.
You think so?
You know, I always
thought I was very decisive.
So, I have no idea why I'm so hesitant now.
I feel like I have no
clue as to what to do.
I'm never like this, you know.
I'm very good at my job.
It's because you've never
really thought about yourself...
or what you want to do.
As for your job, you've
garnered enough experience...
and skills through trial and error.
But you've never really faced
yourself or your true needs,
so you feel lost and confused now.
But even feeling lost and
confused like that is part of you.
And that's the Chae Yong Ju I love.
What if I can't snap
out of the confusion...
and end up falling apart?
Then we'll fall apart
together, holding hands.
We'll take some time off and recharge.
We'll enjoy a good cup
of coffee together too.
That sounds nice.
What? Rao!
You're here already?
It's only 7am now.
Come on, Yong Ju. I always
come to work this early.
I need this time for self-development.
Really? I had no idea.
What is this?
Are you planning to get a new job too?
You too?
No. I meant, you.
- I was talking about you. - I see.
Isn't it something you always think of?
If you get an offer for a better position,
you have to take it.
Really?
I've never even thought about it.
You're too loyal to the company.
I do have the tendency to be like that.
Go on and study.
Wait, Yong Ju.
I thought the idea of "working
hard" would be the same for everyone.
But you taught me that it was not the case.
Compared to you, I'm
not really a hard worker.
It was a pleasure...
working as your teammate.
What's with you?
- Thanks, Rao. - Keep up the great work.
- Should we go for lunch now?
- Sure, sounds good.
- Let's go. - Yes, let's go.
Yong Ju, let's go and have lunch.
I'm not hungry. You go ahead.
Enjoy your lunch.
- You should come with us.
- Come and eat with us.
- Don't skip lunch. - Enjoy your lunch!
(Letter of Resignation)
Thanks.
I support you.
- What do you mean?
- No matter what you decide,
I will support your decision.
Why don't we become friends?
The kind of friend who runs to
be with you when you need a friend.
I'd like that.
I'm a fast runner.
Nice.
Chae Yong Ju.
You're pretty.
Pardon?
I don't know why, but
hearing it always cheers me up.
Thank you.
You're pretty too.
(Letter of Resignation)
Hello?
Yes!
Yes, sir.
Right. Together is getting great feedback.
That's right. Oh, I didn't even do much.
It's all thanks to your
incredible foresight, sir.
Yes, thank you.
Yes, I'll do my best!
That was the chairman. He called me first.
Hey, Ms. Chae.
We should keep the momentum going
and develop other new products too.
Actually, hold on. We should...
make Yoon Min Ju our official brewmaster.
What do you think?
You're due for a promotion, Ms. Chae.
(Letter of Resignation)
Chae Yong Ju.
I thought long and hard
before making this decision.
No, no way. I will not accept this.
I can't accept this. I will not.
Come on. We're on a roll.
Mr. Na.
Please accept my resignation letter.
Those eyes.
Fine, let me at least hear your reason.
I feel like myself only when I'm working.
Outside of work,
I really don't know who I am.
So, I want to find myself.
Thank you for everything.
(Jisang Liquor)
I'll be off, then. You
don't need to walk me out.
Bye.
- Bye. - Thank you for everything.
What? Why do you all look so sad
as if you'll never see me again?
It is sad to think that we'll
never see you again at work.
I still find it so hard to believe.
Chae Yong Ju is leaving Jisang Liquor?
I'm going to call you all the time.
- I'll walk you to your car. - Hold on.
You must never be clingy
when you say goodbye.
I'm totally fine,
and we'll stay in touch,
so you have no reason to be sad. All right?
Bye, guys.
Bye.
Min Ju.
I'm unemployed now.
- Yong Ju. - Yes, sir.
Got it. I'll give it a try.
Hello, I'm here to promote Likey.
It's delicious. Please try it.
You need to pay what you
owe before you run away,
- Mr. Park! - Mad Dog Yong Joo?
Why do you work so hard?
Shouldn't I work hard at my own job?
We're shutting down the business.
I'll get Yoon Min Ju
on board, no matter what.
Mr. Yoon.
How about you spare me five minutes?
Let's brew a new kind of beer.
Together. You and us.
I will sign the contract with Ms. Chae.
Welcome to Jisang Liquor.
- Finally! - Let's do this!
At last, it's ready.
Good job, Ms. Chae.
You too, Mr. Yoon.
And the gold award
winner is Uilhan Brewery.
Why can't the beer be transported today?
This batch of beer will be dumped.
Ms. Chae, don't try to
carry the burden alone.
Let us help you.
We're a team.
My point, exactly. We're a team!
Congratulations on fully selling
the first batch of Together!
- Cheers. - Nice!
It's all over now.
It's not over.
You're starting a new chapter of your life.
He's coming out.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Are you here for the class? - Yes.
- Come on in. - Finally, we're here.
It was so hard to book this one-day class.
It really was. Can you open up more days?
And they're all such small classes.
I like how it is now.
I can only take on what I can handle.
Come inside.
(Uilhan Brewery)
All right. Today, we'll brew ale.
Shall we get started?
All right. Now, we're
going to cool it down.
We'll use this chiller.
Using a chiller like this
helps it cool down fast...
and prevents bacterial growth.
Like this. One moment, please.
Move it up and down like this
while keeping up the pace...
to cool it down quickly.
This helps prevent bacterial growth.
- Do you want to try it? - Me?
Yes.
- Just do this? - Yes.
Move it up and down. Slowly.
You're good.
As I said earlier...
Inside the chiller,
there's something cold...
Wait a second.
When did you arrive? It will end shortly.
Oh, really?
Wait. Are you jealous now?
Not at all!
It's freezing. Why is it so cold?
I felt this summer would never end,
but suddenly it's getting too cold.
Did you have to roll up your sleeves
and be sexy, saying "Bounce it?"
Please. That's why?
Don't go anywhere. I'll be back shortly.
Do you think I have too much
time to spend on whatever?
Gosh.
Isn't it hard to lead the class?
I mean, meeting people itself.
Don't worry. I only do what I can handle.
And most importantly,
I get refreshed soon after.
Whatever.
What? Oh, wait.
Father, please!
- Yes, father. - Are you busy?
Yes, too busy.
Hello, father!
Yong Ju! You were with him.
It's nothing important
but about the pasta...
I made it the same way you taught me.
It actually tastes strange.
I guess you missed something.
How about taking a look at it again?
No way! I followed exactly the same way.
Why don't you come over here
and show me how to make it?
Furthermore,
I miss you too.
Sorry?
I mean, I haven't seen
Yong Ju for a while as well.
I miss you too!
I'll come to you with him as
soon as possible. I miss you.
You should also cook for me!
Yes, Yong Ju. See you soon!
Hang up now.
Don't grumble saying
I always hang up early.
I got it.
Did you hear what he just said?
He's never said he missed me before.
He's also changed a lot.
Let's set the date now.
I want to eat his pasta so much!
Why don't we also eat something now?
I see.
Gosh.
- There's something we should do. - Please.
No, Min Ju. We should
eat now instead of this.
Dad, I'm hungry.
It's almost done!
Min Ho you sweetie, be
ready to enjoy the meal.
Let's see. Here we are.
Nice!
Here.
This is for Mom, and this is for Min Ho.
The former two-star
general broke a sweat...
cooking pasta!
Cooking is much harder!
This pasta makes me totally exhausted!
Min Ho. Please try it. What do you think?
How's it?
It tastes good.
But your face says the opposite.
Tell me frankly. It's okay.
It tastes bad.
Really?
Is it that bad?
But I still like it!
Because you cooked it for me.
Goodness!
Thanks!
Enjoy as much as you want!
Okay.
Oh, and...
How about I get a face treatment?
- What? - I've heard...
there was a treatment called a
facelift that tightens your face.
You hated that kind of treatment before!
You've never had once
whenever I asked you to do.
I mean, I went out with
Min Ho to get him a toy.
But the assistant called me Grandpa.
Gosh.
Gosh, I was so disappointed.
I'm not that old, aren't I?
You aren't yet!
I should dye my hair...
and trim it now and then.
Seriously?
Then, I'll book the entire week for you!
Okay. Let's go!
What a surprise. I don't believe it!
You've never returned home since then?
No, I never went back.
I even saw my family outside.
Congratulations on your return.
Would the door lock password be the same?
Everything is the same.
She must've waited for you every day.
It's so clean.
Aren't you hungry?
Wait a second. I can cook for you.
- Yes. - Is there anything in the fridge?
I guess you usually set the table at home.
You look so natural.
You forgot since I was way too cute,
but I'm the first kid among the five.
I fed up and raised all of them.
I'm the oldest brother!
- Brother? - Yes, "brother."
It's done. Come here already.
Please, say it again.
Come over! The soup
is already getting cold.
I got it.
I loved hearing you say that.
I can say it every day.
Let's eat.
What's this?
Is that for me?
No, it's for me.
Don't guys usually
prepare the diamond rings?
I'll buy my own ring.
Pretty, right?
If you put that on, you'll
really have to marry me.
This is your last chance.
Run when you still can.
Three, two, one. Time's up.
That's a strange proposal.
Fine. I like it.
What's this?
My gosh. When did you prepare this?
Oh, my.
What's this?
(Resident Registration Card, Oh Chan Ran)
- What's this? - Look closely.
"Oh Chan Ran."
Mr. Oh Chan Ran?
Yes. That was my old name.
I changed my name when I got
discharged from the military.
I was hoping a new name...
would make me feel reborn.
Then perhaps, I would be able...
to forget about those nightmares.
That's a pretty name.
- "Chan Ran." - Right?
I liked my name too.
For a guy who took someone else's life,
that name sounds too vibrant.
Only my family remembers this name.
Well, you're my family now.
So you should remember that.
- Gosh, a retirement ceremony? - Goodness.
- It's going to be a big occasion. - Hey.
- Yes, that's it. - You're here.
- My goodness. What's all this?
- You look good.
Hey, you too. You look great.
Well, you know... Were
you going for the BTS look?
- This? Yes. - Yes.
- I'm a member of ARMY. - That suits you.
How do I look? Today is an important day,
so I want to look my best.
You look beautiful. You're just perfect.
Okay. Let's go.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Aren't they a sweet couple?
- Are they getting married?
- How beautiful. - Hello.
Hello.
Welcome, Yong Ju and Min Ju.
You guys are the last ones to show up.
They must think this ceremony is for them.
- Hey! You guys better separate.
- My goodness.
Don't you know our
village prohibits couples...
from showing physical
affection outside their homes?
Do you think you're living in Hollywood?
This is Baegok-ri. Come on!
Why are you bullying them?
They look good together.
- We can do the same thing now.
- My gosh. This is so annoying.
Are you sick?
There they come.
- What is this? - What are they doing?
Why are you doing that?
My gosh, come on.
No! This isn't right. What is this?
- What is this? - What?
- Let me check the microphone. - Okay.
One, two, three, four.
- Yes. I'm Young Ja. - I'm Sook Ja.
We would like...
to thank you all for coming to
our very own retirement ceremony.
Thank you.
We're throwing this party
to talk about our hardships...
and how diligent we've been in life.
Right. We're throwing
this party on our own dime.
- I see. - Okay?
As soon as our retirement ceremony is over,
we'll begin our trip to travel the world.
We worked two jobs and were
so diligent with our lives.
So I guess our hard work paid off.
- Aren't you envious of us? - I am!
- I am. - Could you take us too?
- You guys get to go to Vietnam. - Right.
A long speech at events like
this is bound to be boring.
So we're going to keep our
speech short. You go first.
- You go first. - Come on. Just do it.
My gosh.
We'll keep it short, but still meaningful.
We're not rushing or
anything to catch our flight.
Okay?
We all have our own battles in life.
No one knows how difficult
tomorrow's battle...
will be.
But I hope you will certainly
be happy at least today.
That's it.
That's right.
Fruits aren't the only ones
that have ripening seasons.
Let's pay attention to the
ripening season of our lives.
- Okay? - Okay!
That's it.
- We know it's not much. - Okay.
But do enjoy the food.
- Are you ready? - Ready.
- Have a safe trip! - Safe travels!
- All right. Take care. - Have a nice trip.
- I'm so envious. - Be safe!
- Have a fun time! - We're leaving!
Have fun!
My gosh.
- Mr. Kim? - Yes?
You know that we have unfinished business.
Yes. What do you say?
Should we stir up a
bloodbath here in Baegok-ri?
Rumour has it that...
you're running for village
chief in the upcoming election.
If what I'm hearing is true,
that will put me in a tight spot.
Too bad. Yes, you heard right.
Here's what you have to know about me.
Even my name is Lee Yi Jang.
I was born to live up to my
name and become the village chief.
So I served as chief for
three terms in Baegok-ri.
That means Baegok-ri is me,
and I am Baegok-ri.
I dumbed it down enough for you.
I wonder if you understood that.
My gosh. What are you
talking about? Come on.
Hey, wasn't serving as
chief for three terms...
enough for you?
If you have any sense of decency,
you ought to pull
yourself out of the running.
Wait. Right.
I heard you had already sold
off all your decency at the market.
What did you say?
A young man ought to be the village chief.
I was born a month later
than you. Didn't you know that?
What are you talking about?
Village chiefs these days
have to be good at English.
You must be able to
talk to immigrant workers.
That's what's expected of
a village chief these days!
- You... - Why you...
What's this?
(Candidate for the 18th Village Chief)
(Jjuan)
Honey?
Is there a law that says I'm
not allowed to run for chief?
I'm the youngest one in this village.
I'm the best English
speaker in this village.
It's me. I'm perfect for this position.
You married such an ambitious woman.
I...
- What's that? - Here.
You brought me flowers.
My gosh. Your next
chapter will finally begin.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
What do you say? Should I give you a tour?
Yes.
What's this?
The first step of my next chapter...
is a bottle shop that specializes in beer.
I'm going to buy beer
from small breweries...
across the nation like yours
and sell their beers at my shop.
I will fill the shop with beers I love.
I'll introduce their
beers and sell them too.
You know I can sell anything.
And on one side of the wall,
I'll display some records.
Then I'll play songs I love every day.
Then can my beer have a
presence in your bottle shop?
Well, I'm sorry.
So many breweries already
want a spot in my shop.
But your brewery will be my first supplier.
I should have a meeting with
the bank next week for a loan.
Oh, my. Things are moving so fast.
Is there anything I can help you with?
I'll do this on my own.
You just root for me. Okay.
Okay.
I'm rooting for you.
I can't wait.
It started off with Naro
Beer but ended with Together.
I've tasted every single beer in my shop...
and carefully selected only the best.
I can assure you of the quality.
Especially the beer on the top shelf.
Your grandmother would have been
happy if she were here now. Right?
My grandma?
She would've said, "Good job."
Good job.
Thank you.
They should be here by now.
Yong Ju. I'm here!
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Beom. How are you settling back in Busan?
You look good.
Yong Ju. I'm no longer
an assistant manager.
I'm a section chief.
Who pops open a beer bottle with a spoon?
Hey, new recruit. Many
open bottles with spoons,
but people like us who
brew and sell liquor...
only open them with bottle openers.
Why? When a spoon is used,
bottles can easily be chipped...
which turns them into scrap.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Gosh, look at you!
- I'm proud of you. - Congratulations.
Wait.
Why the long face?
He seems down.
Rao. What's wrong?
- Things are tough these days. - Why?
Sir.
I don't think this is fair.
I know I'm new here,
but I got the job because I
passed the recruitment process.
I don't understand why I have
to make coffee runs like this.
You kept saying that it wasn't fair.
So I accompanied you a few times...
even when I passed the
recruitment process too.
(Jisang Liquor)
That little...
- You deserved it. - Poor you.
Have a drink.
Young people these days
can be quite stubborn.
We have a problem! I'm
serious. This is bad!
Could you please help us?
- Here. - We don't have much time.
- What's this? - What...
I see. You got her parents' blessing.
Good for you. Congratulations.
So Ah Reum's mother was
against the marriage, right?
Don't you know me? I'm
none other than Oh Chan Hwi.
Mother, how about a toast?
Mother, good morning.
Mother, would you like a bite?
My gosh, that's impressive. So
you won her over with your toast?
We thought getting their
blessing would be the end of it.
But there are so many
things we have to prepare.
I can't plan the wedding on my own.
What's the point of planning anything...
when he can't keep up?
Ms. Beautiful Bang is quite upset.
Please cut her some slack.
She has her plate full
with the wedding and work.
She's quite tired.
Ah Reum. You said you would
resign once you got married.
Oh, that? There's a guy
I have to support now.
That's not important.
Guess who the new director
of the Planning Team is.
(Planning Team Director Kim Tae In)
My gosh. I can't believe
he became a director.
My gosh. I can't just sit back and watch.
I'm next. I'll be the youngest
and the first female director.
That's what I'm going to do.
- Oh, my. - My gosh. I love your spirit.
Right. How are you guys?
Us?
- We're so in love. - I love you more.
- I love you more. - No, I love you more.
- I love you more! - My gosh. Okay.
- Come on. - What?
Min Ju. Marriage is all
about making choices. Okay?
Seriously. There are so many
things you have to choose.
Look at the wedding invitation.
We had to choose the paper,
colour, style, and whatnot.
Talk while folding them. Don't slack off.
Okay.
By the way, why are we taking a picture?
Why are you asking? It's nice.
It makes no sense that we
don't have a single group photo.
Right. That's not cool.
Photos will be the only
things we'll have left later.
Min Ju. Hurry.
Okay. The timer is on. We have ten seconds.
I, in my name. Min Ju, in his name.
And for you, live your life in your name.
To beautiful and vibrant us.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
(Thank you for watching Brewing Love.)
(Special thanks to Lee
Duk Hwa for his appearance)
(Brewing Love)