♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 28=
The lord and lady
are really adaptable.
Now that you're in a high position,
they've become servile.
But in my opinion,
they agreed readily enough,
but there's little sincerity.
Sincere or not,
it doesn't matter.
I want them
to bow their heads before Mother
and admit their wrongs.
But that is
a very lenient punishment.
Not at all.
Their resentment is the point.
Mother doesn't need
fair-weather relationships.
I want them
to swallow their pride
and humble themselves
before Mother.
Let them taste
the humiliation Mother endured.
Glad to see your wish was fulfilled.
Not yet.
What?
Well.
Are you done?
Can we go take a walk?
Why are you here?
If you don't come to me,
I'll come to you instead.
I have official paperwork
to complete.
Chu Zhao,
is it on purpose?
It seems
my paperwork needs
your approval?
That's not what I meant.
Yingxiang, let's go back.
What?
Not even some tea
for me?
Must Lady Shijin
personally host me?
Sir.
I'll prepare tea for Miss Xu
and be back shortly.
Aren't you serving me tea?
Let's go.
Enjoy your tea, Miss Xu.
It's cold.
This one seems scalding hot.
Bring another cup.
Is this
how you treat guests?
What has Chu Zhao taught you?
Though I'm a servant,
I keep proper decorum.
You're a lady of status
but lack dignity.
How dare you?
My young master
taught me this.
When above others,
treat them as equals.
When below others,
maintain your integrity.
I've learned it.
I wonder
if you've grasped it.
If you're satisfied now,
I'll take my leave.
Father.
Pingting.
What's it?
What happened?
Tell me.
He doesn't care about me at all.
That's why he let that wretched maid
humiliate me like this.
Don't cry.
I'll make this right for you.
A mere fourth-rank official.
Who does he think he is?
Zilan.
Aren't these hibiscus flowers
laughable?
Laughable?
Yes.
See how they
bloom so vibrantly now.
Unaware that winter's chill
will soon arrive.
When bitter winds blow,
how long can they last?
Your maid...
What's her name?
A lowly person.
Not important.
These gorgeous flowers
can hardly survive winter
without someone to shield them.
Not to mention those worthless weeds.
One careless mistake,
and they'll end up
getting crushed underfoot.
Zilan.
What do you think?
Thank you for the reminder.
I know
I was wrong.
Rufei.
Are you okay?
I'll fetch a physician for you.
I'm the mighty General Feihong.
A minor injury like this
means nothing to me.
Right.
Rufei,
you've been frail since childhood.
I've always worried sick
about you.
But now, you command troops in battle
and have become
the true General Feihong.
Young Master. Please take your medicine.
Young Master.
Your health
has barely recovered.
Don't stop the medicine.
What's the use of recovering?
I'm still trapped
in this wretched courtyard,
unable to go anywhere,
and unable
to do anything.
What do you want to do?
Who are you?
Xu Jingfu.
I know
you're the real He Rufei.
I am the real He Rufei.
Sir,
what brings you here?
I can help you
become the real General Feihong
and achieve your deepest desires.
What do you need
me to do?
(He Yan,)
(every drop of blood I shed,)
(you'll pay back in full.)
(Times have changed.)
(General Feihong's swordsmanship
is peerless,)
(and he couldn't possibly be
an invalid.)
(I can't be who I was before.)
(Chai Anxi resents Xiao Zhongwu)
(for warmongering)
(and has long held grudges.)
(Son Chai Qian)
(Recently,)
(his only child died in battle,)
(deepening his hatred for Xiao Zhongwu.)
(We can exploit this.)
You're General Feihong, He Rufei?
Our family heirloom jade pendant
is only passed
to the eldest legitimate son.
But you're supposed to be
on the front lines.
You want revenge for your son,
don't you?
I can help you.
That message-carrying lieutenant
was later killed
by Ding Yi in battle.
Flawlessly executed.
That's why Xiao Jue
couldn't find any evidence.
I never imagined
you'd done so much
for Chancellor Xu.
My son!
Each of these deeds
warrants beheading
or even clan extermination.
Chancellor Xu
just wants
an obedient general
to counter the Xiao Army.
But if things go wrong,
the blame
will fall solely on you.
I'm not afraid of him.
I'm not his pawn.
I am
the undeniable proof of his guilt.
But...
Father.
As the eldest son
of our family's main lineage,
everything I've done
has been to strengthen
our main lineage.
So, from now on,
no matter what happens,
both of us
must stand united.
Understand?
Yes.
I understand.
Father,
He Yan isn't actually dead.
What?
And she's about to return.
But rest assured.
I absolutely
won't let her enter the capital alive.
Gentlemen,
you look weary.
Please come inside.
(Prosperity Inn)
As we're near Yaojing,
Yan He has vanished.
Seems he's eager to return home.
Sir, your tea.
His wife is pregnant.
He's concerned.
You'll be home soon too.
Right.
That's good.
Where will you stay?
I...
I'll just stay at any inn.
I have recently received some rewards.
So I'm better off now.
Waiter.
Two steamed buns.
Coming.
Why not stay at the Xiao Mansion?
It has a big yard.
And you're Commander's man.
It's appropriate
to be there.
No need.
Okay.
I...
Gentlemen,
our freshest tea.
Please enjoy.
Here.
Sir.
Gentlemen,
fresh tea.
It's best enjoyed while hot.
Alright.
Go.
Who sent you?
Commander,
these men seem to be targeting you.
I have many enemies.
Don't fear. All's well.
It appears
they're after me.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
They couldn't defeat me.
Suicide operatives
with poison in their teeth.
They took it
when cornered.
We're in Chonghuai.
I'll have Yang Mingzhi
from the county office come
and look into their origins.
Okay.
But I know
who sent these assassins
without an investigation.
They've tried to kill me again.
(Chu Mansion)
My painting is crude.
Don't look.
The essence of painting plums
lies in layering and variation.
Like this.
Here.
Zilan.
My bad.
It's okay.
I'll get changed
and return soon.
Sorry.
Our plum painting is unfinished.
Continue?
Yes.
Here, look.
(Yaojing City)
Pendants.
Come and take a look.
(Yaojing City)
- General Feihong!
Do you intend to cling to
an identity that isn't yours
forever?
But
your current achievements
are entirely built upon
being the He family's legitimate heir.
Yaojing.
I've finally returned.
I've sent people to Huayuan
to look for
evidence.
Besides,
recently,
I received a letter from home.
We're commanded to attend
the Mid-Autumn banquet
at the palace.
By then,
Xu Jingfu and He Rufei
will surely attend.
They must have received
news of our return.
But under the Emperor's watchful eye
and considering our positions,
they won't make any moves
before the Mid-Autumn banquet.
You're General Fengyun,
and I'm Attendant Wu'an.
We should naturally
enter the palace banquet with dignity.
If He Rufei
provokes us,
I'm not afraid.
But if he
avoids confronting me,
I'll certainly seek him out.
I'll plant suspicion
in mind of His Majesty
and the court officials.
General He,
you're meticulously planning
every move.
By the end of the Mid-Autumn banquet,
the investigation
in Huayuan will have yielded results.
Then,
we'll determine our next steps
based on the situation.
Stolen things
must eventually be returned.
He Rufei,
between you and me,
it's a fight to the death.
Sir,
the Master and Mistress
ask you to have dinner.
Sir,
your
jade pendant...
(Xiao Mansion)
Jing.
Madam.
You're finally back.
I'm back
with a friend.
This is He Yan.
I am He Yan.
Mr. Xiao and Madam.
So you're Huaijin's friend.
How extraordinary.
We've never seen Huaijin
bring friends home before.
Your friendship must be
exceptional.
Good to see you.
Rongwei personally made dinner
while awaiting your return.
I want
to first see Father and Mother.
(Ancestral Tablets of the Xiao Clan)
(Xiao)
(Commemoration)
(Jing,)
(only by retaking Que City)
(can we uncover the truth of Mingshui,
clear Father's name,)
(and honor the 30,000 fallen men.)
(I)
(deserve to die for this.)
Mr. He,
he's been away so long.
Let him spend time
with Father and Mother.
How about
we wait in the parlour?
After you.
Ancestors,
your descendant,
Xiao Jue, have returned.
This time,
I will surely expose
the disloyal officials,
purge the imperial court,
clear our family's name,
and get justice for our army.
May you protect us.
(Tablet of Father Xiao Zhongwu)
(Tablet of Mother Song Wan)
Father, Mother,
I have something
to tell you.
I've found the most significant person
in my life.
But she still has unfinished matters.
When everything settles down,
I'll surely bring her
to meet you.
These coming days,
I'll be troubling you
and your wife.
No need for formalities.
Since you're Huaijin's friend,
you're our friend too.
Treat this place as your own home.
Stay as long as you wish.
Just relax.
Don't trouble yourself.
The guest room
to my west will be fine.
Huaijin,
didn't you always prefer tranquility?
Why this sudden change?
It seems Huaijin and Mr. He
get along well.
Eat a lot.
The mushroom and chicken stew.
Your favorite.
Eat it.
You remember?
Your favorite.
Of course, I do.
You two share a brotherly bond.
He's never shown this level of care
toward me as his elder brother.
Eat a lot.
Eat.
Miss,
come take a look.
How terribly rude of me
to visit Mr. and Mrs. Xiao
without bringing gifts.
I came empty-handed.
What should I buy?
You're sent by He Rufei, right?
Sir,
what?
I'm merely passing through.
I'll spare you today.
Tell your master.
Your debt
will be paid.
Sir,
our people
were discovered by He Yan.
"Discovered"?
Young Master,
I am useless.
You failed at both tracking
and assassination.
Useless!
Where is she now?
In the mansion?
No.
She said,
"Your debt
will be paid."
Right.
Now that she's in the capital,
it's either her destruction or ours.
Let's go to that cosmetics shop
we went to the other day?
Okay.
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪