[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 10]
Last time you asked me
to get two bottles of shampoo
from two different places.
What was the reason for that?
At this moment,
I can't tell you too many details.
The whole story
hasn't been investigated thoroughly yet.
Then give me a sample.
I'll help you investigate it.
[Purong Hotel Staff Apartment]
[Shampoo]
[Search for Similar Items]
[First-Tier Domestic Five-Star Hotel]
[Exclusive Shampoo for Purong,
100% Authentic, Click Here If You Know]
Mr. Ji, the test results are out.
One of the bottles
is indeed a knockoff with fake labels.
There are plenty of these
in the underground wholesale markets.
Okay. Thank you.
[Purong Shampoo]
[Essential Oil Formula
Hotel Toiletries Set]
[Deep Repair for a Healthy Glow]
[First-Tier Domestic Five-Star Hotel,
Exclusive Shampoo for Purong]
[Dear, the minimum wholesale
order quantity is 50 items in this shop.]
[I am offline now. Please add PR12445.]
[I'll reply once I see your messages.]
[PR12445] [Search]
[Purong Authentic Products Porter]
[Conditioner] [Shower Gel]
[Purong]
[Shampoo]
[Bad Review]
[Purong Authentic Products Porter]
Okay. My treat tonight.
Let's not go home until we're drunk.
[Favorites]
[Purong Authentic Products Porter]
[Send Message] [Audio/Video Call]
[Shampoo]
[Director's Office]
What are you doing?
I'm looking for my boss.
I'm trying to stop you
from doing something stupid.
I know what you've discovered.
But now is not the time to report it yet.
My time is running out.
Now I have three bad reviews.
Zhang Cailu
has already talked about firing me.
Zhang Cailu?
That forewoman?
With this missing link adding to it,
the whole story makes much more sense.
Are you saying they are all in cahoots?
I'm not sure yet.
However,
this industry chain
of reselling hotel supplies
is too big for Zhang Cailu
to possess alone.
She's just an underling at most.
Things
are not as simple as you thought.
In my opinion,
you're also not as simple as I thought.
You left Svelto Hotel Group behind
and came all the way to Shanghai.
You've stayed here for so long
and meddled in so many things
that didn't concern you.
What's your purpose here exactly?
You're definitely not here
for sightseeing.
You can't even protect yourself now.
Yet you're still analyzing other people.
Now Zhang Cailu is in the open
while you are in the dark.
You know
she's trying to find fault with you,
so just don't let her
get something on you anymore.
Also,
try to avoid reporting issues by bypassing
your immediate supervisor like this.
Just do your job well.
What does it have to do with you?
Miyu.
I've been looking for you.
Looking for me?
Come with me to the Linen Room.
I'm fired?
Why?
I don't want you to leave, either.
But the assessment results are here.
It can't be helped, Miyu.
You are indeed
not very suitable to work in our hotel.
Ms. Zhang,
you know how I got
these three bad reviews.
What's more, didn't you say
bad reviews would only affect bonuses?
The situation is different now.
The competition in every industry
is so intense
that our hotel also has to
enhance the requirements for employees.
But
this does not comply
with the dismissal process
stated in the Hotel Staff Handbook.
I'm just notifying you in advance
so that you can be mentally prepared.
The official notice will be issued soon.
Ms. Zhang,
the guest in Room 1801 is looking for you.
Coming.
Let's leave it at that for now.
Just pack up and get ready.
Xu Miyu, you really can't go in.
-I'll just talk to Mr. Wei for 2 minutes.
-You can't do this.
You need to make an appointment
to see Mr. Wei.
Mr. Wei.
I have some work-related matters
to report to you.
HSKP Department, Xu Miyu.
You guys go first. I'll be right there.
Okay, Mr. Wei.
Come in with me.
[Shampoo]
The evidence you provided
probably does not constitute direct proof.
Here.
[Purong Hotel]
But as for the matters
you've reported to me,
I'm aware of them now.
I will personally investigate this case.
No matter who is involved,
I will investigate it to the end
and show no leniency.
Can I apply to
participate in the investigation?
I advise you not to get involved
in this matter.
The more people are involved,
the more complicated it'll get.
If Zhang Cailu
and the people behind her
find out about this,
it will not only be detrimental
to our subsequent investigation,
but it might also bring you
some unnecessary trouble.
Understand?
Okay.
Xu Miyu, right?
Thank you for telling me the information.
As an employee of Purong Hotel,
your sense of ownership
and sense of responsibility for the hotel
have truly impressed me.
Don't worry.
Leave this matter to me.
Get back to work for now.
I'll definitely give you
a satisfactory answer.
Thank you, Mr. Wei.
You don't need to come out.
Xu Miyu.
I am officially notifying you again.
You are fired.
Open your eyes and look carefully.
It has the director's signature
and the HR Department's official stamp.
Stop making trouble.
[Employment Termination Notice]
[Feng Kaixin,
Director of the Customer Department]
Mr. Ji.
What happened?
I'm leaving the hotel.
So you reported it?
Didn't I tell you
not to mess with Feng Kaixin?
I didn't mess with Feng Kaixin.
Zhang Cailu suddenly said
I would be fired.
I really had no other choices,
so I went to see Mr. Wei.
Can I add you on WeChat?
I still owe you 5,000 yuan.
When I gather enough money,
I'll transfer it to you on WeChat.
We can talk about the money later.
Have you appealed yet?
Yes, I have.
Before the results are out,
I won't leave.
But if...
my appeal gets no result,
where can I find you
to return the money to you?
I'm right here.
Will you always be here?
I'll always be here.
Why are you still coming here?
Take off your uniform at once,
return it to the Uniform Room,
and wrap things up.
I still have a half-day shift to finish.
Do you think you'll still get paid
for this half-day shift?
Whether I'll get paid or not,
I'll finish the shift
which I'm supposed to finish.
Ms. Zhang, the guest in Room 1812
made a complaint.
Got it.
[Appeal Submitted, Pending Review]
Miyu.
Why don't you wait a bit longer?
Black Card Ji
is making a complaint right now.
It's driving Zhang Cailu crazy.
Do you know what he's complaining about?
The shampoo.
Is that so?
Ke also once told me that
Zhang Cailu targetting you
had something to do with the shampoo,
so don't be in a rush to leave now.
Wait a bit longer.
There might be hope.
[HSKP Department, Xu Miyu]
Complain... Let him complain.
Just follow
the complaint handling process.
Ask him to wait for us to handle it.
I don't believe
this matter
won't cool down in three days.
Mr. Feng, this complaint hit the bullseye.
The guest has a black card,
so he's very powerful.
I'm afraid I'm no match for him.
He's Ji Feng,
and I've had a drink with him before.
What's there to be afraid of?
Besides, no matter how powerful he is,
he's just a guest.
Is he going to stay at the hotel
until the result comes out?
Let me teach you a trick.
If he is not satisfied,
show him the list of fired employees.
It's not that we didn't handle it.
The rats have been caught.
Then we can withdraw the fakes
and leave the issue aside for a few days.
This matter will blow over eventually.
Yes.
You're right.
Settle it quickly.
Can't you even solve such a small issue?
[Aunt]
Wei Siyuan.
Aunt.
Instead of
properly investigating the corruption,
why did you fire an attendant?
Being unable to solve the problem,
you just dealt with the person
who raised it?
Is this how you manage Purong Hotel?
Well...
Aunt, which matter are you talking about?
I've heard about the matter
of the executive floor.
Are you still playing dumb with me?
Aunt, please don't be angry.
I really don't know anything about this.
I-I'll go investigate it thoroughly.
P-Please don't be angry.
Within today,
I want to see the investigation results.
I'll be waiting.
Okay.
Feng Kaixin.
Can you use your brain when you do things?
You even made a big mess
of such a trivial matter.
I'm sorry, Mr. Wei.
What are you talking about?
Besides that shady business
in your HSKP Department,
what else could it be?
I asked you to handle it carefully.
I didn't tell you to fire her.
You mean Xu Miyu?
I don't care what her name is.
Let me tell you.
Old Madam is now blaming me.
What do you think I should do?
T-T-This is impossible.
I told the HR clerks to ask about it.
She has no background.
How did she get connected
with the chairwoman?
Cut the crap.
Give me a solution right now.
Otherwise, just pack up and leave!
What a useless man.
Wu, find a resume for me.
She's from the executive floor
of the HSKP Department.
Xu...
Xu Miyu.
[Purong Hotel Staff Apartment]
According to the latest news,
the complaint from Black Card Ji
has escalated.
Even the chairwoman heard about it.
There will be a good show
to watch this time.
Miyu!
It's good that you haven't left.
Why didn't you tell me
about such a serious matter?
It has nothing to do with you.
I don't want to drag you into this.
How would they dare?
I would rip their skulls off
and make soup.
Well...
Are you planning to leave tonight?
Stay at my place tonight.
Tomorrow,
I'll go ask the HR clerks properly.
[Notification:
Emergency Meeting for the Executive Floor]
What's wrong?
[Everyone should go to the meeting room
for a meeting in 30 minutes.]
Emergency Meeting for the Executive Floor.
[Feng Kaixin @ Xu Miyu]
He even specifically tagged me.
There's a sudden meeting
at this late hour?
Why are we having a meeting
so late at night?
Mr. Feng.
Is everyone here?
Yes.
Okay.
Since everyone is here, let's begin.
I suddenly asked everyone
to have a meeting here tonight
because I'm going to announce
an important decision
for the hotel's personnel changes.
As Zhang Cailu, the former forewoman
of the executive floor,
violated work discipline seriously,
which affected Purong Hotel's image
in the industry
and among its customers,
the hotel management
has unanimously decided
to remove her from the position
of executive floor forewoman.
Her dismissal
is effective immediately.
I'm fired?
Mr. Feng,
are you mistaken?
This is a collective decision
by the hotel management.
Do you think I'm making this up randomly?
Then tell me what rules I've broken.
Haven't I been doing everything
according to the superiors' instructions?
If you have any objection,
you can tell me after the meeting.
But now I haven't finished speaking yet!
Sit down!
Let's continue.
Next,
I'm going to
announce a personnel appointment.
From today onwards,
the forewoman of the executive floor
will be taken up by Xu Miyu.
Congratulations, Ms. Xu.
I hope
from now on, you can lead everyone
to make progress together
and improve the executive floor's work
to a higher level.
Come on.
Let's all give Ms. Xu
a round of applause and cheer her on.
-Mr. Ji.
-Hello.
I'm Feng Kaixin.
Mr. Feng.
Our department
has just finished a meeting.
Regarding the shampoo quality issue
you raised,
we've punished
the relevant personnel severely.
Who was punished?
Zhang Cailu,
the forewoman of the executive floor.
She has been fired.
Sorry for the trouble, Mr. Feng.
Please don't say that.
Mr. Ji, you have a sharp eye.
You helped our hotel get rid of a pest.
We should be thanking you.
To express our apologies,
we've specially prepared this
hotel toiletries gift box.
It's just a small token
of our appreciation.
Thank you. It's my honor.
I won't disturb you any longer.
Call me if you need anything.
Thank you.
Come in.
Mr. Wei.
Mr. Feng has promoted
Xu Miyu to forewoman as you requested.
The situation
with the former executive floor forewoman
has also been handled properly.
Tell him to keep a low profile these days.
Okay.
There's one more thing
I need to report to you.
Go ahead.
Mr. Ji Feng,
who you asked me to investigate last time,
is a black card guest in our hotel.
As for the executive floor incident
this time,
he was the guest who used
black card privileges to make a complaint.
Did he meet with the chairwoman?
No, he didn't.
But I've checked his background.
Since he graduated
from Birmingham three years ago,
he's been moving across
various countries and regions,
working as a professional manager
to launch hotel business.
Previously,
a rumor came out from the board,
saying that they would
find a professional manager
to take over the hotel management.
At this time, he appeared at...
[Wei Siyuan, In His Youth]
Okay. I got it.
You're quite smug, aren't you?
Mr. Wei, what are you talking about?
On what grounds could you steal my things?
Keep a close eye on him for me.
Report to me if anything happens.
Okay.
[Purong Hotel]
What did I tell you?
Making a comeback
is the main theme of your life.
Cheers.
I still feel like I'm dreaming.
In the morning,
they said they would fire me.
But in the evening, inexplicably,
they said
they would promote me to forewoman.
Maybe that Black Card Ji's complaint
really worked.
You've met your lucky star.
Can you go to any room
on the executive floor
and bring me a bottle of shampoo
from there?
Can you guarantee
this matter won't affect
the hotel's normal services?
Okay. Just rest assured.
He's not my lucky star.
He's the instigator.
It sounds like there's a story behind it.
Regarding this shampoo incident
I've told you,
he was the one investigating it.
I was just a scapegoat.
Then your current situation
is very easy to understand.
Do you know that Black Card Ji?
I've heard of him,
but I couldn't match the name to the face.
It wasn't until last time,
at Mr. Duan Jr.'s caviar banquet,
that I saw him for the first time.
He has always had a good reputation
in the industry.
Nor has he had any dark history.
If you want to learn about him,
you can check his resume.
I don't have time to learn about him.
But lately, I've been thinking
though some people seemed annoying to you,
then they just saved you by chance.
Some people seemed nice to you,
but then they suddenly turned against you,
becoming hypocrites
and stabbing you in the back
while you were unaware of it.
Now you know how dangerous
the workplace is, right?
Let me tell you.
Those guests on your executive floor
are full of hidden talents.
There are all kinds of people there.
When some of them speak,
even Wei Siyuan doesn't dare to disobey.
Even if Black Card Ji had saved me,
why do you think
Mr. Feng promoted me to forewoman?
In terms of seniority and ability,
or youth and strength,
I'm not even qualified.
Forewoman
isn't a very high-ranking position.
We don't know yet
whether it's something good or bad.
Let me
highlight the main points for you now.
Xu Miyu, remember this.
Not only are the guests
on your executive floor
all quite influential,
but your colleagues
are also not to be trifled with.
Even though they might look young,
their workplace experience
is definitely more extensive than yours.
I advise you to be mentally prepared.
It won't be easy for you
to make them respect you.
I know it's not easy
to be their forewoman.
But this is just the beginning.
From now on, I'm going to
learn how to use a manager's mindset
and perspective
to look at the executive floor,
the HSKP Department
and even the entire Purong Hotel.
I'd like to see
how far I can go in this place.
Right! This is the Xu Miyu I know.
Dealing with whatever happens to you
and never taking a step back.
I still remember when you were a kid,
even though your stepfather
and mother treated you like that,
I never saw you cry.
And you always did things
better than your sister.
I think since childhood, you've been
a strong heroine
who can always turn the tide.
Come on.
Let's drink to your workplace debut.
I'm back.
Ke Wenxue.
Why don't you ask about it?
She's back now.
Ask her directly.
On what grounds
can she become the forewoman?
I'd like to hear it, too.
Ms. Xu.
Qingping.
Don't try to cozy up to me.
If you have the guts,
tell everyone the truth.
How did you become the forewoman?
I was also very surprised
to hear this news.
You're still pretending, huh?
When Black Card Ji
cancelled your bad reviews,
I could sense it.
You have such a strong background.
Since you have such a powerful backer,
why are you here
to compete with us for the forewoman?
You should go to the board and tell them
to directly appoint you as the director.
Isn't that even more awesome?
Just like everyone else,
I was hired by the hotel
through an interview.
I don't have any backers.
But since the hotel
has promoted me to forewoman,
there must be a reason.
Because of your three bad reviews, huh?
Then I really couldn't catch up
in my whole life
no matter how hard I try.
Yin Xiang.
Miyu.
You look great
in this outfit.
Do you also think I...
No, I don't.
It's good to become the forewoman.
Luo Qingping is unhappy
because she thought
she could become the forewoman.
It's fine. She's just like that.
Just ignore her.
Thank you all for coming to work on time.
You're even thanking us for that?
Then if I clean
more than a dozen rooms every day,
you might even
have to give me an honorary banner, huh?
Today's morning meeting is about...
Then I'll sue them
for violating the Labor Contract Law!
They notified me in the morning
and asked me to leave in the afternoon.
They didn't give me
a one-month notice in advance.
Nor did they pay me double
for the last month.
Mr. Lin, you are so lucky.
The last sunlit guest room
on the executive floor
just became available.
Room 1812. It's all set.
[Purong Hotel] [Resident Identity Card
of the People's Republic of China]
The elevator is over there.
I've worked in the company
for over 10 years.
Can they just fire me so suddenly?
How could they deal with it like this?
[Weekly Shift Schedule
for Executive Floor Staff]
Have you all
seen this week's shift schedule?
Do you have any suggestions?
A shift schedule is arranged so complexly.
Just some superficial efforts.
Exactly.
Ms. Xu.
Go ahead.
I need to go to the restroom.
Just go.
Ke.
Your mobile phone.
Ms. Xu, someone made a complaint.
I need to go deal with it.
Go. Just go now.
This regular meeting is held
in quite a democratic way.
Isn't it a waste of time?
Ms. Xu.
I want to apply for five days
of compensatory leave
to prepare for the exam.
Five days?
Isn't that too long?
Previously, we only
had three consecutive days off at most.
That's because
you haven't been here long enough, Ms. Xu.
When Ms. Zhang was here,
we could take more than three days off.
Then I'll go back
and check your leave record.
No need.
Over the past three years,
I've accumulated
27 days of compensatory leave,
not even including
this year's annual leave.
Not to mention taking five days off,
I can even take five weeks off.
Then when will you start your leave?
Today.
Today?
There's a conference in our hotel now.
The executive floor is fully booked.
We are short-handed.
Does that have anything to do with me?
As a leader,
you should have considered in advance
the issue
of employees taking compensatory leave.
Bargaining with your subordinates now
shows no competence.
I've rejected your application
of compensatory leave.
Tell your parents to come next month.
Drop everything this month
no matter how important it is.
Alright.
Then you can take five days off.
Ms. Xu, I want to take a leave, too.
If other employees want to take a leave,
wait until Luo Qingping comes back.
Why can she take a leave but I can't?
She's preparing
for the Adult College Entrance Exam
to change her own destiny.
Does taking a stupid exam
make her superior?
You just heard it, too.
Luo Qingping has accumulated 27 days
of compensatory leave these three years,
which means she has been working
without any days off all year round,
so it's reasonable for her
to take this leave.
Gosh. What a double standard.
Our hotel's employee handbook says
two people on the same floor
can't take a leave at the same time,
so I'm not making things difficult
for you all on purpose.
Guys, please understand.
Mi-
Ms. Xu, come here quickly.
Coming.
That's all for the meeting.
Miyu.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry, Mr. Lin. I'm sorry.
Are you playing tricks on me?
The receptionist just told me
there was only this sunlit room left.
And now you're telling me
to move to another sunlit room.
How did you magically produce
so many sunlit rooms?
Was the receptionist lying to me
or are you?
Do I look gullible?
I'm sorry, Mr. Lin.
Please calm down.
I can't calm down.
Why isn't your forewoman here yet?
I'll rush her.
Yin Xiang.
I will take your menstrual cramps
into consideration.
How about this?
I'll cover Luo Qingping's shift tonight.
Really?
Thank you, Miyu.
Ms. Xu, where are you?
Coming.
Which room is it?
You're lucky now.
Someone's got your back.
Speaking of Miyu,
she's very easy to talk to.
Ji...
Mr. Ji.
What are you doing here?
Ask your forewoman to come here now.
I'm the new forewoman
of the executive floor.
You are the forewoman?
What's going on?
It's a double booking.
Mr. Lin, right?
I'm the forewoman of the executive floor.
My name is Xu Miyu.
Here's the thing.
T-Today, our...
Your computer is broken.
She has said it eight times already.
Do you think
it's okay
if I arrange another room for you?
It's not okay!
Why should I give in?
I gave in and then lost my job!
Why do you still want me to give in?
I've agreed
to transfer to another department.
Why do they still insist on laying me off?
Why am I always the one getting hurt?
Am I just unlucky?
I can understand how you feel.
But here's the thing.
This room has always been occupied
by Mr. Ji,
so I think for the sake of convenience...
-Maybe it's still...
- What convenience?
So "first come, first served"
also applies in checking into hotels, huh?
Do I need to show you my resume?
They said the ones who came first
surpassed me in seniority.
And they said the ones who came later
were young and strong,
being easier to order around than me.
Let me tell you!
I'm just staying here today!
I just want this sunshine
and this view!
I've worked day and night
for over 10 years!
I'm just going to enjoy my life properly!
I'm just going to enjoy my life properly.
Mr. Ji.
I won't give in to anyone.
From now on,
I'll do whatever I want.
Clean the room at once.
Mr. Lin, welcome to our hotel.
I'd like to apologize to you again.
Mr. Ji.
Mr. Ji, let me do it.
I also want to thank you
for helping me keep my job.
Your promotion to forewoman
has nothing to do with me.
I also don't know what happened,
but I know because of your complaint,
the shampoo incident was exposed.
And I've never told anyone else about it.
I'm really sorry about today.
Due to the mistake we made in our work,
you have to change to another room.
Thank you for cooperating with our work.
Which room?
1825.
It's the one on the edge.
That's an east-facing room,
but it's without afternoon heat
from the setting sun.
It's a prime location.
Why don't you work as a saleswoman
in a real estate company?
Prime location, huh?
I'll bring the room card for you later
along with a fruit platter.
Once that gentleman moves out,
we'll immediately arrange for you to move
back to your previous room.
Please come in.
I didn't expect the shampoo incident
would involve you.
But luckily, you can keep your job now.
We are even now, right?
Ke, what exactly happened just now?
Miyu, I'm sorry.
That Black Card Ji...
No...
When Mr. Ji asked me
to handle the extension of his stay,
I was busy with something else.
Then I forgot to enter it into the system.
How could you
forget such an important thing?
Fortunately,
Mr. Ji took a step back just now.
Otherwise,
what if the guest complained about us?
Miyu, could you keep it a secret for me?
Please. I promise
I won't make this mistake again.
Please.
Alright. Forget it.
This matter ends here
as far as I'm concerned.
But I have to warn you.
You must never
make such a mistake again.
Thank you, Miyu.
I promise
I'll never make this mistake again.
You are truly an angel.
Thank you.
I've heard the famous Black Card Ji
stood up for a female attendant
on the executive floor.
You even heard of that?
It looks like
Purong Hotel's biggest problem
is being too gossipy.
I've never made any gossip.
I'm just a porter of gossip.
Why couldn't I sense that
you would show such kindness to a rookie?
The HSKP Department
was reselling daily necessities,
which involved an attendant.
I was already investigating this clue,
so I just helped her out.
You just helped her out?
Then you just
helped with her promotion to forewoman?
I wasn't so capable...
as to help an attendant who got
all three bad reviews
in just one month of working here
to promote to forewoman overnight.
Is Purong's current promotion system
really this chaotic?
You're easily surprised
as you haven't seen much.
This is nothing.
At Purong Hotel,
that's just a piece of cake.
Go take a look inside the hotel.
There are stories
of confusing right and wrong.
Their dramatic plots
are completely beyond your imagination.
In my opinion,
what happened to Xu Miyu
was at least not a farce.
That's already quite good.
Do you know Xu Miyu?
I guess I'm the one
who discovered her talent.
Were you the one who recruited her?
I think she's pretty good.
She's both beautiful and smart.
It's just a pity that
associating with these girls
in the HSKP Department
is a bit of a waste of her talent
and is holding her back.
Ji Feng.
If you're really determined
to reorganize Purong Hotel,
you must have your own people by your side
who you can trust
and are also capable.
Xu Miyu is a very suitable candidate.
You think she's suitable?
I think she's too weak in personality.
She won't remain in the position
of forewoman for long.
If I ask someone whose position
is precarious to be my trusted aide,
what's the use of that?
I think it's quite good.
[REC]
What happened?
It hurts, doesn't it?
It hurts, huh?
Ke Wenxue, Ke Wenxue.
Are you in charge of Corridor A?
No, I'm not.
I swapped with someone else.
Who did you swap with?
I also forgot.
Why didn't you guys
follow the shift schedule?
Things would get messed up easily
if you swap by yourselves like this.
It's messy not because of me.
As soon as Luo Qingping took a leave,
everyone's shifts got messed up.
Alright. I got it.
Is anyone there?
Someone in our room
is having an allergic reaction.
Her neck is all swollen.
Coming!
What's wrong?
Hurry up!
Right here.
It's so severe.
I'll contact the receptionists
and ask them
to bring some allergy medicine up here.
Please wait a moment.
Go at once.
Hurry up.
Today, it just feels so itchy.
As a result...
It's alright, Fang.
It's alright.
We've prepared so hard
for over half a year,
but we didn't even make it
to the finals in the end.
This is really...
I'm sorry.
The Front Office is really so busy.
I'll go downstairs to get it right now
and bring it up here immediately.
Please wait a moment.
Okay.
Please hurry up.
-Bring it here as soon as possible.
-Thank you.
Don't cry.
What is this for?
In the past few days,
her neck problem has relapsed.
She can't sleep on a pillow,
so she can only put a towel
under her neck and sleep on it.
In the past few days,
Fang has really suffered a lot.
Yin Xiang.
We have an important guest
coming tomorrow.
The room is already booked.
It's Room 1818.
Go clean it now.
Miyu, why are you only telling me now?
My shift is almost over.
Don't you still have half an hour
before your shift ends?
Half an hour.
Just wait another half an hour.
And then ask someone else to clean it.
I'm leaving now.
The guest in Room 1817 is complaining
about allergies caused by towels.
I'll be right there.
Why is it getting worse?
Do you need me to contact the hospital?
We're going to
the high-speed rail station soon.
She can go to the hospital
after she gets home.
But the towel issue
must be resolved first.
You have to
give us an explanation today.
Yes.
We can't leave
until this issue is resolved.
Allergies to towels?
Absolutely.
Such a situation
has never happened to her before.
But just in the past few days,
after putting this towel from your hotel
under her neck to sleep on it,
she has gotten this allergic reaction.
I'll go report this situation
to our superiors right now.
Please wait a moment.
Okay. Please hurry up.
We have a train to catch.
[REC]
Okay. I'll be right back.
Please hurry up.
This hotel is not okay.
If it's really because of the towel,
we need to ask them for compensation.