=Eight Hundred=
Now that you're technically recovered,
there's something I need to ask you.
What is it, Dad?
The day of your accident,
what exactly
did Huo Kaiming say to you?
Yes,
what did he say?
Chen Hongbing,
what are you doing?
Hui went through so much.
As his father, is it wrong
for me to ask?
Enough already.
Don't you know Hui's illness
was triggered
by emotional stress?
Do you want him to relapse?
He'll relapse just because I asked?
I'm telling you,
if anything happens to Hui,
I'll be coming for you.
Is it necessary to be so harsh?
Fine, I won't ask. Happy now?
Every single day,
pinch, pinch...
Hui, it's okay.
Don't think about it anymore.
Just forget it.
Now that you're back,
the whole family is here.
No one dares to hurt you now.
- Okay, Mom.
- Think of something happy.
Here, have some celery.
Thanks.
What's that smell?
My mutton!
- Songge, help me!
- Okay.
Still pinching me?
Look.
Songge.
- I'll get the water.
- Hurry, get some water!
Okay.
This is a total waste of my cooking.
It smells great to me.
I'm sure it's delicious.
Songge,
there's something
that's been weighing on my heart.
I think
I should talk to you about it.
What is it, Mrs. Chen?
I want to apologize to you.
About that day at the hospital,
when I told you to leave Hui.
I was being inconsiderate.
I was wrong.
These past few days,
you've cared for Hui day and night.
I've seen it all,
and I feel for you.
Songge,
can you forgive me?
Mrs. Chen,
I never blamed you.
Actually,
I've always felt
really bad toward you and Mr. Chen.
All these years,
you both worked so hard to raise me.
I wanted to grow up
and properly repay you.
But instead,
I ended up getting this illness
and burdened everyone.
I'm the one who dragged you down.
Look at you, silly child.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Getting sick isn't your fault.
I just hope...
I hope our whole family
can be happy and well.
Good girl.
We'll all be just fine.
Dad, here's a toast to you.
Don't be ridiculous.
You haven't recovered yet,
so how can you drink?
Just this one glass.
I want to toast you.
What's wrong?
You've been so busy for me,
worrying yourselves sick.
I've let you down.
Why are you saying this to me?
You're my son.
Your mother and I
looking after you
is only natural.
There's no need for apologies.
Lately,
I've been in a daze.
Every day feels like a dream.
I even saw you crying.
That's nonsense.
Why would I cry?
Tell me.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Don't think too much.
Focus on getting better.
That's more important than anything.
The mutton is ready.
Come on, quick.
You mom finished making dinner.
Coming.
Careful, it's hot.
- Hurry and try my cooking.
- Here.
Move a bit closer to Grandpa.
I can reach it.
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
Chen Hui,
today has been the happiest day
I've had in a long time.
Songge,
let's start over.
Starting over?
I've been thinking.
We can't sell the cough syrup anymore.
And I don't want to run
the roller skating rink anymore.
Is it because of Mr. Chen?
Yes.
This was wrong from the start.
If we keep selling it,
we won't have a home left.
While there's still time,
let's go somewhere else
and start fresh.
If we don't do the roller skating rink,
what will we do for a living?
I want to open
an internet cafe in the city.
An internet cafe?
Yes.
I've thought about it for a long time.
Young people love
going to internet cafes now.
And there's only one in the city.
I think it's an opportunity.
But Chen Hui,
we still have
a batch of stock out there.
Since we've decided to quit,
we won't want the stock.
Once the heat dies down,
we can just dispose of it then.
Okay.
Since you've made up your mind,
I support you.
Songge,
close your eyes.
Why should I close my eyes?
Just do as I say.
Close your eyes.
Stand up slowly.
Give me your hands.
Slowly.
Where are we going?
Careful now.
Alright.
No peeking.
You can look now.
It's so beautiful.
What fish is this?
They're called Pterophyllum.
Some call them angelfish.
So pretty.
Pterophyllum.
I hope we can be
as happy as they are.
We will be.
=Episode 10=
(A New Beginning)
(People's Public Security)
There is some good news
to announce to everyone today.
Regarding the case
handled by our station and the Criminal
Investigations Brigade
of the municipal PSB,
the Zhang Mei, Yu Susu, and Jiao Yuqin
"Death Benefit Bride" gang case,
the court
has already reached a verdict.
For this, the bureau
leadership has awarded
our station
a Collective Second-Class Merit.
This is the highest commendation
we've received
since our station was founded.
- Great!
- Excellent!
(Fengyang Town Police Station, Jiangbin City.
Collective Second-Class Merit. Honorary Credential)
Although the bureau leadership
has given our station
such high praise,
none of us can afford
to let our guard down.
For instance, Huo Kaiming,
who committed the body-burning homicide,
is still at large.
The scarred woman
selling the cough syrup
hasn't been found yet either.
So I hope that you keep working hard
to strive for a First-Class Merit.
- Good.
Hongbing,
how is the investigation
over at the water treatment plant?
It's like this.
Over the past week,
we have visited every single
water treatment plant
around Fengyang.
The polyacrylamide
that Tang mentioned
is actually used by the plants
to treat sludge sedimentation.
We requested
the list of employees who have access
to this substance,
but we found that none of them
have had any contact with Huo Kaiming.
In fact, none of them
even has a criminal record.
This is what's giving us
a headache right now.
How is the investigation
into Huo Kaiming going?
Director Tong,
after Chen Hui woke up,
he came to the station.
He gave a statement
about the day Huo Kaiming escaped,
recounting what happened.
It's basically consistent with
what Gao Songge and the owner
of the photo studio said.
Rest assured,
we set up surveillance
at every station
where the coal train
passed during his escape.
However, at Linchuan Station,
Huo Kaiming's blood was found
in the nearby bushes.
At that time, we conducted
a joint search operation
with the local police,
but we couldn't find him.
Given the current situation,
I suspect that Huo Kaiming
is either already dead,
or he has escaped to
a neighboring province.
Limin,
share this information
with the surrounding provinces
so they can stay synced.
Tell them to give us
timely feedback on any news.
Understood.
Keep up the good work.
That's all for today's meeting.
Meeting adjourned.
(There is no way out for violations.
Reform through hard work for a new life)
Hui,
what are you doing here?
Mr. Huang,
I'm here to see you.
I topped up some money on your card.
Why be so polite with me?
Mr. Huang,
I want to start a business,
and I want you to invest.
Me? Invest?
Look at my situation now.
How can I invest?
You just need to provide the funds.
Is this your father's idea?
It has nothing to do with him.
It's my idea.
Mr. Huang,
there's a new thing
in the big cities now
called an internet cafe.
You use a computer
to chat with strangers
from all over the country.
I've researched the market.
Right now, there's only one
in the whole city,
and it's packed every day.
You can't even get in line.
If we can open one,
it will make money for sure.
Wait,
you can make money just by chatting?
Yeah.
I wouldn't believe it
if I hadn't seen it myself.
Once those young guys
get on,
they play all night.
They don't sleep at all.
Computers...
I've heard of them too.
But can you actually
figure out those things?
I've already sent
Han to Beijing to learn.
If others can figure it out, so can we.
How much do you need?
I'll put in 100,000.
Mr. Huang,
I'd like you to put in 200,000.
We'll split the profits 50-50.
200,000?
That's a lot.
Mr. Huang, this makes way more
than the roller skating rink.
And there's no risk.
I could actually scrape it together,
but then I'd have to use
Gao Songge's kidney transplant money.
That's why I'm planning
to give up half the shares.
I just want to invest less capital.
Fine.
I'm in.
Okay, when you go back,
go see my sister.
Tell her to come over tomorrow.
Okay.
Mr. Huang,
don't tell my dad
about this.
If he finds out,
he'll chew me out.
Look at you.
We two officers are acting
like thieves who are sneaking around.
Master, it's about
my transfer to the municipal PSB.
It's almost settled.
Just waiting for the official notice.
When are you leaving?
In the next few days.
I've been by your side
for so many years,
learning so much.
I wanted you to be the first to know.
You little rascal.
Impressive.
So you're leaving.
When I first started at this station,
my son, Hui,
was still in high school.
In the blink of an eye,
your wings have grown.
You're ready to fly.
Master, why would you say that?
You're making me
feel like I'm not a good son.
Look at yourself.
I'm just getting old
and like to nag.
But seeing you
doing so well for yourself,
I'm truly
happy for you.
Master, since I'm leaving,
let me buy you dinner soon.
Forget it.
You're leaving.
We can't have you pay.
Let Director Tong treat.
We'll get everyone together
and give you a proper send-off.
Alright. Master, look,
since I'm leaving,
teach me a few more tricks.
After all, I'm going
to the municipal PSB...
What tricks could I possibly have?
In my whole life,
all I've seen
is this 800-meter radius area.
But you, you're capable.
You've got talent.
But wherever you go, never forget
to always be a good cop.
If you run into trouble
at the municipal PSB,
you can always come to me for advice.
I'm sure about that.
I'm leaving.
Hello, Chief Liu.
Director Chen.
Regarding the Gao Ying case
you mentioned,
after I returned to the city,
(Witness Inquiry Record)
I reviewed the case files from back then.
Conditions were limited at the time,
and no physical evidence
or test data were left behind.
If, as you say,
Gao Ying's death
really is related to Huo Kaiming,
there's only one way to prove it now.
You mean an autopsy?
Yes, but given the current situation,
we still lack direct evidence.
To start the autopsy procedure,
we must have a signature
from Gao Ying's family.
There aren't many
of Gao Ying's relatives left now.
Only Songge is left.
I can take on this task.
Director Chen.
Chief Liu, if you have
something to say, just say it.
Don't you think you should discuss
this matter
with your wife
first?
You're right.
Thank you for the reminder.
In this matter, it really requires
my wife to give the nod first.
That's the safer way.
Dr. Ding, you're back.
I'm back.
Ding Yue, you're back.
Better to arrive at the right time
than to arrive early.
Why does this smell so good?
Look at this.
Wash your hands and get ready to eat.
This is a first.
You've been working too hard lately.
Of course I have to show off my skills
to reward you.
Do you have something
to tell me?
You go first.
Come on,
can't I just care about you?
Please don't do this.
It creeps me out.
Just say it.
Well, nothing gets past you.
There is indeed one thing.
The municipal PSB recently...
Mr. Chen, Mrs. Chen, we're back.
Dad, Mom.
Hui, Songge.
You brought so many things.
My grandson, you're back.
You two, did you follow
your noses back here?
- Come, sit down.
- Come, quickly.
- It's just in time for dinner.
- Sit.
- It smells so good.
- What a coincidence.
- Get a bowl.
- You're lucky, Hui.
You're back whenever there's good food.
Come on.
Here.
Thanks, Mr. Chen.
Such a feast today.
Today's dishes were all made by your dad.
Dad, did I interrupt something?
You didn't interrupt me,
but maybe we
interrupted something of yours?
Actually, I really do have something
I want to tell you all.
There, you see?
Speak.
Songge and I
plan to
sell the roller skating rink.
We're going to the city
to open an internet cafe.
Internet cafes?
What's an internet cafe?
It's a place where young people chat
and play games online.
They're very popular now.
Right. And there's only one
in the city right now.
If we go there,
we can get a head start.
You're going to the city?
So suddenly?
In the future,
won't it be inconvenient to come home?
Mrs. Chen,
we'll still come back often.
This is our home.
Yeah, Mom.
Don't you worry.
Dad,
you made Mom angry earlier?
Nonsense, I've been
trying to cheer her up.
Mom,
are you angry?
I'm not angry.
I'm just a little out of my element.
It's so sudden.
But you two are grown-ups now.
You can't stay
in this small town forever.
It's right for you to go out.
This
is a bit of savings
from your dad and me.
Opening an internet cafe
will require money.
It's not much,
but it can help for a while.
No, Mom.
Please take the money back.
The money from selling the rink
is enough.
Could you sell
the roller skating rink that quickly?
Yes.
The day I went to the police station
to close the case,
I ran into Mr. Tong.
I told him I wanted to sell the rink.
He said his niece
happened to want to start a business.
We even settled on a price.
No matter how much you get
for the roller skating rink,
that's your own money.
This is from your dad and me.
You must take it.
Mom...
- Take it.
- Just take it.
Take it.
It's good that young people
have ambitions.
Your mom and I
wish you a successful opening.
Thanks, Mom.
Thanks, Mrs. Chen.
Thanks, Mr. Chen.
Hey, Hui,
once your internet cafe opens,
you must invite me to take a look.
Let me see something new.
Of course I'll take you to see it.
We've talked enough.
Eat quickly.
Look, the food is getting cold.
Come on, eat.
Try it.
Try your dad's cooking.
I'll wash them.
No need, go rest.
Before dinner,
what was it you wanted to tell me?
It was nothing.
Well, I gave you a chance.
If you won't say it, I'm leaving.
Wait.
There is actually something
I need to discuss with you.
Go ahead.
The suspect in the case
I'm working on
is on the run.
The municipal PSB has also
been putting a lot of pressure on me.
They say this person
is closely connected
to Gao Ying's death back then.
So the municipal PSB has decided
to conduct an autopsy
on Gao Ying.
So this is what was waiting for me.
No, I'm reporting it to you.
Consider it
a heads-up in advance.
Go on.
Done,
that's all.
Chen Hongbing, what are you trying to do?
It's my job.
After all these years,
have you ever considered my perspective?
Ding Yue, no...
No matter what I do,
I've always looked at things
from your point of view.
Back then,
I was the one who proposed marriage.
My parents didn't approve.
I nearly cut ties with my family
just to be with you.
Over the years,
I gave birth to Hui,
helped you lay your mother to rest,
and cared for your father day and night.
Even if I don't get credit,
at least recognize my hard work,
- Chen Hongbing?
- Yes.
Is there any room in your heart for me?
How could there not be?
I'm telling you,
for all these years,
your place in my heart
has always been the most important.
Don't give me that.
Did I say you
couldn't investigate Gao Ying?
That day when you were looking for
that little broken box,
didn't I give it to you?
What did you actually find?
Now, they have stopped
the investigation.
What are you trying to do?
Exhume the body?
Announce it to the world?
So that all of Fengyang Town
knows about this?
How romantic of you.
A deputy director
reopens a cold case
for his former fiancée.
It's so touching.
So, should I set off fireworks
to celebrate for you?
Look at you.
Ding Yue, listen to me.
Ding Yue,
you and Gao Ying
were best friends back then.
Gao Ying has been gone for many years.
The things between her and me
are long in the past.
Now,
you are my wife,
but I am still a police officer.
From a professional standpoint,
I find this case
truly suspicious.
Don't use those high-sounding excuses.
Listen to me.
Since the municipal PSB is here
to investigate this,
I want to use this chance
to get to the bottom
of this case.
Isn't that giving Gao Ying closure too?
Have you considered me?
Have you thought about me?
Do you know what
people outside say about me?
They say Chen Hongbing's fiancée
was Gao Ying.
I'm nothing but a replacement.
Do you understand? A replacement!
After all these years,
I thought
I must have finally
warmed your heart.
I didn't expect
that your heart
still only holds Gao Ying.
Fine.
Stop crying.
Don't be sad.
If you're against it,
I won't go through with it.
For you, as long as it makes you happy,
I'd even quit the police force.
- I will retire.
- Why would you quit?
Did I ever say
I didn't want you to be a cop?
You've been a cop all these years,
neglecting the home and the kids.
Have I ever complained?
What did I even say?
What kind of person do you take me for?
What are you trying to say?
Isn't it because I'm a cop
that I have to do this?
If you weren't a cop,
could you even do this?
But you won't let me do my job.
Tell me, then, how am I supposed
to be a cop?
You...
Fine, investigate.
Go ahead and investigate!
Ding Yue,
what did you just say?
You told me to investigate.
I did not.
I just heard you say "investigate",
right?
Alright, that's enough.
Sorry.
Listen.
Honey,
with your level of awareness,
you should be
the director at our station.
You'd be way better than Director Tong.
Don't you think?
Knock it off.
I'm telling you,
just this once.
Thank you.
Stop crying now.
Come on.
It's my fault.
Here.
Have some water.
Alright.
Choose an auspicious time
to break ground.
Offer a stick of incense.
Lift the coffin!
Tang.
What's wrong with Chief Liu?
I'll go check on her.
Okay.
Officer Liu.
Officer Liu, are you alright?
The medicine... In the car...
Medicine...
You saw everything.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
It's not your fault.
Officer Liu,
is it because of chemotherapy that you...
Songge,
don't tell anyone.
Don't worry.
I won't tell a soul.
If it were possible,
I wouldn't want
anyone to know I'm sick.
Thank you.
Officer Liu,
the way you are now,
shouldn't you be getting some rest?
It's stage three lymphoma.
I don't have much time left.
Songge,
I'm already very lucky
that I still have the chance
to do what I want to do.
You don't need to pity me.
Officer Liu,
aren't you afraid?
Everyone's destination is the same.
It's just a matter of distance.
But as long as you can still run,
there's nothing to be afraid of.
As long as I can still run.
Songge,
don't just keep your eyes
on the finish line.
You still have a long road ahead.
Songge,
I rented a place near the internet cafe.
It's not far from the hospital,
and it even has a courtyard.
We're here.
What do you think?
This is the courtyard I told you about.
It's really nice.
If we tidy it up a bit,
it'll look beautiful.
Yeah.
In this flower bed,
I'm going to plant
all my favorite flowers.
I'll plant
hydrangeas,
Chinese roses,
bellflowers,
and cherry tomatoes.
And also...
And you.
I'll plant you here, too.
(Yingxiong Internet Cafe)
Chen Hui, come over here for a second.
Close your eyes.
Okay.
You can open them now.
How?
Does it look good?
It looks great.
Thank you.
It was nothing.
This is our new beginning.
(Yingxiong)
I'll do it.
Dad,
take a break.
Just watch from here.
Come on.
All right, here we go.
What's all this fuss about now?
Let me do it.
Dad, let me.
- I can manage.
- Just sit down. Sit down.
Isn't this the stuff from
when Hui was sick?
It's an eyesore and takes up space,
so I'm clearing it all out.
It's good to get it tidied up.
Tang.
Director Chen.
I'm here to update you
on Gao Ying's case.
Over here.
Gao Ying's autopsy results
are out, right?
Yes.
Although the body was buried for so long
that much evidence
was destroyed biologically,
we found a powder
on the body,
and it's potassium manganate.
It's the same substance found on
Yu Susu and Lu Yuan's bodies.
That's wonderful news.
Tang,
what does the municipal PSB think
about merging the cases?
The municipal PSB says
there's now direct
physical evidence linking
Gao Ying's case to Huo Kaiming's case.
We can start the process
of merging the cases.
Tang,
thank you.
Alright.
Go and get that mutton stewing.
I have good news.
What good news?
Gao Ying's autopsy results are out.
It wasn't spontaneous combustion.
We finally found evidence,
so we can merge the cases.
That really is good news.
All right. I'll go stew the mutton.
Okay.
Dad,
we're having mutton tonight.
Good.
Dad,
let's go inside.
Let's go in.
Tell me,
has that criminal been caught yet?
We are still
after the criminal.
Catching a criminal
is like flying a kite.
The stronger the wind,
the more you have to let out the line.
That's what they call
"balancing tension and relaxation".
Otherwise, the kite string will break.
What you're describing
is how to catch a fish.
I told you
I would definitely
get to the bottom of this case.
See?
That's for sure.
When it comes to cases,
you've never been wrong.
You certainly have a good eye.
Enough.
Anymore praise will be too much.
Why do I feel like
you've put on weight lately?
That's impossible.
The case isn't solved yet.
How could I get fat?
I remember back then,
when I first met you,
you looked quite fit.
Don't dwell on past glories.
In those days,
you wore your hair in two small braids.
It was really quite pretty.
You still remember it?
How could I forget?
That feels like
it was over 20 years ago.
Hey, girl.
Let me have a look
at your Chairman Mao badge.
Let us borrow it
and see it.
What are you doing?
- What are we doing?
Just give it here!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Stop.
You're asking for it!
Give it back! Move!
You're so bold.
Move it!
Get lost!
What the heck?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Wait a second.
Do you still remember?
Back then, Gao Ying
always had this rainbow glow
on her head.
When the sun hit it,
it was all colorful.
It looked quite nice.
I don't remember.
Are you angry?
I was just asking.
What's wrong?
Yes.
Back then, she often had
a glow or something
in her hair or on her body.
I asked her about it once later.
She said
it was because her dad
worked at the old coal washing plant.
She used to go there often
to bring him meals.
Every time she came back from that,
on her body
and in her hair,
there would be that glow.
It seemed to be
from the water in the coal washing pool.
The old coal washing plant.
(Heyi Coal Washing Plant, Fengyang Town)
What's this?
A motorcycle.
It looks a lot like
the one Ma Heping described.
Is it the scarred woman's?
Very likely.
Go.
Take a look around.
Quickly.
Go find a pole.
Okay.
Director Chen.
There's something underneath.
It's quite heavy.
Give me a hand.
Open it up and see.
There's another layer.
It's cough syrup.
(Peidun Cough Syrup)
It's full of them.