MARS really wants to stay together.
But this is the best
the company can offer.
Help him, okay?
Mick told me.
I just want him to get
what he truly wants.
From today onward,
you’re no longer an Oner employee.
Mick had Miss Pemika fire you
so you could work on this more freely.
So, you’ll go up for this concert,
and the plan is being coordinated by Mick.
And I’m the "free" one
who can do whatever I want?
So, if we're going to take action,
we have to be really sure
that this time, it has to succeed.
In the concert, the setlist
is divided into four parts.
The opening, the fun moment,
the emotional moment,
and the celebration of success
before a goodbye.
But no matter which part it is,
from what I’ve heard from Mick,
there’s no way
the company will let us meet Thame.
I’ve also heard that
we’ll have separate dressing rooms.
And backstage,
Thame will be kept alone.
The only place
we can meet Thame is on stage,
where we can’t do anything except perform
and follow the script.
That means we have no chance
to talk to Thame at all, right?
So, the only thing we can do for now
is change this breakdown.
Yeah.
The part I think we can most
easily interrupt is right here.
It’s after Thame’s solo performance
because it’s when the documentary
will be shown.
- Are you going to use the documentary?
- Yeah.
That’s because it’s the easiest thing
we can manage.
Also, I know what’s going to be shown
because I edited it myself.
Then, we need
to figure out a way to replace
the original documentary
with this new version.
Do you think Mick can help us with this?
Like, switching the file?
Yo!
How is it going, everyone?
I bought some snacks for you.
Share them, okay?
Eat first.
Even if we can change the file,
and Thame realizes what we’re doing,
the company will definitely
stop us during the concert.
We have to take control
of the stage and make it ours.
Huh?
What do you mean?
After the documentary is shown,
we need to take control
of everything on stage.
I’ll show you how.
Then it’s all on you now,
whether you can do it or not, Po.
Of course, I can.
No matter what,
I’ll bring Thame back to you all.
LOVE YOU DYLAN
This is your seat.
Thank you.
Well, Miss Gam…
Oh, Miss Gam informed us
that she isn’t available to attend.
Today, the Korea team
will be watching the live stream.
Make sure there are no mistakes, everyone.
- Noted.
- Enjoy, and do your best.
- Got it.
- Okay.
Good luck.
Is everything all set, Mick?
Yes, it is.
Hello.
I’m here to watch
the stage from this angle.
Thame.
Do your best.
Let’s live up to MARS’ fame.
Let’s go.
I know you want me
I know you wanna
Just admit it, baby
I know you want it like like me
Where do I go to file my complaint?
What you did to me, it just ain't right
Won't back down, won't compromise
Until you say you'll be my girl tonight
The damages I need you to pay?
All I need is
You… you… you
All I need is you
One, two, three, go!
Jun. I lost.
I want to see that one more time.
Will you give him another chance?
Of course!
Okay. Everyone is so kind to you.
Let’s do it one more time then.
One, two, three, go.
They’re spinning now.
They’re doing it.
Hey, that looks promising.
Wow, he's even doing it
with his arms crossed.
Nano, go.
There we go.
Wait.
Now, Nano missed once.
The last image I’ll remember
Is when we were together
The last image
Is when you gazed at me tenderly
The image of you, I’ll hold dear
Still beautiful year after year
You’re in my heart always
MARS started with us
supporting one another,
and even if we’re saying goodbye,
we’re doing that for each other as well.
I’m so happy for you
that you’ve come this far,
but it didn’t surprise me much
because I know you’re a talented one.
But from now on,
I’m no longer with you,
but I want you to remember that
you’ll always have me here.
I’m proud that I got to work
with a talented person like you.
Don’t worry about us at all.
I believe someone talented like you,
no matter where you are,
will be successful.
I’ll grab a ticket to cheer for you
at your concert in Korea!
I’m genuinely happy
for your success, Thame.
But this time, I guess I really need
to let go of your hand.
Come here.
What’s going on?
It’s back now.
I’m sorry,
but all we just said was scripted.
Someone like me
wouldn’t say something cringe.
And there’s only one truth.
And the truth is…
Damn it, Thame.
We won't let you go.
See you!
Dude, you heard it already,
that we wouldn’t let you go,
no matter what, right?
Tell the stage manager to bring
all five of them backstage now.
Noted.
You might be a bit confused
about what you have to do next.
But after you go down there,
someone will guide you
on what you have to do.
Hey, Thame.
We’ll go play tag now.
Good luck.
Hurry up.
I have no time to explain,
but I just want to let you know
that the other members and I don’t want
the whole thing you’ve done to be in vain.
This is what you have to do.
Here’s your position.
The closest exit is over there.
Po.
Hmm?
Any questions?
Is this really you?
Yeah.
Hey, Thame. Thame. Are you there?
Thame, we’ve got no time left.
You should quickly see your members now.
Go.
MARS!
Nope, I mean, how do we
start fixing the problem?
What’s going on?
- Huh?
- Well, I have no clue either,
but I already asked the team
to control everything,
but we can’t do anything about it now.
Well, it seems the main control
of the concert is no longer here.
Eh? Where is it then?
Everything is all set here.
But let me say something as your manager.
Your plan is seriously…
worth my frustration.
We must take control.
Are you saying
we have to set our own control
to monitor everything?
Correct. We need someone
to set up the wires
and cut the signal
from the original control.
Do you think you can do that?
I’m here to watch
the stage from this angle.
I’m sorry,
but all we just said was scripted.
Someone like me
wouldn’t say something cringe.
Ming, find the main control
and get it back.
- Got it.
- As for you, Tae, follow me.
Find the members. We need to talk.
Noted.
MARS!
Is there any possible way
to get everything back on track?
We can’t find the members.
Miss Pemika,
Ming said she already found the control.
Mick and Po are monitoring it.
- Mick and Po?!
- Yes.
Do you want me to switch off the light now
so that we can reset the control?
But it might take some time.
For now, just let it continue.
Disconnect the live stream link
from the Korea team
and let me talk to them.
And what’s happening right here
strictly can’t be leaked anywhere.
I also want to know how much they can do.
Noted.
Po! Po!
Mick!
What are you two doing?
All right.
Let’s go all out.
Light.
Ready.
Living life on dreams
Doing things on my own
I create with my heart
Let my feelings shown
I paint the scene, paving ways for my path
But when I get closer
Why does it get so hard?
My left says this one’s right
My right says that one’s nice
They say I must do this and that to start
Everything is good, except for my heart
I’m tired of things they want me to do
Though they never ask if I ever want to
Do I need to pretend to be someone else?
Another person who is not myself
My dreams are my own, can’t be stopped
Just want to follow my heart
Don’t want to be on top
Flying high
But I don’t need to be number one
Just a breeze is enough to keep me up
Like someone who understands
Who takes me for me, never want to compare
The weight on my shoulders
It’s time to let go
So my weary heart can rest on a stronghold
I may not achieve
What’s written in someone’s book
But I succeed today in being
As happy as I could
Being the greatest may not be the answer
If it means I hurt someone
That’s not what I’m after
Follow what my heart decides
I keep flying high
Let me fly to the endless sky
Good or bad, I got no clue
Just let me fly to that place so high
Where my dreams are waiting to come true
I’m gonna fly higher
JUN FANCLUB
OT5!
OT5 MEANS FIVE MEMBERS FOREVER
Did you even realize what you’ve done?!
Huh?
Not only did you turn
this concert into chaos,
but you also caused damage to our company.
We’re sorry.
- But we did this because…
- Don’t say anything more
because you already said
what was on your mind up there.
I’m really disappointed in what you did.
I don’t think I can continue
with MARS anymore.
As for you,
the Korean team watched your performance
and now they want to cancel
the contract with you.
This much damage comes with a cost
that you all need to help compensate for.
You need to compensate Oner
under your own names
because you’re no longer our artists.
But I heard that
you disconnected our live stream
from the Korea team.
They didn’t even see what happened.
But you now want us to leave Oner.
Oner wanted to separate MARS,
but you all didn’t want to,
so you have to leave.
Thank you… for understanding us.
I know it must be hard for you too.
It’s not hard.
You just have to pay.
So, you’re the one
who made all this happen?
It wasn’t just me.
That’s amazing.
You know what?
That was their best performance so far
ever since I became a fan of MARS.
Yeah. I hoped it would work out.
I also hope that from now on,
nothing can stand in MARS’ way.
But when they said
they were tired of always doing things
based on other people's opinions,
I’m not sure if I’m also one of the fans
who made them feel like
they’re not being themselves,
or I’m probably
the one who gave them pain.
Are they really doing
what they love happily,
or are they enduring the pain
to make fans like me happy?
Fern.
When Per’s dating scandal was leaked,
I admitted it didn’t sit right with me.
But after the press conference,
I’ve never seen Per
look truly happy again.
I can tell through his facial expressions,
eyes, and gestures.
Today should be
the happiest day for him, right?
I want to see him truly happy.
I don’t want him to choose,
say sorry,
endure the pain,
or force himself to smile at us,
their fans, to make us feel good
or meet our expectations.
Po was the one who stood up for you.
He fought against
the company until he got fired.
Can you pass my message to him?
If he’s still in love with her,
follow his heart.
Live the life the way he wants to
because in the end,
what fans like me want to see the most…
GAM
Hello, Per?
Gam.
…is their happiness.
Hello?
Where are you?
Behind you.
Don’t go anywhere again.
You aren’t mad at me at all
that I left you that day?
Because of me,
you could barely protect anything.
Though you couldn’t bring back
everything to my life,
just having you back…
is enough for me.
Thame.
Po.
No matter what the future brings,
I’ll say the same thing.
Don’t go anywhere again.
Please continue being by my side,
no matter what I’m going to face.
Don’t think that
you’re an obstacle in my life.
You aren’t.
Because of you,
my life can move forward.
I want to wake up, see you every morning…
and go to work.
The beginning might be a bit tough
since we have to start over on our own.
Also,
what we did today
will bring a lot of debts later.
But don’t worry.
They will help
each other get through this.
You just have to…
bear living with this poor artist.
But you also know that
I’ll be broke too, right?
All I can do is probably
work as a regular
suit shop staff like I did.
Hello, Uncle.
Hi.
Please put the suit
in the bag for our customer.
Got it.
I might just keep doing random things.
Thank you.
I won’t be doing something cool,
like being a director anymore.
I think that’s cool, though.
I love you.
No matter what you are or aren't,
whether you succeed or not,
I’ll still love you.
I’ll love you
in every chapter of your life.
Even if we're both a mess,
can you still love me just the way I am?
Yeah.
Are you nervous
about your first performance?
I’m not that nervous,
but Pepper feels pretty tense.
I see.
You had him replace you
as the leader already.
But why would he feel tense?
The song is perfectly all set,
and so is the choreography.
Today, we’re going to meet
the new group from Oner
and probably Miss Pemika too.
As a leader,
he might not know how to act.
I think he doesn’t have to worry.
Honestly, they’re very kind
to you, aren’t they?
Hello, Uncle.
Hey, hi.
Help me finish this.
Got it.
SING STREAM
STUCK RIGHT IN MY HEART - GUMP
That's the debut single
from the newly launched boy band.
But that’s not it
because I bet everyone is looking forward
to the group that is about to perform.
So, please give it up for MARS!
I get what you’ve been through
The love you had and all the blues
Made you cry, feeling lost
TRUST ME - MARS
Now you’re not ready to open your heart
If I were you, I’d be scared too
Would love again leave me bruised?
Love has given you nothing but regret
That’s why you see love and feel afraid
Hey!
The suits we made for them
are cool, aren’t they?
I agree.
Which is all fine
But hear this plea of mine
If you stop fearing to love
I’m ready to be the one you love
Yesterday’s past
Today is here
He’s the past
I’m right here
It seems those kiddos
have a promising future.
They must feel so delighted that
you allowed them
to use MARS as the group name.
The person who feels delighted is you.
Hey.
We haven’t cleared things up
about you helping them at the concert.
I know you’re also glad
that the whole thing has ended this way.
Am I right?
PLEASE KEEP THE NOISE DOWN
Hey, Gam. Hello.
Hi.
Are you waiting to have dinner with us?
What are you talking about?
I’m waiting for Per.
Aw.
Did you hear it?
It’s about my girlfriend and I.
Don’t mess with us, okay?
Let’s go.
Bye, buddy.
Are you lonely?
Do you want someone to feel lonely with?
This guy kept complaining that
he’s hungry since we left the stage.
How about this? You two go eat together.
Me?
With him?
No way I'm having dinner
with just the two of us.
As for you, turn off
your shipper mode already, all right?
All right. I won’t do that anymore.
I’ll drop everything, okay?
Let’s go eat.
Do you want to join us? No?
Then, it’s the three of us.
Let’s go. Go.
Let’s go.
- See you later.
- See you.
My work is done.
Same here.
Should we meet at the restaurant,
or do you want me to see you first?
Let’s meet at the restaurant.
How have you been?
It’s been so long since we met.
Cheers.
How have you been? Long time no see.
When is he arriving?
I can’t wait to see him.
How have you been?
- I’m good.
- He’s here.
Come on.
- Po!
- It’s been a while.
This way.
I’ll be right back.
Why did you arrive just now?
Busy with work, huh?
I wasn’t busy.
There was nothing much to do
at the suit shop, you know.
And how come you’re working
at the suit shop?
Well, it’s fun.
That’s it.
Let’s not talk about work anymore.
Let’s talk about Mr. B.
When will you bring him to meet us?
I can’t wait.
When he arrives,
I will do a full interview,
asking where, when, and how you two met.
You know I’m such
a little great detective.
I must spy on to make sure that
he’s good enough for you, my buddy.
There he is. He’s here.
Hello, everyone.
Guys, this is Thame,
my boyfriend.
Shit!
Aren’t you going to interrogate him?
You said you would.
Hello.
You’re Bifern, right?
He… knows my name.
- Fern!
- Wake up!
Shit!
- Fern!
Wake up!
It’s true!
I’m not drunk.
- I’m not drunk.
- You’re not?
You’re already drunk.
Sure.
Hey, come.
Looking at him closely,
I think he’s super handsome.
Hey, Po.
- Cheers.
- Hey.
Hey.
Hello. I’m Earn, the owner of EarnChop.
Mind your own business.
- What, Baifern?
- Go back to your table.
Baifern, you’d better stay quiet.
Ouch!
- Cheers.
- You!
- Bottoms up!
- I’m here.
You still haven’t stopped?!
She’s always like this when she’s drunk.
Your reunion party was fun.
I didn’t expect it to be this fun either.
You know what?
I never joined the previous reunions.
I was scared.
What were you scared of?
Well,
I was scared
that I wasn’t as successful as others.
I wasn’t as good as others.
But in the end, it doesn’t matter.
That’s because you have me.
I guess so.
Won’t you argue a bit?
Having you here really feels nice.
You know what?
Because of you, I like my typical days.
Because of you, I like my ordinary job.
From now on, I don’t have to be afraid
of answering anyone’s questions anymore
because every answer
I have, ever since meeting you,
has made me realize that…
I’m truly living the life I want.
Thank you.
I told you already
staying together forever will be fine.
By the way,
which movie should we watch tonight?
Let’s finish the previous one first, okay?
Fine.
I’ll try.
What’s up, Mom?
Hello.
Is something up?
You’re watching it like this again?
Why?
Well,
we never really finish it, do we?
And who said
I actually wanted to watch the movie?