Are you sleeping, Sohrab?
Go in and lie down.
We have to leave
very early tomorrow.
Are you mad at me?
Sohrab?
Hope you know I didn't mean it.
You know that.
Don't know what happened.
I just lost it there for a bit.
I'm really fond of you.
You know that, right?
Sohrab?
Sandeep, wake up.
- Jayanti?
- What's wrong?
What's going on?
Jayanti!
- What's wrong?
Oh my God!
- Maddy, he's been...
- Guys! Let me sleep...
What's going on?
Call the police.
Kumar, I think he's dead.
- What do you mean?
- I think he's dead.
Oh, no!
Nena, come on.
Let's get out of here.
We can't leave...
What's wrong with you?
You can't leave now.
Says who?
Kumar, where are we going?
- Nena, let's go.
- We can't leave.
- Kumar.
- You don't get it.
All of you'll be fine.
I'll be in trouble.
Kumar!
You can't leave this house.
Isha.
Isha...
Why is everyone up?
How come you are awake?
I don't sleep before two.
Finishing up the chores.
'Saheb' ...
'Saheb' is dead!
Did anybody come
from outside?
- Satya?
- No, ma'am.
I locked the gate at 11:30.
- Sure?
- Sure, ma'am.
Not a soul can come in after that.
Tea, anyone?
Ma'am.
Wake her up.
She takes very strong medication.
We can't let her sleep through it.
Move aside.
Isha.
Wake up, Isha, please...
What happened?
What time is it?
Please wake up.
Something has happened.
It's Sohrab.
What has Sohrab done now?
Calm down.
What did he do?
- Sohrab!
- Please, Isha.
Be careful.
I've been driving carefully
for the last 30 years, Daddy-o.
Not a single scratch on the car.
You don't have to be rude.
You have your seat belt on, right?
Sit back and listen to music.
- Sohrab!
- What?
Drive a little slower.
The roads are pretty bad as it is.
What are you doing?
Is this better?
Stereophonic chorus, you lot!
From one side, be careful.
From the other, go slow.
Should have gone in Sandeep's car
if you wanted to go slow.
Is this better, Daddy-o?
- Sohrab.
- Careful!
You guys are too much.
- Amazing!
- Thank you.
Are you okay, Tiger?
Oh my God!
- Look at that!
- Babe!
- Did you see that?
- What?
Did you see that cottage?
I'm trying to drive.
I can't see anything.
Sorry. I forgot.
I forgot we can't multitask.
That's the truth about my husband.
Why are men like this, Doc?
- Like what?
- Like this.
Can't do more than one thing
at a time.
They miss out on
all that is beautiful.
Always following their nose...
Yeah, men can be like that.
- Unbelievable!
- But you married a good one.
- Hey!
- This is a good one?
- Are you the good one?
- Thanks, Chandra.
He's one of the best.
Your cheque is in the mail.
Thanks!
This is the best chance.
I'm going to talk to her.
- You'd better talk to Raman.
- Will see.
Why are you nodding your head?
Spent your entire life nodding.
They treat you like a peon.
I said, I'd talk to him.
You do all the hard work
and they skim the cream.
No cream, no cholesterol.
The cream is for them.
We were ordained
dry bread.
That's what we get.
Seat belt.
Seat belt!
- Hey, Handa!
- Hi!
- Handa.
Happy anniversary!
You're done for!
- How was the drive?
- It was good.
Oh wow!
Look at this!
- Heavenly!
- Look at these flowers.
- What flower is that?
- It's called angel's trumpet.
- How do you know?
- I know a lot about flowers.
This is better than the pictures.
- I know.
- It is so nice.
Chandra, have you met everyone?
Everybody, wait.
That's Chandra.
- And this is everybody.
- Hi.
Did they tell you
the check-out time?
They say
this was built in the 1920s.
Really?
Hundred years, huh?
Looks it.
- In a good way.
- What a find! Well done.
Sandeep get the bags.
- So?
- This is a find!
- What's your name?
- Satya.
- Is it possible to get some tea?
- With ginger?
- How many rooms?
- Total six, ma'am.
Four in the front,
two at the back.
- All clean?
- With fresh sheets.
Sandeep, give me a cigarette.
- What are you looking for?
- Our room.
Come here. I'll show you your room.
Right here.
Baba, take this room.
Vijaya, settle him
in this room please.
Sandeep!
Ashtray?
Where's your bag?
Open the window.
Have you gone deaf?
Can't you hear
I am asking you to do something?
Can't leave you alone at home.
Not suitable for polite company.
What the hell
should we do with you?
Must be the punishment for our sins.
Got two demons for sons.
Move away from the window.
Ask Isha to cut some fruits.
Go on.
I'm going to talk to her tonight.
I have a feeling
she'll say yes.
Don't know how you do this.
I'd be petrified.
Oh my God!
Raman, look at this.
Wow!
- It's really tall, man.
- And pretty!
Wow! How pretty is this!
What are you doing?
Use a spoon, at least.
You have to try it.
- Happy anniversary.
Mmm... Yummy.
Can we eat it all?
Thank you.
Rohan.
Come.
Food is ready.
Okay.
- Ask my dad about the leather jacket.
- Arun, you too.
Why are you
pulling his leg, Sohrab?
- It's very stylish.
- Correct.
- I've had it since Second World War.
- Second World War!
- He's jumping down.
- Got it myself from Sarojini Nagar.
You don't get it in that market.
Sohrab, you're awful.
They latch on whenever
they see an opening.
- What's Sarojini Nagar?
- It's a market in Delhi.
Second World War, my foot! He
took it off a dead soldier's body.
- Please shut up.
- Rohan, sit here.
- Doc, can you serve Arun please?
- Yeah, sure.
Sohrab, stop it.
You can't tease your father.
- Baba?
- Jayanti...
- Isn't this your sweater?
- Yeah.
Hey, why are you
in your wife's sweater?
So, what?
I wear his shirts too.
Didn't you bring your own?
So, the two of you
went to the same college?
Me, no.
I was with Raman's brother.
Oh, okay.
Both studied science.
He studied medicine,
psycho-analysis, all that jazz.
Oh wow!
Oh, you're one of those doctors!
You treat the retards.
- You can't say these things.
- No. I don't treat them.
The patients
have to treat themselves.
- You must prescribe medicines.
- No.
Your friend is such a fake doctor?
Doesn't treat anyone.
Doesn't prescribe meds.
So, you give them a massage?
Actually, I just point the way.
I watch, I listen.
And somehow that seems to help.
Like our homeopathy doctors.
They can diagnose just by feeling
the pulse.
Something like that.
The pulse I feel is words.
Words reveal, you know.
He can look into your soul.
Don't make eye contact
with the doc.
Are you serious?
And he charges money for that.
Don't scare everyone away.
This is a good business.
- Easy street.
- He's very famous.
Google him.
I've already googled him.
- Isn't it good?
- Yeah.
It's good, is it?
- Sure?
- It's good.
Isn't the salt a little less?
- Maybe a little.
- I knew you were too shy to say it.
- It seems fine to me.
- Add some salt.
It's okay.
- Why don't you eat?
- It's just salt, man.
- Have some roti.
- Try it.
- Sohrab, let it be.
- Here.
Come on.
- Sohrab, let him be.
- Can't eat without salt, my love.
Here you go.
It's just salt, kiddo.
You need it.
Now try it.
Go ahead.
- Better now?
- Better.
Isn't it?
You're not doing it right.
What are you doing?
Jayanti, say something.
- Sohrab!
- Mix it well.
Shut up!
Eat your food.
Mix it.
Here you go.
Now give it a taste.
- Isn't it better now?
- Much better.
Great!
I love you, Sandeep.
Doc, forget about Canada
and come back.
You'll earn a lot of money.
You should know when to stop.
Sometimes you really cross the line.
This is nothing.
If I'd put in half a bowl,
he'd still eat it. Right, Sandy?
- I would.
- Tell that to your wife.
Give me your bowl.
- Can I get a roti?
- Yeah.
Yes, sir.
-Alright, so who called?
-I did, Raman Chawla.
Are you Inspector Aditya?
No, sir is busy.
He'll come later.
For now,
you can talk to us.
Who is the victim?
Sohrab Handa, our friend.
Who killed him?
We're cops.
You can trust us.
Tell us.
Sir, we were asleep.
We were sleeping too.
Come along, Amar ji.
Get her out of here.
Ma'am.
Ma'am, if you could step aside...
He isn't well.
So, I will have to be here...
Isha.
He's not well, Suman.
- She's his wife.
- I'll stay here. Okay?
- Just...
- He's not well.
It's fine.
- What's his name?
- Sohrab Handa.
- How is he related to you?
- He was my business partner.
- Your business partner?
- Yes.
- Amar ji?
- Yes, sir.
- You've got the plastic bags?
- Yes.
Whatever you find...
Keep it in the bags.
All of you, listen carefully.
Nobody touches anything.
It's all evidence.
- Got it?
- Yes.
Got it...
What's going on?
Didn't you hear what I said?
Cigarette...
Sandeep.
- Arun!
- Amar ji.
- Put this in evidence.
- Arun!
- Take his number.
- Get a blanket for your brother.
It's getting chilly.
Did you hear me?
Who was the first one
to see the body?
I did.
What's your name?
Jayanti.
She's my wife.
Jayanti ji, he's asking you.
Tell him your name.
My name is Jayanti.
Amar ji, note down 'Jayanti'.
Go on...
I came here to get some water
at around 12:30.
That's when I saw him.
I see.
You were here at 12:30.
And...
Who was the last person
who saw him?
I did, sir.
- Alive?
- Yes.
- Your name?
- Madhvan.
Madhvan.
What did you see, Madhvan ji?
It was around 12 and I
was here for some cake. And...
Sohrab
- was seated on this very chair...
- Hey!
Look who's here!
Can't believe it's you!
- Recognise him?
- I'm a huge fan.
- He's from the show "Pardafaash".
- Right.
Kumar ji, this is amazing!
Put it on your brother.
Do I need to spell everything out?
Have both of you lost it?
Take it away.
My child...
He doesn't need any of this now.
He'll fall ill, Baba.
Then, we'll have to
take him to the doctor.
Vijaya, explain it to him.
Ma'am...
Ma'am.
He won't get up now.
- Isha!
- Isha! Stop it.
How dare you?
- How dare you?
- Stop.
Isha...
Stop!
- Stop it.
- Isha...
- Stop it!
- Isha!
Just shut up!
Isha...Calm down.
That's enough.
Stop...
Some tea?
Tea?
Is the sugar okay?
I need to get the injection...
For Baba.
You know about ma'am, right?
What?
She walks in her sleep.
Sleepwalking.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
Don't be scared.
Why would I be scared?
You didn't do it, right?
Of course not.
Then I don't care.
From here to here...
in one brutal move!
With something very sharp.
- What?
- The knife is not here.
You mean like a blade or a knife.
- The cake knife is not here.
- How can that be?
- It's missing.
- I left it right here.
Not there, now.
Whose birthday was it?
Not a birthday.
It was our wedding anniversary.
I see.
Happy anniversary.
But this wasn't done
with a cake knife.
No!
Actually, it was a big knife.
To cut meat.
Is that what you used?
To cut the cake, yes.
What does he mean?
And now it's missing.
Where did you keep it?
What do you mean?
I mean you must have hidden
the knife after slitting his throat.
So, where did you hide it?
You think I did it?
- That I killed my friend?
- You're one who called the cops.
Because that's
the right thing to do.
Have to call the police.
We'll figure it out at the station.
Get him along.
- Let's go.
- No...
- What do you mean?
- Move aside.
What's going on?
Come on.
- Your cake. Your knife.
- Sit here.
So what?
- You're the one who called.
- Just because I called you,
I'm the killer?
Madam, put your phone off.
- Talk to him.
- We're trying to do our work.
Give me the phone.
You can't just use your phone.
We're inquiring.
Just answer the phone.
- Hello?
- We're trying to work here.
- Just let us.
- Go ahead.
- Who is it?
- Boss.
Yes, sir.
No, sir.
Just regular inquiry.
No, sir...
Nothing till you get here...
Don't know what
he's trying to imply.
We'd just take their statements.
We'll find out what happened.
Rest assured, sir..
You spoke to him?
Why would you do that?
- My phone?
- He'll keep it.
- Why?
- You can't make calls like this.
- Please don't talk disrespectfully.
- How am I being disrespectful?
Nena...
- Give us the room.
- Don't raise your voice.
- Let us do our job.
- Please go ahead.
- It's my earnest request.
- Show some respect.
Then I will talk to you.
Come with me.
- Kumar ji?
- Yes?
- Can I have a minute?
- You don't have to talk...
Madam, please wait.
It won't take long.
This way, sir.
Kumar, don't say anything
without a lawyer.
Yeah, so...
Now, tell me. In detail.
Everything that happened
since you got here.
We got here around 3:30.
We got late
because we were recording.
When we got here,
the party was in full swing.
Hey, Jayanti.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
- Happy anniversary.
- Thank you. Is this for me?
Of course. Who else?
I'll have all of it.
Hey, Isha.
Hi!
You look more handsome
in real life.
Thank you so much.
Absolutely.
We have to party tonight.
- How are you, Sandeep?
- Very well.
- Okay.
- I'm too excited.
- Are we the last ones here?
- Madhvan is still to come.
You know how he is.
Has to make a stylish entry.
Hey, Raman. My friend!
- Superstar.
- Happy anniversary.
- You survived ten years?
- Feels like 300.
I did. Managed.
Handa!
How are you you, hero?
- How are you?
- Very well. Thank you.
- Congratulations!
- Thank you.
Kumar, meet Dr Chandra.
- Hi.
Dr Chandra. Kumar, Nena.
- Hi, Nena.
- Hello, Doctor.
Just Chandra.
I'm not a doctor.
Hey.
Of course, he's a doctor.
And he's come all the way
from Canada.
Shall we step out for a bit?
- Their crap will continue. Come on.
- I was already in Bangalore.
But I did come from Bangalore
for your party.
You have such loyal friends, Raman.
That's saying something about him.
And Jayanti.
- Baba!
- Look who's here.
"Pardafaash!"
- Good to see you.
- Please sit.
- Hi, Suman.
- Hi!
- Hello, uncle. How are you?
- Hi. How are you?
Sandeep is your biggest fan.
Biggest!
Will you record today's episode
from here?
No, I've already recorded it.
That's why we got late.
- We've recorded it, Baba.
- So, it's not live?
Can't go live every day.
Not possible.
That's cheating.
It's been one hell of a hectic ride
for the last eight months.
She is a slave driver.
Hello, your life has changed
in the past eight months.
The world has changed.
People's attitude has changed.
Working like a slave.
Do you see that tree?
How beautiful it is.
Who would have made it?
One branch...
Another one out of that.
And another.
And the leaves.
And how they move, man.
Amazing!
What an amazing job He has done!
Just messed up
while making humans.
Isn't it?
You okay?
Hope you're not getting bored.
Let me know if you get bored,
we'd leave.
Cake!
Wow!
Who got this wonderful cake?
Thank you.
- Who got the cake?
- He did. Thank you, Chandra.
Well done!
Did you get it from Canada?
I am not cutting it...
with a butter knife, guys, come on!
Satya, get a proper knife.
Jayanti, wait a minute.
Madhvan is almost here.
He's parking his car.
- He's here.
- Wait for me.
I'm waiting. Just get him.
- Wait, I'll get him.
- I am.
Look at this.
- Is this good enough for you guys?
- Yes.
That's the perfect allegory
for our 10th anniversary.
What are you going to do with it?
Cut it or stab it?
Stab!
That's a very good idea.
Satya!
Madhvan is here.
- Are they here?
- Madhvan, brother!
Hi, Sandeep.
So sorry, man.
- No problem.
- The GPS was confusing.
It's okay.
You got here in time.
This is Nazia.
- So sorry.
- Sure, blame the GPS.
- Hey, Maddy!
- Hey, Kumar!
- How are you, brother?
- Good.
- We've been stalling for you.
- Thank you.
- Hey, how are you?
- Haven't let Raman and Handa start.
Haven't let them cut the cake yet.
Surprise!
So sorry. Hope this makes up for it.
Better be sorry.
Better late than never.
- Go on. Cut the cake.
- Shall we, baby?
Okay, baby.
Here we go.
Just cut it.
Oh my God!
You first.
No. You first.
Kiss!
Guys, get a room.
This day will be forever
marked as Raman-Jayanti day!
Speech, guys!
Okay, time for the speech, now.
Okay.
I've not prepared this.
I have actually.
I've got two words to say.
Fudge you for coming late.
He's just saying it.
But seriously, Jayanti...
Without you,
none of this would be possible.
So thank you
for rocking up into this world.
Thank you for accepting me.
And dealing with me.
And for being you.
He is such a schmoozer!
He's a smooth operator.
- How's that?
- Your turn.
- Jayanti, your turn now.
- Come on.
Your turn.
Okay...
When we met 10 years ago...
It's been 10 years, Raman.
I can't believe it to begin with.
I guess it was a leap of faith
as all marriages are.
And yet, here we are.
- Yeah. We're here.
- Yeah.
Cheers to that!
You know how they say
it takes a village to raise a child.
I really think it takes a village
to raise a marriage.
I really do.
And...and...
For us, you all are that village.
- And--
- Are you calling us villagers?
You're definitely a villager.
- She's saying such nice things.
- I know.
But I really mean it.
Thank you for being there.
I...
- We wouldn't have it any other way.
- True.
Can we eat the cake now?
Have the cake but don't finish it.
Congratulations.
Love you, guys.
Get the glasses.
Don't drink from the bottle.
- Okay, let's cut the cake.
- Guys, guys.
Congratulations!
This is Nazia.
- Nazia, this is the gang.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Nazia, sorry.
Nazia, be careful
of these intellectual types.
He is all hollow on the inside.
That's my good friend,
Sohrab Handa.
You're lucky that I'm your friend.
And not your enemy.
Forget it, Handa.
With you, it's all the same.
Here we go again.
Where's your beautiful wife?
Isha!
I'm here.
Year after year, I wonder...
How do you keep living
with this Neanderthal?
That's not for you.
He's my Neanderthal.
- Here.
- Enjoy the champagne.
Spent his life drinking champagne.
- Thank you.
- Cheers.
Cheers, guys.
So nice to see you all.
Can we chat for a bit?
Now?
Yeah.
Sure.
Not here, Nena.
Am I entitled to some cake?
So, this is what we'll do.
You buy him out.
Buy his shares in the company.
He moves out.
You move in.
Seriously?
He'll never agree to it.
You let me handle that.
Yeah?
You tell me.
Are you in?
How come you are so confident?
Nena, just say it.
Well, if he's out, I'm in.
I love you.
Yeah, right.
Cheers to that, partner.
Ladies...
So, you know her father?
You are her father's friend?
Isha.
-Do you want some?
-Give me a small one.
'Give me a small one',
says the tipsy man.'
Daddy-o will be the first one
to get drunk.
- Stop talking nonsense.
- He won't change.
- This is the last one.
- What nonsense?
No more for you.
- Sadia is an actress too.
- Oh really?
It's Nazia.
No wonder you look so familiar.
Tell us Sadia baby,
which films you're in.
- It's Nazia!
- I'm not good with names. So what?
- It's Nazia.
-Tell us.
I've done a few ads...
For now, yeah.
- Right... Ads.
- Something we might have seen?
There's a lot of
struggle in this field.
Our friend, Kumar,
also struggled a lot for 15 years..
He used to beg for smokes.
Now, look at him.
Hosts his own show in a jacket.
Don't jinx it, bro.
We used to smoke a lot together.
You're so aggressive on your show.
You don't let anyone speak.
You're not like that in real life.
That's part of the performance.
Public demands high pitched drama.
We have to dish it out.
That's acting.
That's not me.
- Is this you?
- I should think so.
What about the stand
you take on the show?
- Well, that helps with the TRP.
- Exactly.
- Are you serious?
- Money, money, money.
Guilty.
Suman, let's say
you make bush shirts.
No, I'm making mutton.
Good one.
Let's assume
that you make bush shirts.
But the customer wants to be naked.
Pardon my language.
What are you going to do?
Can't force him
to wear the bush shirt.
- You sell what the customer wants.
- I don't buy that. That's very wrong.
If you don't like it,
don't watch it.
- Don't watch it.
- We'll give you more choices.
He's not selling it to you anyway.
- Democracy.
- It's not about me but everybody.
Everyone should have their beliefs,
their moral code.
Gone are those days!
When the world
ran on principles.
Now they are all opportunists!
- Just thinking of profits.
- Exactly. I agree with that.
Bravo, Daddy-o!
Amazing thought!
Wow!
My dad just slayed irony.
When his dad died,
he told me...
That's your grandfather.
You should perform the last rites.
Shave your head.
Don't want my image spoilt.
And now he is talking of principles!
Drink up!
Bloody fraud!
You know, Baba...
Ideology doesn't work anymore.
Have to sell what
the customers want.
We're stuck.
So, we're selling what we have to.
Sometimes it's matches or oil.
- Sometimes, it's news.
- Go, sell it all.
We have sold everything.
What's left to sell, anyway?
We have even sold our souls.
We've become morally bankrupt.
I don't mean you.
I mean society as a whole.
The terrorist has dropped a bomb!
You're the biggest fraud
of them all.
You and your entire community.
Your Socrates...
What's his name, Emanuelle Kant.
Your Plato, Pluto... Sartre...
Your Nietzsche.
All frauds.
They are not just mine,
they belong to you too.
I've nothing to do with them.
By the way, you know a lot.
Spent years
with this pretentious prick.
Must have some effect.
What were you saying, Maddy?
Let it be.
He'll say I'm dropping bombs.
- Go on, Professor.
- Go on.
- Sohrab...
- If you stay quiet, your whiskey
won't go down.
This is your chance
to impress the ladies.
It's party time!
Show us how much you know.
If not now, then when?
I mean, look at us.
We were free.
We could have achieved anything,
we were free to choose.
And what did we choose?
This?
- Where did we land up?
- I think we're in a nice place.
There's fresh air, at least.
Suman!
Hear that, Prof?
- You're a cutie.
- What?
- Isn't it true?
- It's true. I agree.
We're truly doomed.
You're a real pessimist.
I feel like killing myself
right here, right now.
On the contrary, my friend.
I'm an optimist.
How are you an optimist?
An optimist who thinks we're doomed?
It's sad but true.
Luckily, we are...
not dead.
I'd say we're alive.
But that'd be a gross exaggeration.
- Professor...
- The fact that we're not dead...
- Our messenger of doom!
- ...Is reason enough to be hopeful.
- Professor?
- What?
What will save us, Professor?
- I'll tell you.
- Not asking you.
I'll save you from this bullshit.
- Now, keep your trap shut.
- Sohrab...
He won't even let me speak.
Nonstop lecture!
Please, can you be quiet
for a minute?
Let somebody else talk for a change.
Maddy, tell us what you think.
Go on, Maddy.
I was just saying that...
As a collective,
we've all failed miserably.
Any hope left for us
is at the individual level.
Because as individuals
we still have some inherent goodness
- that can pull us out of this...
- Shut up or I'll break this on you.
Shut your trap
and make me a drink.
I guess I was wrong
about inherent goodness.
Move a muscle once in a while.
Your philosophy is useless.
It's worthless.
- Sohrab...
- You can only impress
the chicks in class.
You're absolutely right, Mr Handa.
Philosophy is useless.
Just like art.
There he goes
twisting my words again...
But I'm agreeing with you.
I admit I'm useless.
- Look at him.
- I'm glad I opted out when I did.
- Opted out?
- When were you even in?
You travel around the world
delivering lectures.
You get a fat cheque
from the university.
And you think you opted out?
Please show us how to opt out too.
You get money for nothing...
for just blabbering!
We work our asses off
to earn our daily bread.
You don't add a shit
to the economy.
- True.
- You don't create jobs
You don't generate wealth,
occupation, employment.
Nothing!
- All you do is jabber.
- True, all true...
We move things around.
We're making the world go around.
Get it, Mr Philosopher?
I wouldn't go that far, Handa.
We do real work.
Work!
Ever heard of it?
Labour!
Have you heard of it?
Toil, action...
We sweat it out.
We build.
We create.
We make empires.
Empires also fall, you know.
We'll figure it out
when that happens.
The night is still young.
There is still some life left in us.
Let's say cheers to that.
- Cheers!
Mr Handa, our ideas
remain beyond us.
You know that, right?
You...
You remain in people's memories.
Who gives a crap about
what people think?
- Really?
- People are shit anyway.
Look at you guys.
- Hey!
- Excuse me.
Please.
Handa, your shit stinks
but we love you, bro.
- Okay. Now stop it.
- All hail Lord Handa!
It's an interesting bunch.
But then I find
most people interesting. So...
Yeah, we know you do.
Come on now.
Tell us.
What?
Tell you what?
- Come on.
- Sing for your supper.
- Chandra, don't be such a bore.
- No, no, no.
They're all lovely people.
That's it.
I'll make it simple.
What do you think about the bully?
By that, I suppose, you mean
your business partner, right?
Yeah.
I'm not sure he's a bully.
I mean, he pretends to be.
But there's something
soft about him.
Almost vulnerable, I feel.
But there are others in the room
who are hard, really hard.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Like who?
How's your relationship
with your sister?
- Alright! Caught you out.
- That is...
You're terrible.
Okay...
Can you guess who the other bully
in the room is?
Who?
Did Sohrab ever mention
he got beaten up as a kid?
I mean, real bad?
Doc, we all got beaten up as kids.
- I know..
- It was the norm then.
Yeah but this old man,
he was vicious.
Really.
I see him and I see blood.
- Wow.
- That's intense.
Okay, don't stop.
Keep going.
- Don't.
- No. That's it.
That's it for today.
She's not going
to let you off easily.
Maybe on our way back,
I can tell you more.
No.
Some more.
- Come on.
- Okay. Last one.
This...
Nena... And what's his name?
Kumar...
Is there a problem
in their… relationship?
- Wow!
- How do you know?
I'm not wrong, am I?
- No, you're not wrong.
- No. Bang on.
Last month, she came over and...
She said that she's planning
on calling it off with him.
But Kumar doesn't know yet.
Kumar doesn't know it, dammit.
How do you know?
- How do you do it, Chandra?
- Yeah.
I don't know.
I pick up on things.
Okay.
I remember.
She said...
"I finished recording and came."
And he said,
"We finished recording."
And that kind of
sent me a signal.
Wow!
Okay.
I'm not talking in front of you
from now on.
Not happening.
You'll find out
all my dark secrets.
It's alright.
We all have our dark corners.
As long as we learn
how to live with them.
No...
I'm off.
Bye.
- See.
- Bye.
- I'll be right in.
- Okay.
Oh my God!
It moves! It flies!
- This one's for you, my friend.
- Okay, we fly.
Thank you.
- Shall we go in?
- Yeah.
Your cigarettes?
- I don't smoke, Doc.
- Right.
- Listen.
- Hmm.
You and Nena...
Doc...
- Okay, I thought so.
- Yeah.
Something...
Way back.
But there's nothing right now.
- Alright.
- Okay.
And Kumar and Nena
are not splitting because...
No, man.
Are you nuts?
Just checking.
Man, shouldn't have invited you.
There's nothing now.
I believed you the first time.
Why are you repeating yourself?
Kumar, keep it to yourself now.
They are all a pack of wolves!
Don't tell anybody.
Okay?
This is going to be fun.
This is going to be epic shit!
Handa is never going to
sell the company.
What do you want, Arun?
Baba wants water.
The glasses are behind you.
And there's water in the fridge.
Sandeep, this is taking forever.
- Ready in 40 minutes.
- Really?
- Suman, is something burning?
- No. It's fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Raman.
- Raman?
- Yeah?
What is the thing with Maddy?
- I know..
- Isn't it?
She is no more than 24.
Maybe, 25 at the most.
Yeah...
She is 28.
- Really.
- Yeah, he told me.
She's 28 and he is 52!
He's double her age.
What's going on?
- Is the mutton washed?
- Almost done.
- Men go a little crazy as they age.
- Correct.
It's okay, guys.
- You'll justify it.
- Raman!
Raman!
Have you tried talking to her?
- Raman!
- Yeah.
What do they even talk about?
They wouldn't waste
their time talking.
All day?
Got you, my friend.
Got you.
What is it?
Want something?
I know what you want.
Ma'am, Baba's calling you.
I'll be right there.
Got you, my friend.
Kumar, take it easy.
What's wrong with him?
He's drunk.
- What's his thing?
- Drunk and how!
Does this nurse stay
with them 24x7?
Yeah, they've a 4 bedroom house.
They've given her one.
She takes care of the family.
Come on.
She does.
- What did I say?
- You always twist my words.
I believe you.
She does take care of everybody.
Baba and Arun...
And Sohrab.
She does.
- Jayanti.
- What did I say?
What's going on?
What did I miss?
- Nothing.
- All okay?
Where's my gin?
Is it done?
- Almost done.
- Raman. Here.
Sandy!
- The sambar tastes amazing.
- Thanks.
Sandeep, I'm eating
your mutton curry after ages.
Need anything else?
All the kids, sit there.
Nazia, sit there.
Make space for Nazia.
- Sandeep, this is fabulous.
- Thank you.
What can I get for you, Mr Handa?
At your service.
You are a fake.
You don't have any principles
or beliefs.
But I believe in friendship...
Get lost.
You tell me your name first.
Kumar.
Your real name.
What kind of a name is Kumar?
It's a middle name.
- What's your real name?
- What's in a name, Rose?
I am me and you are you.
That's it.
No.
We are who we are.
And you...
- You are fake.
- Never.
Your life is fake.
My name is Kumar.
Does anyone have a problem with it?
We don't have a problem.
Kumar is a great name, bro.
You know, it's just a label.
Your name.
My name is Chandra.
I'm from India.
What are these?
Just labels I was given.
- And I became that.
- Correct, Doc.
He became Kumar.
I became Chandra.
I became Raman.
Are you saying we just become
what we're given?
Well, that's the starting point.
And we also make ourselves.
We're constantly
making ourselves, right?
We pick labels.
What is hard-working or liberal
or honest?
These are labels.
We take them.
Put them on our foreheads.
And that defines us.
Then we become that.
I agree with you.
I think my husband is honest,
diligent and gentlemanly.
- Shrewd!
- And a great sambhar maker.
- Yes!
- That's true.
- New label for you.
- Think he's a gentleman?
Bollocks!
Your gentleman can't even
run a business.
The company is still afloat
because of me.
If it were up to him,
the business would have tanked.
Really? You think..
Raman can't manage
the business on his own?
But I think you guys
make a good team.
You know... You play the good cop.
You play the bad cop.
I don't play.
I am the bad cop.
Basically, the thing is...
You need an ass of steel
to run a business.
Pardon my French.
There are kids here, Sohrab.
If you have steel,
get into business.
Otherwise, do something else.
You don't have to run a business.
No one's forcing you.
Work in fashion or art.
Stay at home.
No need to do anything.
You know what I'm saying?
What?
No reaction?
No protest? Come on,
you guys are becoming boring now.
No, actually, I think
you're becoming boring.
And very predictable.
I like that.
I like a bit of a challenge.
Want me to up the ante?
No.
Please spare us the misery.
Thank you.
Hard-working, loyal, honest...
These are all good labels.
- Right, Doc?
- Sure.
What about mean, rude,
lazy, awful?
Who'd choose labels like these?
Hi, I'm Kumar.
Nazia.
It's none of my business but...
Do you know Madhvan
has a wife?
- He's happily--
- Yeah, I know.
Maybe, he's not so happy anymore.
Good.
No secrets. No lies.
Good one.
...our own moral
code of conduct.
We have to form our own morality.
I think that's the problem.
When we try and impose our truths
and our beliefs
on to others.
That's the root of all evil.
That's the beginning
of evil for sure.
I don't think people are evil.
I think they're inherently
good at heart.
- She is so sweet.
- I'm serious.
Just trying to
come to terms with--
Oh my God!
There goes Ms Twinkle Eyes!
You're so sweet.
Everyone is so good.
This world is so beautiful!
Come on, Jayanti.
My cake is the best cake.
I live in a fairytale house.
My husband is the most handsome...
You're giving me diabetes.
Please give me a break.
You don't have to be so
fricking mean all the time, Sohrab.
You know that?
Grow the hell up.
Why are you getting so touchy?
- I'm not being touchy, actually.
- Yes, you are.
Just trying to have
an adult conversation.
And if you can't have that
then you should...
I don't know...
Just sit down.
And try and be social.
I am being social.
Why do you think I've come
to your fairytale anniversary?
I wish you weren't here.
If wishes were horses.
- He needs to stop doing this.
- Calm down.
Bravo!
I'm glad somebody is finally
giving it to the Handa.
Shut up and finish your food.
Everyone has cooked
with so much love.
- Give him some 'sambhar'.
- Satya, coffee.
But I'm glad I came.
Especially,
for your 'sambhar', Raman.
- It's good, right?
- Very good.
- It's amazing.
- Have some more.
Sandeep, give me a cigarette.
Alright.
Here's a mealtime game.
- Shall we try?
- Yeah.
Go for it, Doc.
Okay, if you
could be somebody else...
Anybody else...
Who would you be?
I'd be like papa.
- What?
- Okay.
- Fine. Okay. Spiderman.
- Spiderman.
I pick JK Rowling.
JK Rowling.
Jhunjhunwala.
Okay.
Good choice.
I'd be my mother.
She was such a lovely lady.
Wasn't she?
I'll be Sohrab Handa.
Bro, I want to be you.
- It's beyond you.
- I can always aspire to be...
Missed your chance this time.
Next birth.
Be a proper Kumar first.
Jayanti, what about you?
I would be Raman.
- Always kind.
- So sweet.
Of course.
- Don't you have anything to say?
- What did I say?
Did I say anything?
Even when I'm quiet
you want to provoke me.
- Baba, some more mutton?
- Two small pieces and gravy.
"Two small pieces
and a little gravy."
Polished off half a kilo already.
It's okay to indulge
once in a while.
It's not okay.
Doctors have forbidden it.
He is surviving on half a kidney.
That's why this nurse
follows him like a shadow.
Be good and eat sambar now.
- Whatever!
- Oh!
And now he'll play the victim card.
- Please don't mind him.
- Daddy-o had a surgery recently.
He gets hormone injections everyday.
It's all been cleaned
out down there.
Nothing's left.
Factory is permanently shut.
Unfortunately...
- Can't have siblings anymore.
- You fool!
I am going to kill you.
Baba!
- Will you talk to me like that?
- Baba! Stop it!
Old man's gone crazy!
I am going to kill him!
Stop hitting me like a little girl!
Signs of life!
Gabbar Singh!
Calm down, Baba.
- The hormone injections are working!
- Enough!
- Sohrab...
Otherwise, my father will
become my mother.
Shut up!
Mummy!
Mr Handa is going to be Mrs. Handa.
- Stop it!
- Daddy-o will be turning into my mommy!
Stop it.
That's enough.
Wow!
The old man still has some life in him.
Sohrab.
- That's the limit. Just stop.
- It's okay.
Everyone is entertained.
Not a big deal.
What's for dessert?
Where is Ram Gopal Satya?
Did you guys fight often?
We didn't fight.
But there were moments of discord.
He was my flesh.
He was a piece of my heart.
Look at him now.
Uncle is right.
Sohrab was a nice man.
He didn't mean any harm.
He was a gem.
It's true.
He was a remarkable man.
We misunderstood him.
He had a good heart and I was...
Oh please, guys.
He was a horrible man.
He was mean and vicious.
Nena.
He was not nice.
No!
- Nena, please.
- I am sorry but it's the truth.
- Nena, come on.
- Don't speak ill of the dead.
I wouldn't.
But you guys are going on and on
about him being a gem.
You guys couldn't stand his guts
and now he's become a gem?
Stop it, Nena.
- Isha, I'm sorry.
- He's my husband. Just stop.
But this is the truth.
- Everyone now suddenly...
- How dare you! Just stop!
Who are you to talk
about my son?
So you want to defend him now?
- Yes!
- Nena...
Two hours ago,
you wanted to kill him.
- That's our family matter.
- He's my son!
He was my flesh, my blood!
Please. Enough of this.
Please...
Please, guys.
We've just lost our friend.
We're all here...
thanks to Sohrab.
And now he's gone.
May his soul rest in peace.
If he was this kind of a man...
I mean,
someone who picked fights...
Then...
Then everyone in this room
must have a motive to kill him.
What are you saying?
I'm telling you
someone killed him.
And the killer is one of you.
Sir, listen.
He was an ass.
- What are you saying?
- Hear me out.
- He was a jerk.
- Is this necessary?
But that's not reason enough
to kill somebody, right?
- Right, Raman?
- Yeah.
Maddy?
Sir, Sohrab was our friend.
We've been friends for 20 years.
Sir!
We'd accepted him
for what he was.
Sir, think I found it.
- What?
- The murder weapon.
It's okay.
- Put it in the plastic bag.
- Yes, sir.
Calm her down.
Call boss and ask him how soon
can he get here.
I know who did it.
Who?
He killed himself.
It was a suicide.
- Arun.
- I know!
He hated himself.
He wanted to end it.
So, he ended it.
- Suicide?
- Yes.
So, he slit his own throat...
hid the knife behind the cupboard...
and then went back to the sofa?
Anyone can hide the knife.
Arun.
Go and rest, sleep.
You killed him!
Calm down.
All of you killed him.
You killed my brother!
Move!
- Arun...
- No.
Let him be.
I was thinking...
All this will settle down
in a week or two.
What about the future?
What do you mean?
I mean...
Life has to go on, right?
Raman will need a helping hand.
And Sohrab...
Talk to Raman...
...about Sandeep.
Once he's given responsibility
he can prove himself.
Right?
Tell Raman, he's hardworking.
You guys won't be sorry.
Yeah?
I'll speak to him later.
Yeah.
Whenever you get the chance.
I just wanted you
to keep it in your mind.
That's it.
Okay.
- Wait.
- What?
Do you know about Isha?
What?
She sleepwalks.
What have you decided,
Mr Qureshi?
You see...
That's for my boss to decide.
We'll just have to wait for him.
Yeah, but you are boss for now.
It was an unfortunate accident.
Will you keep us up all night
for that?
I'm your fan, Kumar ji.
I'm not an idiot.
Huh?
His throat
did not get slit accidentally.
This is a murder.
Premeditated.
Don't write it off as a mishap.
Used the wrong word.
It's a disaster.
A tragedy.
He was our friend.
We're all heartbroken.
But we have a prime time show.
Can't skip the recording.
- So much to do--
- Yes, sir.
We're right here.
There's no problem, sir.
Everything is on track.
Yes, sir...
Amar ji, it's up to you now.
Please find a way.
How?
You tell us.
We're ready...
for whatever needs to be done.
Are you making an offer?
We are open to make a deal.
I'm also open, ma'am.
He's also generally open.
But the big boss...
if he gets a hint of this,
we'd all be in deep shit.
We have a suspect...
- Amar ji!
- Yes, sir!
What happened?
Sandeep!
- Arun fell off the tree house.
- Raman.
Maddy!
Arun!
- He's alive.
- Arun!
- Careful.
- Be careful.
Isha!
Wait.
Are you okay?
Sandeep, come this side.
What's this?
- Families should stay together.
- You go there.
- What are we playing?
- Dumb charades.
- Come here.
- What's happening?
Nena, you go there.
- I'll go there?
- Come, come.
We'll beat them anyway.
You guys have just let me go, huh?
I'm not that bad.
- We're a better team anyway.
- Okay, start.
I'm going first.
I'll give her the name.
Don't give her an easy one
because she's your sister.
I can hear you.
What did you get?
- Okay.
- We're keeping time.
Okay, guys. Listen.
- Hindi.
- One word.
- It's begun.
- 'Talaq'.
'Talaq'.
Why are you only talking to him?
Talk to us too.
- Wait!
- You're not allowed to talk!
- Drive...
- You and me, driving.
- Give up.
- Boy and girl.
Both of us?
We were driving?
You and me driving...
- And?
- Highway!
- Bomb blast!
- Bomb! Bomb!
'Daud?'
And we got a flat tyre...
We were going for 'Badla'!
Yes!
- 'Badla'?
- No, no, no.
This is cheating.
How is this cheating?
You're supposed
to describe the film.
Not how you saw it.
I didn't say anything.
It's valid.
Fair and square, we won.
We forgive you.
Thank you.
Okay, who's next?
Sandeep!
- Good luck.
- Go get them!
- Hey, Satya! Get me a drink.
- You're sore losers.
- Put one cube of ice in this.
- Right away.
- Kumar, shift a little.
- Okay, ready?
- Yes, ready.
- Your time starts now.
English?
One word.
- English or Hindi?
- Hindi.
Tell us clearly.
Hindi or English?
It's Hindi.
Dangerous?
Ghost?
Anger? Fear?
Wolf?
Tiger?
- Monster? Predator?
- Beast?
Fear? Fright?
- Predator?
- Tiger?
- Do something else.
- Give another hint.
Bear?
Please do something else.
- Bat! Bat!
- Bird?
- A bat?
- It's a bird!
- Bird?
- Eagle?
- Kite!
You guys are so bad at this.
- Witch!
- Pigeon...
Sohrab Handa!
Bat!
Crow!
- Crow!
But crow is an English word.
Okay crow is half the word.
Crow dancing?
Dancing crow?
- A dancing crow?
- A crow that dances?
No. Dancing crow.
Time is up.
'Krodh'.
- 'Krodh'.
- 'Krodh' meaning anger.
Why were you showing a crow?
Crow-dha!
We got the crow part.
But how would we ever get 'dha'?
'Ta dhin dhin dha'.
Crow + dha!
Come on, Sandeep!
- Shouldn't have sent you.
- It's okay.
Did a crow eat your brain?
You're too cute.
I'll go.
Just remember,
you guys are 2-0 behind.
And we're kicking your butt.
Who's going to give me the title?
- I am.
- Oh my God!
You're going to
give me something?
Or you'd give me something else?
I could.
In front of all these people?
- We don't mind.
- Okay, come on.
- May I?
- Go on.
We can watch this
instead of playing.
Not tonight.
Is this 'Gone with the Wind'?
- What's going on?
- Okay, fine.
What name did you give him, Isha?
Three words.
English.
Oh sorry.
It's English.
- First word.
Is it an old film?
Brother... how nicely you cut it...
I love you, brother... I love you...
Kumar, let him show properly.
I love you.
What's that?
What are those?
- Blood oozing out.
- Cutting.
- Cutting out.
This is from when I was 13.
This, when I was 18.
This one is pretty recent.
Want to play something else?
You guys are really bad at this.
Arun has fallen down.
Raman, come.
Be careful.
Easy there.
What happened, Arun?
Are you okay?
What were you doing up there?
- Any broken bones?
- Oh my God!
- Take him in.
- Is the leg broken?
- Careful.
- It's not broken.
What happened, Arun?
Please relax.
But how did he slip like that?
That's really bad.
- Careful.
- We should put turmeric. Satya!
No need.
I have an ointment.
It works like magic.
-I'll get it.
-Ice.
One second.
What were you doing there?
Huh?
Who asked you to go there?
Is anything broken?
No, it's fine.
Oh God!
How did he fall?
How would he fall like that?
Did you lose your footing?
Did someone push you?
Maybe...
- I'm just asking.
- Sorry.
Who was it?
Did you see him?
- No.
- What the hell is going on?
Who has gone bonkers?
What's going on?
Who's doing this to us?
Do you want to kill us all,
one by one?
Raman, please stop.
Who is it?
- You? You? You?
- Raman!
- Did you take money from my bag?
- No.
My money is missing.
My money has been stolen.
Someone stole 20 thousand bucks
from my bag.
Who's going to take
your money, Suman?
There were 10 bills of 2000.
Must be somewhere.
I'm telling you
it was stolen.
Someone stole money
from my bag.
Who'd steal money?
How would I know?
Please check carefully.
It's probably still there.
- I checked everywhere.
- You'll get it back.
- Here's the turmeric.
- Ask him.
Satya.
Yes, ma'am?
Did you take the money
from the bag?
No, I didn't, ma'am.
Stop lying!
Own up.
- Sir, I haven't stolen any money.
- Then who did?
- Did I?
- Tell us the truth, Satya.
Search him.
He must have it.
- He said he didn't do it.
- I don't have anything.
Get him here.
- What is this?
- Sir...
There's been a theft
and you're showing me your pockets?
- Why are you hitting him?
- What are you doing?
Please stay out of it.
Let us do our work.
Take him in.
He said he hasn't taken it.
Got the poor man in trouble.
You didn't steal this?
No, sir, I swear I haven't.
It magically appeared here?
- Sir... That man gave it to me.
- Who?
Speak up.
What's his name?
The one, who is slightly fat.
Mr Qureshi,
he's trying to be smart.
Lock him up.
These guys are all thieves!
No, sir, I'm not lying.
He gave it to me.
He asked me not to tell anyone.
Not to tell anyone, what?
- Bring him out.
- Did you find the money?
Yeah, he had it.
Show me who it was.
Hmm?
Tell us who gave you the money.
I'm sure it's him.
He's lying. Give him a tight one.
Come on.
Are you going to speak up
or should I take you to the station?
- It was him.
- What?
He gave me the money.
What rubbish!
He stole the money.
Why would Sandeep
give him money?
Right, Sandeep?
Why would I give him money?
Sir, he gave it to me.
He was washing blood off his hands.
When I saw him,
he asked me to wait.
He went in and got the money.
And asked me not to tell anyone.
- Are you sure you saw it?
- Yes, sir.
- Sure?
This is nonsense.
- I'm telling the truth.
- Who the hell are you?
I'm the caretaker.
Did you give him the money?
- Did you?
- Yes, gave him a little tip.
Sandeep!
Rs. 20,000 as a tip?
It was from all of us.
Who asked you to?
What time was this?
About 12:30.
What about the blood
you were washing off?
He's lying.
Is he lying?
Or are you lying?
- Huh?
- Sandeep?
Say something, Sandeep.
I...
Yes?
I had come out for a smoke.
Sohrab was already dead.
The knife was on the floor.
I picked it up. Got blood on my hands.
- I was washing the blood when--
- Okay, that's enough!
- You can't do this.
- Raman!
- Baba!
- One minute.
Wait!
I haven't done anything.
Sandeep, look at me.
Did you do it?
No! Why would I kill him?
He was like my brother.
- He hasn't done it.
- Take him away.
- He wouldn't lie to me...
- Move!
- What are you doing?
- Let me do my job.
I didn't kill him.
- Let's go.
- I didn't kill him.
- Swear on God.
- Are you a leftie?
I swear I didn't kill him.
- I...
- Are you a leftie?
Yes.
- Suman.
- You use your left hand for everything?
Yes.
- Are you a leftie?
- Yes, he is. He's a leftie.
- Amar ji.
- Yes, sir.
Let him go.
Why, sir?
Why are you letting him go?
Because, ma'am,
he didn't do it.
How do you know?
He's a leftie.
And the murderer is right-handed.
The throat has been slit
left to right.
I told you he hasn't done it.
Why did you lie?
I didn't lie, he had blood on
his hand, he gave me money.
I would make you confess.
So, you'd blackmail him?
- He did it.
- I didn't do it, sir.
- I'm sure he did it.
- Stop it! Raman!
One slap and he'll confess.
It's not him, Raman.
How do you know, Chandra?
Because it's way too convenient
if it's him.
Now she can talk.
Yes.
It's not him.
It's you.
It's one of you.
Who the hell are you?
Take a breath, please.
Everyone.
Stop crying!
- Go inside and cry if you have to.
- Arun.
- Stop stinking up the room.
- Arun!
You lied to me?
How could you?
Here's the thing, you know...
- They really stood by us.
- Yeah.
Both, Raman and Jayanti.
Who is older of the two of you?
Take a guess.
No idea.
- You can't tell, right?
- No...
- I'm am older by five years.
- Okay. Really?
I've taken care of her
more than our mom.
Your father passed away quite early.
Yeah.
Too soon.
He was so young.
I was probably 10 years old.
Papa had a serious drinking problem.
I see.
His liver was damaged.
That's why I don't let him
drink at all.
No drinking allowed.
Haven't had a drink in 15 years.
Oh please now.
Don't make me start.
When was the last time
I had a drink?
You dare take one sip.
You're scolding me
for something I may do in future.
I have to scold him.
To keep him in line.
You don't know him.
He can do anything.
- Yeah?
- Anything at all.
Good night!
Good night, Nazia.
Bye.
We'll leave
by 7 tomorrow, Madhvan.
Yes, I'll be up and about.
That's a six.
Not a nine.
I need to leave too.
Nena, stay a little longer.
Have to wake up early.
Have to drive.
Come on.
Your turn.
Sleep well.
Satya!
Put the cake in the fridge.
Don't take the cake away.
Let it be.
Keep it back.
For midnight munchies.
Leaving it for you!
Thank you.
- Good night.
- Good night, Doctor .
- Good night, Doctor.
- Good night, Handa Saheb.
Let's go.
I'm done.
One more game.
Please.
One more, please.
Let's go.
This wasn't such a great idea.
No?
Nope.
I wanted you to meet the gang.
Yeah, but they're a bit strange.
Huh?
Come on.
They're okay.
Yeah, they're okay.
They're just...
I don't know.
- What?
- They're old.
Something like that.
That they are.
Yeah.
Don't judge them for being old.
I'm not judging them.
I don't judge you.
That's true.
Yeah.
But then again...
You're not old.
Are you?
- No, I'm not.
- No, you're not.
I don't like it, Raman.
He's not even going to agree.
And...
He's going to hold it against you
all his life, so...
What should I do?
Should I be scared
for the rest of my life?
Because Handa is going to be mad
at me.
You don't have to deal
with him everyday.
- I do.
- I know, babe, but...
Everything is going well.
I'm saying why--
Why are you saying anything at all?
I'm handling it.
I need to believe
this is going to work out.
You just keep filling my head
with doubts.
Why?
Okay.
Fine.
Do whatever you want.
Do it the way you want,
with whoever you want.
Hey.
Look, I...
Just... Please...
Have you fallen asleep
in the bathroom?
Why didn't you die
as soon as you were born?
You are like a stone
around my neck.
Guys, is there any left?
Look at that.
The philosopher falls
for a mere cake.
Handa Saheb,
I tried really hard but...
couldn't resist it.
Why should you?
To hell with self-control.
You won't become fat
in a day.
You know something?
You're absolutely right.
Maddy, can you take a photo
of us, please?
- Okay.
- One more.
Okay, got it.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Good night, guys.
Good night, Professor.
Look at this.
- So nice.
- Hmm.
What happened, sir?
- Did you cut your hand?
- Yes.
-Don't tell anyone.
-What?
That you cut your hand?
Just don't say anything, okay?
Don't say what?
I don't get it, sir.
Wait here.
Sir...
Keep it.
It's your tip, from all of us.
Thank you, sir.
- You can go.
- Okay, sir.
Jayanti.
Sandeep.
What happened?
You came, ate some cake
and left.
And madam, at about 12:15,
you went to sleep.
Yes.
When you came down at 12:40
he was already dead
according to you.
Yes.
Got it.
So between 12:15 and 12:40,
did anyone see anything?
Anything at all?
I had already crashed.
We were also asleep.
Around 12:30...
I heard a loud noise...
of a door banging shut.
Very loud.
Actually, that's true.
I'd heard a loud bang
in the middle of the night.
There was, right?
Which door was it?
I'm not sure.
One of the doors.
Okay, fine.
No problem.
- Amar ji, do something.
- Yes, sir.
- Shut all the doors one by one.
- Okay, sir.
Try to identify which door it was.
- But they--
- Let's try.
You'll figure it out.
- This one?
- Amazing!
Amazing!
When Nena told me first,
I thought it was impossible.
Sohrab would never agree.
- Never.
- Kumar, please.
- At least, your problem is solved.
- Kumar!
He'd never have agreed.
You're being very
insensitive, Kumar.
- Insensitive?
- Yeah.
I am the insensitive one here?
What wouldn't he agree to?
Nothing, I'll tell you later.
Why don't you tell her now?
The person you were
hiding it from is dead.
- Oh my God!
- Kumar!
- How can you talk like that?
- Did you know?
He wanted Nena
to invest in the company.
To buy out Sohrab's share.
Did you know?
This was going on behind your back.
Stop it.
- Now you're ashamed to admit it.
- Can you please...
- Why can't you tell everyone?
- Please be quiet.
What is he saying, Raman?
- It's not what you're thinking.
- It's exactly what she's thinking.
Jayanti?
Did you know about this?
Jayanti knew?
- You knew about it?
- There's nothing to know.
Such hypocrites!
- I was begging you.
- We were just talking.
What kind of people are you?
Ready to stab anybody
in the back?
Today it's Sohrab.
Tomorrow it might be Nena.
Then somebody else.
You didn't think of Sandeep
at all?
Or your sister?
Do relationships mean
anything to you?
You only care about money.
- Selfish people!
- Suman, let it go.
Kumar, was this necessary?
- I can't stand his charade!
- Yeah, right!
You were going to cut Sohrab out?
No, Isha.
Only if he agreed.
I'd have given him
his fair share.
Fair share?
It's his company, okay?
He included you.
- And you!
- No...
Suman, I don't get
into their business...
Relations are like business
for you.
No one cares
for anyone in this room.
Everyone has a price.
Everything remains the same.
Okay?
Sandeep is still part of the company.
Nothing has changed.
We don't need your charity.
Nothing has changed?
This party...
was there to make a deal?
- No.
- You're sick!
Yes, exactly!
- You guys are sick!
- Isha, no.
Yes, it was there
to make a deal.
When the cops were taking him away,
no one came to defend him.
Cat got your tongue.
It's only Sandeep...
How does it matter?
- Let him take the blame for murder.
- You'd never do this...
All my life I have lived
on your alms, but this!
Remember, pride comes
before the fall.
It will be the end of you!
- What lengths would you go to?
- Suman, please. We're leaving.
What are you capable of?
Did you kill him?
You killed him!
- You killed him!
- No, Isha. I didn't.
Did you?
Did he push you, Arun?
- Isha.
- You've done it.
Isha!
- Kumar, are you happy now?
- Did he push you?
- Are you happy?
- He is the one, right?
Isha!
Be quiet.
Inspector...
I killed him.
- Baba, stop it.
- Arrest me.
He gave us all a lot of grief.
He was like an open wound.
Don't be silly.
Just go to your room.
- You just go.
- Keep quiet.
You don't know a thing!
He was a monster!
- Arun.
- He hurt you too...
Did you not hear any door bang?
I should have done it
long time back.
He was forever a pain.
He was neither a good son.
Nor a good husband.
He couldn't even
be anyone's friend.
But I am his father.
I had to fulfill my duty
as his father.
- Inspector, let's end this.
- We'll do it.
Give us your statement first.
Tell me exactly how you did it.
Well...
Not much.
Everyone was asleep.
I came out here.
The knife was on the table.
I went behind him...
And put it to his neck...
Then I went back to my room.
The door banged shut.
I got startled.
What did you do
with the knife?
- Did you take it with you?
- Why would I take it with me?
- Left it here... On the table, probably.
- Sir...
Sir?
The knife was not on the table.
See, inspector.
I'm not lying.
You're not lying.
It's true that the sound of the door
came from your room.
Also true, that you're trying
to be a good father.
By trying to save your son.
Am I wrong, Arun?
Why did you have to speak?
It was getting to be fun.
Everybody's cover was getting blown!
What are you doing, Arun?
- What are you doing?
- You're the only sane one here, right?
- Arun!
- That's enough!
Arun is dead!
He was an open wound.
A stone around your neck?
Now you are free.
Now live happily ever after.
Is this statement enough?
So you admit
that you killed your brother?
You're a sub-inspector, right?
This will get you a promotion.
Yes, I did it.
Let's go.
Take him away.
Arun!
- Arun!
- Why the hell did you do it, Arun?
You're asking me, Madh?
I did it because of you.
Because of all of you.
All of you
were always mean to him.
All of you are involved.
He cried himself to sleep
every night.
Every night!
Couldn't bear to see him like this.
Someone had to end it.
So, I did.
I have no regret.
I did the right thing.
Wa-wait a second.
Who did you kill?
You are the educated one, Doctor.
You tell me.
Was I wrong?
All of them used to avoid him
like the plague.
They tolerated him
because he's my brother.
Because they are all scared of me.
Not like he was living anyway.
He'd cut himself up three times.
So you just helped him along,
did you?
I delivered him!
I set him free.
Wherever he is,
he's happier now.
So all of you can buzz off
with your fricking fake grief.
Arun, my son.
Son... Son…
You more than anyone else,
old man...
You were the biggest pain
for both of us.
Please atone in peace, Daddy-o.
No one will trouble you anymore.
- Arun!
- He's not Arun.
What the hell just happened?
He switched.
- Switched?
- Who?
What?
He idolised Sohrab.
He wanted to be like him.
Sohrab was his hero.
Now he has become Sohrab.
That's not Arun you see there.
That's Sohrab.
Sandeep, give me a cigarette.
I think I might have to bear
some of the blame.
And you too, Madh.
If you could be
somebody else...
- We were free...
- Anybody else...
- ...free to choose.
- No...
We're all us, but you..
- Who would you be?
- I'll be Sohrab Handa!
Bro, I want to be you.
Are you saying we become
what we are given?
You're writing your own story.
You choose your hero.
Want some cake, tiger?
- ...and you become that.
- I'm me and you're you.
We make ourselves...
Want to cut it or stab it?
What did we choose?
Anybody else?
Who would you be?
What's in a name, Rose?
I'm me and you're you.
Survival... We lie to survive...
I can always aspire to be...
...nobler in the mind
to suffer the slings and arrows...
Why didn't you die
the moment you were born?
Or take arms
against a sea of troubles...
He became Sohrab.
But in the bargain
Sohrab became Arun in his head.
I suppose the only way...
to help him was...
He was right.
It was suicide in a way.
What is this rubbish?
- Who pushed him down?
- No one pushed him.
He jumped.
Bravo!
Everyone has gotten smarter
with the day break. Wow!
You had a good game going.
Well done.
So you do have some balls.
Be very careful
what you wish for.
Very careful.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Let's take him to the station.
Both my sons...
I lost both of them at one go.
It's okay.
Take care.
Bye, Kumar.
Bye, Chandra.
Bye, Maddy.
Bye, Doctor.
Nena?
Carry on, Kumar.
I'll see you at the studio.
I'm coming with Suman.
Why are you going
with Suman?
Nena.
- Satya!
- Yes, ma'am.
Sometimes, these games
don't turn out so well.
It's not your fault.
Please don't blame yourself.
I should have seen it earlier...
It's not you.
It's us.
We choose to fall
every single time.
We're doomed.
I hope you're wrong.
Good luck, Professor.
Nena, come with me, please.
Just carry on.
I'll see you there.
Professor.
What will save us, Professor?
Beauty.
Did you have the cake?
No?
Didn't even taste it?
It was a good cake!
Very expensive.
What's your salary?
Fifteen thousand?
Twenty grand with bribes.
- Amar ji.
- Yes, sir.
Don't talk to him.
He's crazy.
It's okay,
If dry bread is your fate
how will you ever eat cake?
Talk to me.
Or I'll get bored.
Hey, look there.
See that?
What an amazing job He has done!
He just messed up
while making humans.
"A wayward weird worrying thing"
"Has sunk within me"
"Some wordless, worthless thing"
"Is stuck within me"
"He drowned, sometimes he swam"
"He clung to me, sometimes he died"
"The life of the party,
Or a maudlin thing"
"Kicked the door open with a sickness"
"And no cure for him"
"Who is he, who is he?"
"Who could he be?"
"Who is he,
who could he be?"
"Friends with their hands"
"Full of deceits"
"Even the good ones"
"Muddy with guilt"
"The lies were inexhaustible"
"The masks fixed
Tightly to their skin"
"Clawed and clawed and clawed"
"How I clawed at their facades"
"How I ripped into their faces"
"How I strangled each one's neck
"Until the truth came out,
Sputtering, bleeding"
"From the shadows for so long"
"A wayward weird worrying thing"
"Is stuck within me"
"Some wordless, worthless thing"
"Has sunk within me"