Andrés?
- Mmm…
- What are you doing naked?
Tourists come here all the time
to visit the site.
Don't worry. Nobody will come today.
I bought all the tickets.
I'm absorbing the telluric energy
from these stones cut by ancient masons.
C'mon.
Lie down. C'mon.
Don't be shy. It's okay. Lie down.
Did you know that the rock this castle
was built on has magical properties?
It was founded in the 13th century
by the Templar Knights.
They always built in strategic locations.
Portals of energy, Sergio. It's magical.
Fun fact, Pope Luna used to live here.
A man who'd been repudiated
and excommunicated,
and in a time where life expectancy
was less than 40 years old,
he lived to the ripe old age of 94.
I mean how is that even possible?
Would you like to know?
Because of this stone.
It has a primal healing energy.
Primal healing?
Sergio!
Who do you think I am?
I'm not the kind of man who makes
his family travel across the country
to give them news
to make them all depressed
I… only give wonderful news.
Little brother.
I'm getting married.
You mean again?
This is the fourth time,
and you're head over heels, I guess?
More than ever.
Mm-hm. I bet you just met the woman?
Mm… kinda.
- It's a gift that I have.
- That'd be improbable, Andrés. Improbable.
Sergio! Loving someone
brings true happiness.
And being loved
really is a pale imitation.
The best part about being in love
is to be able to act on it,
to follow your animal passions.
And I have that gift.
Isn't it simply marvelous?
I'm happy for you, brother.
Thanks.
But first of all,
you and I are going to celebrate
the end of my bachelor lifestyle. Hm?
You and I.
Um… Did you bring anything else to wear,
aside from the librarian uniform?
- Um, uh… To be honest, uh…
- Listen, go buy some clothes.
I have to go see the Dutchman.
You buying art?
Something like that.
I've thought it over. My answer is no.
Please, Genoveva, lower your voice.
I don't wanna wait
until you've completed the robbery.
We could lose this passion.
I'm just asking you for… some more time
to do things correctly.
But you have no idea what will happen
when you stop working for my husband.
And maybe…
I'll lose interest in you.
Or maybe, you'll lose interest in me.
Or who knows, maybe…
someone will murder you.
I know you're seeing all the obstacles
right now.
But we just might be happy.
Am I interrupting?
If only you had been here
a second earlier.
This man,
he attempted to kiss me.
Darling, would you kindly leave us
for a moment?
Look me in the eye.
Did you just try to kiss my wife?
No, I didn't do anything.
I give you my word, sir.
I can see you're not lying.
Things are not going well between us.
She thinks that I don't see it,
but I see it all.
Absolutely everything. Everything.
And now, with you staying here
at our house,
you've gained our trust
and become a friend.
So I'm afraid, Damián, that just makes you
the bait to feed into her fantasies.
In any case, my friend…
I always know when someone's lying.
I need you to understand
that if you imagine or even dream
about laying your filthy hands on my wife…
If you touch her,
or if you even breathe the same air…
with God… as my witness…
I swear you will never leave this place
because I will bury you six feet under,
deep in the crypt.
Alive!
But I will leave a very small gap.
A tiny one.
Just enough to get some air,
to give you enough time to repent,
to think about the consequences.
Do you understand?
Okay. Great.
Our first cocktail. Sex on the beach.
So tell me, who is she?
Her name's Candela.
- A joyous ode to life.
- Mm.
- What does she do?
- She's a pickpocket. A thief.
And together,
we've designed a beautiful plan.
It's okay. No need to worry.
Because the plan is a fake one.
What do you mean, it's fake?
There's this aristocrat.
The man's insufferable.
But he hired me
to steal a painting for him.
And I said yes.
But I'm not going to do it.
You made a deal,
and you're not gonna do it?
It's not like I'm short on ideas.
On the contrary, Sergio.
It just so happens that robbing a painting
is rather simple.
Andrés, Andrés…
Oh! Good afternoon. Hello there.
Have a nice day.
But robbing the Bank of Spain…
now, that's complicated.
It's got nothing to do with
whether this is easy or difficult.
You made a deal. You promised.
It's your word of honor, brother.
Sergio, come here.
This gentleman will most definitely want
to murder me
once he realizes that robbing the painting
was just a subterfuge
to stealing all his money.
Andrés, maybe he is an aristocrat,
but from what you have told me,
he's obviously a criminal.
Do you wanna spend the rest of your life,
looking over your shoulder
for some would-be assassin?
The only way you can guarantee your safety
is to make sure that whatever happens,
he has something to gain
and something to lose.
In other words,
if he decided to take revenge,
he would lose much, much more
than he can gain. Hmm?
- So we both win or we both lose.
- Exactly.
But for that, you need to do the job.
You're right about that.
And in any case, preparing a heist
and not going through with it,
it's not very exciting.
- This is much better.
- Go ahead, steal the painting.
Here's to the Lady with an Ermine.
The Da Vinci?
Wait, how are you gonna…
How are you gonna do it?
Why change your mind?
Because nothing
is holding me back anymore.
Because if your husband's gonna kill me,
I may as well kiss you.
And now that I've kissed you,
there's no stopping me.
Your Grace. The Duke
has sent me for his keys.
They're in your bathroom.
I haven't seen them…
But if I do,
I'll be sure to bring them down.
He wants them now.
You know how anxious he can be.
I'm in the middle of getting dressed.
I told you,
I'll bring them down when I'm ready.
Would you like me to ask the maid
to make the bed?
That won't be necessary.
I'll take care of it myself. Thank you.
Keila, I'm kinda busy.
Hey, hey, hey, one minute, one minute.
It's important.
- Did something happen?
- No, not yet.
But something might.
I was an hour early for my date.
Your date? With Bruce?
With Bruce. And another guy.
Claudio, my lover.
But now it looks
like we're gonna be a throuple.
But I don't know. I'm not sure.
I made a list of the pros and cons
for each of them.
But I could only find
good things for both.
So, you see, my system's not so good.
Can I have another margarita
with extra tequila, please?
Keila, are you all right?
A bit tipsy.
So tell me, Cameron,
when you had that thing with Jimmy,
did you have any doubts?
Did you know
whether you loved Jimmy or Roi?
I knew perfectly well. It was Roi.
In fact, I was madly in love with him.
Then Jimmy turned up,
and everything went to hell.
I went to talk to him
with a knot in my stomach.
And I thought that feeling was
because I was going to meet
the love of my life again.
But… I fucked up.
I completely lost it.
We went from bar to bar.
He invited me to a concert…
I just lost the plot.
It was only later,
after we'd had sex on the beach
that I realized
that this knot in my stomach
had nothing to do with seeing Jimmy.
It was because I realized
that the most important person
in my life was Roi.
And you know what?
When I got back home that day,
even though I loved him…
I was incapable of telling him.
So all I did was blame him.
Blame him for everything.
Well, then tell him.
I mean, if you think Roi is
the love of your life, you gotta say it.
Maybe I'll talk to him when I get back.
Good.
But get back here soon, okay?
Yeah.
I have to go now.
Mm. Bruce wants us to have
a three-way relationship.
Are you serious?
Mm-hmm.
I am personally overwhelmed.
Being in a couple is hard enough.
Imagine being in a throuple.
Before I only had virtual relationships.
I'm not good up close.
You might think
I'm pretty damn good, but no, no, no.
I'm not good, no…
We don't know each other that well yet,
but this is the strangest situation
I've ever been in.
It is, yeah, totally.
You're my lover,
but you might leave as my fiancé.
In a throuple made in Las Vegas.
Hey!
Before we end up in Vegas,
I've got something to say.
You see, the thing is…
I believe that I put you up
to this whole crazy thing,
and, well, it's… not fair for you.
Keila, I've… pretended all along
that this was all for love.
'Cause… I'm generous
and because, you know, polyamory
and open relationships are cool.
But all that's not for me.
Roi helped me understand that.
What I'm really feeling is… total fear.
I'm afraid, because this is the first time
I've ever loved someone so intensely.
And this ridiculous idea
of a three-way relationship,
that's just me clutching at straws.
We all know what this is.
This is the story about a guy
who arrives in your life like a hurricane.
And I get blown away.
So now I've made my decision.
I'm leaving.
Your margaritas.
But for tonight…
…we're gonna celebrate
'cause we deserve it.
The three of us. Hmm?
And no sad faces
or depressing conversation.
Tonight we're gonna party. Hmm?
Guys, let's drink
to the shortest threesome in history.
So what do you think?
This is brilliant, Andrés.
Come here.
Hey.
And now… our work is over, it's time
to get this bachelor party started.
What is that?
That's not music. What is it?
I think they call it "flamenco chill."
Do you remember those house parties
with our aunts and mom singing karaoke?
- No. Please don't.
- Yes. Yes. Come with me.
Let's go and show these kids
how people party in California.
Don't make me do this. For God's sake.
- Relax, Sergio. Just follow my lead.
- I'm begging you. Don't do this.
Ba, ba, ba, ba, Barbara Ann
Barbara Ann
Take my hand
You got me rockin' and a-rollin'
Rockin' and a-reelin', Barbara Ann
Ba, ba, ba, ba, Barbara Ann
Went to a dance, lookin' for romance
Saw Barbara Ann
So I thought I'd take a chance
Barbara Ann
Take my hand
You got me rockin' and a-rollin'
Rockin' and a-reelin', Barbara Ann
Ba, ba, ba, ba, Barbara Ann
Barbara Ann
Take my hand
You got me rockin' and a-rollin'
Rockin' and a-reelin', Barbara Ann
Ba, ba, ba, ba, Barbara Ann
Barbara Ann, Barbara Ann
You got me rockin' and a-rollin'
Rockin' and a-reelin'
Unreal.
All right, then…
It's time for me to leave.
It's been an epic night.
Claudio.
My pleasure.
Keila.
See you around.
Do you remember Captain Hook?
Remember when he pokes Peter Pan
on the gangplank with his sword
to push him
into the sea filled with sharks?
Yeah.
You feel like Peter Pan walking the plank?
If I have come this far,
it's only because I've been blessed
to meet someone as wonderful as you.
I've had an epiphany.
You've realized
you're still in love with him?
I knew from the start
it was gonna end this way.
I'm the intruder in this story.
Our story has been a beautiful one.
Everybody deserves a beautiful affair
if it helps them to appreciate
the love they already have.
You should go catch up with your guy.
Watching the sun rise above the ocean
with my brother… It's a miracle.
Fantastic.
You really should get married more often.
You don't do it enough.
I'll get us coffee.
You were right about the rice.
It's a stash for diamonds.
I hid one of my phones inside.
That way, even if they move the goods,
we'll be able to track them.
Not doing what you're told
can be a good thing.
Ciao, Berlin.
Thanks.
- You okay?
- Just perfect.
That fool of a duke I told you about?
I've got him right where I want him.
- May I come in?
- What's going on?
Are you all right?
Because you look a bit pale.
The storm, I guess.
I'm not getting much rest.
I got a call from your friend Cristina.
- Is she feeling better?
- Much better.
As well as one could expect,
considering you poisoned her.
I'd appreciate you telling me
why you're here.
I'm here to steal stuff.
I sign up on these cruises
because the guests travel
with jewelry and valuables.
Fascinating. And you work alone?
I don't need anyone else to do what I do.
Let's play a little game.
I'm gonna go through three theories
about why you're here.
Have a seat.
Hmm…
So the first theory is
that you are a thief who works alone,
who came on board to steal jewelry
and ended up making a hole
underneath your cabin bed.
Give me that phone.
The second possible theory is
that you're an undercover cop,
who came on board to get information
from your informant.
However, let's disregard it.
Unlock the phone, please.
Why disregard it?
Because no cop would be stupid enough
to drill a hole in a boat.
And my third theory is that you are…
part of a gang of thieves.
A gang, who, for whatever reason,
has information about
what we are carrying on board,
and they've paid you to do the dirty work.
A gang… who take their codenames
from the planets.
JUPITER
NEPTUNE
Captain, they need you on the bridge.
It seems… our little chat
is being postponed.
Look at me.
When I come back,
I want you to give me the real names.
Otherwise, it'll be hypothermia for you.
You can't imagine
how many sailors fall overboard.
It's unreal.
My dear friends and comrades.
Good morning.
Um… Did you get some sun?
Yes, I've been thinking about things
while sitting on the beach,
and there's going to be a change of plan.
We're going to steal
the Lady with an Ermine.
Can you tell us why?
This is the best way
to guarantee our safety and peace of mind
for the rest of our lives.
Check this.
What is it?
This is the shady business
that the duke gets up to on his yachts.
It's how he managed to accumulate
that fortune in his vault.
The man smuggles diamonds.
Cameron has just discovered it.
Diamonds?
Uncut diamonds that come
from the mines on the African coast.
Smuggling and selling precious stones
is one of the most profitable
criminal activities in the world.
Local laborers extract tons of diamonds
from mines of Botswana and Sierra Leone,
and then they're sold on the black market.
An uncut diamond
that the duke pays 100 or 200 euros,
once polished and cut in the Netherlands,
can sell for 70,000 euros.
No less.
The fact of the matter is that betraying
hardened gangsters is not a good policy,
so we're going to fulfill
our end of the deal.
Well, in that case, I guess there's
no point in stealing money from his vault.
On the contrary.
But we'll do that shortly after
we steal the painting.
I wanna show you something.
Pardon me, please, Keila.
Looking back, I think those days spent
preparing the heist
were the happiest days of my life.
Nourished by the sweet taste of love.
And the dazzling beauty of Seville.
Surrounded by friends.
Carefully analyzing
every aspect of the plan.
Preparing every minor detail of
the most spectacular and audacious heist
the art world had ever seen.
No.
We've been thinking about how we can open
the last vault door,
and Keila and I believe we've found
a solution that might work.
We analyzed the information we gathered
and found a small notch in the door.
A tiny opening
of about five centimeters in diameter.
I've seen it myself.
At first, we thought it might be
a biometric scanner,
but in that case it would be made
from silicon and aluminum. This is iron.
We've come to the conclusion
that he opens the door with a magnet.
It makes perfect sense.
All of this fits with the twisted,
eccentric personality of the duke,
constantly moving between the complex
and the simple.
Exactly. And I know it is.
It's attached to his keychain,
and it never leaves him.
We need to find someone to steal it.
Someone to pick his pocket,
very discreetly.
A brilliant,
talented work of prestidigitation.
No. Out of the question.
This time, I promised
I wouldn't mix business and pleasure.
I'll have a talk with her.
Is this… what you're looking for?
I gave him a big hug
to wish him safe travels,
and I nicked them from his pocket.
Are you sure he didn't notice
that you stole them from him?
Well, I didn't steal them.
I switched them with another set.
Get me my hand cream.
- May I come in, Your Grace?
- Sure.
The thing is, uh… I'm a bit worried, sir.
I don't trust the people
you invited to the palace.
And forgive me,
but you treat them to your table,
your home, you sing in your stables.
You would do well, sir,
to remember why they are here.
They are thieves… not friends.
What are you trying to tell me, Santos?
They have no intention of stealing
the Lady with an Ermine.
They intend to rob you, sir.
Samuel, what do you think?
Every day, I go to the library
and see what they're doing.
They're going to steal
the Lady with the Ermine.
- What's wrong?
- Where can I find our guests?
The library, sir.
- I've had enough of this!
- Álvaro, what's going on?
We have less than 24 hours
before the robbery,
and you've told me nothing.
- Nothing!
- What are you worried about?
Are you worried my team
and I don't have the talent
to pull off the job
with the panache it deserves?
You have an excellent eye
for these things.
Yes, that is exactly
what I'm worried about.
Because it would be unforgivable
for it to be inconspicuous.
You understand?
I want all of Seville to be talking
about it for decades.
I want headlines across the world press,
on the front page of the Washington Post.
I want the Philippines to wake up to news
about the Lady with an Ermine.
I completely agree with you, Your Grace.
How about you just sit back…
and enjoy the show.
This is an example of the armored trucks
that will be transporting the painting.
The walls are made
of 35 millimeters of solid steel.
So, are you ready to play? Question one.
How do you break into the truck?
Ah…
Two of the team will do it
with thermal lances.
Mmm… That would take approximately…
nine or so minutes.
As we're going to be in the city center
around noon, we can only afford seconds.
How exciting!
- So tell me.
- Ah…
We'll use their own codes
to break into the truck.
Ah.
You'll hang around the airport
and spy on them with a pair of binoculars.
It would be very risky and rather naive
to put all our eggs into one basket,
and using binoculars seems
a bit primitive.
And in any case, the truck is covered
by a large tarp to avoid detection.
Bruce.
So how are you going to get them?
We found the perfect moment
to infiltrate when the doors are opened.
Forty-eight hours earlier…
in the peace of the hangar,
the drivers were checking the truck
to make sure everything was ready,
and that is the moment we captured them
using four cameras we installed. Keila.
The security codes.
This is…
It's amazing.
Darling, take a look at them.
People would think
they're a bunch of Boy Scouts,
posing with their scoutmaster
for a group photo.
When in fact,
they are criminal… masterminds.
And where exactly are you going to do it?
On the Bridge of Triana.
Please tell me…
Tell me I can be looking
from one of those rooftop bars,
watching as my masterpiece unfolds.
I'm afraid not.
You need to be as far away as possible.
Go to the countryside.
Stay with some of your friends.
Most of all, do not browse the internet
concerning the Lady with an Ermine.
So that way, if you ever become a suspect,
these precautions
will guarantee your innocence.
God, as my witness, I'll leave. I will.
Now, you tell me
how you're going to steal it.
Damián, the truck just got on the highway.
It's heading your way.
I've got a visual. It's right behind us.
Initiate Operation Bumblebee.
What's Operation Bumblebee?
It's a very simple operation, whereby
we surround and box in the armored truck
with a makeshift convoy of our own.
It's quite complicated, logistically.
You'll need… 19 vehicles?
Do you have
that many people you can rely on?
100% reliable.
My future wife.
I'm right behind the truck, darling.
And my new in-laws.
In position.
- Everybody's ready, baby.
- Closing the convoy.
The armored truck will be
in the middle of the motorcade.
Like the Virgin in a Holy Week procession.
But the drivers will think
that they're held up in a traffic jam
caused by a truck delivering watermelons.
Brilliant. You got to admit,
there's nothing further from an art heist
than a farmer's truck
making its delivery of watermelons.
Where will it happen?
On the Bridge of Triana.
In the middle of the day.
The Bridge of Triana.
You've chosen the bridge because you can
control the only two accesses.
Yes, that's right.
Public security is essential
during the operation.
All pedestrian and bicycle lanes
on the bridge will be blocked, completely.
This will allow us…
to create a secure, controlled corridor.
ACCESS CLOSED
Our convoy will arrive safely
and on time to the site of our operation.
And once everyone is in place,
then our marvelous magic show will begin.
I'm a big fan of magic.
You ready, Roi?
Let's do it.
Our first act of the show
will begin with a tragic accident
that will capture
the attention of our public.
The blowout of the century.
Go for it.
Once the truck is completely boxed in,
a symphony of screaming brakes
shall ring out.
Each of the vehicles
will be equipped with hidden explosives,
similar to devices used
for special effects in the movies.
These are the sensors.
A small tap, and… pfft!
We will wrap the armored truck
in a cloud of smoke,
dropping a dense cloak
around the entire scene.
Passersby will think
that they are witnessing a spectacular
and tragic accident.
While, in reality,
we will be staging the entire show,
drawing their attention
from one point to another.
They won't have time to think.
Get outta here! It's gonna blow!
Get outta here!
And while their eyes move
from explosion to explosion…
….no one will notice that…
behind that cloud of smoke,
in the middle of the bridge,
hidden in broad daylight,
the greatest art heist
in history will be taking place.
These are replicas
of a real-life explosive device.
I'm impressed.
These gentlemen aren't going to risk
opening that door and having bomb explode.
We're not dealing
with Arnold Schwarzenegger.
Neither Roberto Cornejo nor Blas Mencía
seem to be aspiring heroes,
willing to risk life and limb
to save a masterpiece of Renaissance art.
The painting, including security frame,
is 59 centimeters high and 45 wide.
So we've built
our own custom-made transport.
TRIANA PIZZA
SEVILLE
You're going to stuff
the Lady with an Ermine in a pizza box?
Exactly. And with a driver.
That's a stroke of genius.
And now comes the grand finale,
our finest accomplishment.
While the Lady with an Ermine
continues its route
through the streets of Seville,
a couple of outlaws will remain behind
and brazenly, courageously,
attempt to open the truck
with thermal lances.
They will cut the steel
at 3,500 degrees Celsius.
Halfway through the job,
we'll hear the sirens,
blaring from the nearby streets.
It's time to move!
Everything will be meticulously controlled
to make it appear like a hasty getaway.
So when the police arrive
amidst this chaos,
they'll find it very difficult
to understand what's going on.
Little by little,
as the smoke begins to disperse
they'll start to put the pieces together.
Armed robbery in progress.
Explosives! Everybody, move back!
As the doors are opened
and the final curtain is drawn…
…they'll breathe a sigh of relief.
Because before their very eyes,
they'll discover the Lady with an Ermine,
safe and secure.
A perfect forgery
of the Lady with an Ermine.
Now I see why you went to the Dutchman.
- Sure you do.
- Huh.
We'll make the switch with a forged copy.
It's such a magnificent copy.
So good, you'd think it was painted
by Leonardo da Vinci.
Hm.
Everything has been taken care of.
The packing tape, the reinforced glass,
and the aluminum frame.
We even duplicated the security barcodes.
These numbers are generated randomly
once the artwork leaves the museum.
How did you manage to have
the barcode stickers printed
when the cargo
hasn't even left Poland yet?
Their software was pretty vulnerable,
so we were able to make
a few changes of our own.
In perfect order. Let's go.
They'll think that the heist has failed.
And they'll believe it
for a long time too.
The plan is
absolutely magnificent, however…
where will you keep
the Lady with an Ermine?
She will be exploring Seville,
wrapped nice and cozy in a shopping bag.
The last place anyone would be looking
to find the painting
from a robbery that never took place.
They use wicker baskets
to collect the Boletus edulis mushrooms.
Beautifully crafted. The mushrooms are…
News from Seville
of an attempted robbery
on the Bridge of Triana in broad daylight.
The thieves targeted a truck
transporting da Vinci's masterpiece
the Lady with an Ermine,
which is set to be on display
in the city in the coming days.
For the moment,
no serious injuries have been reported.
They did it.
Understood?
- It's mine.
- Congratulations.
For a moment, you had me doubting, because
of your mediocrity,
your defeatist mentality.
I was doing my best.
I was being cautious, sir.
Goodbye.
It's all yours. I'm leaving.
The moment the duke hung up
on his loyal guard dog, Santos,
fate would have it that one loose end
sentenced us to an almost certain death.
I see you've brought your own.
How long have I been here?
So, anything to tell me?
Maybe a little more tequila will help.
Tell me.
I'm not part of any fucking gang.
And even if I was, you'd never find out.
Any signs of boats?
There is no one within 42 nautical miles.
The radar's clear.
No luck for you, dear.
You won't be running into friendly ships.
And the more you swim,
the more body heat you'll lose.
I'm afraid that's bad news.
The nearest shore is Algeria,
and that's more than 370 miles.
Give it up.
Who's trying to betray my boss?
Who wants to steal from us?
Give me something.
Give me something so I can warn him.
Talk or swim. It's your choice.
My boss's name is Diego.
Diego?
Diego who?
Die-go fuck yourself.
You're a smart-ass
with more balls than brains.
I'll make it out of the water.
Who knows.
Maybe by hanging on to a piece of wood.
Resisting and fighting.
And I'll find you, I swear to God.
When dawn comes,
we'll report you lost at sea.
Until then, best of luck.
Initiating system decode.
The geo radar indicates
a cylinder under the vault.
And the color confirms
that the cylinder contains methane.
So once the methane and oxygen
are consumed during the fire,
the cylinder will refill with gas.
Or not. At the moment, we can't confirm
that it refills automatically
or whether it requires
someone to manually operate it.
It's true we cannot confirm,
but we must assume it.
As soon as I hack that door,
Bruce and Roi will enter,
and there will be an explosion
in the inner ring.
But whatever happens,
the door to the vault should only
be opened once more to get the money out.
Or else face a second gas explosion…
one that you could never survive.
Five more digits.
I'm sorry,
but I'm not brave enough for this.
Bruce, don't do it.
We have fireproof suits,
we have oxygen, and helmets.
We can walk through the fires of hell…
screaming at the top of our lungs.
- Roi…
- It's only 40 seconds, c'mon, Bruce.
- C'mon.
- No, Roi, no.
I know why you wanna go in there.
Because you need the adrenaline
to not be as miserable as you really are.
You act like one of those fools,
the kind who does
the opposite of what he feels.
Instead of feeling sad,
he drinks champagne
to celebrate when his girlfriend leaves.
Instead of running from the fire,
you run straight in
because you're trying to forget…
how much you're hurting.
I don't know
what to do to help you anymore.
No one's going in.
At last, some common fucking sense.
Everyone, get out.
Two digits left.
Damián, I'm going in.
- All clear?
- Everything's clear.
Roi, you don't have to do this.
Last one.
Bruce? Bruce, no!
Bruce, don't do it! Bruce!
Bruce! Bruce, no!
Can someone tell me
what the fuck is going on?
They're both inside now.
What have we done?
The fire's going to start soon.
Roi, Bruce, can you hear me?
So far, so good. The suit's holding up.
45 seconds.
Bruce, are you okay?
Bruce? I can't see anything.
I can't see Bruce!
30 seconds to go.
Bruce, talk to me!
Something's wrong! Something's wrong!
I'm on fire.
Ah! Fuck! Roi!
25 seconds left.
The oxygen tank is getting hot.
His leg is burning!
Oh my God! My back's on fire.
Get us outta here!
- 20 seconds.
- We have to go in.
We're going in. We have to.
- Help! Get us outta here!
- Don't open the door, Keila!
We can't open it.
The influx of oxygen will feed the fire.
As soon as it's done, I'll get them out.
Open the door!
15 seconds left.
Keila! Keila!
We can't let them die!
We're burning alive, for fuck's sake!
Open the fucking door! Open the damn door!
Ten seconds.
We've gotta wait.
Damn it, Berlin, get us outta here!
Bruce! Bruce! Bruce!
Five seconds.
They're both dead.
- Four.
- They're both dead.
Three.
Two.
One.
- Time's up!
- Keila, open it!
You have a few seconds to get them out
before the door's closing once more.
Is that Roi?
Is that Bruce? Are they alive?
Berlin, hurry up!
There's no more time left.
Come on, Roi.
I don't know if I can get back up.
You can do it.
The door's closing!
Berlin! Berlin!
We're never gonna make it out.
There's no gas.
It's empty. There's no more gas.
Roi is alive!
Let's go.
Berlin, what about Bruce?
Berlin?
Say something! Is he alive?
God.
Bruce is alive!
My leg…
Shit… It looks like I'm really fucked.
Don't think about it, okay?
You're not the only one.
Get up!
We've made it this far…
For fuck's sake, let's get in there.
- How much do you think there is?
- Way more than in Ali Baba's cave.
Roi! Are you okay?
I need another driving glove.
Made from diamonds.
We left the duke's palace
without knowing that our last loose end
hadn't caught up with us
and ruined everything.
None of us had any idea that when Samuel
found the tracer in the money bag,
instead of grabbing his gun,
he grabbed his pajamas,
turned out the lights, and went to bed.
Later at dawn, when we were
already 500 kilometers from Seville,
a furious and very irate duke woke up
a sleepy Samuel
because we had emptied his vault.
I've been robbed!
They've taken everything!
It's gone! They took it!
Do you understand?!
They took it all because of you!
You said nobody was gonna rob me!
And the next thing he did was
run out like a bat out of hell,
to go to his gallery to make sure
his collection of paintings was there.
My Rembrandt…
My Van Gogh…
My Cézanne…
My Modigliani…
They've taken away my whole life.
Your Grace… Look.
It's the original.
They've robbed it for me.
Just for me.
Good morning, Your Grace.
Before you is the Lady with an Ermine,
just as I had promised.
It's cost you a little more
than we had agreed upon,
as I had underestimated the real value
when we met.
It appears that… the painting is worth
more than 350 million euros
if you put it up for auction.
So… to compensate
for the miscalculation, I increased
all of my professional fees
to the 75 million euros
I found neatly packed in your vault.
Where are my paintings?
I don't give a fuck about the money
you stole from the vault.
I want my collection.
My collection!
Would you kindly turn around?
Please.
Do you see that light?
That's it. It means you're being recorded.
We have all the evidence to prove
you are the world's greatest art thief.
We also have recordings of the shipment
of trafficked diamonds from your yacht.
You'll find some
of the evidence on your bed.
If you decide to take revenge,
or if something happens to us,
all of this evidence will be made public.
People will no longer see you
as a noble gentleman,
and you'll spend
the rest of your life in prison.
I'm sure this is not what you want,
so I propose a deal.
Let's say I leave you
the Lady with an Ermine,
your boats, and your diamonds,
and you leave me the rest?
That way, we both win.
But if you want me to lose…
both of us will lose.
Your Grace!
The duchess.
She's gone.
"I never thought I could love someone else
with the same intensity and passion
with which I loved you."
"I'm sorry to do this to you
because you are
the most beautiful half of my life,
but there comes a day
when things come to an end."
"And that day is today. Genoveva."
Your Grace…
Just let me go and find a few good men.
I'll track those bastards down.
I'll track them until my last breath…
and I swear I will find them.
No.
Leave them be.
Get some rest, Santos.
I'm so exhausted.
I need to lie down.
I want to have her close by.
Bring the lady over here.
Stay with me, Samuel.
Come lie down.
And there you have it.
Here was the reason
that the bodyguard didn't give us away.
Love.
He saw this as a sort of miracle.
The possibility to eliminate
in one fell swoop
everything that separated him
from the duke.
His wife…
His millions…
His social class… His obsession with art…
It was a chance to stop being
a lackey, and to become, in his eyes,
the only man on earth
who had stayed loyal.
Samuel had always been by his side
and had let it all happen.
Maybe it's time for us
to start from scratch again, Samuel.
But you know what?
Starting from scratch is what I prefer.
Yes, of course… Álvaro.
That afternoon,
after those moments of intense danger,
we finally got to reunite,
let loose, and enjoy ourselves.
We had just pulled off two
of the most perfect heists ever imagined.
The first one was a masterclass of style
and panache.
The other almost killed us.
Having a close brush with death makes you
want to celebrate life even more.
At that moment, however,
we had no idea how quickly joy
can turn to unbearable pain…
….accident at sea.
48 hours after the captain
reported her missing,
the body of the sailor who fell overboard
from the luxury yacht has been found.
Coast guard rescue teams
recovered the body
around 55 nautical miles
off the coast of Sardinia.
Police have identified the body as that
of 23-year-old Natalia Reyes Guzmán.
Sources confirm she had
no experience in recreational boating
and has only just recently enrolled
with the crew.
Initial autopsy reports from the coroner
revealed high levels of alcohol
in her system
when she was recovered.
Hey, Roi.
It's Cameron.
I don't have
any cell phone service here, so
I guess you'll only get this message
once the yacht reaches the coast.
I've been caught.
I promise you, I'm not afraid.
And right now, I've just got one thing
on my mind, and it's driving me crazy.
It's kinda silly, I know that.
Because it's just a simple word…
But it's been so difficult for me to say.
I know now
that Berlin was right all along.
He always said I was spoiled
and self-centered.
That I was forever screwing up.
It's true, I always make things
more complicated and more difficult
when actually it's quite simple.
I should've said those two words to you.
I regret it now.
I'm sorry.
If I had found the courage to tell you
that back then,
I probably wouldn't be here right now.
But most of all…
if I had said I was sorry,
we'd still be a couple.
I'm so sorry, Roi.
I'm so sorry.
And someday,
I hope maybe you'll forgive me.
Of course, I do.
I forgive you, Cameron.
And I'll run to you
When the waters rise
I'll still call to you
If I lose my sight
And I'll fall for you
If you need a fight
And I'll run to you
When the waters rise
If the bombs ignite
I'll still call to you
If I do go blind
And I'll be all for you
If you lose the fight
Say what you wanna say.
- What do you want me to say?
- Say what's on your mind.
That I should never have let her leave
on that yacht.
Say I put her in danger
by asking her to fight this duel
with an eccentric and selfish man.
A man who is exactly like me.
And because of me, one of my friends
is dead and two others are injured,
and that has gone way too far for you.
And that's why we're different,
because I can cope with my conscience
and you cannot.
You're not the center of the world.
We're here because we chose to be here.
Bruce, Roi…
and even Cameron.
They all made their choice.
And me, I could be in… Marbella…
robbing safety deposit boxes.
Celebrating Christmas alone.
But these… past few days in Seville…
have given me more memories
than a lifetime at the university.
Some of these memories…
provided me with…
unbelievable pain.
But that's the price we pay
for being alive.
And there's something else
that I've come to realize.
I've got no regrets.
Thank you.
Listen.
If you really wanna do
the job in Marbella, we can both do it.
I'm not a fan of holidays.
I know.
And you have a taste
for last-minute heists.
Before we go to Marbella,
I'll need you to take a break.
Just a couple of weeks.
Because you've been invited to a wedding.
You made me feel
Like this would last forever…
Promise that you'll hold me close
Don't let me go…
WOMAN WITH A FAN
AMEDEO MODIGLIANI
You and I stargazing
Intertwining souls…
We were never strangers…
What if we spend Christmas in Sapporo?
A ski holiday in Japan?
It's a wonderful idea.
Yeah, but it's just that I've got
this job in Marbella…
A job in Marbella?
When I'm without you
I can't help but feel so lost…
It was the groom who waited
for the bride at the altar. You look…
Yes. But I might have
to ask you a little question first.
In fact, I'm a professor
of quantum mechanics at a university.
A university professor, really?
Basically, it's a kind of distraction,
a hobby of mine when I have free time
from my work as a criminal.
Let's go to Sapporo.
Don't break it, love me to my…
- When you were at the hotel…
- Yes?
…I had the impression
you were hiding something in your jacket.
- Mm.
- It looked like panties.
The ones in my jacket were old ones.
She gave them to me as a souvenir…
uh, from our time in Paris.
Mm.
Intertwining souls…
What's wrong? You're being weird.
I'm not a big fan of weddings
And I don't like wedding figurines
and definitely not wedding cakes.
Okay, I promise I won't go
near the wedding cake.
All along…
Do you get sad at weddings as well?
I get emotional.
You're his friend from Paris, right?
- Oui. Je suis l'ami.
- Oui.
- Enchantée.
- Moi aussi.
Intertwining souls…
So tell me,
where's the Lady with an Ermine?
A magician can't reveal his secrets.
But I can give you a little clue.
It's quite possible that
the Lady with an Ermine shall be sold
at an unusually low price
at a future auction.
What would that price be?
Nothing less
than four hundred million euros.
Take my heart, don't break it
Love me to my bones
All this time I wasted…