[A Splendid Match]
[Episode 29]
My...
Xuruo!
Third Uncle,
Uncle Yu.
I...
wanted to go back to my own quarters.
Your quarters aren't in this direction.
Go back to rest since you're drunk.
Yes.
Then I'll...
take my leave now.
Why did he drink so much?
Jiuheng,
I won't be escorting you
to the bridal chamber.
I'll go keep an eye on him.
Okay, go check on him.
May you be blessed with children soon!
Xuruo!
Third Master...
♪ A good moment is strewn with starlight ♪
♪ Flames burn away
the frost of bygone days ♪
♪ Reflections tremble,
hearts beat in unison ♪
♪ Candlelight weaves the web of fate ♪
♪ Petal shadows
trace the lines of your face ♪
♪ Fleeting light
sketches the shape of fate ♪
♪ Footsteps fall lightly,
yet feelings can't be concealed ♪
♪ In a backward glance,
a few hidden feelings slip through ♪
♪ Ask the passing time
whether it has forgotten ♪
♪ The moonlight of our first encounter ♪
♪ Year after year,
it etches your likeness ♪
♪ Count the faint shimmer
of the starry river ♪
♪ Yet none compares
to the gentle light in your eyes ♪
♪ At last, I see the galaxy
shimmering and swaying ♪
♪ Reflected in our eyes ♪
♪ I'll be with you forever ♪
♪ And enjoy
the beautiful scenery with you ♪
♪ For all the days of our lives,
our love will endure ♪
♪ Soft whispers turn into verse ♪
♪ Beneath the bright moonlight,
you and I stand together ♪
♪ Hand in hand, our love deepens
with each passing year ♪
♪ By your side,
I'll follow wherever your heart leads ♪
♪ Ask the passing time
whether it has forgotten ♪
♪ The moonlight of our first encounter ♪
♪ Year after year,
it etches your likeness ♪
♪ Count the faint shimmer
of the starry river ♪
♪ Yet none compares
to the gentle light in your eyes ♪
♪ At last, I see the galaxy
shimmering and swaying ♪
♪ Reflected in our eyes ♪
♪ I'll be with you forever ♪
♪ And enjoy
the beautiful scenery with you ♪
I've been
♪ For all the days of our lives,
our love will endure ♪
meaning to ask you—
why do you have
so many scars on your body?
Ever since I've known you,
you've
encountered danger several times.
Aren't you a civil official?
Why do you keep getting injured?
They say,
"When civil officials shun greed
and military officials do not fear death,
an age of prosperity may yet dawn."
But our dynasty is different.
Though it has stood for a century,
it's beginning to show signs
of instability and decline.
Civil officials
must not only refrain from greed
but also have no fear of death.
Only then might there still be hope
for the state.
As expected of a Grand Secretary.
You always talk about
the dynasty's grand legacy
and the welfare of the people.
I know I was wrong.
I really
didn't care enough about my own life.
But from today onward...
I'll take better care of myself.
Then remember this well:
since
I've married you,
you're only allowed to
stay alive and well.
Understood.
What's wrong?
There's something
I have to tell you.
Marquis Changxing...
passed away
in the middle of the night yesterday.
So,
the funeral procession we encountered
on South Gate Street earlier
was...
The court has bestowed 200 taels of gold.
His Majesty has
granted an additional
1,000 taels of silver
and permitted the funeral vigil
to be held at Xuanmiao Temple.
The Ye family should all be
at the temple right now.
Did the court mention anything
about Ye Xian inheriting the title?
What do you think
is more important—
life, or a noble title?
Naturally, life is more important.
His life
should have been preserved.
[Great Merit and High Esteem]
[A Legacy of Virtue and Grace]
[Spirit Tablet of Ye Guangsheng,
Late Marquis Changxing of Great Yan]
Miss Xue.
Why are you here?
To offer incense to the Marquis.
If you had come alone,
I might actually have believed you.
But now that you've brought
your husband along,
I can only assume
you come with bad intentions.
Where is Ye Xian?
Ye Xian.
Aren't you here to offer incense?
Go ahead.
I have a few words
to say to Young Lord Ye.
Why don't you...
wait outside?
Miss Xue.
Ye Xian, receive the decree.
Marquis Changxing, Ye Guangsheng,
[Imperial Edict]
fought for the country
with loyalty and valor
worthy of commendation.
Upon hearing the sorrowful news,
I am deeply grieved.
[Ye]
Jinzhao.
I don't blame you.
You had your own choice to make.
You chose Chen Jiuheng.
Ye Xian, foolish as he is,
can only accept his loss.
There's no right or wrong in such matters.
Even if you blamed me,
I wouldn't be angry.
Why?
Because you truly care about Ye Xian.
I mean it.
Thank you
for looking after Ye Xian all along.
You don't need to thank me.
I've just been blind.
The day I come to my senses,
I'll walk away without a second thought.
By the way,
what does your husband
want to say to Ye Xian?
I have no idea.
An owl visiting in the night—
never a good sign.
That reminds me—
there was a time Ye Xian
saw me together with Yanyun,
and he said the same thing.
According to the laws of our dynasty,
his son Ye Xian suffers from illness
and is unfit to inherit the title.
Therefore, the title of
Marquis Changxing is revoked.
Additionally, 200 taels of silver,
500 bolts of silk, and one chest of
calligraphy and paintings are bestowed.
Receive the decree, Ye Xian.
This subject
receives the edict with gratitude.
It was only to be expected
that you wouldn't inherit the title.
Why resort to
such childish theatrics?
His Majesty has another verbal decree
for you.
By His Majesty's verbal decree—
A new Xuanfeng Guard shall be established,
drawing 500 elite troops
carefully selected
from the Imperial Guards
to form its ranks.
Ye Xian is hereby appointed
Commander of the Xuanfeng Guards.
He shall command
the Emperor's personal guards
and hold authority over
supervision and interrogation.
So it is decreed.
This subject obeys the decree.
This subject shall not fail in his duty
and will share His Majesty's burdens.
His Majesty has truly gone to
great lengths
for your sake.
Be sure you prove worthy of it.
Thank you.
[Marquis Changxing's Mansion]
[Memorial]
You mean
His Majesty played the long game—
first agreeing with
the Senior Grand Secretary
to rescind the Ye family's title,
then using the pretext of
unrest within the palace
to force the Senior Grand Secretary into
establishing the Xuanfeng Guard?
Yes.
Ever since
the late Prince Chengqing's rebellion,
the Penal Court
has long been infiltrated by
various factions within the court
and is no longer trustworthy.
The entire court knows this.
And Ye Xian's
loyalty to His Majesty is unshakeable.
Even my mentor
cannot argue otherwise.
So His Majesty came up with this plan—
both to protect Ye Xian
and to secure
for himself a personal guard
to keep watch over all officials.
That's quite
the calculated move.
Yes.
His Majesty...
has grown up.
[Happiness]
Please have tea, Mother.
May you love each other dearly
and soon be blessed with children
to carry on the family line.
Yes.
Thank you, Mother.
Second Brother, Second Sister-in-law,
please have tea.
Okay, okay.
My third brother
has always been reserved
yet strong-willed.
Whether in state or family affairs,
he has never once complained.
In the days ahead,
I hope you will take good care of him.
Tend to his needs and care for him well
so that I, as his elder brother,
may feel at ease when away from home.
Why are you being so noisy?
Drink your tea.
Second Brother, I understand.
I'll take good care of him.
Good.
Here,
this is for you.
Thank you, Second Brother,
Second Sister-in-law.
Third Madam,
please have a seat.
Please have tea, Third Sister-in-law.
Thank you, Third Sister-in-law.
Congratulations, Third Sister-in-law.
Please drink this tea,
Third Sister-in-law.
Thank you, Third Sister-in-law.
Jinzhao,
from now on, we're one family.
Mother and Old Madam Ji
have long been bosom friends.
Now that our two families
have become in-laws as well,
we're truly closer than ever.
Indeed.
Now,
your second sister-in-law
manages the household.
If there's anything you need
or anything you don't understand,
just go to her.
Yes, Mother.
If any maid
or servant gives you trouble,
just tell me.
I'll sort them out for you.
I understand.
Thank you, Second Sister-in-law.
The younger ones
haven't paid their respects
to their aunt yet.
Go quickly.
These two
are my children with your second brother—
Xuansong and Xuanbai.
They came back especially
for the occasion.
Please have tea, Third Aunt.
This is Xuan'an,
Fourth Brother's only son.
He's only just begun his studies.
Please have tea, Auntie Third.
You should call her "Third Aunt."
Third Aunt.
Alright, you may leave now.
Thank you, Third Aunt.
This is Xuanqing.
We've met before.
Right.
When I was still living with
my grandmother in Tongzhou,
Mother and Yanyun both came.
Xuanqing was there too.
Right, right, right.
I remember now.
At your coming-of-age ceremony, right?
Fate truly works in mysterious ways.
Xuanqing.
My Lady!
Well...
Are you alright?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
Let me see.
You got burned.
I'm fine.
Fetch some Sanhuang Ointment.
It's fine.
The tea was only warm.
Prepare a fresh cup of tea.
No need.
Consider it already offered.
Qingpu,
bring the gift
prepared for Xuanqing.
Yes.
Thank you.
Alright.
I know
you men
have no patience
for all these formalities.
Go on and leave
so we ladies can have a good talk.
Yes, Mother.
Mother,
I hardly think you actually want to chat.
You're just eager to
set up the card table, aren't you?
You needn't rush.
This time,
I've brought a whole box of silver.
You may win to your heart's content.
And if all my money
ends up in your hands,
there's still Third Sister-in-law.
She's the real one with deep pockets.
You cheeky little thing.
I ought to pinch your lips shut!
Mother.
After you, Second Brother.
Second Brother, please.
Okay.
Thank you, Yanyun.
Thank you, Third Uncle.
Back then,
when Lady Jiang died,
you told Mother
you wished to observe mourning rites
and refused to remarry.
And you kept that observance
all these years.
I'd thought
you would never marry again.
Yes, Yanzhang.
Even I myself
didn't expect it either.
Yes, Yanyun.
How exactly
did you and Lady Gu
get together?
Surely it wasn't the Ji family
deliberately presenting her to you
to ensnare you?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Since your third brother has
married Lady Gu,
he naturally has his reasons.
Don't speak carelessly.
Where
did you hear such things?
I...
I heard it from people outside.
Which people outside?
I don't want to hear
this kind of talk a second time.
I know I was wrong.
As for Lady Gu and me...
how should I put it?
It should be—
our hearts entwined the moment we met,
but fate brought us together too late.
This is the first time I've ever seen you
so deeply devoted.
It seems that my third sister-in-law
is no ordinary woman.
But
rest assured.
Since she's the woman
you cherish so dearly,
no one in this entire household
will dare let her
suffer even the slightest grievance.
Since I've married her,
naturally,
I won't let her suffer any grievances.
Of course.
When I saw the grandeur
of your wedding procession yesterday,
oh my,
it would've been grand enough to welcome
a princess into the family.
By the way, Yanyun,
there is something
I wanted to ask you.
Please go ahead, Yanzhang.
I just remembered
the shop manager came earlier.
Maybe there's something wrong at the shop.
Yanzhang, Yanyun,
you guys talk first.
I'll go take a look.
Go ahead.
Then I will
head back first.
Are you alright?
What?
You don't look so well.
Is that so?
Perhaps I didn't rest well last night.
How could you rest well?
There they are discussing court affairs,
and it's understandable to
shut out someone like me
who only handles family business.
But you are a dignified Tanhua,
a future Grand Secretary.
And yet they shut you out too.
I really feel it's unfair to you.
You jest, Fourth Uncle.
I'm a junior.
When elders are discussing matters,
I naturally shouldn't get involved.
How could I possibly feel slighted?
Oh, right, Xuanqing.
You also attended Lady Gu's
coming-of-age ceremony.
So was it really the Ji family
offering her to Yanyun or not?
Of course not.
Really?
Really.
Now that's strange.
If it weren't for her,
how could your Third Uncle
have cared
so much for the Ji family?
Just the land reform case alone—
there was no way the Ji family
could've come out unscathed.
I don't know why Third Uncle
showed favor to the Ji family.
But during the days
of Lady Gu's coming-of-age ceremony,
Third Uncle was with me
the whole time.
He never once
met her alone,
much less anything like
the Ji family offering her up.
You truly are someone
your Third Uncle brought home himself.
Alright then.
If it wasn't, then it wasn't.
He's a Grand Secretary, after all.
Whatever he says goes.
I'm off.
Yunting.
Young Master.
I keep feeling
that something is off with Fourth Uncle.
Think of a way
to keep an eye on him secretly.
Okay.
Yanyun is something else.
It's only the second day
after his wedding,
and he's rushed out
first thing in the morning.
Mother,
Yanyun had official duties.
Someone from the palace
came early in the morning.
If it was official business,
why did he take Zhao along?
Listen to yourself, Mother.
Yanyun dotes on his wife.
That's a good thing.
Doting on his wife
is all well and good,
but not to this extent!
Especially with all those rumors around...
I mean...
Yanyun is willful.
You should've talked him out of it.
Why did you go along?
Because...
I wanted to go in the first place.
Mother, you might not know this.
When I came here yesterday,
I happened to encounter
the Marquis Changxing's household
transporting the coffin
to Xuanmiao Temple on South Gate Street.
By all rights, the deceased
take precedence,
and we should have made way—
especially given that
it was the Marquis's household.
But unexpectedly,
they
made way for us first.
So I've felt
deeply uneasy about it ever since.
And as it happened,
early this morning,
His Majesty ordered Yanyun
to offer incense to the Marquis.
So I thought
I should go along
and offer incense
for the Marquis myself as well.
You are just
too sincere-hearted for your own good.
Mother, Second Sister-in-law.
It was clearly His Majesty's decree.
Why did you take it all upon yourself?
It was His Majesty
who ordered Zhao to accompany you?
Well...
How could that be possible?
Mother,
that was an imperial decree.
It's not something we should question.
Alright, alright.
I won't ask anymore.
There's news from Shanxi.
How about...
you go and help me look into it?
There's news from Shanxi?
Then let's go quickly.
Mother.
Why does he also need
Zhao to help with the affairs in Shanxi?
I heard
Jinzhao has business there.
She even donated grain and money
when Pingyang was struck
by a severe drought.
Yes, I heard that too.
Didn't
His Majesty commend her
for it at the time?
With so many businesses,
a young, newlywed wife like her
is even busier than a grand secretary.
You're really good at making things up.
What did I make up?
You actually claimed
that was His Majesty's decree.
Does that count as
falsely invoking an imperial order?
You'll say anything, won't you?
Well, you said
it was His Majesty's decree.
Tell me,
did His Majesty order me
to offer incense
at Marquis Changxing's Mansion?
His Majesty's decree
indeed said so.
And all I said was,
"It was clearly His Majesty's order."
What was wrong with that?
How are you
so full of tricks?
You're no less so yourself.
I only said
that news had come from Shanxi,
yet you played right along.
Well, you'd already come to pick me up.
If I hadn't left with you,
I'd be stupid.
You walked away rather quickly just now.
You've suffered grievances because of me.
Those things
are nothing to me.
Mother
is not a bad person at heart.
It's just that our marriage
wasn't arranged by her,
so she's just displeased.
Most of it falls on me.
I'm sorry that you've been
caught up in it as well.
But fortunately,
Mother is
a bit of a snob.
Seeing that I've
brought honor to the whole family,
she won't do anything unreasonable.
Oh my,
you're actually calling Mother
snobbish behind her back?
Later,
I'll secretly tell her.
Really?
You're asking for trouble.
Put me down.
I'll talk. I'll tell you everything!
Ye Xian! Ye Xian!
I'll tell you everything I know!
Everything.
Just let me go.
Alright.
Wang Xuanfan!
Wang Xuanfan has ties...
has ties with the bandits in Shandong!
And...
In the disaster relief grain case,
that Secretary surnamed Sun
was killed by the men he sent.
Also,
in Daming Prefecture,
he's concealed over 1,000 men
and tens of thousands of acres
of fertile land.
Anything else?
Also...
The wealthy merchants in Shanxi...
On the surface,
he accepts their bribes.
But in secret,
he's been colluding and trading
with the northern tribes
through them!
What else?
That's it. That's all I know.
Ye Xian!
I'll kill you!
Let go of me!
Ye Xian!
Zhang Ling, the former Commander
of the Penal Court,
has admitted that his crimes were grave.
By His Majesty's secret decree,
he is hereby sentenced to execution.
Throw his body into the mass grave
and bury it.
Yes, sir!
Zhang Ling is dead?
Yes.
They say
he committed suicide out of guilt.
Impossible.
He valued his life too much to die.
Then...
could it be because the Ye family
was stripped of their title
that Ye Xian, in a fit of rage,
took his anger out on Zhang Ling?
Did you see the body?
Well...
The Xuanfeng Guards
are all personally selected
by His Majesty.
Our people
haven't had the chance
to be planted inside yet.
Master,
are you suspecting
that it was him...
Master!
The Wang family had someone
deliver the guest list for next month's
tea gathering.
As expected, there was
no sign of Gu Jin...
Jinzhao's name.
I've loaded Master's luggage
onto the cart.
Take good care of Master on the journey.
Rest assured, Changshun.
You needn't wait any longer.
Today is the Eldest Miss's
first return home after her wedding.
No one from the family
will come to see you off.
It's just me.
But they shouldn't just
send no one at all.
Master,
go.
The road to Pingyang is rough.
We mustn't be late for taking office.
"Had you known it would end this way,
would you still have done what you did?"
It's too late
to regret it now.
Go.
Take good care of Master on the road.
Will do!
Hyah!
[Gu]
What time is it already?
Why haven't they arrived yet?
Quick, send someone to check
where they are!
I've already sent someone.
Now that Zhao's become
a Grand Secretary's wife,
she's certainly putting on airs—
making the whole family
wait for her like this.
Isn't she afraid of
using up her good fortune?
Old Madam, Old Madam!
Well?
Where are they?
They're...
Spit it out!
Well...
O-Old Madam, Master,
Madam,
Eldest Miss and her husband
aren't coming here.
Then where did they go?
They said
they've gone to Tongzhou.
Tongzhou?
Well...
What about Rong?
Is he still at the Qifang Hutong Academy?
I asked.
Young Master Rong
left the academy yesterday
and went to Tongzhou first.
[Gu]
You...
Let's go back too.
-Yes, My Lady.
-Mother.
Gu Lan!
Did you know all along
that Gu Jinzhao
wasn't coming back today?
How would I know that?
Stop pretending.
Do you think
that with Gu Jinzhao marrying Chen Yanyun,
you'll get to rise in status
along with her?
Lian.
Stop dreaming.
She doesn't care about you at all.
She's long taken Rong
back to Tongzhou,
leaving you here alone.
Tongzhou is Zhao's maternal family.
It's only natural
that she wouldn't take me along.
So what if I'm alone?
Can't I live my life alone?
I have my own ways
of getting by.
-Go.
The nerve of you!
Oh, you.
If you don't want to go back, just don't.
Why did you intentionally not tell them?
If I had told Grandmother in advance,
with her temperament,
she would certainly have
invoked family ethics and filial duty
to pressure me.
And then,
for the sake of your reputation,
I'd have no choice but to give in.
So it was better not to tell her at all—
act first, inform her after,
and leave her no time to react.
So in the end,
it's my fault.
Yes.
Just because you're
a dignified Grand Secretary,
in everything you do,
you have to be a model for others.
Therefore, there are so many things
I can no longer do.
Oh?
And what is it you wish to do?
♪ Ask the passing time
whether it has forgotten ♪
♪ The moonlight of our first encounter ♪
♪ Year after year,
it etches your likeness ♪
♪ Count the faint shimmer
of the starry river ♪
♪ Yet none compares
to the gentle light in your eyes ♪
♪ At last, I see the galaxy
shimmering and swaying ♪
♪ Reflected in our eyes ♪
♪ I'll be with you forever ♪
♪ And enjoy
the beautiful scenery with you ♪
♪ For all the days of our lives,
our love will endure ♪
Oh, right.
At the banquet the other day,
Mu mentioned
that his eldest son
wishes to seek your third sister's hand
in marriage.
What a mood-killer.
The eldest son of the Mu family,
Mu Zhidi?
Before my mother passed away,
he'd already brought it up once.
But
that was three years ago.
I thought Young Master Mu
had already been betrothed.
I'm afraid
this match won't work out.
At that time,
Lan had already refused him.
Besides,
she found Young Master Mu
looked too simple-minded.
Corrupt official, get out!
Give us an explanation!
-Get out!
-Give us an explanation!
Corrupt official!
Explain yourself to us!
Corrupt official, get out
and explain!
Third Master,
there are seven or eight
young scholars ahead
blocking the road with banners.
They read:
"Unjust land reform—
all under heaven cries out."
They also mention imperial lands
and noble estates.
Get out now, corrupt official!
This feels rather suspicious.
I'll go take a look. Wait here.
Okay.
Be careful then.
Give us an explanation!
We deserve an explanation!
Corrupt official,
give us an explanation!
Seize them all
and question them one by one.
Squat down!
Take them further away.
-Don't startle the Madam.
-Get down! Down!
Yes.
My Lady.
These scholars
actually knew
we would pass by here.
Someone must have instructed them.
There is no shortage of people
who resent Yanyun.
But
those capable of stirring up scholars
to cause
this kind of trouble are few.
Third Master,
that fellow confessed.
It was a servant
from Wang Xuanfan's household
who instructed them
to remonstrate with you
and revealed our whereabouts
to them.
Wang Xuanfan...
I made him pay
tens of thousands more taels in taxes,
and it seems he's come to truly hate me.
Well then,
assign two men
to escort them back to the capital
and have them detained.
Treat them properly.
As for everything else,
we'll talk about it when we get back.
Yes, sir.
Third Master.
What happened?
Our men were ambushed.
Jinzhao...
[A Splendid Match]