I've decided to reopen the Astronomy Club.
You want to quit the club?
Ongsa.
We joined this club together.
You can't leave me now.
What's up, Ongsa?
Ongsa, since when are you
friends with Ton?
-Ton is...
-I'm Ongsa's ex-boyfriend.
-What?
Ton is Ongsa's ex-boyfriend?
Ongsa, so you and Ton used to date?
Well, I wouldn't exactly call it dating...
Dating Ongsa
was such an incredibly memorable
time for me.
It's a shame we only dated for three days.
Three days!
Too short, isn't it?
-It's too long.
What?
Ongsa, ever since we've known Ton,
he's never dated anyone
for more than a day.
Really?
That means you're a special one
for me, Ongsa.
From the moment I met you,
I knew right away
that you, Ongsa, were the one.
Songkran festival last year,
Alpha and I planned to play
water-spraying games together.
It was the first time I met Ongsa.
Then, a random group of bad guys turned up
and violently applied powder
to Ongsa's cheeks.
Ongsa was terrified.
Hey, stop!
That's too much. Enough already.
Hello, Mr. Handsome. Can you please help?
Then my instinct told me...
Hey!
Hey! Stop it now.
Help.
-Ouch.
-Who is he?
Hey!
Hey.
Go! Get lost!
When I saw those innocent eyes of yours,
-I fell in love with you instantly.
-You should wash your face.
You've got a powder stain.
I wondered...
-Thanks, Ongsa.
-...if that was the magic moment of love.
After that, we went out.
We dated for three days
on public holidays.
Ongsa, would you like to be my girlfriend?
Yes, I would. I guess.
Really?
Ton, you can let go now.
I can't.
Please, let go.
I reluctantly let go of her hands
so she could go back to Phuket.
It's hard to forget
your first love, isn't it?
Ton.
Ongsa,
though we broke up,
this brother of yours
still loves and cares for you.
You're the coolest love I've ever had.
You know that?
Ton!
Wow! That's romantic.
Sun.
Oh, hey! Guys.
Can you please keep this story a secret?
Because I know I'm famous.
The security guard has been seeing
this green light for two days.
When he went up to check what it was,
it was gone.
What do you think it is?
I don't know.
It's hard to pinpoint what it is.
It could have been generated by anything.
Maybe it's the reflected light
of an object
or just
an ordinary light bulb.
I don't think it's from a light bulb.
If so,
it should stay in the same spot
whether it's on or off.
If we want to find out what it is,
we should check it out ourselves tonight.
Are you nuts?
We just need one of the teachers
to sign a permission slip.
We're the Student Committee.
It shouldn't be that hard, right?
And what reason would you give?
To figure out the source
of a mysterious light?
I doubt you'd be permitted to.
You might even get scolded.
Mawin is right.
Don't risk it.
Just forget it.
It doesn't matter what the light is.
-True.
-Fine.
Alpha.
Aylin, why didn't you knock
before coming in?
Alien wants to borrow a charger
for this thing.
You're borrowing my phone charger?
I don't have it, Aylin.
Why don't you go borrow Ongsa's?
What. A. Waste.
Hey, Aylin!
Be careful with those.
You're wrinkling them.
Maybe this is
a friend.
Don't mind her.
She's also like this at home.
-It's normal.
-Normal?
Students.
We're voting for the class president,
the class vice president,
and the treasurer.
You should all be fairly well-acquainted
with each other by now.
Let's start with the class president.
Nominating Sun.
Sun.
Sun, as well.
-Me too.
-Yes.
-Sun.
Let's start voting then.
Raise your hand if you want Sun
as our class president.
That's unanimous.
Sun, can you be the class president?
I can.
Can I be the class vice president
so that I can help her?
Sure. What do you all think?
-Yes.
So, we have the treasurer position left.
Any volunteers?
I'd like to volunteer.
Ongsa. No.
That's great.
Thank you for your sacrifice.
Please cooperate with them, everyone.
Oh, Ongsa.
The school needs a 100 baht sports day fee
from each one of you.
Please collect it
and hand it to me tomorrow.
Guys, what should I do?
I still need to collect money from
over half of the students in our class.
I don't know how to ask them.
I've never demanded money from anyone.
Even when a vendor gives me
the wrong change,
I'm not bold enough to complain.
What should I do?
Who told you to volunteer?
You raised your hand with confidence,
but now you're depressed.
This duty doesn't suit you a bit.
If I were you,
I'd ask them civilly and politely.
For example.
Greetings, my friend. Kindly pay up.
If they paid willingly,
I would give them blessings.
I'd wish them wealth.
Thank you, my friend.
I wish you wealth and prosperity.
Come on! If you do that,
you will never get the money.
You must play hardball.
Roll up your sleeves.
Stare them down.
If you don't have cash, pay by scanning.
If you don't have money,
pay in installments.
If you don't pay installments,
you're dead, exploiter!
That's it. I guarantee
they will pay quickly.
Are you sure?
Hey!
The Nestlings admin has an update.
"Nestlings"?
Ton's fandom name.
What does it say?
Holy crap!
What's going on?
You should see this.
TON'S 3-DAY EX
-SHE MUST BE SO COCKY
-THAT'S ALPHA'S YOUNGER SISTER
I wondered if that was
the magic moment of love.
There's a video too.
Hey. Is that her?
-Ongsa. Here's the sports day fee.
-Ongsa. Here's the fee.
SPORTS DAY MONEY
Thank you.
How did you manage to date Ton
for three days?
I've never seen anyone
last longer than a day.
We just met by chance.
Because you're Alpha's
younger sister, right?
But you and Alpha are so different.
You think so?
I need to collect more money.
I'll talk to you later.
Blossom, will you please pay
the sports day fee?
If you don't have it today,
you can pay tomorrow.
But it can't be later than tomorrow.
Even if I had it, I wouldn't freaking pay.
You can't do that.
Teacher Nida told us to pay.
Why are you asking me to pay when
you're the one with the profit?
What profit?
You dated Ton.
Roll up your sleeves. Stare them down.
If you don't have cash, pay by scanning.
If you don't have money,
pay in installments.
If you don't pay installments,
you're dead.
You...
I said I won't pay!
You must! It's unfair to others
if you don't pay.
It was unfair too that you dated Ton.
What does that have to do
with the sports day fee?
Right!
It doesn't have anything to do with that.
Blossom, you should pay.
I wish you...
You want me to pay?
Fine.
How about a one-on-one basketball game?
If you win, I'll pay.
Got the guts?
How can she win?
-You're on the school team.
-Exactly.
That is
wrong, Blossom.
Okay. Fine!
It's not fine!
I will compete with you tomorrow.
I guess.
That's it.
Ongsa.
Hello, everyone.
This is Tinh. I'm now a member
of the Student Committee Club.
Today is a good day
to take you on a tour
of our S-Tar Student Committee room.
There's an activity board.
Oh, look! Look at them.
It's Alpha, our student president.
She looks beautiful
both in photos and in person.
All right.
And this is an activity schedule.
Wow.
It's jam-packed.
But let's move on
to the next interesting thing.
This is our trophy shelf.
Look.
We've received numerous honors
across multiple fields,
including education,
academics, sports,
and music.
Wow!
All right then.
Moving on to the next one.
This is our school's long table
for meetings.
Whoa. How is it?
Hey.
Will you stop following me?
I'm not.
The table is dusty so I am cleaning it.
Then, if you're done cleaning,
please step out of my frame.
Okay.
Thank you.
All right. Let's carry on
with our tour, guys.
Look at these trophies.
We're not done yet. Let's keep exploring.
Mawin.
What are you doing?
Why were you being weird with him?
I wanted to get to know Tinh
but I didn't know what to do.
Mawin. I know you like him.
Just muster up the courage to talk to him.
Be confident.
Remember. It's best to be yourself.
Trust me.
When I'm being myself,
you call me a freak.
Who wants to hunt
the filth-eating spirit with me?
-Me.
-I do. I do.
What filth-eating spirit?
Well, that mysterious green light that
was captured by the security guard.
Stop it, Ton.
You're being nonsensical.
And you're persuading them
to be nonsensical too.
Everybody, listen. You are the members
of the Student Committee.
You abide by the rules.
You must be role models
for other students.
Mawin, what's the punishment for those
who sneak into the school at night?
Those who enter school after 6:00 p.m.
will immediately be placed on probation
and have to complete social work
for the entire semester.
So stop being obsessed
with the green light.
If I find out any of you have broken
the rules, you're doomed.
Why do you have to be so fierce, Miss Al?
You are frightening my juniors here.
Stop talking, ass.
Back to your club. Go.
Come on, Miss Al.
Miss Al, please listen to me.
-I'm not listening.
-Look around you.
-Just leave, Ton.
-Everyone wants to join in.
-Miss Al. Miss Al...
-Go.
Go back to your club.
Ton. Ton!
Hi. What's up, handsome?
Are you still up for
the filth-eating spirit hunt?
How can I not be?
Otherwise,
my reputation would be ruined as leader
of The Mysterious Stories Club.
Can I please join you then?
I'm so drawn to the word "light."
I also have a YouTube channel
called TinhTinh.
Ah, a channel called TinhTinh.
Let's do it.
-Your friend Charoen is going too?
-Yeah.
The more the merrier.
But you cannot let Alpha know
that this was my idea
or I'll get completely chewed out.
-Okay?
-Sure.
Let me see your channel.
Hey, Ton. Ton!
Can I come as well? Can I join in?
What's going on now?
You were against me going just now.
I know.
And you are terrified of ghosts, Mawin.
Yeah, you're right. But I...
I want to learn its anatomy.
Anatomy?
Then, meet me here at 7:00 p.m.
If we don't see the light
or the filth-eating spirit,
we don't go home.
Right.
Filth-eating spirit.
What do you think this light is,
human teacher?
This is like...
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
It's a UFO light.
I must see with my own eyes.
Please.
DOCUMENT OF AUTHORIZATION
FOR OVERNIGHT STAY AT S-TAR SCHOOL
I can't sign this for you, Aylin.
You are aware that it is against
the school's rules.
If I do, the principal
will certainly fire me.
You are a mean human teacher.
This is the only way that
Alien will see her friend.
What are you doing?
You like to ask weird questions, human.
You can clearly see what.
Hey. I won't allow you to crash
in the club room.
You must go home.
Alien doesn't care
what a human being orders.
But if the teacher on duty finds you,
you won't be the only one in trouble.
Teacher Bambam and I
will be in trouble too.
Please.
Don't cause trouble.
You told me what I believe isn't nonsense.
Why are you going back
on your word, human?
Come on. It's different.
If the teacher on duty catches you,
you'll be on the probation list.
But this is important.
If this is the light from a UFO,
it's the only chance to meet my friends.
A person with lots of friends like you
wouldn't get it, human senior.
If you want to tell the teachers,
go ahead.
You don't care that you'll be punished?
No.
Then I'm coming with you.
Why?
I want to see more aliens.
See if they are stubborn
like the one right here.
Did I spook you?
Come here.
How are you doing?
Difficult, isn't it?
You don't know how
to play basketball, do you?
It's like I've already lost
even before the game started.
I shouldn't have accepted her challenge.
I think I might have to pay for her.
You can't do that.
You will just be spoiling your classmate.
What if Blossom doesn't want
to pay again next time?
What if she comes up with another excuse?
Will you keep paying for her?
No way.
Ongsa,
listen to me.
I believe you can do it.
How can I do it?
I don't even know how to shoot this thing.
I'll show you the ropes.
Sun...
Why are you making that face?
You don't trust me?
It's not that. I...
I was a champion in primary school.
That's awesome, Sun.
Here. Let me teach you.
Hold the ball like this.
Palm open.
Fingers apart. Okay.
Right. Yes. A bit more.
Then use your left hand
to help hold the ball.
Now, try again.
Open your right hand. Okay.
Like this.
Hold it up. Arm upright.
Right.
Use your left hand to support the ball.
When you shoot, bend your knees a little.
Down.
Down. And then throw it with force.
That's okay. You almost got it.
Arm upright.
This time throw harder.
As hard as you can.
You can do it.
One, two, three.
I never knew human hearts
could be this fast.
Mine is beating so hard
I'm afraid Sun might find out
what I think of her.
Get up slowly, Ongsa.
-Are you okay?
-I'm so sorry, Sun I'm so sorry.
Are you hurt, Sun?
Hey, I'm fine.
Are you all right, Ongsa?
I'm okay.
Why is your face red?
Are you sick?
Do you have a fever?
I...
I'm hot.
I've been practicing
and the sun is burning bright.
I'm hot.
Ongsa,
you're cute.
Where is the ball?
Over there.
You asked for trouble, Ongsa.
Why did you volunteer?
I thought it was one way
to be close to Sun.
If I had known I'd be in this position,
I wouldn't have dared.
Where are you going, Latte?
Earth, is everything all right?
Why do you sound sad on your Stories?
You can talk to me.
It's nothing.
I just feel like
I am not good at anything.
I fail at whatever I do.
I don't know what you just experienced,
but I believe that you can do it.
Thank you, Sun.
You don't have to thank me.
I will always send you support.
Ongsa. Aylin didn't come home with you?
No. I came home by myself. Why?
Aylin isn't in her room.
She isn't picking up my calls.
I don't know where she is.
Have you talked to her at all?
She isn't an irresponsible kid, usually.
Where did she go?
Is Alien looking for her friend?
Get up. Let's go find Aylin.
Dammit. Latte, do you want to go too?
There are no motorbike taxis at all.
That's okay. I'm going to book a cab.
Sun?
Ongsa, Alpha.
What are you two doing here?
We are going to school.
Right now?
Aylin didn't come home.
So, we think she might be at school.
I think she is hunting down
the green light
captured by the security guard.
She must think it's her alien friend.
Can I give you guys a ride then?
No, that's fine. Alpha is calling a cab.
Thank you, Sun. We do need your help.
Ongsa, you hop on first.
I'll take the back.
Why should I get on first?
If you sit at the back,
you might fall off the bike.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Scoot over a little.
There's not enough room.
Hold on tight.
Let's go.
Let's move. Be careful when you walk.
Hi, guys.
I'm still at S-Tar.
My friends and I are hunting down
the filth-eating spirit.
Let's see if it's real.
Let's go.
Shit! The teacher. Hide.
Almost busted.
If we get busted, we will all be expelled.
Then don't get busted.
Walk closer.
You might get lost.
I've attended here since I was a kid.
I can get around with my eyes closed.
You can trip if you close your eyes.
Poor humans.
What are you doing?
You might get lost. Come on.
I can walk myself.
Don't be stubborn. Come on.
Let's go.
Gosh. Move already.
This kind of feeling...
What is it?
Thank you, Sun.
The gates are locked.
Alpha, don't you have a spare key?
I am the student president,
not the school owner.
How would I have the key?
We have no choice.
I think
we should climb over.
Sun, are you serious?
Damn.
She's so cool.
If you're not gonna move,
then I'll go first.
Hey.
Ongsa, come on.
Ongsa,
if you don't climb over now,
I'll leave you here.
Alpha, wait a second.
-I'm coming.
-Up.
A bit more. You can do it, Ongsa.
Be careful, Ongsa!
Ongsa.
Are you hurt?
Ongsa? Are you all right?
You okay?
What are you all doing here?
Good evening, sir.
Hey, it's you.
-Aren't you the student president?
-I am.
What are you doing in school
this late at night?
I forgot something in the committee room
and I really need to use it.
Next time, you can just let me know.
Don't climb the school gate like that.
You might get injured if you fall.
Sure. I'll remember that.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Let's go. Come on.
Ongsa, move.
-Alien!
My friend.
Where is it, Ton? The filth-eating spirit.
Not so loud, Tinh. We'll be caught.
Hey! It's there.
Hey.
Let's go.
Oh, gosh!
-Ton!
-Luna!
-The filth-eating spirit is gone.
-The alien is gone.
Filth-eating spirit?
Seriously, Ton? How on earth
did you come up with that?
Alien isn't much better.
-Filth-eating spirits aren't real.
-You are talking as if aliens are.
They're more likely to be
than filth-eating spirits.
Damn it, you guys.
Why didn't you listen to me?
I told you to ignore this stupid light.
Especially you guys, Mawin, Ton,
and Luna.
You guys are Student Committee members,
but you are the ones breaking the rules.
You are old enough to know better.
Instead of stopping the young ones,
you are leading them here.
And this stupid light is nonsense.
It's not real.
Hey! That's...
The spirit!
My friend.
-Ton.
So, the mysterious light is you guys.
What are you three doing here?
We are here to make light sticks
for Ton's fan club.
Tomorrow is Ton's birthday.
We hoped to finish them and surprise him
by the end of the first period.
Why didn't you guys do it at home?
Why in school in the middle of the night?
People thought the light was an alien
or a fifth-eating spirit.
Thank you so much
for sacrificing your precious time for me.
Though I didn't find
a filth-eating spirit,
I found your love.
That's enough to make me feel whole.
Students, what are you all doing in here?
TON'S FC
Guys, run!
Hurry!
Go on. Run. Keep running.
Students, stop it.
Students!
Guys, move, move! The teacher is coming.
-Move it!
-Students!
-Go! Run!
-Move!
-Quickly! Run!
-Get up.
Hurry up!
Students.
-Ouch!
-Hey, Ongsa.
Let's hide in there. Get up slowly.
Students.
Show yourselves.
I think he's gone.
I thought we would get caught.
We should go.
Can you walk, Ongsa?
Get up slowly.
Aylin, let's go.
I will take you home.
Hey, why are you crying?
Everything's gone wrong.
I thought I would get to see my friend.
Turn this way look at me. Aylin...
Aylin.
Why are you poking me?
Poke out your finger.
Let's be friends.
I don't wanna be your friend,
human senior.
Who said I was human?
I am a moon.
Can an alien be friends with a moon?
Well?
So, we're friends from now on, Aylin.
Come on.
Let's go home. I'll take you home.
Give me your hand.
Hey.
Come on, let's go.
Quickly, or the teacher will catch us.
Put on your school bag.
Come here. You!
You!
And you!
You're on the Student Committee, but you
are the ones who breached the rules.
What are the rules for
if you don't keep them?
You're lucky no one caught you
or all of us would be screwed.
But Miss Al,
we didn't get caught, did we?
Stop back talking!
Even though you didn't get caught,
I, as the student president,
will punish you guys myself.
Every one of you
must clean the Student Committee room
for the whole semester.
Don't let me see PM 2,5 dust in here.
-But...
-No buts.
Unless you want toilet-cleaning duty too.
Do you want that?
Hello. Good morning, seniors...
I guess you guys are busy.
I'll leave you to it then. Goodbye.
You too, Tinh.
Come here.
Hey, Alpha. Don't punish him.
We seniors should take responsibility.
Fine.
There will be no punishment for you
because you're younger.
Really?
But
you must be Mawin's assistant
for the whole semester.
Though I got through last night
without punishment,
there's still a big deal
waiting for me today.
I almost forgot that I have
a basketball game with Blossom.
How's your foot?
Does it feel any better?
It's been better.
Ongsa.
Are you really competing with Blossom?
I must collect all the fees.
How about I try to talk to her?
It's okay.
I'll handle it.
But your foot hurts.
You can't play.
Why am I always the one
who gets help from Sun?
Thank you, Sun,
but this time,
I want to try it myself without any help.
Then do your best.
I'll be cheering for you.
I hope Sun develops
a more positive opinion of you, Ongsa.
Ongsa, do your best.
Fight hard, girl. Don't back down.
-Ongsa!
-Go Ongsa!
-You can do it!
-Ongsa!
-Ongsa, keep fighting.
Ongsa, hang in there.
-Ongsa, go!
-Go, girl!
-Ongsa, keep going.
Ongsa, keep fighting.
I'm giving you blessings.
-Ouch!
-Ongsa, go, go.
One point for Blue.
Go, Blossom!
Blossom, you did great.
It's okay, Ongsa. Try again.
You can do it. Start over.
Go, Ongsa.
-Ongsa, keep fighting.
-Go Ongsa.
Keep fighting, Ongsa.
Keep fighting.
Hey!
-How is she this good?
-Two points for Blue.
Ongsa, are you hurt?
Ongsa, keep going. You can do it.
Ongsa, fight her.
-Ongsa, keep fighting.
-Ongsa!
You can do it.
Ongsa, keep fighting.
-Keep trying, Ongsa. You can do it.
-You can win, Ongsa.
Hey!
-Hey!
-Blossom, are you okay?
Ongsa, the ball.
-Get the ball.
-The ball!
Ongsa, hurry up. Shoot.
-Ongsa, you can do it.
-You can do it!
-Give her blessings!
-Go Ongsa!
-Ongsa, go for it.
-You can do it.
Fight!
-Keep fighting.
-Don't back down, Ongsa!
Keep going, Ongsa.
Game over.
Blue wins 8-0.
In the end,
you're still a loser as always, Ongsa.
Here. The fee.
But I lost.
How could an amateur
beat a member of the school team?
Your leg is also injured.
I was impressed you could steal
the ball from me at all.
For such a timid person,
you're one hell of a fighter.
Here.
Thank you.
At least you did it, Ongsa.
You collected all the money.
Can you hear me?
I guess you can.
I'm done with the basketball game.
I'm waiting for you
in front of Building 3 as always.
Do you hear me?
You do.
See you.
Ongsa.
See? I told you you could do it.
But I lost.
I could only collect all the money
because Blossom was nice to me.
But it's because you didn't give up.
What you did today was so cool.
Cool?
Did she just say I was cool?
Why are you making that face?
Don't you believe me?
No one has ever said I was cool before.
Really?
Then listen to me carefully.
What you did today was so damn cool.
So cool
that if you were a guy,
you'd attract all the girls in our school.
Right. I forgot.
You're not a guy, Ongsa.
You're exaggerating.
It's true. I'm not exaggerating.
Ongsa, you're the coolest.
I'm heading home now.
See you tomorrow.
Get home safe.
Are you all right, human?
It's nothing.
Is it about Sun?
Hey!
How did you know that?
I took a wild guess.
Aylin.
Please don't tell anyone about this.
-About human Ongsa liking human Sun?
-Hey!
What? Ongsa, you like Sun?
Hey!
The Astronomy Club will be holding
astrological fortune readings.
You two must be the fortunetellers
on Club Fair Day.
Aylin and I?
For our Astronomy Club, keep fighting.
Borrowing power from the stars
to foretell someone's fortune
requires you to sell the power
of your own soul.
Ongsa, do you want my help with Sun?
Would you like your fortune told?
-I was born on a Friday.
-Ongsa was born on a Tuesday.
That's why I felt like
we hit it off especially well.
Our fortunes are compatible.
Let's say I like someone.
How likely is it that the person
will reciprocate my feelings?
Very likely.
That person must like you very much.