MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
Kim Seon.
Da-rae's asleep.
Oh, right.
She's unable to hear.
I'm here to take what is mine.
Where is it?
I can take it today, right?
GI SU-JONG
SEON
Hey, Seon. What's up?
What do you want?
GI SU-JONG
Hand it over.
- Hand over your phone.
- Why...
No.
SEON
Goodness, Gi Su-jong.
What's going on?
Hello, Mr. Gi.
- Hello?
- What do you want?
Where's Seon?
Hello?
SEON
POWER OFF
What?
Are you looking for something
to stab me with?
Like this?
It's in the main bedroom.
The main bedroom.
Over there?
You just need your thing, right?
Yes.
I'm really busy today.
I have an appointment.
Give it to me fast.
The phone is turned off.
Darn it.
Are you all right?
Is something wrong at home?
I think I need to get home.
I understand.
I'll take over from here.
Okay, I'll pull over.
- Hurry home.
- I will.
Before I give it to you.
I have a question.
What's that?
Kim Gyun.
You killed him, didn't you?
Me?
Why would I kill him?
I didn't kill him.
A truck ran him over.
That's it.
Lady.
Everything has a cause and effect.
Think carefully.
If that detective
hadn't tried to take my files
would there have been an accident?
If you hadn't had an affair
would I be able to blackmail you?
I'm just a small cog
in the wheel of cause and effect.
Are you crying?
Why would you cry?
Don't cry.
That is a convenient way to think.
You wouldn't feel guilty
when you hurt others.
What if
I don't want to give it to you?
Cause and effect, I said.
Think carefully.
What effect would this have?
- Da-rae!
- Oh, no.
We're busy, so just bring it quickly.
Go get it.
Bring it to me.
(Nice to meet you.)
Let Da-rae go first.
You make things unnecessarily hard.
I have an appointment.
I've got to run.
Hello, Mr. Gi.
Your wife won't give me what's mine.
What is it?
Let me see.
What are you doing?
Are we done now?
Yes, you did great.
You're way more efficient
than your wife.
I would've missed my appointment
if he had come any later.
Learn from your husband, lady.
Let's go.
Oh, right.
Guess what, Kim Seon?
When your brother died
he was at the scene.
He could've saved him
but he just walked off.
You're so quick to assess situations.
You look great dressed like a doctor.
We're off.
Are you all right?
Is that true?
Were you really there when Gyun died?
No.
That's not true.
It wasn't like that.
I'll explain everything.
Why didn't you tell me the truth?
I said it wasn't like that.
I know what you're saying
but we have no time to argue.
Let's be honest about one thing.
That's all in the past now.
We can't dwell in the past forever.
Gyun wouldn't want you like this.
You think it's all in the past?
This is hard for me as well, Seon.
Let's just forget about it.
How could you possibly say that?
Is that all you can say right now?
I wanted to better our lives.
Whatever the situation or problem
for our family and future
I've sorted everything out so far.
Yes, sure.
That's why you destroyed
the evidence Gyun left behind.
What a great solution that was.
I did that for our family.
For you and Da-rae.
I'm sick of hearing that.
Stop using us as an excuse!
Let's sit down and talk.
Can you give up on the property?
For our family
can you give up everything
and choose us?
See?
You've changed.
The look in your eyes has changed.
You'll choose the property, not us.
The Gi Su-jong I knew is gone.
You scare me now.
Gi Su-jong.
Let's live in the present, please.
I can't do this anymore.
Let's get a divorce.
What?
I can't stay here any longer.
I told you to stop snooping around.
You're making a mistake, Sergeant.
What is this mess?
I don't want to threaten
one of my own.
You're just...
You're beyond help.
Drop your gun, Sergeant.
What do you think you're doing?
You're under arrest for bribery
and illegal solicitation.
Drop the gun.
- Koh Ju-ran, you...
- You're the one beyond help.
You went way over the line this time.
Koh Ju-ran, you bastard!
Sergeant!
That's enough, Sergeant.
You...
I'm sorry about this.
We caught the insider, thanks to you.
You can hand over the evidence.
Gyun's flash drive.
I don't have it anymore.
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
FINAL EPISODE
A bit more to the right.
Yes, right there.
QUICK SALE
REDEVELOPMENT CONFIRMED
WELCOME TO YANGCHEON
Is Yi-gyeong doing okay?
She's asleep.
Let's talk inside.
Sure.
I did as you asked.
Pyeongbukgwan's grounds
will be included in Nouveau City
and in return,
your share will be guaranteed.
Any future profits from the business
will be transferred to Yi-gyeong.
Since the police are after her
she can't be out in the open.
I will manage Pyeongbukgwan.
Are you going to continue doing this?
Did I forget something?
That's not what I mean.
You're in danger.
Thank you for your concern.
Please let me know
where I may be lacking.
Don't worry, Mr. Kim.
He said he'd take care of it.
Are you all right, Yi-gyeong?
You have everything now, right?
You got rid of everyone in your way.
He's an amazing guy, Mr. Kim.
I had no idea at first.
I learned a lot over time.
He's even harder to read
than Hwal-sung.
We should watch out, too.
Su-jong.
What kind of person are you?
I wouldn't know how to answer that.
Da-rae's doing well.
I'll tell you this much,
just in case.
She doesn't blame you one bit.
She feels bad about everything
and misses you.
Su-jong.
Don't use her as an excuse.
Hwal-sung will be put to rest
next to your mother
as soon as the case is closed.
I'll take care of everything
and make sure it's done.
Don't come back here again.
You're going to be even busier.
I'll go to my study now.
And you.
I don't know
if my words will reach you
but I'll say this.
If I have one regret in my life...
it's that I failed
to protect my family.
All that remains is your family.
Thank you for the advice.
I'll keep it in mind.
QUICK SALE
REDEVELOPMENT CONFIRMED
What the heck?
- Can you pull over?
- Sure.
QUICK SALE
REDEVELOPMENT CONFIRMED
Why bother to take it down?
I called the realtor already.
What are you thinking?
I'm glad we met.
I was going to call you.
What's this?
DIVORCE SETTLEMENT
It's a divorce settlement.
Sell the property
and give me my share.
CAUSE OF DIVORCE
ASSET SPLIT
Hang on.
"Fault of divorce"?
"Asset split"?
What did I do to cause a divorce?
Do I need to tell you?
You kidnapped people,
caused their deaths
and burned down our property.
Didn't you have an affair?
I could say you caused our divorce.
Affair?
Yes, I cheated on you.
Do you want to air our dirty laundry
to see who did worse?
Seon.
Let's not do this.
Do you really want to divorce me?
Okay, let's say we do get divorced.
It can't be right now.
How many times must I tell you?
Bear with me,
and we'll be set for life.
We'll make more than enough.
Seon.
Seriously.
When it all blows over,
it'll just become a memory.
It means nothing.
Su-jong.
Do you really not know why I want to
sell the building and leave you?
That thing you're talking about.
The business you're trying to do
with Real Capital.
I want to ruin it.
Su-jong.
You've lost your touch.
I'm so very worried about you.
You could get into real trouble.
What do you mean?
Is that a threat?
No, it's not.
You know the people at Real Capital.
Watch who you're up against.
How could you say that
after all we've been through?
Absolutely not.
Let's get through this first
then talk about the divorce.
Do as I say.
Don't sign the settlement
if you don't want to.
I'll take you to court.
Darn it.
That was quick.
You secured all the new properties.
Now we must discuss what's important.
What's more important than this?
Jeon Yi-gyeong.
If she were to show up
and ruin the deal
by exercising her rights
it'll be a hassle,
so I'll take care of it.
We have leverage on her,
so she won't do that.
If Yi-gyeong were to die now
we would lose the Pyeongbukgwan lot.
Not to mention
there'll be no one
to inherit Pyeongbukgwan.
The court will have to get involved.
Do you want that?
That's an even bigger hassle.
It's way easier to manage things
as they are now.
You've really stepped up your game.
Goodness.
Excuse me.
Hello, Gi Su-jong speaking.
Oh, that property's not for sale.
I'm not selling.
Bye.
Se-yoon Building?
I saw the banner on the side.
Is it your wife?
It's a tiny issue.
Some emotional baggage.
You don't have to worry.
How can I not worry?
In the event of divorce,
your wife gets part of your share.
The problem was Kim Seon,
not Jeon Yi-gyeong.
So what?
We shouldn't let her live, should we?
We have a lot to do.
What are you talking about?
What do you think?
SEON
Why won't she pick up?
What's wrong?
Why won't it work?
Seon.
Kim Seon.
Da-rae.
I need to talk to you right now.
(Mom told me not to talk to you.)
Will you hear me out?
I'm doing this for you and Mom.
To protect you, okay?
Where's Mom?
(I don't know.)
(I should go, I still have class.)
Real Capital is after Seon.
Are you sure about that?
You destroyed Gyun's flash drive.
Why would they bother?
They're about to finalize the project
and see Seon as the last obstacle.
So what?
You know how they work.
I'm sure they'll kill her.
I get what you're saying.
What do you want us to do
when nothing has happened yet?
Set a trap.
So they don't cross the line.
Didn't you set a trap
that got Oh Dong-ki killed?
No.
That...
I'll tell you everything
after we stop them.
I need your help, Detective.
We have to avenge Gyun.
Are you sure about this?
We don't have clearance.
Who's going to clear it
if our sergeant's in a cell?
Yes, but still...
It'll all be over once we get them.
I will get them this time.
Okay.
Hey, Seon.
Why couldn't I reach you?
Jeez.
Hello.
We took your wife and Da-rae
to the place you mentioned.
Hello.
Please take care of her.
Shall we?
Yes.
Okay.
This is a wiretap.
Keep it in your pocket.
Don't try to get them to talk.
Be cautious with specific questions.
DETAILED PROPERTY REGISTRY
COLLECTIVE BUILDING
PYEONGBUKGWAN, SEJEONG-RO 3-GIL 33
OWNER: MIN HWAL-SUNG, GI SU-JONG,
NOUVEAU CITY DEVELOPMENT
There was a slight delay
but there's no problem
with the property.
The head office wants to know
why you didn't report
Deputy Nam's death.
He had an affair and killed himself.
Why should I report that?
Nam Sang-ho still had a role to play.
We're in a bind now.
Do as you're told
and report everything.
I noticed
Se-yoon Building
is up for a quick sale.
That shouldn't be a problem, right?
The head office waited long enough.
Let's wrap it up soon.
Why are you here this late?
I texted you earlier.
- You texted me?
- Yes.
Oh, you did. Sorry.
Is it urgent?
No, I wanted to run something by you.
Was that guy a lawyer?
Yes.
Here.
I got it because it looked good.
I don't eat sweets.
I only eat sugar-free food.
Desserts are nice once in a while.
It helps you recharge.
What got into you all of a sudden?
You're trying to feed me dessert?
Talk to me. What's the problem?
If you're asking about problems
I have a few.
My life's about to go down the drain.
I'm done for.
You're not done for.
If you take care
of just a few trivial issues
you'll be rich and successful.
"Trivial issues?"
They're not that easy to handle.
My wife wants a divorce
and I might lose the property.
I have a feeling
it might disrupt our business.
Why did you even start a family?
I'm a bit hesitant to ask, but...
Can you kill my wife?
You killed Jung Chang-su
my brother-in-law
and Deputy Nam.
You killed them all.
There's more.
Who?
A man named Morgan Lee.
My previous superior.
I killed him.
To eliminate the risk.
It's business.
Tomorrow night
my wife will be alone at home.
My daughter is traveling,
and I'll be out.
You can easily get rid of one person.
Isn't that how we eliminate risks
and move forward with the project?
Sorry for laughing
when you were being serious.
I'm glad I chose to work with you.
So what? Are we on?
Can you do it?
It can be done today.
No, not today.
Her nurse friend is coming over.
You say you're getting divorced,
but you know all her plans.
We still live together,
so I know her movements.
You want her dead?
You're a bad man. A psychopath!
There are no good or bad people.
We all do what we can to survive.
Let me have a taste.
- Put this on.
- Okay.
Let's get ready.
3RD-FLOOR BADUK CLUBHOUSE OWNER
Is Da-rae well?
She's asleep.
THURSDAY, APRIL 23
Something's off. It's been too long.
I'm running a bit late
due to work at the head office.
I don't need him just yet.
Yes, hello?
We lost her, Su-jong.
What do you mean you lost her?
Get over here.
There's no time to buy a cake.
PYEONGBUKGWAN
DAD
Hello.
Yi-gyeong.
You're Jeon Yi-gyeong, right?
Where are you going?
We have so much to talk about.
My heart's racing.
Yi-gyeong!
Yi-gyeong.
Darn it.
Eenie, meenie, miney, mo.
Tell me which way to go.
Are you in here?
Is this how you're going to play?
What the heck?
Darn it.
Who the heck was that?
This is so much fun.
I'm out of breath.
Hey.
(Why? Did you hear something?)
(Yi-gyeong, I won't leave you alone.)
Hey, you're here.
Perfect timing, just as expected.
I'm glad that I'm not late.
Don't worry.
I won't kill your daughter.
She can't talk, anyway.
Then again, you never know.
I might change my mind and...
Bang!
Let's stop here.
I'll give up on my shares
of Nouveau City.
Why?
That's the only reason we're here.
Well, the thing is
I don't have what it takes.
That's disappointing.
Mister.
I always thought
we were the same kind of people.
Did you think I'd be fooled today?
Hey.
I give up on Nouveau City.
You can have it all.
You're giving up
on your share of Nouveau City?
That's really disappointing.
Right?
Let's make a deal.
You can take Jeon Yi-gyeong out.
Then I'll let your daughter
walk out safely.
Wait.
I have a question before we do that.
How much more money
are you trying to make from this?
I'm just really curious.
I won't make much.
Also
there's something
more important than money.
Something more fun.
You were still alive.
You're late.
What's the situation?
Well, Mr. Gi right here
asked how much I was going to make.
Is that so important?
I'm kind of curious as well.
I don't care about that.
Let's wrap this up and talk outside.
I'm hungry, Mr. Gi.
You should also save your daughter.
Your precious daughter.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Stop dragging this out
before I change my mind.
Undertaker, will you just shoot her?
Sure.
INTERROGATION ROOM
Are you sure you only heard gunfire?
Yes.
Back then
I went to the scene
and found Jonah and Mr. Kim Chun-gil
already dead.
How did they know it was a trap?
I don't know.
The information could have leaked.
I'm not so sure.
Why do you think
all these deaths have occurred?
I don't know.
Right.
It's all because of Se-yoon Building.
Sorry?
Yi-gyeong's abduction
the deaths of Oh Dong-ki
Madam Jeon, and my friend Hwal-sung.
It all happened at Se-yoon Building.
I may not be legally responsible
but I believe I am a sinner.
Is there anything else
you wish to ask?
One moment.
Is this what you mean
by telling everything
from start to finish?
Everything was an accident.
No one expected
these things to happen.
You shot Oh Dong-ki with your gun.
Wasn't that also an accident?
Feel free to reach out to me
if you need help with anything else.
What happened? How's Da-rae?
She's fine.
She's at the hospital right now.
Also, Jonah died.
Died?
She died?
How?
She was shot to death.
It seemed like
a professional took her out
but we're investigating
the details right now.
I doubt anything dangerous
will happen right now.
But you never know, so be careful.
We'll keep an eye out.
Why did he let you live?
I don't know.
I have no idea.
What do you want?
I came to talk business.
But what I'm about to say
isn't supposed to leak out.
Okay.
Tonight, one of your staff
is planning to murder my wife.
However, it's a trap.
The undercover police will be there.
Why are you telling me this?
You'll have a huge headache
if your staff member gets arrested.
So I gave this some thought.
Just...
Just?
Just let her die.
I'll pretend like I didn't hear this.
I couldn't care less.
You'll be interested
after seeing this.
You killed Jung Chang-su
my brother-in-law
and Deputy Nam.
You killed them all.
There's more.
Who?
A man named Morgan Lee.
My previous superior.
I killed him.
You need a partner
to do business in Korea.
And you already know
I'm in charge of Nouveau City.
And?
Choose between your employee and me.
You can remove the employee
who poses a high risk
and do business with me smoothly.
Or you can go down with that risk.
How can we trust you and choose you?
There's no need to trust me.
What's there to trust
when doing business in Korea?
Simply make use of me.
How useful am I?
What are the risks?
Just think of this
from a business perspective.
At the very least,
I'm the type to follow the law
so you'll appreciate that.
Give me a moment.
I can't make the decision
in this situation.
But you know
the kind of deal
you're making right now, right?
Can you handle it?
Yes, I can.
It's also a part that I like.
So?
Are you in?
Sure.
Su-jong.
Let me ask you one thing.
You promised
you'd never lie to me again.
Do you remember that?
At Gyun's accident scene
did you just stand there and watch?
Yes.
I really don't know anything.
I wasn't at the scene.
Are you sure?
Yes.
THE LATE JEON YANG-JA
THE LATE KIM CHUN-GIL
THE LATE MIN HWAL-SUNG
Yi-gyeong.
Our family told the police
we didn't want you to be punished.
I see. Thanks.
You should take care of yourself.
They'll treat the case leniently
and investigate without detaining me.
So I'll keep my baby safe
as the trial continues.
Let me know if you need any help.
You managed to protect everything.
Both your building and your family.
I lost everything
except for this baby.
Congratulations.
I SHOULD'VE GIVEN IT TO YOU EARLIER,
I'M SORRY
YOU CAN DO WHATEVER YOU WANT WITH IT
I don't need it anymore.
I'm not the type who holds a grudge.
However
things won't be the same as before.
Yi-gyeong.
I know an apology
won't turn anything back
but I'm sorry.
Do you know
how much I adored you?
I want to ask you one thing.
I thought you liked me as well.
Was that all just an act?
No, Yi-gyeong.
That's not something I can fake.
I always liked you
and I still do.
I brought this to give to you.
Hwal-sung had it with him.
Goodbye, then.
1 YEAR LATER
Hello.
Your iced latte without syrup.
What about the tenant discount?
My boss said you can
always have it on the house.
Bye.
Hello.
All right.
CEO GI SU-JONG
Sir.
They're ready to shoot.
Okay.
I have no time
to work out these days.
Where are we going?
- This way, sir.
- Okay.
I built myself up from nothing
and became a landlord.
An ordinary man in his forties,
Gi Su-jong.
It's nice to have you here.
You introduced yourself
as an ordinary man in his forties
who started from nothing.
Why don't we go back
to why you bought your building?
- A close friend of mine
- Right.
brought it up to me.
Every ordinary worker
dreams of becoming a landlord, right?
But in my case, it wasn't for me
since I already had a family.
I thought about the future
of my family and my daughter.
I wanted to provide
a better future for them
so I knew I needed more income.
I thought, "What can I do?"
I should invest in real estate.
I guess that was how I started.
What's the best investment
you've ever made in your life?
My family is the best investment
I've ever made.
My daughter...
has a hearing impairment.
It's hard for her to hear
and communicate.
But she studies at Harvard.
When I wanted to become a landlord
my greatest source of strength
was my daughter.
And...
She was my biggest motivation.
I'm sure you had great support.
WHO GAVE YOU THE BIGGEST SUPPORT?
I think I got quite lucky.
I had help from many people
to achieve this level of success.
Especially my wife.
She supported me
and stayed with me through it all.
So I'm most grateful to her.
The entire world
has its eyes on Writer Kim's World.
Why don't you leave a message
for your beloved wife?
- A surprise message. Yes.
- Is this the camera?
Hey, honey.
I'll call you later.
That's about it.
Are you not going to do it?
No, I'll give her a call later.
All right.
We spent this episode
with CEO Gi Su-jong.
Thank you for spending
your precious time with us.
As always, presented by Writer Kim.
- Great shoot.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
- Mr. Kim.
- Thank you.
Thanks.
Thank you for your time, sir.
Don't mention it.
Of course, I can do this for you.
Happy birthday, Mr. Gi.
Goodness, this isn't necessary.
Have you talked to your daughter?
I'll call her later since it's late.
You should also talk to your wife.
If you're considering alimony,
you should finalize the divorce
before building another building.
You should wrap it up and...
I understand what you mean.
But I'll manage.
I apologize for bringing this up.
Well, it's your birthday,
so please enjoy your day.
- Please excuse me.
- Goodbye.
MY DAUGHTER
What?
SEON
The cellular customer you're trying
to reach is unavailable.
Why won't they pick up?
Gosh, this is always the problem.
- Mr. Gi.
- What?
By any chance, are you done?
Why? What is it?
You have visitors.
Visitors? Who?
Representative Yong and someone else.
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
THE LAST WEEK BEFORE THE EXPANSION
The soup is amazing.
THANK YOU, DEAR CUSTOMERS
WE WILL RETURN EVEN BETTER
Goodness, Mr. Gi.
- Congratulations on the expansion.
- Thank you.
Drink first, noodles later?
I'm working, so maybe another time.
Okay.
Please enjoy, sir.
Have you been well?
I'm not sure if I'm doing well.
What about you?
I'm just like you.
I'm just living.
He comes by every week.
He always gets boiled pork
on the house in a large portion.
Are you two close?
Sure.
There's an old saying that goes
"Keep your friends close,
but keep your enemies closer."
Oh, is that so?
Enjoy.
- Let's talk somewhere else.
- Let's go.
PYEONGBUKGWAN
Good grief.
Look at how indecent people can be.
Look at all these cigarette butts.
How many times do I have to do this?
Jeez.
I should just get rid of the ashtray.
What?
NARA CREDIT CARD: HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Happy birthday, Mr. Gi Su-jong.
Three of these.
That's 15 million won.
PAYMENT REMINDER
THANK YOU FOR USING NARA BANK...
I'm barely making ends meet.
AIDEN FIRE INSURANCE
I'm just working on a bigger scale.
Darn it.
ELECTRICITY BILL
862,300 WON
DA-RAE'S LIVING EXPENSES
4,000,000 WON
Da-rae, try to save some money.
Goodness.
JEON YI-GYEONG
All done.
YOUR SON WILL BE 100 DAYS OLD
THIS MONTH, RIGHT?
I SENT YOU A LITTLE MORE
Thanks. Happy birthday, Su-jong.
YI-GYEONG
Hey, Yi-gyeong. It's me, Su-jong.
It's been a while, Su-jong.
Have you been well?
What do you think?
You should be doing well.
I'm doing well.
I've never been better.
I see. I'm glad to hear that.
Logan, do you want
to listen to Su-jong's voice?
Hey, there. Is that you, Logan?
Can you talk, Logan?
I'm Uncle Su-jong, Logan.
He's a scary guy
but you're smiling big.
Are Seon and Da-rae doing well?
Yes.
They're doing well.
They reach out to me once a month.
Anyway, what's up?
You never call me.
Well...
Of all people,
I should at least call you.
I have something to say.
Sure.
With Pyeongbukgwan relocating
can you hang my mom's picture
in the dining area
at the new location?
You have the picture
I sent you before, right?
Yes, of course.
We even prepared a banner.
Once we relocate,
I'll print it out in high quality
and hang it up in the best place.
Thanks.
I want people
to remember her as a good person.
Yes, of course.
Madam Jeon deserves
to be remembered that way.
I haven't forgiven Gi Su-jong yet.
I will spend the rest of my life
repaying you for that emotional debt.
But more importantly
we shouldn't hurt Da-rae and Logan
because of our mistakes.
I want to live for the future
instead of dwelling on my past.
Of course.
I will pray for you, Yi-gyeong.
Thanks.
Come here.
Hey, there.
Seon.
It's my birthday today.
We may be far away right now
but I believe we'll meet again.
Man, that's not it.
That was such a lame line.
Why don't we start over
and be together
in the second act of our lives?
Darn it. Will that work?
That line was also...
I'll give it a try.
Is she still sleeping?
I knew you'd be here like this.
Hey.
My friend.
Why are you all alone like that,
looking so sad?
Hwal-sung.
There's no way
I'd forget my best friend's birthday.
If you wanted to drink,
you should've called me.
Oh, right.
I found out something awesome.
I was going to keep this to myself.
Do you want to know?
Yes.
Hey, one second.
I made myself a business card.
You can have one.
GI SU-JONG
Me?
What's seaweed in sign language?
Look at this.
I was making this.
(Did you have a birthday party?)
I went out for drinks with friends.
(I'm sorry I don't have a gift
for your birthday.)
Stop it.
You're my present, Da-rae.
To me, that is.
Anyway, where's your mom?
(She went out with her friends.)
What?
With whom?
(Mr. Beard and someone else.)
Mr. Beard?
Who is that?
Ta-da!
Happy birthday, Gi Su-jong.
We're using your birthday
as an excuse to eat cake.
- My gosh.
- Happy birthday.
Is that seaweed soup?
Now that you're alone,
you finally started cooking.
It's not that.
I got it at the grocery store.
Anyway.
You remembered my birthday.
Thank you for celebrating with me.
Da-rae remembers.
That's my girl.
We're going to Seoul tomorrow.
- You know, right?
- Yes.
I'll be at the airport.
No, it's all right.
We'll get ourselves home.
You're a busy man.
It's okay.
You probably have a lot of luggage.
Okay.
When we go to Seoul this time
let's finalize our divorce.
Gosh, what a great birthday gift.
The timing is kind of odd, right?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
The paperwork is ready.
If we separate now,
I think we can still remain friends.
That would be better for Da-rae.
All right.
Thanks, Da-rae's mom.
Su-jong.
You've done well so far.
I'm sorry, and thank you.
And don't change who you are.
You must be busy. Let's hang up.
See you tomorrow.
Yes, all right. Bye.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
ATTORNEY ROBERT
I have something to discuss with you,
so please call me.
ATTORNEY ROBERT
Why won't he pick up?
GOLD RUSH INVESTMENT
What is this?
MR. GI SU-JONG
A CERTIFIED MAIL
CONTAINING INFORMATION
REGARDING THE AUCTION PROCESS
OF NOUVEAU CITY'S SHARES
SE-YOON BUILDING, HANMAEUM BUILDING,
AND PYEONGBUKGWAN HAS BEEN SENT
Is this a phishing scam?
Attention, please.
Aviation security...
ATTORNEY YANG
OPEN LINK?
Gold Rush?
GOLD RUSH INVESTMENT'S
HOSTILE TAKEOVER OF REAL CAPITAL
What is this?
Gold Rush Investment.
A CERTIFIED MAIL
CONTAINING INFORMATION
REGARDING THE AUCTION PROCESS
OF NOUVEAU CITY'S SHARES
SE-YOON BUILDING, HANMAEUM BUILDING,
AND PYEONGBUKGWAN HAS BEEN SENT
IF YOU DO NOT COMPLY,
YOU WILL RECEIVE A PENALTY
ATTORNEY ROBERT
This punk won't pick up.
You must be Gi Su-jong.
(Dad said he would wait at the gate.)
You're right.
I mean...
Where did he go this time?
What are you doing?
Me?
I got a new job.
Mr. Landlord.
Why don't we
start discussing business?
Sure.
With pleasure.
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Jennifer Lim