(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
[Episode 5]
Okay, come on, look over here.
Three, two, one, smile.
Smile.
You came, too.
Fei, I'll take a couple of photos for you.
Sure, sure, sure!
Happy graduation!
You're late.
The graduation ceremony is already over.
Stop nagging.
There's so much to do.
Can the graduation ceremony happen again?
I already received my diploma.
The principal's gone, too.
Then I came here for nothing.
I'll go find the principal.
Wait.
I'm already happy that you're here.
I know.
Tonight, there's an outdoor movie
at Fortress Square.
Dad and Fei both want to go.
Do you want to come along?
What's so good about a free movie?
Are you coming or not?
Sure, let's go.
It's all in English.
I can't understand it.
No way you'd understand English.
You should ask us college students.
- Dad, let me do it.
- Mr. He!
Let me do it.
- Come, take a break.
- Okay.
- Here you go, Dad.
- Isn't this simple?
Dad, sit here.
No need, this seat is fine.
This spot is good enough.
- Can you handle it?
- It's very simple.
Thanks so much.
Thank you, Fei.
No problem at all.
Look.
Got it! It's up!
We can watch now.
Listen, only I can get the official DVD.
Everyone else is watching pirated copies.
Impressive, right?
Amazing! Come on, eat.
You can even use a VCD.
- Sit down.
- I want to sit opposite He.
Go ahead, sit down.
Thanks.
I can only eat if I can see He.
Here comes the wine.
This is my ten-year
brewed bone-strengthening wine.
- Tonight, we drink it.
- Ten years, that's a long time.
It contains many precious Chinese herbs.
In short, it's very nourishing.
It must taste great.
You must savor it, really savor it.
Yes, and here are my meatballs.
It's amazing, excellent! Come on, dig in!
Today is a good day.
Yes.
Let me say a few words first.
Chu San.
Dad is lucky to have a son like you.
You haven't had wine before.
Just have a sip.
I'll down this cup here.
Then I'll drink, too.
Chu San, I wish you a smooth career
and lots of happiness.
Most importantly, good health.
You don't have to drink. I'll drink.
Fei can really hold his liquor.
Then I'll drink, too. Thanks, Fei.
Have a cup with me, too.
Forget it, just watch the movie.
Why not?
You, Mr. He, and Fei all drank.
But not with me. Don't care about me, huh?
Then come on.
Drink up.
I'm watching you.
Come, dig in.
This movie is pretty good.
Of course it's good.
The bride looks beautiful with a veil.
Yes!
She's so fair and clean, like a fairy.
You're not bad either.
I really like Marlon Brando.
Why is he called Brandy?
It sounds like a liquor.
It's Brando, Fei.
Brando.
Is it Brando or Brandy?
Who's Brando?
Gosh!
Fei!
Look at them.
You're injured?
No.
There's no injury.
Try this.
Okay, fine.
Xiao Liu, come to Qi's place.
Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
♪ Did you wait patiently? ♪
♪ Still waiting, waiting to be missed ♪
♪ Please don't be afraid ♪
Xia Liu Yi.
You seem really happy today.
I have a place where I feel safe.
And that makes me really happy.
Then you can...
live here forever.
Okay.
Can I have a bite?
Give it to me.
He Chu San.
Do you like lollipops that much?
No.
He Chu San.
Xia Liu Yi.
How could I have such a dream?
Give me a bite.
Give me a bite!
If you want it, go get it yourself.
There's none left.
Chu San.
Why are you up so early?
Dad.
Why are you washing sheets in the morning?
Last night... I...
Was it because of my wine?
Men of this age...
Dad.
Hurry up and cook.
Okay, you keep washing.
I'll make breakfast for you and Mr. Xia.
Good morning, Mr. He.
Good morning.
He Chu San.
Why take my blanket?
He dirtied the blanket yesterday
and was already washing it early this morning.
- You caught a cold?
- Do you get cold easily?
You'll get a cold
if you don't cover up in summer.
Hey, He Chu San...
Have you brushed your teeth?
The toothpaste and brush are over there.
Go brush your teeth.
Hurry up. Go on.
Chu San.
You guys eat first. I'm going to find Fei.
The past feels like a fleeting dream,
and it's hard to recognize my feelings...
Why do we bury our old names
after a hundred trials and reunions?
He Chu San.
Are Mr. He and Fei getting it on?
You're the boss of a gang.
Why are you so gossipy?
He Chu San.
I ask you, but you don't answer me.
He Chu San, you're done for.
Do you know how to play pool?
No.
My company is near yours.
Come play pool with me after work.
No way.
You idiot.
What's going on with you today?
You keep saying no to everything.
Xia Liu Yi.
Let's keep our distance.
What's wrong with you?
Crazy.
Xia Liu Yi.
Is your phone just for show?
I called you so many times.
If you still don't pick up,
I'll sell Xiaoqi Hall and run away.
I left it at He Chu San's place.
Looks like he doesn't want to be your lackey.
More like you want to become
the live-in son-in-law of the He Family Clinic.
Yesterday at the Sha family gang's dock,
their boss was making a deal
with some Burmese guys,
and the Organized Crime Bureau
wiped them out in one go.
They were caught red-handed.
Our people at the dock
and the informants in the police
didn't get any news at all.
What?
It might already be on the news by now.
This is a special report.
The Organized Crime Bureau
and the Narcotics Division
launched a joint flash operation
early this morning.
Under the command of Inspector Xie Jia Hua,
they successfully dismantled
a drug trafficking syndicate that had operated
on Hong Kong Island for many years.
It is reported that Inspector Xie
comes from a police family.
His father, Xie Ying Jie,
serves as Deputy Commissioner of Police.
This Xie Jia Hua is 31 years old.
He earned a master's degree
in criminal psychology in the U.S.
He returned to Hong Kong last August
after completing his studies.
Studied in the U.S., huh.
He Chu San is pretty smart, too.
Xia Liu Yi, are you even listening to me?
Yeah, I hear you. I'm listening.
He's just some young master
from the Xie family.
Now that he's on TV, he thinks he's a star.
With the police making such a big move,
they'll definitely come after us next.
What should we do?
Every year, we give Inspector Hua
so many red envelopes.
If you ask me what we should do,
I'd go straight to Inspector Hua's house
and make him spit the money back out.
So, you mean...
Xiao Ma.
Boss, the men are ready.
They're ready to move anytime.
No need to go.
Let Fei Qi off this time.
Tell the boys not to act so recklessly for now.
- All right.
- Wait.
What's going on?
Yesterday, Boss went to Hung Hom
and was chased by Fei Qi's men.
Boss told us to smash two of his shops
to teach him a lesson.
But he's called it off now.
Xia Liu Yi, why did you
go to Fei Qi's turf alone?
Looking for your grave?
It was He Chu San's graduation ceremony.
Fei Qi's guys happened to tail me,
and I almost didn't make it in time.
All right.
I'm sitting here just fine today.
A loser like Fei Qi can't keep up with me.
You lousy hall master.
Whoever wants the job can have it.
I'm done with it.
And this damn mobile phone still needs fixing.
Boss, then the position of hall master...
Keep dreaming. She'll come back.
All right.
Stop.
Boss, any other orders?
You've been with me for eight years.
I remember the first time I met you,
it was at Ganglong.
Yeah.
I was almost beaten to death back then.
You saved me.
Saved your life.
I saved him, too. So, why can't it work?
What's the issue?
Why won't he be my lackey?
I really can't figure out
what He Chu San is thinking.
He's just a student.
Boss, why take such a weakling as a lackey?
He can't fight, can't curse.
Miss, your drink.
I heard about it.
Thank you.
- Young and promising.
- Go say hello.
Is that him?
Xie is one of the police force's elites.
His future is limitless.
It's part of my job.
Inspector Xie is the youngest
Senior Superintendent in history.
Inspector Xie's son is really impressive.
Young and promising.
Thank you, thank you.
Hua.
- Inspector Hua.
- Inspector Hua, you're here.
You don't recognize me?
I'm Uncle Hua.
You've grown up so much.
I still remember over twenty years ago,
I was at his first birthday party.
He didn't even look at
all the things on the table,
but he grabbed his father's
police badge right away.
- Impressive.
- Yeah.
That was when I knew
this kid was born to be a cop.
This is what you call young and promising.
After he returned to the country
and took office,
he immediately took down
the most troublesome drug dealer in Kowloon.
Impressive.
You're wasting your talent
staying in the Organized Crime Bureau.
Soon, I'll be transferred to Kowloon West.
District Superintendent.
I'll save the Assistant Superintendent
position for you.
- Congratulations.
- Chief Superintendent Hua.
I'd think the Kowloon West District
is your family's business.
Personnel transfers must follow the rules.
We're police officers.
We must uphold the law.
And we certainly can't steal from within.
Come on, cheers.
Let's drink.
Hello, sir.
Congratulations, Hua.
Dad, you're here.
Hua, you're looking very impressive today.
Congratulations.
Don't worry about me today.
I'm just here as James' dad.
Enjoy yourselves.
Let's sit over there.
Thank you.
Dad.
You're so busy.
You didn't need to make
a special trip for this small case.
What small case?
The drug lord who's been a menace for years,
and the whole drug trafficking network.
Your dad's been a cop his whole life,
and hasn't handled many cases as neat as this.
By the way, were you injured on this mission?
No.
You've got a wound on your neck.
It's an allergy.
I knew it, you can't take care of yourself.
- Huang's daughter...
- Dad.
I just want to be like you,
and be an outstanding police officer.
To fight evil, protect the good,
and uphold justice.
But you can't just focus on work.
It's time.
Got it.
Excuse me.
Are you the Deputy Commissioner
of Police, Xie Ying Jie?
That's me.
Hello.
My name is Lu Guang Ming.
I've just joined the Independent Commission
Against Corruption.
I'm an Assistant Investigator.
You've been my idol since I was young.
Your integrity inspired me
to pursue a career in law enforcement.
Thank you, you're too kind.
Can I sit down and chat with you?
No.
Hua.
Sorry about that.
Jia Hua is a little introverted.
He doesn't have many friends.
Most of the people here today
are his colleagues.
I didn't even know he had friends here.
I've only just met Jia Hua recently.
He's taught me a lot.
Right, Jia Hua?
Sir, the car is here.
I'd love to chat more with you,
but I have to leave now.
You guys carry on.
By the way, since you're Jia Hua's friend,
feel free to come by anytime.
[Xie Ying Jie]
Definitely.
What are you doing?
Why are you here?
Who are you?
Inspector Xie.
Take it easy.
I just started working,
and my salary isn't high.
It's not easy to buy a decent suit.
Answer my question.
Lu Guang Ming.
Assistant Investigator of
the Independent Commission Against Corruption.
Today, I'm here on behalf of the ICAC
to attend the Outstanding Case Seminar.
You just gave a speech on stage.
I wrote everything down.
Not a word missed.
Every word was brilliant.
You deliberately got close to me last night.
Inspector Xie.
You can't just say anything.
There are so many gay bars down in Central.
Who doesn't hide their true self?
You don't want anyone to know
about last night, do you?
I saw you speaking on stage today
and that was when I realized
how destined we are.
Have you told anyone about us?
What are you talking about?
All right.
We just ran into each other last night.
A one-night stand.
But Inspector Xie...
Last night, I thought we both
had feelings for each other.
But you treated me
like a prostitute for 163 bucks.
Isn't that a little cheap for a prostitute?
I was drunk last night.
I only had that much on me.
It's fine.
I'll take care of it myself.
I really have to thank you.
How else would a big shot like your father
give his business card to someone like me?
You came because of my father.
Inspector Xie, last night...
it seemed like you asked me
to have a drink first.
I didn't ask you for your ID.
All right.
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone about this.
That wouldn't be good for you or me.
Let's get to the point.
I've been working with a detective recently.
I suspect he's involved with
the drug case you just cracked.
I want...
all the information on this case.
The drug case is classified.
Many of the related forces
are still on the loose.
I can't give it to you.
If you want to investigate,
give me the information you have.
I'll look into it along with the drug case.
If it's really like you said,
I won't let him go.
Okay?
No, Inspector Xie.
Someone like me had no resources,
no background, no connections.
It's not that easy to investigate a case.
I'm counting on this case to get promoted.
You don't want to investigate the case.
You want to use my information
to make it your leverage.
In simple terms,
you're trying to use me and climb the ranks.
Inspector Xie.
Someone like you, born under a lucky star,
would never understand ordinary people like us.
Listen, from now on,
we have nothing to do with each other.
Please keep last night's encounter to yourself.
I'll act like it never happened.
One more thing.
Don't think you can use my position
for personal gain.
I hate people like you the most.
Inspector Xie.
Please make sure to investigate
Senior Inspector Hua in Kowloon.
If you get any information,
please tell me immediately.
If you need me, I will always be...
here.
Are you Senior Inspector Hua of Kowloon?
About the transfer from the Sha family gang
to your daughter,
you'd better come up
with an explanation quickly.
Otherwise, I'm afraid you might
compromise your reputation before retirement.
Dad, I'm heading to work.
So handsome.
Wait a second.
All right, good luck.
Thanks.
Come back early.
Okay.
Hello.
Lily, give him the project ID badge.
Sure.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
This way.
Lucy.
This is Sonny.
Hello, I'm He Chu San.
Call me "Sam".
This is Mike.
Hello.
This is Pam.
This is Mark.
Your seat is here.
- Mine?
- Yes.
Work hard.
Okay.
- Michael.
- All right, thanks.
David.
Thanks.
Take a look at him.
He's so handsome.
Do you want a bite?
No, you eat.
No, thanks.
- Is this okay?
- Not bad.
Very handsome.
Sam.
You did a good job on your report today.
The clients all said
you were very professional.
They feel very reassured.
Young man.
- Call him over.
- Chu San.
What brings you here?
Sam, who are they?
Sir, you are our young man's...
Chu San's superior, right?
Chu San works here.
No one would bully him, right?
Of course not.
What are you doing?
Boss wants to talk to you.
He sent us to pick you up.
Chu San is now in Xiaoqi Hall...
Just kidding.
Come on, get in the car.
Get in.
- Drive.
- Let's go.
All right.
Well, feeling flattered?
Boss.
What are you doing?
Today's a good day.
I specially arranged
a formal initiation ceremony.
In front of Guan Yu,
you pledge me as your big brother today.
From now on, you'll be my brother for life.
A brother's promise,
blood spilled across the land.
Why did you do all this
without asking me first?
Xiao Ma is right.
We were too hasty in
making you join Xiaoqi Hall before.
So, this time, I'll handle everything
with the highest standards.
Cheers!
- Cheers!
Cheers! Cheers!
Cheers!
I've said it once.
Now, I'll say it again.
I, He Chu San,
will never be your underling.
Young man!
Are you unhappy?
He Chu San is immune
to both threats and persuasion.
What's wrong?
This time, are you set on getting him?
Didn't you say you wouldn't check the accounts?
Aren't I looking for a cultured person?
I meant someone cultured like him.
If you really want someone
to be your subordinate,
it's not that easy.
His mother died because of the triads.
What did you say?
You didn't know?
He Chu San was adopted.
His real mother was a beautiful woman.
She was with a gangster.
Right before giving birth to him,
his father was hacked to death in the street.
His mother gave birth prematurely to him,
and then passed away.
Then Dr. He adopted him.
It's said that just before she died,
her last words were...
"Never let He Chu San
get involved with the triads."