YUMI'S CELLS 3
EPISODE 19
EXPULSION ORDER
Shin PD.
I thought you went to see Mr. Kim.
Why are you here?
I felt like I had to see you first.
Why?
Why did you come here?
Right.
Why are you here, Soon-rok?
Why did we come here?
Why did Soon-rok come here?
I don't know.
What do you mean, you don't know?
I'm not sure either...
What? I don't know,
and you don't know either?
What do you mean you don't know?
Why did you break your plans
with Jennie and come here?
- I don't know.
- You don't know that either?
I shouldn't have done that.
Get a grip, Soon-rok.
What are you talking about?
Why is Soon-rok acting like that
right now?
I know. You shouldn't have.
So, did you come here
to apologize to me for that?
It's fine. I'm okay.
- Just go to...
- I didn't come here to apologize.
- Then why?
- I think...
I like you.
Emergency! Emergency!
Everyone, it's an emergency!
An emergency!
He likes Yu-mi?
Soon-rok confessed.
Soon-rok likes Yu-mi?
- Soon-rok likes Yu-mi.
- What? Since when?
- Since when?
Soon-rok confessed!
Wait.
What is this...
Is someone here?
Shin PD!
Are you okay?
- Are you hurt?
- No.
No, I'm fine.
Na-hee was worried
so she waited for you.
Why did you do that?
- I'm so curious.
- Well...
I'm... sorry.
Why did you two fight?
We'll hear the details later.
You should get going.
The Chief Editor is waiting.
Right, I'll be on my way.
But you just got here.
Gosh, just hurry.
Okay, then.
By the way, why did he come here?
I don't know.
He was probably worried about us.
Na-hee, you should go now.
It's getting late.
It's not that late yet.
I'm leaving too, so let's go together.
Hurry and get your things.
But...
Door closing.
You're crazy.
What is up with you today?
Hey, what's wrong with him?
Why did Soon-rok
suddenly confess like that?
This is so absurd.
Oh, about that.
Take a look at this.
What's this?
You performed the removal surgery.
But it got bigger.
No
that's not an x-ray of Writer Yu-mi.
It's Soon-rok's.
What?
It was only this big earlier.
But I took an x-ray today
and it's gotten this big.
Then why did he even draw the line?
I...
made a misdiagnosis.
I'm sorry.
Everything's a mess because of me.
Do you think "sorry" is going to fix this?
You quack...
A quack...
Hey, where are you going?
I'll fix it.
Just wait.
What are you going to fix?
- Someone's coming!
- Who is it?
Hey, guys!
I'm Soon-rok's Love Cell.
Love Cell?
Can you open the door?
I have something to say
to Yu-mi's Love Cell.
Soon-rok's Love Cell?
Yeah, what should we do?
Should we let him in?
Wow, he came all this way?
This is for real.
It was a real confession.
What's gotten into him?
There's one more thing that's changed
as I've gotten older.
Open the door.
Let's call Love!
Hold on.
You stay put.
Let go of me!
I, Rational Cell, can feel
my power getting stronger too.
Thanks.
Get him!
What's wrong with you?
Now...
the trial will begin.
The charges against the defendant
Shin Soon-rok
are as follows.
First, Shin Soon-rok
acted bizarrely from day one
confusing Yu-mi
and often disrupting her writing.
Do you accept this?
Let's talk, Shin PD.
Are you unhappy working with me?
- Yes, yes, I understand.
- Huh? Excuse me.
- Bye.
- Hello?
Hey!
Ms. Kim.
Well...
It wasn't intentional...
DEFENDANT
I'm sorry
if I made you uncomfortable.
Do you admit it?
I admit it.
Second.
The crime of making
her heart flutter with his cute smile
and puppy charm.
- He was just like a puppy.
- He was cute.
He is cute. I really remember that.
He was cute.
Do you admit it?
That's just
- Soon-rok's charm...
-Do you admit it?
I admit it.
Third.
Texting her to see a movie.
You're cool.
Spouting the word "cool" carelessly
and sharing his umbrella in the rain
making Yu-mi's heart flutter.
My heart really fluttered that day.
Do you admit it?
I admit it.
Fourth.
The crime of leading her on
then asking her to get him a blind date
and confusing her.
Someone for a blind date.
That's right.
I was so pissed off then.
Seriously.
Do you admit it?
I admit it.
- Fifth.
- There's more?
After going on a date with Yu-mi's junior
you canceled last minute, hurting Jennie
and making it awkward for the matchmaker.
Do you admit it?
I admit it.
That was truly wrong.
But this happened
because Soon-rok
hadn't realized his feelings yet...
Sixth.
For suddenly confessing his feelings now
and making all their relationships
a complete mess.
Do you admit it?
Admit it.
- You have to admit it.
- Admit it!
- Come on!
- Do it!
I admit it.
The defendant has admitted to all charges.
Defendant Shin Soon-rok
caused a stir in Yu-mi Village
delaying her work.
And is found guilty of dealing
a fatal blow to her relationships.
Therefore...
the verdict.
Shin Soon-rok's confession...
is rejected.
- Reject his confession?
- Emotional, sit down.
At the same time, to prevent
Shin Soon-rok's further influence
I order his banishment from Yu-mi Village.
Soon-rok is
out of Yu-mi's Village!
Are you okay?
Get out of here now!
Get out!
Shin PD.
I'll pretend I didn't hear
what you just said.
I didn't know you were this immature.
You're being very reckless.
Apologize to Writer Ju-ho
and I hope you sort this out.
Smells nice.
It's delicious.
My mind feels calm
for the first time in a while.
This is the real Yu-mi.
My mornings always used to
start like this.
Calmly thinking about
what to write for the day.
It's finally peaceful.
Soon-rok.
Soon-rok. It's already 11 o'clock.
I know.
How long are you going to
lie here like this?
I have no energy.
I can't get up.
Oh, no.
Even though I've been lying at home
all day, it's not recharging.
What should I do?
But there's one thing
left to do, Soon-rok.
You have to contact Jennie.
Use your last bit of strength.
Let's finish this with some manners.
Jennie.
I'm so sorry about yesterday.
The truth is
I haven't had much time lately...
It's Jennie.
Hello?
Yes, Jennie.
Soon-rok, are you busy?
Is it okay to talk for a moment?
Yes.
I'm really sorry about yesterday.
JENNIE
Hey, Jennie.
I meant to call you yesterday
but it got too late.
You were baffled yesterday, right?
Yes.
I was a bit baffled.
It seems he had something urgent
at the publishing company.
I couldn't ask for details either.
But I'll ask Shin PD during our meeting.
I already spoke with Soon-rok.
A little while ago.
Oh, really?
He seemed really sorry.
He asked to meet today.
So you agreed to meet?
No.
Yu-mi.
Actually...
Jeong-sik suddenly
contacted me.
Your ex-boyfriend?
Yes.
It's been a little over two months
since we broke up.
But he suddenly came over last night
so we decided
to get back together.
Oh.
I see.
I'm so sorry.
This all happened so suddenly.
No, it's okay.
It's... a good thing.
That's great.
I felt I should tell you the truth.
Yu-mi didn't know when she set us up.
Please don't misunderstand.
Yes.
Of course.
I'll tell Yu-mi too.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
No, don't worry about it.
Congratulations.
It feels a bit strange for me
to say thank you...
I'm truly happy for you.
I mean it.
I told Soon-rok
and I feel so bad.
Well...
I'm sure he'll understand.
I'm so sorry to you too, Yu-mi.
Gosh, it's fine.
That's great.
Really great.
Yu-mi.
Call me when you're done
with your deadline.
I'll buy you a meal.
Thank you, Yu-mi.
Okay, sure. See you later.
What the heck?
If she was getting back with him,
she should've done it a day earlier.
We wouldn't have kicked him out.
Can't we go see Soon-rok?
It's over now.
How so?
Soon-rok said he likes Yu-mi
and Yu-mi liked Soon-rok too.
We already wrapped it up
neatly.
That's right.
- What's done is done.
- It's over.
What's done is done.
It's deceitful
- to break our word.
- That's not good manners.
Let's not do that.
You've got to be kidding me.
Where is she going?
You cold-hearted things.
That's how a person's heart is.
Doesn't it change
depending on the situation?
Fine.
If you all don't want to,
I'll do it myself.
Let's go, Yu-mi.
We're going to Soon-rok.
Starting now
it's Heart Fever Time!
HEART FEVER TIME
WHEN EMOTIONS EXPLODE
Heart Fever Time.
A state where emotions
temporarily explode.
When in this state,
there's nothing you can't do.
Heart Fever Time!
Time!
Time, time!
- Time!
- Emotional.
Enough.
Move.
I'm good at this.
Don't you remember
what happened with Ba-bi?
Heart Fever Time.
Don't you know
that has an age limit?
-Yu-mi can't do that anymore.
Sadly, Heart Fever Time
has an age limit.
The ability disappears
in your mid-thirties.
However
Heart Fever Time
isn't an ability only Yu-mi can use.
Heart Fever Time will now begin.
What's going on?
It's Emotional's house!
This is Heart Fever Time.
Heart Fever Time?
Really?
I've only heard about it.
This is the first time
I've seen it in our village.
EMOTIONAL CELL
Soon-rok, let's go!
We're going to Ms. Kim, no...
We're going to Yu-mi!
Run, Soon-rok!
I guess she's not home.
This was a bad idea.
She clearly rejected you.
What did you expect to hear?
Think about it.
The age difference is huge.
She won't even see you as a man.
Let's go back.
This isn't like you.
Soon-rok.
Thank you for understanding
and for your support.
Take care.
Someday we'll see each other again, right?
Yes.
You take care too, Jennie.
Maybe we'll see each other
at Yu-mi's wedding?
Though there's no set date.
A wedding?
Hurry up and come.
I think we...
You look so pretty.
Shin PD, come over here.
Oh, my.
Come on up.
Thank you.
He's the editor in charge.
Soon-rok.
Hello.
It's been a while.
Come on up.
No, no.
I don't want to imagine that.
So squeeze it out one more time!
It's Heart Fever Time!
Run, Soon-rok!
ONE WAY
Hello.
Who is it?
Ms. Kim.
It's me, Soon-rok.
But haven't I seen
this scene somewhere before?
Shin PD?
That's right.
This is the exact same situation
as yesterday.
What are you doing here?
It's the same as yesterday. Damn it.
Why did you come...
without calling?
Huh?
Don't tell me...
You don't know again?
- What on earth...
- No.
Everything you said is right, Ms. Kim.
I'm very immature.
And I was reckless.
I admit it.
It's ridiculous.
So sudden
and out of the blue.
But...
But still...
No matter how much I think about it...
I like you, Ms. Kim.
It's pathetic that
I've only just realized it...
I think I've liked you...
from the beginning.
Yesterday...
you told me.
Yes.
And...
I rejected you.
Yes.
But you're saying the same thing...
again.
Yes.
Because I think I'll regret it.
There's no answer.
Did I get rejected again?
Let's go.
Soon-rok got rejected twice in a row.
I've never experienced such humiliation.
But...
Have you had lunch?
No.
Do you want to eat together?
It opened!
He's here again.
He got kicked out, but he's back.
How brave.
What if he gets kicked out again?
Hang in there.
- Welcome!
- Cheer up, Soon-rok!
- Welcome, Shin Soon-rok!
- You can do it!
Thanks.
I came to see Yu-mi's Love Cell.
If you want to see Love, go that way.
- Okay.
- I'll be cheering for you.
- Be careful!
- Thanks!
Hello.
You must be Love.
Ms. Kim is on another level.
Having such a huge Love is why
she's a master of romance stories.
I'm not Love. I'm Hunger.
Love lives over there.
Go over there.
Is that so?
Thanks.
Wait!
But have you had lunch?
Lunch?
Love is great, but you have to eat.
Have you had lunch?
- No.
- Do you want to
eat together?
Come in.
I was just about to have lunch.
Do you like naengmyeon?
I'm going to make bibim-naengmyeon.
- So?
- What?
Is bibim-naengmyeon...
okay?
Yes, yes.
That's great.
Have a seat.
Hi.
Is Love Cell's house around here?
Are you Soon-rok's Love Cell?
Yeah. It's nice to meet you.
I'll be coming here often.
- You'll be coming here often?
- Yeah.
Weren't you banished?
Do you have the right to be here?
You can eat two servings, right?
Then I'll have to make four.
Four?
Because there are three of us.
But why isn't she coming out?
Na-hee! Shin PD is here.
What? Na-hee is here too?
Did she just mean for me to eat and leave?
Was I getting the wrong idea?
- But there's no meeting today...
- It was...
a joke.
I'm alone.
One serving isn't enough, even for me.
Get a grip.
I was just joking because
you seemed so nervous.
Please sit down.
Make yourself comfortable.
It's a good thing we have eggs, at least.
By the way...
Are we only having
cold noodles?
Sorry?
I was wondering if this is all...
It won't be enough, will it?
Grilled meat with it would be nice
but we don't have any.
- Should we just go out to eat?
- No.
That's not it...
I didn't get...
an answer.
Because you didn't...
answer me, Ms. Kim.
Right.
So?
I asked you
to have lunch with me.
That's why I'm boiling water now.
Is that...
your answer?
Is this the place?
Hi.
I'm Soon-rok's Love Cell.
I came because I have something to say.
I've been waiting.
Thank you for coming back.
I thought I'd never get another chance.
Welcome.
It's nice to meet you.
I...
like you too, Shin PD.
Starting now
let's give this a shot.
Are you satisfied?
Yes.
Okay.
Can I help you with anything?
Oh, no. Just stay seated.
Or get yourself a drink.
There are plenty in the fridge.
Do you like bibim-naengmyeon?
Yes, I prefer spicy
over non-spicy naengmyeon.
How about you, Shin PD?
Spicy for me too.
That's a relief.
Are you making egg garnish too?
I prefer it with egg garnish
rather than a boiled egg.
Then I'll do this part.
Oh, no. I told you to sit.
I'm an egg garnish expert.
I'll do it here.
Here, for the eggshells.
Yes, Yu-mi.
Should I not call you by your name?
It felt weird
to keep calling you Ms. Kim.
No, it's fine.
Do you not like it when I call you Yu-mi?
It's fine.
Yu-mi...
I like it.
Yeah.
You can speak informally to me too, Yu-mi.
Should I do that?
All right...
Shin PD.
No, let's take our time.
- Yes.
Calling Yu-mi became the fuse.
Yu...
mi!
YU-MI
Hello, everyone.
The new semester has finally begun!
I'm finally returning to class
after a very long time.
I never thought a day like this
would come again.
The new cells didn't know
I lived in this village, right?
- We didn't know.
All right, the new semester's topic
is dating a younger man.
It's a new topic
and might feel a bit unfamiliar
but let's hurry.
Our goal is to make progress quickly
so try to keep up. Got it?
- Yes!
Yu-mi.
Have you ever
dated someone younger?
No.
Shin PD, have you ever
dated someone older?
No. This is my first time.
Have you ever dated a coworker?
What about you, Shin PD?
This is my first time.
What about you, Yu-mi?
Just once.
How did you two act at the office?
Well...
it wasn't for long.
I quit the company soon after.
And your coworkers...
They didn't know.
When was that?
Before my debut as a writer.
But are you always this full of questions?
Because I'm curious.
Be careful.
I need sesame oil.
It looks delicious.
All right. Given the mood
it seems fine to make some progress.
Today's goal for progress.
Chapter One.
Linking Arms.
Naughty Cell.
It's the first day. Let's not rush.
Don't mess it up again.
What are you talking about?
We have to consider
Soon-rok's personality.
He's not like her ex-boyfriends.
Why, you...
Let's be careful at the publisher's
or when we have meetings.
Right, we should.
As it is, the Chief Editor
already has it out for me.
Oh, that's right.
See? Soon-rok's personality...
Let's avoid holding hands,
interlocking fingers
and putting an arm around the waist
within a 1km radius
of the publishing house.
Teacher, the class next door
is moving faster.
They say nowadays, they do
Chapters one, two, three all at once.
Jeez, our teacher is such
an old-fashioned cell.
Quiet! Are you all ignoring
Yu-mi's experience points?
As if you know anything.
And the studio, too.
It's absolutely dangerous
within a 1km radius of here too.
No physical contact.
Ah, that's right.
That's how it should be.
- All done.
- Oh, it's all done.
Wait.
I forgot this.
Master.
Did you call for me?
I have arrived.
NAUGHTY CELL
No, I don't think I called you.
No, sir.
You definitely called me.
Soon-rok
was definitely looking for me.
Let's eat now.
Can I ask you one more thing?
Usually, when you're dating
how soon do you kiss?
Is the first day...
okay?
But...
this is the studio.
-What?
-You said no touching
near the studio.
It's...
the weekend today.
Oh, right.
So it's okay.
EPISODE 21
ALL ABOUT MY BOYFRIEND
Soon-rok, I'm here.
- Hello.
- I don't know why
but it's a bit weird seeing you here.
Ms. Kim.
The Chief Editor is still in a meeting
so you'll have to wait a bit.
Will about 30 minutes be okay?
What's with you?
You're so serious.
Yu-mi.
Yu-mi, this is the office.
Did you forget that I said
we should be careful?
I'm already on thin ice.
- If we're being conspicuous...
- But...
I think you're the one being
more conspicuous right now.
Please go in, Ms. Kim.
Oh, okay.
JULLY LITERATURE RADIO
Ms. Kim, hello.
Hello.
Your new hairstyle is pretty.
Oh, really? Thank you.
Ms. Kim, this way.
Oh, okay.
Would you like to sit over there?
I've printed the translated
version in advance.
It's best to review it
before the Chief Editor arrives.
Oh, okay.
Please check off any parts
you have questions about.
Oh, okay.
JULLY LITERATURE RADIO
Would you like some coffee?
Oh, okay.
"Oh, okay."
Can you please stop that?
You told me to be careful about security.
I'll get you an iced Americano.
But...
are you always going to
talk to me so formally?
But you are older.
Well, when you talk to me like that...
it makes me feel like
I'm so much older.
Why? I like it.
No, it's just that...
if you like it, you can call me that.
Please excuse me.
On the titles, later this week...
I will organize my thoughts
and provide feedback again.
Yes, if you email me your opinion,
I will review it.
But, Shin PD.
There's something I'm curious about.
- If you just check that part...
- So...
what did you like about me?
- You, Yu-mi?
- Yeah.
What did you like about me?
Well, of course...
I like your concise
and simple writing style.
I'm sorry, I took the wrong one.
A concise writing style.
We're at work.
Let's talk later.
Tell me now.
I'm curious.
Why do you like me?
Yu-mi?
Because you're pretty.
Because I'm pretty?
Hello.
Pretty?
Am I especially pretty today?
When dating someone from MZ Generation
everything is unexpected.
What time do you get off work?
Let's have dinner.
2026 JULLY PUBLISHING
READING CULTURE FESTIVAL
I can't do dinner.
Today is my laundry and cleaning day.
What?
Do you have to do them today?
Yes.
Wednesday is my chore day.
I mean...
Hey, Housekeeping Cell.
Do you understand what he's saying?
He must be out of his mind.
That guy who's out of his mind
is Yu-mi's boyfriend!
Is their routine more important
than dating for Generation MZ?
They just started dating a few days ago.
Yu-mi.
Come over at 9 o'clock.
Where to?
My place.
I'll have it all clean, so come over.
Teacher!
Soon-rok asked her to come over.
Wait a minute.
He asked her to come over today?
This is moving way too fast.
That... that's...
What chapter was it?
Visiting his house is Chapter 13.
Just a moment. Hold on.
Well... the progress...
How far have we gotten?
Linking arms, holding hands
arm around the waist, hugging
and the first kiss.
We did it all on the first day.
That's right.
We've mastered up to Chapter Five.
Oh, right.
Sir! If we skip from 5 to 13
when do we do Chapters 6 to 12?
Sir! The book's order is all messed up.
Sir! How far are we going today?
Stop, stop!
Be quiet!
Wait.
Rational!
- Change the textbook!
- Huh?
It's so outdated!
This is totally unrealistic.
Is that okay with you?
It seems too late.
Tomorrow's a holiday.
Let's hang out.
Hang out? Doing what?
Dating someone from Generation MZ
is so unpredictable.
Can I really go to his place?
Shin PD, here are the documents
you asked for.
- Yu-mi.
- Soon-rok, I'm here.
Come in.
You didn't have to get anything.
Of course. It's my first time here.
- Your place is nice.
- This way.
What's this?
Ta-da.
Do you remember this?
You know how to play games now.
- Yeah.
- It's more fun with two people.
Hold on. I'll change the settings.
So you wanted to play games?
What?
It's nothing.
Can I look around your place?
Of course.
Be careful.
Playing games, reading comics
and working out at home.
So that's why you're a homebody.
I'm busy all night.
But what's this?
Why haven't you opened it?
What is it?
Oh, that?
It's a rare Superman item.
I haven't even opened it
because I'm afraid I'll break it.
Do you want to see it?
Oh, no.
It's okay if you want to see it.
No. I'm scared I'll break it.
- It's really okay.
- Come to think of it...
you're like Superman.
- Me?
- Yeah.
Superman wears glasses
and a suit to work.
All serious and stern.
But when he takes off his glasses,
the female character can't recognize him.
My first impression of you was
that you were very serious and stern.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
But on the train
without your glasses and smiling
you looked so different.
- Yu-mi
- Yes?
Then, as you said
I'll throw away
all the glasses I have at home.
Hey! No, that's not it.
It's because it's a twist.
You wear glasses at work.
So with glasses, you're Kent Clark
and when you take them off,
you're Superman.
So I'm dating Superman.
But Superman's name
isn't Kent Clark, it's Clark Kent.
It's Kent Clark.
It's Clark Kent.
I'm the one who bought this.
Oh, Soon-rok.
It's Kent Clark.
- Want to make a bet?
- Fine, sure.
Do what you want. You can flick my
forehead or something.
- No going easy.
- Of course not.
Okay.
Jeez.
Here.
It's Clark Kent.
I was right, wasn't I?
Come here.
A bet is a bet.
Wait...
Hold on...
Present your forehead.
So cute.
Did it hurt?
- It hurt, right? Hit me back.
- No, it's okay.
- It's okay, really.
- No, it's fine.
- Really. Just hit me once.
- It's okay. It was a bet.
It's okay. Give me a good one.
Go ahead and hit me... Ugh!
- Let's play the game, Soon-rok.
- Okay, but...
Yeah, let's play a round.
- You hit me too hard...
- That's the one from before, right?
Virtual reality.
Yu-mi, let's stop playing the game
- and go see a movie instead.
-A movie?
Did you book movie tickets?
Did you think we were
just going to play games?
Let's go.
- Okay.
- Hurry.
Since you're such a big Superman fan
it's the original version.
Really? Where is it playing?
Let's see.
Row J, seats six and seven.
Oh, this is the theater?
Huh? Here it is.
Yu-mi, over here.
So this is how you have fun at home.
Goodness, this is a tough vibe to match.
Just play along.
Our boyfriend is from Generation MZ.
What are you doing? Over here.
But...
there's no one else in the theater.
I rented out the whole place.
This whole place?
Renting a theater
is nothing...
for me.
Is this a "rich family's
youngest son" concept?
And compared to that,
you're a poor writer.
For me to fall for you
and even rent a theater...
is just ridiculous.
What on earth...
about you made me like this?
Well, it must be my pretty face.
You're not wrong.
I think the ice cream delivery is here.
Oh, ice cream.
Ta-da!
Why is there so much?
They're all different flavors.
Twelve flavors.
But isn't this too much?
I ordered extra
since you were coming.
I was worried it wouldn't be enough.
I'm just worried you spent too much money.
It's okay. Let's eat before it melts.
This isn't the kind of ice cream
you can get just anywhere.
Especially...
in the middle of a mountain like this.
Wolves might be drawn by the smell.
Let's finish it all.
Soon-rok.
I lose all track of time
when I'm with you.
Did you hear that?
Yeah.
- I think it came from over there.
- You're right.
Who would've known
that Shin PD was this kind of person.
He's cute.
Soon-rok.
Where'd he go?
Who is it?
Delivery.
Soon-rok?
What was that?
This is your house.
Why did you ring the doorbell?
Soon-rok?
What are you talking about?
I'm here...
to deliver the waffles.
A deliveryman this time?
Don't you think leftover ice cream
would go well with the waffles?
Good idea. Thank you for the delivery.
So how should I pay?
With a kiss?
What?
You're really addicted to role-playing.
You should've been the writer, not me.
Just a moment.
Thanks.
I'm sorry, Master.
I dozed off...
and didn't realize you called.
When did I call you?
I didn't ask for you.
No.
You did.
I have restored all
of Master's health and mana.
This looks delicious.
I'm full, but since we're eating,
let's finish it.
One moment.
TONGUE CELL
Don't be so nervous.
Not at all. I'm always ready.
There's no need to be nervous.
It's not your first time.
Of course. But today's mission
could be a very long one.
The kiss is always ready.
The hard part...
- Yeah.
- It's all about timing.
Gosh, you should have called.
No, I'll go now.
I'll be right there.
Yeah, I'm in the neighborhood.
At a book cafe.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Where are you going?
I'm so sorry.
My parents are at my place.
Right... right now?
Yeah, they showed up unannounced.
They said they're just
dropping off kimchi.
I should go.
That's my dad's car.
I see.
It's better if I go from here.
Okay.
Get home safe.
- I'll call you.
- Okay.
- I'll get going.
- Bye.
Go.
Bye.
Yu-mi's gone now.
I wanted to hang out with her all night.
WRITER KIM YU-MI
Yu-mi.
What are you doing? Were you asleep?
No.
My parents just left
after dropping off kimchi.
I see.
Want to come over?
If you're tired, we meet tomorrow.
I'm on my way.
I'll be right there.
But then I remembered
I forgot the carrots.
So I called my mom to ask if she
really needed the carrots
but she insisted that she needed them
and told me to buy them.
So, what could I do?
The moment she finishes her sentence
I'll jump into the empty space.
So I went, and what?
The supermarket was closing.
They wouldn't let me in.
So I begged and pleaded...
The problem is that's still one sentence.
I rushed in, saying sorry
and quickly grabbed the carrots.
This isn't working. Let's cut her off.
There's no other way but to interrupt her.
What if we interrupt the conversation
and initiate an emergency kiss?
My mom was buying carrots.
She said I was the one to buy them...
No. It's too risky.
The distance is too great.
We could break
the wine glass.
- Did you know?
- What?
Most of my missions are adventures.
Tasting to see if it's salty...
Damn, it's so salty.
Checking the battery's charge
is also an adventure.
That's so absurd, right?
So I said to my mom, "Mom, no..."
I'm afraid of adventure...
but no one can do this but me!
How many people in the world would know
what kind of person Soon-rok really is?
YUMI'S CELLS 3
You said you wanted to go to Kyoto, right?
Did you see who just walked by?
Hello, Yu-mi?
Don't you think
we should tell the Chief Editor?
Soon-rok's principles are his identity.
A fist-sized face!
Skin as fair as snow!
I object to this!
- Let go!
- Watch out!
I can wait.
The reason love is always surprising
is because no two loves are ever the same.