(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
The birds are flying…
Ho-jin, glad you're here.
Ah, he's been drowning in his sorrows.
There.
Hey.
Let's go, okay?
Oh, Ho-jin.
You're crying in public.
It's embarrassing, okay?
Let's go. Get up.
Listen, she said
I broke up with her first,
but that's not entirely true.
That's not what happened.
She said I don't remember,
but I'm telling you,
I never did anything like that. I swear.
I know. Let's just go.
Tell me about it on the way home.
Come on. Get up.
Why would she say something
like that to me?
I'm losing it! What should I do?
Keep walking. Walk straight.
- Okay, sure.
- This way.
One, two…
My life just goes on
Hey.
You feel better? I'll drive you home.
- Take this.
- No.
Um… I don't want it.
Ji-sun would come
and get me whenever I got drunk.
What?
Mm-hmm. When my heart is broken,
I share my pain
and my sadness with everyone.
That makes you feel better?
Mm.
Yeah, when I express my feelings,
I always feel better, you know?
But people like you hold back
and just act like it's all good.
You try to fix it by yourself.
I just don't get it, man.
That's true.
I deal with it my way.
Why would I burden someone
with my emotions?
I don't understand you. You're so cold.
I'm just hiding my feelings.
Doesn't mean I don't have them at all.
It's easier to deal with them alone.
You're posting on Instagram?
Make sure the sponsored watch brand
is really visible.
Hey, listen, Mu-hee.
Nanami reached out to us earlier.
Her and Hiro just arrived in Seoul.
All right.
He has a gig in Seoul or something?
She asked if you were free by any chance.
Maybe he wants to meet up with you?
With me? Why?
You two were on the same plane.
Did something happen on that flight?
Oh.
We did see each other.
I was kind of in my own world.
I fell asleep after my glass of wine.
Maybe you have offended him
without realizing it?
You've been going crazy
over Ho-jin lately.
Seems like you're just losing it.
That's true.
I did act a bit crazy recently,
but it's all over now.
Well, if it's over, maybe you can stop
posting this depressing stuff?
These raindrops and black clouds,
you know?
I know you hope Ho-jin's gonna see it,
but I doubt he spends his time
on social media.
Hmm.
So, did
you talk?
I know you and Ho-jin have become friends.
No.
We haven't seen each other.
But sometimes, we just text.
What kind of texts?
Ah, you know…
Hey, wait, wait.
You can't just take my phone!
How do you know my password?
What?
You're moving in?
With him?
He's got a huge house, so I'm moving in.
We arranged it when we were in Canada.
I told him about my lease,
and he said I could move in.
It's for a few months
until I get myself settled.
Why wouldn't you tell me about this?
I didn't tell you
because I knew you'd react like this.
You would interrogate me
and ask me about him, what he's like.
We'll be shooting again soon.
You'll see him every day.
How can you work together
if you act like this?
I'm going to tonight's concert alone.
Don't come with me.
What?
It's a gig, and the concert
is sponsored by a client.
You'll meet with the agency staff as well.
You said I wasn't supposed
to interrogate you.
So leave before I cut your head off.
Fine, just go alone, then.
But at least message me later.
Now I feel like I'm lying outside
in the rain.
It would be nice and warm in his arms.
We can put things back together.
So Do Ra-mi was wrong, and you were right?
No.
I was wrong.
Run away!
Do Ra-mi was wrong.
It's my fault I ran away.
Hey, cut it out already.
I'm gonna get out of here. You'll see.
You hear me? You ran away on your own,
and you know that!
Hey, where are you?
You're running late?
Young-hwan and his publisher are here.
Sorry, I can't make it.
What?
You planned this whole thing.
You begged me to come because you said
you wanted to clear your head, dude.
You told me you need
to apologize to Young-hwan,
so you invited him and Mr. Oh.
Now what? You're bailing?
You're not coming now?
I'm at the airport.
I'm going to Santiago.
What?
Ji-sun was right.
I'm the one who broke up first.
JIN-SUK &amp; JI-SUN
OUR STORY WILL BEGIN
UNDER THE CLEAR SKIES OF JEJU
You got exactly what you wanted
for the wedding invitations.
Do we need to do anything else?
We'll do whatever you want.
Just tell me, okay?
It's happening super fast,
and I won't be able
to do things the way I want.
Ji-sun, you keep bringing it up,
and you insist we do it soon.
Yeah, even though I don't know
if we'll be able to pull it off?
Let's just… get it over with.
If we don't do it now, we never will.
Both of us will get cold feet.
Babe, why do you… wanna do this?
Hmm? You said you wanted to get married.
I'm acting like a coward.
I'm embarrassed.
So, I, um…
I just need time alone
to think about what I did.
Have a safe flight.
Stop crying in bars, okay?
Stop drinking too much, Jin-suk.
Noted.
Ho-jin, dear, my wise little brother,
you better take your own advice.
My own advice?
What's up with that record?
I saw you staring at it all sad.
See ya.
I hope your trip sucks.
Oh…
- Good evening.
- Hello.
- Goodness, how are you? It's been so long.
- How are you?
Good, very good!
Kim Yong-u couldn't make it?
Something came up.
Oh.
The Italian ambassador is at the concert.
Would you like to say hello afterwards?
- Yeah, that's an honor.
- Ah, great. I'll arrange the meeting.
Thanks. Perfect.
Ho-jin, we have a situation.
Could you please help us out?
Sure. What is it?
Don't. I invited him here as a guest.
It'd be impolite to ask.
We don't have an interpreter,
so I'm unable to greet the theater staff.
They'll arrive soon enough.
- They're at Chungmu-ro.
- How far can it be?
Chungmu-ro is over an hour away!
You've been the ambassador for how long?
Yet you still don't know Seoul geography?
Isn't there anyone from the embassy
who can interpret for you?
I don't think they'll make it in time
with the traffic and all.
Uh…
Then would you like me to help?
That'd be lovely.
That would be fantastic.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
I prepared some opening remarks
for the concert.
Could you just help with those?
I'll just let the people I came with know,
and then I'll get ready.
Of course. Thanks a lot.
You're a lifesaver. Thank you.
Do you often come to the concerts?
I like them, but no. Do you?
This is my first one.
I'm starting to lose it.
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
Guess he's not coming.
Oh.
- Bravo!
- Amazing!
The ambassador's wife is a fan of yours.
When we're introduced…
Yes?
…there'll be an interpreter with us?
Yes, he'll be there.
They're waiting.
Hello, thanks for waiting.
Here is Ms. Cha Mu-hee.
"It's very nice to meet you.
Thank you for coming."
"We're big fans of Do Ra-mi."
Thank you so much for inviting me.
Mu-hee, you seem very tired.
It's okay. You don't have to come
to the embassy event.
The ambassador's wife invited you,
but it's fine.
Was this a different translator, this guy?
Sorry?
The interpreter
at the beginning of the event.
Um, it was a different person, right?
Oh, I wouldn't know, Mu-hee.
Was I just imagining that too?
Joo Ho-jin, where are you?
Are we still going to your house?
I had a call.
I couldn't get there on time.
Can you catch a ride
and come to my house with the CEO?
The CEO already left, so I'm stranded.
Wait. Just wait where you are.
The elevator's here.
I gotta go.
- Oh, Mu-hee, wait.
- Going down.
The door is closing.
Uh, get home safely!
Which floor are you going to?
Uh, I'm going… to the ground floor, sir.
- Thank you so much.
- All right, then.
You're Cha Mu-hee, right?
- Do I know you?
- Well, you're famous.
So I know who you are.
Ah.
And I was sitting
right next to you, Mu-hee. One seat over.
There was an empty seat in between.
- Ah, there was.
- Yes.
I hope you don't mind,
but I overheard you.
You're absolutely right.
It wasn't the same interpreter.
Oh?
I know the person
who was interpreting at the start.
The seat that was in between us?
That was supposed to be his seat.
He's someone I know well.
Door opening.
That's my friend right there.
Joo Ho-jin.
Glad you're here.
There were four of us
who were going to have dinner,
but two of them canceled.
Uh, I hope you'll join us
and fill an empty seat.
- You're welcome to stay.
- Ah, that's very nice of you.
But the owner of the house
hasn't invited me.
That doesn't matter.
This house almost belongs to me.
On paper, it's his.
But my guests are his guests.
Uh…
Because I'm starving,
I'll accept the free meal.
Terrific.
Don't mind the guy.
He's quiet, and he cooks well.
Think of him as a housekeeper.
Make yourself at home.
This place is a museum. You'll see. Yeah!
The first owner,
the person who decorated and built this,
traveled all around the world,
buying old art, antiques,
collecting porcelain.
Even old records.
You see the vinyls over there, Mu-hee?
This place needs to be showcased.
People would pay to visit it.
Oh, so I guess that was
Ho-jin's grandfather, am I right?
Yes! So, you knew that?
Have you been here before?
Oh.
Just briefly. Once.
Ah!
Then feel free
to relax and enjoy yourself.
Hey, my friend.
You going to start prepping?
Ms. Cha Mu-hee, what food do you like?
I like most kinds of food, actually.
But especially spicy food.
Spicy food?
You heard her.
What's spicy on the menu for tonight?
Jin-suk made the selection,
and he hates spices.
Really? Whatever.
Stir-fried octopus, then,
or braised monkfish.
- Mu-hee, sounds good?
- Very good. Thanks.
So be the chef.
I can't.
I don't have any monkfish or octopus.
- Cod, then.
- Sorry.
- Squid?
- Nope.
Blue crab?
- Can't make what I don't have.
- You do! Your fridge is always stocked.
You'll make spicy stir-fried squid.
That sounds good?
Stir-fried squid's great.
Very spicy.
He's a… good cook and a great guy.
- Of course.
- I see.
You know everything about him already.
You two are a match, I'd say.
- Excuse me. Sorry, one moment.
- Yes.
Yes. Hello, Mr. Oh?
Listen to me!
You can't come here! Turn around!
But I'm almost there,
and I have the team leader too.
You told me to come.
I know, I know,
but you can't come tonight!
Joo Ho-jin, may I do anything?
Should I cut this round thing?
Sit down, since you're Mr. Kim's friend.
Why did you come here, anyway?
Because my new friend invited me
for a meal together.
I'm super hungry.
Well then, you're super hungry
and want some food, okay.
I fail to see why you'd come
unless you're absolutely starving.
Oh wow!
What is this?
Oh! Smells so good.
It's broth with seaweed.
It hasn't boiled yet.
That's what it is.
So it's just like us.
We're broth with only seaweed in it.
Nothing's even begun.
Just please go sit in my living room.
It's too uncomfortable having you here.
You're not heating it?
It has to cool down first.
I'm using it as seasoning.
Um, look, Joo Ho-jin.
I know that
I took sips of broth
with nothing except seaweed in it.
It was me who turned off the heat.
Could we maybe have the water boil
instead of letting it cool?
It's a waste to stop
just after a little taste.
I think it's a shame.
I turned off the heat at the right time,
and it's cooling nicely.
No waste or shame. It is what it is.
It's just water with kelp to add flavor.
It'll be fine.
It's more than flavored water.
Okay?
I made a move by kissing you.
I was gonna fry that mushroom.
Should I try contacting Ms. Cha Mu-hee?
No. There's no need.
Once she finds out I'm in Seoul,
she'll get in touch.
Why not just reach out to her first?
You did come all this way to see her.
Nanami, I didn't come here
to meet that zombie.
I came to take photographs.
Look.
Aren't the fall night lights beautiful?
You can take pictures of fall scenery
anywhere in Japan.
It's different.
The cityscape is completely different.
- You can see it through the camera.
- Sure.
So you won't meet Ms. Cha Mu-hee
before you leave?
If she contacts me,
I guess I could see her while I'm here.
Mmm!
Spicy and absolutely delicious!
You're a great chef!
You should compete on a cooking show!
I went with him and his family
on that trip to Canada when he was young.
Mm. You've known each other for decades?
We're family.
You went to visit that park again?
The same one?
- It's where the shoot took place.
- Nice.
It was where we saw that double rainbow.
That waterfall.
I tried to find it… but couldn't.
That's too bad!
It was a special waterfall.
It's just a waterfall
for you and me, Ho-jin.
The waterfall water feels
so nice and cool.
Our little waterfall we saw
was pretty special too.
That wasn't a waterfall.
We agreed it was a beautiful waterfall.
I'm no longer in the mood
to go along with it.
You just keep on insisting
it was a waterfall, Mu-hee.
By the way,
you were at the concert.
Did you take the gig on purpose
because you knew I'd be there?
Why do you think that?
Why would I take on an assignment
knowing you'd be there?
You have done so before to meet me again.
The answer's no.
Then why didn't you sit down?
I didn't want you to be uncomfortable.
But why would you let Yong-u
move in with you?
I have to come here if Yong-u's here.
You've never been to his though.
That's what he said at least.
So you'd have no reason
to show up here either.
Very true.
That's fine.
You thought you could just come here,
assuming all that with such confidence?
I feel confident
'cause I wanna get you back.
I should
probably step back,
but instead,
I let this crazy demon take over.
She's controlling you!
So I just…
I got my hopes up
because of what you… said on that day.
You said you'd cross the tracks for me.
And I know…
That was a waterfall. I believe it!
Wow! Everyone needs to go
at least once in their lifetime.
Oh. We have though.
When that drone fell into a ravine,
we went to go get it.
Oh, that's right.
That wasn't fun.
I swore I'd never go there again.
- It looks amazing like that.
- Yeah, I know.
It's because it's a rom-com at a distance
and a tragedy from up close.
Am I right?
The real tragedy is the footage
we haven't been able to get to yet.
We've so much to do,
but my eyeballs wanna pop out.
Don't cry like a baby. I see a tear!
Yong-u, thank you so much
for bringing snacks.
And Mu-hee is fabulous, so don't worry!
Thank you. Good luck.
- I'll put these away.
- It's fine.
- Thanks.
Leave the macarons for Shin Ji-sun.
She loves those.
It'll be an all-nighter again, right?
That's true.
Ji-sun will have more time
starting tomorrow.
Her fiancé went to Spain.
Spain? He's a writer, isn't he?
Yes, he posted on Instagram
that he's going to Santiago, Spain.
I wish I could be there.
We'll be in Italy soon.
It's a work trip.
You think we'll have fun?
NA JIN-SUK
#SPAIN #SANTIAGO #CAMINO
Mm.
Thank you for your payment.
Print receipt.
You may now proceed.
Your transaction has been approved.
Please take all your belongings.
Wow. She's making her way around town.
Thank you.
- To Yeonnam-dong, please.
- Of course.
Yes, hello?
I stopped by the editing room.
All good.
- The producers loved the coverage…
- Yong-u!
…they got of Mu-hee.
- The Canadian clips look great.
- Hey, my bag! Yong-u!
Italy's a different vibe than Canada,
so I'm looking forward to it.
They'll get fun footage for sure.
Hey, sorry.
I was on the phone with my CEO.
I couldn't hear you.
Thanks.
Is that your work outfit?
I mean this one.
Are you going to change
before going back into the editing room?
Sorry. I wasn't implying
you're cheating on him.
Well, these work shoes are comfortable.
Ah! One is for editing.
The other is for cheating.
Your plate must be full, working two jobs.
Did you hurt yourself?
An anterior talofibular ligament injury.
Anterior fibular what?
I was an athlete. I know injuries.
I'll wrap it up with tape.
If you let me.
- Are you okay?
- What?
Oh.
I thought I was fine,
but it hurts a bit
when I put weight on it.
Let me see.
Oh.
- Does that hurt?
- It does.
An anterior talofibular ligament injury.
Is that something serious?
It's a fancy way of saying
you twisted your ankle.
I knew you'd limp to work if you had to.
Which sport did you do
when you were an athlete?
I was a shooter.
For how long?
Until I started military service.
Then I got injured.
When I finished my service,
my mom's brother gave me a job.
Your mom's brother hired you?
That means the CEO of your company is--
Yes. He's my uncle on my mom's side.
Which makes you a nepo baby.
That makes sense.
I wondered why such a newbie
was working with Cha Mu-hee.
They put me to work right away.
Mu-hee was a nobody when we started.
Whenever she got a "no" after an audition,
I was always there to comfort her.
I'm sorry.
I take back my insults
and the other thing.
Then… take back what you said
about cheating.
I wish you hadn't told me anything.
Now I think about it when I see you.
You kept me company tonight
so I wouldn't have an affair?
And used my injury as an excuse?
Kinda.
Because I knew you were very hurt today.
But I'd rather be left in the dark.
So Jin-suk left, right?
You said you wanted to have an affair
so you'd never go back with him.
If you still have feelings for him,
just go to the airport and stop him.
You're so out of it. You lost your bag,
and you twisted your ankle.
Do you really want a meaningless affair?
You'll be alone
in an editing room all night.
It's so pathetic.
You're that worried for me, Yong-u?
Help me, then. That would be nice.
I know you like me a lot.
You've been hanging around,
hoping for a chance, right?
Do you wanna go for it?
All right.
What if I agree to help? What's next?
I'm a joke to you, is that it?
Shin Ji-sun, you're no joke.
I don't believe this is who you are.
Why not?
Before shooting,
you have to aim at the target.
And you have to really want it.
I'm going to aim and hit it
because if I miss, I'll get shot.
But you,
you're just not putting your heart in it.
That's why you won't pull the trigger.
Because you're doubting it, Ji-sun.
Thanks for your help, Yong-u.
You've pulled the trigger.
Should I contact Ms. Cha?
Don't.
No matter what, don't contact her first!
I'm not meeting that zombie
until she asks to see me.
Sure.
Cha Mu-hee.
Why isn't she calling me?
After what she did to me
on the plane that day…
You seem okay.
Hiro, it's too cold out.
Shall we eat too?
It'd warm us up.
No, thanks.
Ms. Cha Mu-hee
has not reached out.
Let's go back to the hotel.
TO CEO OH SEONG-CHEOL
TO CHA MU-HEE,
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL WOMAN IN THE UNIVERSE
Hmm.
Here. Hmm.
I'll bring you Do Ra-mi merch and sign it
next time I see you, okay?
That would be great, my dear.
This is my latest book.
Thank you very much.
It's funny,
I never had a chance to meet a novelist.
You have met a novelist.
And there's another one.
What? Really?
Joo Ho-jin, you have written a novel?
Just one. I wrote a book in college.
It won a literary prize,
and it was even on the bestseller list.
I'd like to buy a copy of it.
Tell me the title?
- It's been out of print for years already.
- I have some at work.
You can come over to my writing studio.
I'll give you one.
Thank you, Mr. Kim.
I'd love to post a picture
of your autographed book.
Great! I'd be grateful.
I'll follow you on Instagram.
We should follow each other.
I was told if we follow each other,
your public profile might get chaotic,
and I wouldn't do that to you.
Oh, is that so? Hmm.
Then why do you and Ho-jin
follow each other?
But we don't follow each other.
Well, he follows you.
Tell her.
You've been following her.
- Uh…
- I saw it when I checked out your account.
So, uh… So you have…
You've been following me.
It was… the bet, you know?
I followed you
'cause we made a bet back then.
You see?
Oh, I see.
But I didn't know.
Really? You had no idea?
I have many followers on my socials.
Oh! You got buried, Ho-jin!
She had no idea!
It's just… I'm really sorry.
I should have followed back
because of the bet we made.
Well, we can't right now.
We don't have to.
- I don't need you to follow me.
- She offered. Just say yes. Accept.
That's it!
Are you finished?
If your tea cups are empty, you can go.
No, I still have some in my cup.
Here, Mu-hee, have another sip.
Sorry, but it's very late already.
Is it?
Oh, what time is it?
My favorite TV show is about to start.
Love At First Sight.
Let's watch it, then. I'm a fan too.
Great, let's do it.
I usually watch it by myself
and bawl my eyes out.
- Yeah, me too.
- We'll bawl while watching it together.
- Yep, let's do it!
- Great!
Oh, wait. I'm gonna need my glasses.
I think they're on your backseat.
Hmm.
Seems like you're having fun.
It's time to go home, Young-hwan.
Is it?
Well, I'm here already.
I might as well get going.
Now go back inside.
Don't leave Mu-hee by herself.
I get it. Stop.
At the concert, you bailed on us.
Your seat was empty.
You tried to avoid her?
Do you think she's that difficult?
You told me before that everyone on Earth
speaks their own language.
Mm-hmm.
And I am having a hard time
understanding her language.
I thought she was interested,
then she pushed me away.
I thought she rejected me,
so I avoided her.
And now she's here, acting like this.
Is she interested again,
or does she feel bad about what she did?
It's impossible to tell.
I don't wanna go back inside.
What do I say? I'm not sure.
It must be frustrating
not being able to understand her.
I see.
But are you just gonna give up now
because you don't understand her?
You're an interpreter.
It's an unfamiliar language.
You should probably just try to learn it.
The order of the words…
if she uses an exclamation point
or question mark.
All those things are different
from the way you speak.
Look for the deeper meaning
and translate it.
Do your best.
Good luck, my friend.
The moon is shining bright
So softly through your eyes
We're dancing on the clouds
Don't know how to waltz
Your lovely gentle smile
Feels like a glass of wine
I see the dreams you hold inside
So don't let your heart run away
Farewell to loneliness
In every single night
Want you to know
Can't get you off my mind…
The weather is great.
This song is perfect.
Your lovely gentle smile
Feels like a glass of wine
I see the dreams you hold inside
So don't let your heart run away
Farewell to loneliness
In every single night
Want you to know
Can't get you off my mind
Your lovely tender smile
Keeps running through my mind
How would you know
If I could be the one?
So please come closer
We're dancing on the clouds
Don't know how to
Waltz
Hi there. Everything all right?
I'm heading out. Thank you.
Where's Mr. Kim?
He had to go.
I didn't even say goodbye. I wish I had.
The food was yummy.
Really, it was so delicious.
Well, I'll go now.
Wait a minute.
Let me tell you something.
What are you hiding?
What is that?
That.
The book? It's what your friend
gave me earlier. That's all.
- There's something suspicious.
- What? These belong to me.
You're acting weird
and obviously hiding that.
- Show me.
- No.
What's that?
Wow!
Okay, I guess you must have X-ray vision.
How'd you know I stole it?
It was obvious by how you moved.
Look at that. I got it back.
You really have a knack for…
driving me completely insane.
Give it back to me
unless you wanna call the cops on me
'cause I just wanna leave.
What are you doing?
I bought it for you.
As a gift, when we were in Canada.
I didn't have a chance to give it to you.
Though it's no excuse for stealing it.
Well, thank you.
For the food, company, and gift.
Thank you for everything you've given me.
I won't forget it.
I'll repay you! Next time,
I'll buy you dinner and bring you a gift.
The next time?
Yong-u!
You said he was going to live here.
At the housewarming.
I can bring good food,
drinks, and a gift just for you.
See you next time, then.
Next time.
She forgot to take this.
I took the sleeve,
but I forgot the record.
I'm so stupid.
PAPAGO♥
The record's still here.
You only took the sleeve.
Are you gonna steal it next time?
I'm sorry. I forgot to take it
because I was in a rush.
This might be hard to believe,
but I didn't mean to leave it with you.
Are you close by?
Well, I'm… kinda far away already.
Wait outside of your place.
I'll drive over to you.
What? Huh?
You're coming?
Yeah. Yeah, just text me your address.
I'll be there soon.
Okay.
If it's a pain,
you don't need to come over now.
I'm already in the car. Should I get out?
No, don't. You're in the car,
you might just as well.
I'll be there soon.
The birds are flying
I heard it in the sky
Something they want to imply
I greet the breeze
And nod to the trees
I heard the winds reply
A thousand languages
Start to whisper around my world
One quiet voice answers them
In gentle word
Stuck in my throat
Round and round
I wanna speak out
But no one's there
Echoes of my voice
Answer alone
Tell me the truth
What don't I see?
Stuck in my thoughts
I walk till I fade
I feel the love in the morning sun
But why am I blue…
Mu-hee.
Your family is here.
PAPAGO♥
Your call cannot be completed.
You will be forwarded to voicemail
and charged after the beep.
Your call cannot be completed.
You will be forwarded to voicemail
and charged after the beep.
JOO HO-JIN
Hey, Ho-jin.
Hey, Yong-u, I couldn't reach you.
Uh, things have been busy,
and my phone died.
Have you been calling? Sorry, man.
Cha Mu-hee is not picking up either.
What if something happened?
You can't reach Mu-hee?
She's here at a photoshoot, getting ready.
- What?
- She's in hair and makeup.
Want to talk to her?
No, thanks. I'm just calling to check in.
Hey, did you see the article
that came out today?
It's a… touchy issue.
That's why she's not picking up right now.
Don't worry about her.
She's okay. She's gonna be fine, you know?
Okay.
PAPAGO♥
The company knows
things are bad with your family.
Why did they publish this?
The journalists went to my uncle's house
since I'm still registered at his address.
They went there,
thinking they'd see my parents.
They say you were born
with a silver spoon in your mouth.
There's no problem with that these days.
Your fans still love you.
They'll love you even more now.
I guess.
It's a relief.
Hmm.
Hey, Ho-jin called me.
He was worried.
He said he couldn't reach you today.
Were you supposed to see each other?
We were supposed to.
But we're not meeting.
I stood him up and didn't call.
You have no idea at all?
No memory of what happened
to your parents?
Are you sure, sweetie?
Stop smiling!
You're repulsive.
That's me.
It was my birthday.
The house I lived in.
The flowers I had on the balcony.
And my sweet chicks.
Dad visited for the first time in a while.
He had a birthday present for me.
- Mu-hee!
- Oh, Daddy's here!
Happy birthday to you!
- Thank you for the teddy bear!
- Happy birthday to you!
- I love it!
- Here you go!
You're the best, Dad!
Teddy bear, eat up.
You're so cute.
Mom?
This serves you right, you liar.
Your little scheme.
You lied and pretended
you don't remember a thing,
but now you're scared they'll find out.
You were so uneasy
when people started loving you.
Must be wrong, you thought.
And you were sure it wouldn't last.
It's because you're so broken.
That's why I'm here.
Do Ra-mi's the one that everyone loves.
Ms. Cha Mu-hee, are you ready?
Yeah.
She still hasn't
reached out. What should I do?
Just call her and set up a meeting.
I debated leaving,
but I'm just too curious.
- I'm curious too.
- About what?
What happened between you
and Ms. Cha Mu-hee on the plane?
This will do, I guess.
What are you watching?
The Do Ra-mi movie. I wanna add clips
in between shots of Mu-hee.
Have a pleasant evening.
Like that one.
I watched it before, but it's so scary.
Freaks me out.
A zombie killer. Terrifying.
So scary.
She kills a bunch of people in it.
Actually, Do Ra-mi herself
only kills one person.
It's the man she loved.
Young-hwan?
Are you here?
Uh, ma'am?
Today isn't our cleaning day.
Hello?
Cha Mu-hee?
Why are you here?
If I tell you to wait for me, Ho-jin,
you should do as you're told
and wait in the exact place I choose.
I've no idea what you're up to this time,
and I'm tired.
'Cause I'm not in the mood
to accommodate you.
Get out.
Awesome. So you still care.
Yesterday, I was only a thief.
What am I now?
Please tell me.
Are you sick or something?
You're polite again, I see.
That wasn't being polite.
It's who you are. You're kind,
which is why she likes you.
"I felt like I might die
if someone was kind to me."
"It felt like kindness might kill me."
I'm not like that.
I enjoy…
killing people.
Just tell me what you want.
Who are you?
Well, today I am…
Do Ra-mi.
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
I wanna switch off my head for a while
You're always saying too much
Can't you just dial it down?
I wanna shut down my POV for a while
Your shadow lingers too close
I can't take it now
Let me sink in my quiet melancholy
Sometimes it's fine
To lean into the lonely
Perfect light, perfect stage
Oh, please, turn on the lights for me
I'll be dancing alone
Dance! Feel alive!
I would dive into the dark
I love to be alone, so leave me alone
Dance! Feel the vibe!
I might be a narcissist
I love to be alone
Just leave me alone
Dance alone, I'm dancing alone
Dance alone, don't ring the alarm
Somebody to love
Somebody to hurt
I'm exhausted by all of them
Where should I go
Well, don't give a "uh"
Lately, I don't overthink for myself
I'm growing up
But why can't I get used to this
Like adolescence
It's getting tough
So I gave up on this early
Just leave me alone
Dance! Feel alive!
I would dive into the dark
I love to be alone, so leave me alone
Dance! Feel the vibe!
I might be a narcissist
I love to be alone
Just leave me alone
Dance alone, I'm dancing alone