Why just the two of you?
Where is Jinzhao?
Sister said she had no appetite,
so she won't come over for dinner these two days.
Well...
In the future,
it will get hot day by day.
Or else,
from tomorrow on,
I have the maids in the kitchen deliver the meals
to each room,
so that you won't have to run around in the hot weather.
Well...
Yesterday, the Vice Crown Seneschal
Mr. Mu came looking for me
and asked about you.
Me?
Why did he ask about me?
His words were somewhat vague,
but I heard the meaning.
He wanted to propose marriage to his eldest son.
The eldest son of Mr. Mu...
Mu Zhidi.
In my opinion,
this is a good marriage.
The Mu family is a household steeped in literary tradition.
Mr. Mu is a Hanlin Academy alumnus
and currently serves as Fourth-Rank Vice Crown Seneschal.
As a minister of the heir apparent,
he has a boundless future ahead.
Father...
I really don't want to marry Mr. Mu.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with the Mu family?
It was Mu Zhidi.
Have you seen Mu Zhidi?
Not really.
Does he have any defects?
No.
He was ugly.
You didn't know
that
he is almost like a pillar.
If I marry him,
I will be laughed at by others.
Like a pillar?
Listen to yourself,
what you said is too childish.
That Mu Zhidi is the eldest son.
Logically speaking, it was you who got the upper hand.
However, they
care not whether one is born of the legal wife or a concubine.
Why do you still dislike
someone who is not good-looking.
That's really not good.
I really don't want to marry him.
Shut up.
Don't say such words
that judge people by their appearance anymore.
You are simply ill-mannered.
A great marriage relies on
parental command and
matchmaker's arrangement.
There's no place for you to speak.
You
only care about family background,
and never care about appearance or character.
Mother,
can you
help me?
I really don't want to marry
that Mu Zhidi.
Actually, I told your father
about this,
and let him listen to your opinion.
But
he still refused and
let me not interfere in this matter.
Mother,
I beg you,
please help me talk about it again.
But your father won't say yes.
But you're the mistress of the house.
No matter what,
I grew up in front of you.
You can't just ignore, mother.
I beg you, mother.
Please help me talk again.
Miss Gu,
Madam Ji is weak.
Can't stand you like this.
Mother, I beg you.
I...
I can't help you either.
Miss Gu,
you go back first.
I know that
you just hold a grudge against my mother.
That's why you didn't help me on purpose.
What are you talking about?
Madam Ji is tired.
Please go back first.
Don't touch me.
Lan...
Do you...
Do you still want to stop me?
Get out of the way.
Mother,
I...
Lan...
Nanny Zhou is dead.
What should I do in the future?
Lan...
They said that after sending her to the village,
she passed away in the middle of the night.
Madam Ji ordered that
don't give funeral expenses and
throw her into mass graves.
Lan,
what should I do?
She is Nanny Zhou.
Mother,
stop crying.
I'll go to find the chief steward tomorrow.
Let them buy a coffin
to Nanny Zhou.
Can they listen to you?
They came to tell you.
Just want you to
beg them with the money.
Right, right, right.
You are smart.
But Lan,
you came to me so late.
Has anyone bullied you?
Bully?
I won't let them bully me.
They thought they
wanted to control me
with my marriage.
Don't even think!
Madam Ji Is making a fuss about
your marriage.
What is she trying to do?
She can't do anything.
Mother,
before Nanny Zhou came to village,
she told me one thing.
She said that
as long as this matter is uncovered...
Right,
there's something about it.
You have to tell your mother.
What's the matter? Tell me.
Do you still remember Madam Yun?
Madam Yun?
You mean Yunxiang?
Madam Ji, please have a tea.
Of course I remember her.
She is the Madam Ji's dowry maid.
Madam Ji married her to your father
as a housemaid.
At seven months pregnant,
she ingested oxytocin by mistake.
One corpse, two lives.
But why did Nanny Zhou
tell you about this?
Yuping, who served Yunxiang.
back then, told her
it was Madam Ji who killed Yunxiang.
What?
I decided.
I want to find Yuping.
Then,
I can uncover what happened back then,
so that father and Madam
will have a fight.
There will be a mess in the family.
They won't have time to take care of
my marriage.
And
once my father knows
the truth of that year,
he will hate Madam Ji.
In that time,
he might
remember your goodness.
Let's go back to the old days.
Right.
Lan,
You're right, Lan.
Right.
Thank you, Mr. Chen.
Thank you for your support for our temple over the years.
You're welcome.
This is all
what I should have done.
But...
Amitabha.
I'll leave first.
OK, please.
Qingpu,
there's a sachet seller in front,
so you pick a few more for me.
Okay.
How are the matters
at your home going?
You want to persuade
your parents to divorce.
I know
it is not a good reputation.
But
is fame more important than life?
Things have come to
this point.
My father still
still took Madam Song's side.
It's so sad.
Would your mother want to divorce?
She was unwilling.
I really don't know what the
hell she was worried about.
Someone may be for fame,
but our Ji family will not.
If my mother
can divorce and go back to Tongzhou,
my grandmother
certainly won't make her difficult.
It's too late to feel sorry for her.
Or maybe
your mother did not want to make
Mrs. Ji feel distressed.
Is that the case?
I guessed randomly too.
But,
many people are soft on the outside and strong on the inside.
The don't want to show
their bad side
to their relatives.
But I'm afraid her body won't
be able to endure it.
The doctor said that she had
been ill for a long time.
Because rhubarb was
found in the medicine.
Because she's worried too much.
Depression leads to illness.
What happened in this house
is more complicated and dangerous than doing business.
Forget it, forget it.
Why am I telling you all this?
Why can't you say?
Because you're a man.
These disputes,
you men
don't understand.
Why don't men understand?
Because you men
are the reason for these disputes.
Not only the source,
but also the prize.
You think,
Song and my mother
had no grudge or enmity.
They're fighting to
the death now,
because they were
married to my father.
Okay.
May I show you somewhere?
This place is really nice.
Every time I encounter trouble,
I'll always come here
and stay for a while.
You say that
the clutter of things in the house
is not conducive to your mother resting her body and mind.
You can bring her
here and stay for a while.
You can also watch the mountains and listen to the springs every day.
No outsiders to disturb.
Perhaps after relaxing for a while,
her mind will change.
That's a good idea.
But I'm worried that if mother
knows this is your house,
she will be uneasy.
Makes sense.
Then don't you say it's mine.
Just say
it's your friend's.
Good.
Then I won't be polite to you.
Get up.
You're welcome.
His courtyard is near
Baoxiang Temple.
And it is
elegant and quiet.
Surrounding scenery is
good.
It was just right for you to recover from your illness.
That would be too much trouble for others.
No.
He's a friend of my brother.
He heard you are ill.
Just take the initiative
and let you live in.
Right...
Okay.
Let's leave in two days.
Good.
Nanny and Molan are also going.
That's good.
I will go too.
Then we have to pack up quickly.
It is cold in the mountains.
You have to bring warm clothes
and
what mother loves to eat.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go too.
No one said they would take you there.
He is just like Cao Cao,
and he can catch up with all kinds of good things.
Yes.
Everyone.
You see.
Yuping.
Long time no see,
Madam Song.
Do you know what to say
after seeing the master later?
What else could there be?
Just tell the truth.
The tea is a little cold,
so change the pot.
Yes, master.
Why is it you?
Why can't it
be me?
Aren't you supposed to be grounded?
Who let you out?
Lan?
No.
It was me who secretly
dressed up as a Nanny and
sneaked out.
If there is not one
important matter that I need
to talk to you face to face,
I don't need to be so anxious.
What's going on?
Master,
do you still remember Yunxiang?
Why do you suddenly think of her?
You're the one who hates her most.
I naturally hated her back then.
You love her so much.
I'm not a god.
How can I not be jealous?
What's to be jealous of?
She didn't have any children.
Her blessing
is much thinner than you.
Okay.
Don't say this.
It
makes me feel uncomfortable.
What's going on?
Ziling is Lan's servant girl.
Her sister got married a few days ago,
so she went back.
She just happened to meet the girl
who once served Yunxiang.
I wonder if you still remember
Yuping,
she had talked to
Ziling a lot.
What did she say?
She said she knew who changed
Yunping's medicine back then.
It killed Yunxiang and her child.
One corpse, two lives.
Yuping.
Master.
She was Yuping
who was waiting beside Yunxiang back then.
Yunxiang was born prematurely that year.
You knew
that it was because she had
taken the decoction of oxytosis,
but
at that time,
medicines for stabilizing the fetus and decoctions of oxytosis
were kept in two cabinets.
How could Cuiping
be confused?
At that time,
apart from Cuiping and me,
the only one who will go to Yunxiang's kitchen
is
Madam Ji.
She is concerned about  Yunxiang's diet
and often going to check how she is eating.
Sometimes she goes in for a long time
and never comes out.
Cuiping's elder brother, who
is away from home, is ill.
It is Yunxiang paid for the treatment.
Cuiping was loyal to
Yunxiang.
She won't harm Yunxiang.
Since you can't make mistakes with decoctions
and it wasn't Cuiping who deliberately
confused.
Then
It is only
Madam Ji changed it.
This is
a good choice.
Good.
Mother, you are too biased.
You always help Jinzhao.
Then I'll help you next time.
But that's what you said last time.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Father.
Master.
Why did you come suddenly?
What a bummer.
Master.
Something happened?
I ask you.
Yunxiang died of dystocia in that year.
Is it because of you
change her medicine?
What did you say?
I...
How?
How do you bring this up?
Yuping is here.
Yuping?
You can't even forget her, can you?
You pointed her to Yunxiang.
Of course I remember.
She's my personal maid.
What's wrong?
Yuping said
it was you back then
secretly replaced
Yunxiang's fetal medicine and oxytocin decoction
which caused her sudden premature birth,
blood collapse and death.
I still remember
that year,
you see me in harmony with Miaohua,
so you deliberately married Yunxiang to me.
Yunxiang is a good person,
gentle and honest,
and I also accept your kindness.
Unexpectedly,
you actually have a heart of fear towards
Yunxiang.
One corpse, two lives. Ji Han!
I...
At least,
she served you once.
How can you
doing such a vicious thing to her?
Master,
that's not true.
I haven't harmed Yunxiang, I haven't.
This is a slander.
She is also your personal maid.
Why should she slander you?
Where's Yuping?
You call her over.
I confronted her face to face.
What's there to confront?
She has been dead
for many years.
All the evidence has long vanished.
Naturally, you wouldn't admit it.
Which murderer would admit
to killing someone.
Then you decide I'm the murderer.
And you don't think about that
Yuping has been gone for so many years
and how did she come back at this time?
And who told her to come back?
Right.
Who brought her back?
Who?
I don't have to hide it from you.
It was Madam Song who found her.
Qingpu.
Hurry up and find
Yuping.
She must be quite old,
around thirty,
who worked as mother's personal maid.
She shouldn't be in the house now.
But find her anyway.
Bring her here.
Okay.
Song Miaohua again.
What are you laughing at?
I laugh at you.
You believe
Song Miaohua's words.
She just put rhubarb in
my medicine.
She wants me to die,
and you believe her words.
These are two different things.
Yes.
Song might not be nice to you,
but Yuping's words
may not be false.
You've always disliked Yunxiang,
when Rong was born,
it was always brought by Yunxiang.
You see Rong
was very close to Yunxiang
and was unhappy,
so you punished her
to go to the kitchen.
It took months to get her back.
Then you asked Yuping to raise Rong.
Do you recognize what I said?
As...
As a mother,
of course I don't want my children
to be closer to others.
At that time,
Jinzhao was not with me.
I only have Rong by my side.
I...
I certainly don't want my children
to be closer to others.
What's not understandable about this?
What happened afterwards?
You married Yunxiang to me.
But after she became pregnant,
you become jealous again.
Every time I go with her.
You have to make an excuse to call me away,
one moment saying that you are sick,
the other moment saying that Rong is sick.
I...
Because
Yunxiang's father and mother
are still in the Ji family,
you warn her to stay in her place.
Don't keep haunting me.
You think I don't know.
But it is obviously...
I get it.
Fundamentally,
it's not because of Yuping's words.
It wasn't because of Yuping's words
that you doubted me.
No wonder since then
you start to distance yourself from me.
Originally in your heart,
you have long decided
I'm the murderer of Yunxiang.
Act.
You keep acting.
There is no excuse for adding guilt.
Mother,
what you said
is nothing more than
Yuping's words.
Otherwise,
it's all about
the past.
Now that you has decided
that it was my mother who harmed someone,
then I will ask you to show the evidence.
Evidence?
Even if there is evidence,
could I still be able to
send her to court
for questioning?
That's
why she's so confident.
Besides,
about Yunxiang's death,
your mother is the one
who benefits the most.
What evidence do you need?
According to the master
who benefits the most now?
It's Song.
Then I can also conclude
it was Song who found Yuping
deliberately frame my mother.
You...
You just don't know what it means?
Mother.
Miss Gu.
How's it going?
No messages.
When I got to the front yard yesterday,
Yuping has been gone for
a quarter of an hour.
I dare not go out at night.
Early this morning,
Mr. Luo sent people out to search for.
We must find her.
Otherwise,
even if mother arrived at Shuntian Prefecture,
she still couldn't explain it clearly.
I'll go out and look for it later.
Miss Gu.
Slow down.
Miss Gu,
your mother said at dawn
that she was going to see Madam Song.
Nanny Zhao couldn't stop her
and had already gone with her.
Thinking of what you said,
I have to tell you about everything.
You're doing the right thing.
I'll be right there.
Miss Gu.
Where's my mother?
Inside. Don't let me in.
I've always felt that I treat you well.
Where are you dissatisfied?
It has come to the point
where you have to kill me.
You put rhubarb in my medicine,
and instructed Yuping to
frame me.
I didn't frame you.
So do you really think
I was the one who harmed Yunxiang?
If I'm really jealous,
I should have framed you.
How could it be Yunxiang's turn?
That's because you married Yunxiang to
master.
In the beginning, you wanted to take away master's affection for me,
so you married your personal maidservant
to the master.
But you didn't expect
that she was more favored than I was.
And she was pregnant.
Everyone in this house said
she is pregnant with a boy.
Master was very happy
and visited her every day.
How could you not hate being tricked
by your own person?
Besides...
Besides what?
Besides,
I guess you can see it.
Master really likes Yunxiang.
Doesn't he really like you too?
Maybe.
But I'll always remember that day.
I told him
in order to marry him,
I have written a blood letter
and cut off contact with my parents.
But guess what he said?
He was in a hurry.
He said he was going to send me back.
He said that I had caused him to
offend a high-ranking official
of the fourth rank.
But I can't go back.
I can never go back.
I'll tell him that
I'm pregnant too.
He just gave up.
Do you think
this is genuine affection?
Right.
He also told me
if he hadn't
been desperate
and need the help of the Ji family,
he won't marry you either.
After I was kicked out of my parents' home,
I became a dispensable person.
But Yunxiang is different,
the way the master looked at her
is different from looking at us.
That's really like, right?
Jinzhao,
I'm looking for my mother.
Wait a minute.
Do you know where Yuping is?
Yuping?
Who is Yuping?
Your mother last night
brought
a maidservant named Yuping
into the house
and went to see the master together.
Now Madam Song is grounded,
and Nanny Zhou died too.
You are the only one
who can help her.
Are you sure that
you really don't know anything?
So what if I know?
Yes,
I found Yuping.
But so what?
What's done in secret
will come to light.
Do you know
what you're talking about?
You let me go.
Speak out.
Why did you frame Madam Ji?
I didn't frame her.
Yuping said it clearly.
In those days,
Madam Ji Is jealous of Yunxiang,
so she deliberately changed the medicine
and caused the death of Yunxiang and her child.
Do you dare to go to Shuntian Prefecture
and say the same thing?
I dare.
Even when I arrived at the Imperial Main Hall,
I would say the same.
I didn't frame Madam Ji.
She did it herself.
She...
You said she
Who is she?
Why don't you call her mother now?
She was the one who didn't treat me like a daughter.
Back then, the master wanted to marry
you to the Liu family.
She asked everywhere in a hurry.
For fear that others will pick on you.
Rong doesn't want to study,
so she begged the master
to let him learn how to do business.
Only me.
I begged her...
begged her not to marry me to Mu Zhidi.
I begged her on my knees.
Did she pay any attention to me?
Did she ask anyone about the Mu family?
Not at all.
Because of this,
you go and find Yuping?
When a court convicts someone,
it still needs all the witnesses and physical evidence.
Why did you
convict her on
one person's words?
You said that Madam Ji didn't treat
you as her own daughter.
Have you ever,
truly, treated her as your mother?
Anyway, I have a clear conscience.
Since you have a clear conscience,
then you tell me
where's Yuping?
I want to confront her face to face.
I don't know where she is?
She said that she exposed Madam Ji,
she would surely be retaliated against
and dared not return to the original place.
I don't know where she is?
Mother,
what did you and
Madam Song say?
It was some
personal affairs at home.
You, a girl who is not married,
there's no need to know this.
You've been busy for half a day,
haven't eaten yet?
I won't keep you.
Mother,
anyway,
I'm all your daughter.
You can tell me
anything you have.
No need to avoid.
Madam Ji.
I'll go and call the doctor right now.
No need.
I've been wanting to cough just now.
I felt a little better
after spitting out a mouthful of blood.
But...
Go grind ink for me.
Quickly.
Yes.
Now you and I
hold different hearts,
unable to share one mind.
We choose to part amicably,
each returning to our own way.
Master,
someone who served Madam Ji
sent a letter.
Put it there.
Master.
Get out.
You guys go out.
Yes. Yes.
You coughed on purpose to show me.
Do you have anything to do with me?
What does this mean?
Of course I want to divorce you.
I think your intention wasn't
to divorce me.
You are trying to use it as an excuse,
and use it to threaten me.
Do you want me to apologize to you?
That's what you think.
Look.
You looked aggrieved again.
You always do this.
It was the same way back then.
I didn't want to marry Miaohua,
but you advised me
and said you agreed to let her marry me.
Yunxiang too.
I never mentioned.
It's all up to you.
You let her marry me.
Each time,
you're the one
who got the reputation of virtue first,
then became the
one who is wronged.
You've got all the benefits.
That year,
you went to the Song family for a banquet
and were caught
having an affair with Song Miaohua.
To cover up for you,
I had no choice but to agree to her marrying you.
As for Yunxiang,
you've been interested in her.
You two keep exchanging glances.
Can't I see?
I don't want a scandal at home,
only then did I agree Yunxiang to marry you.
I've done
so much.
In your heart,
I just want
a virtuous reputation.
Well, what else?
I've been alienating you all these years.
Except because of Yunxiang's death,
it's also
your own temperament.
Obviously you are a jealous woman,
but you
pretend to be very virtuous.
You...
You what?
You still have the guts to call me.
The inner quarters are in utter turmoil;
the children are ignorant and idle.
As a mistress,
had you been even halfway competent,
I won't blame you.
Our love as a husband and wife is over.
To tell you the truth,
actually, several times
I have even written a letter of repudiation.
But in the end,
I burned them all.
It's not for you,
but for children's
future marriage.
As long as you understand a bit of reason,
don't bring up divorce again
in the future.