(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
ALL FIGURES,
INCIDENTS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS,
AND OTHERS ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
WERE FILMED SAFELY
IN ACCORDANCE WITH GUIDELINES.
What in the world
do you think you've been up to?
Why keep doing something unnecessary?
An attorney proved her client's innocence.
What's the problem?
All the animals
that escaped the lab because of you
were their research subjects.
They even claimed damages against us.
I did it to catch the murderer.
You're not a prosecutor.
What's with you lately?
First, you hand over
evidence against us to the police
and then, you sue an artist
of our partnered client.
Why do you keep blowing things
out of proportion?
I couldn't turn a blind eye to those
who obviously committed crimes.
There's a limit to my patience
as a partner attorney.
Am I even a partner attorney to you?
What?
If you took me for a partner attorney,
you'd hear my side of the story first
instead of accusing me.
Your side of the story? I can already tell
you're messing things up everywhere.
I'm a managing partner of Taebaek.
It's my job to discipline attorneys
who can't get their act together.
Exactly.
You're only doing your job,
so why do I sense personal feelings?
When did I do that?
This time again,
you'll be given the kind of punishment
you deserve. End of discussion.
No.
I quit.
I'll compensate you
for the damages in a week.
Are you saying you'll leave Taebaek?
Who says you can?
Me.
You're the one who wanted to join Taebaek.
That's right.
But without the Chairman,
Taebaek isn't Taebaek anymore.
I give her an inch,
and she tries to take a mile.
TAEBAEK LAW FIRM
PARTNER LAWYER HAN NA-HYUN
Welcome.
I'm sorry for entering without permission.
Don't be. I know you've come a long way.
A long way?
No one can see you,
and you don't remember a thing.
It must've been so lonely to be invisible.
I'm not quite following--
I understand how flustered you are.
Let me explain it one after another.
- Have a seat.
- What…
I-rang, what's up?
- Hi, Bong-su.
- Hi.
- Hello.
What the?
You can see him too?
Yes.
Liar.
I know you can't.
- Ouch! What…
- Goodness.
- W-Who are you?
- Why did you hit me?
I'm the new security here!
I'm sorry!
A-Are you okay? Sorry about this.
What are you doing? Carrying fire
in one hand and water in the other?
I-I mistook you for a ghost.
I'm truly sorry.
Does my face look like a ghost?
What in the world… I've had enough!
Wait…
I-rang, why did you have to do that?
I don't see any.
S-See what?
I don't hear any, Bong-su.
I'm finally free from them!
Yes!
Hooray!
Hooray for I-rang's independence!
Ghosts aren't coming?
He says it's been more than two weeks now.
Maybe it was a temporary thing.
You must be happy, Mother.
You didn't show it,
but you were quite concerned.
Right.
I sure am glad to hear the news.
What did I-rang say?
He's cleaning
for his future living clients.
He's so excited.
What are you doing?
Do you want to play hide-and-seek?
Oh, my. That must be painful.
Come on, mister.
That's so distracting.
Will you stop already?
What the heck!
This can't be.
What is going on?
No.
There's no way I'm missing the ghosts.
Hey, Shin I-rang.
Pull yourself together.
You've finally been set free.
After how you left that day,
I felt a little sorry.
Attorneys don't always win their cases.
And mistakes are bound to be made.
I was too harsh on you.
Please don't bother.
I compensated the lab for the damages.
You've heard, right?
You didn't have to.
I only said that to tell you off.
Here.
What is this?
Traineeship overseas.
It may be called training,
but you can take a break to travel
and clear your head.
In New York.
Afterwards, return to Taebaek.
No, thank you.
Is it because I hurt your pride
the other day?
That's why I came all the way here.
Let it go now.
- I'm not going back.
- Okay, fine.
It wouldn't be you
if you didn't refuse three times.
I'll ask you three more times.
- Come back.
- I won't.
- No, no, no, I won't!
I'm not going back.
Okay?
Take this with you while you're at it.
Let's see how long you can last.
Hello, Mr. Choi.
Stop Han Na-hyun
from joining any law firm.
Call all the law firms out there.
If you have nowhere else to go,
you'll come back to me.
KIM AND JEONG LAW FIRM,
HWASEOL LAW FIRM,
BHN LAW FIRM,
YSP LAW FIRM, SP LAW FIRM
You used to work at Taebaek.
Taebaek certainly is
one of the top performing law firms.
However, I believe my convictions
align with your founding philosophy
of prioritizing basic ethics and values
and upholding social responsibility
rather than performance and profit,
which is why I've decided to apply.
…WE ARE INADEQUATE
TO EMBODY YOUR NOBLE ASPIRATIONS
They turned me down?
…WE ARE UNABLE TO MOVE
FORWARD WITH YOU THIS TIME
What?
…YOUR VISION DOES NOT ALIGN
WITH OUR CURRENT DIRECTION
Again?
Attorney Han Na-hyun, please come in.
LATERAL HIRING
ATTORNEY INTERVIEWS
INTERVIEW ROOM
Please have a seat.
Care to ask a question?
I don't have any questions for Mr. Shin.
What do you think you're doing?
JOB APPLICATION
NAME: HAN NA-HYUN
That's my question to ask.
What…
I'm turning you down.
I'm turning you down
because you're way below my level.
- I-rang.
- Yes?
Here's your utility bill.
Oh, thanks.
It's a lot.
Are you going somewhere fancy, Bong-su?
I'm starting a new gig today.
Really?
What's your role this time?
I told you about it before.
It's a paralegal.
Do you have many lines this time?
Goodness, how can you be this positive?
Aren't you worried at all?
Not even a rat walks into this office.
I am.
That's why I cleaned the whole place.
What's the use of cleaning?
It's in a remote area,
and it was a shaman's house for decades.
How will you possibly have
clients come here?
Not unless you advertise yourself.
Advertise?
Doesn't it cost a lot of money?
What are your business cards for?
There are clients
everywhere at the courthouse.
It'd be really worthwhile
to visit those going through a hard time.
You think?
It's my line in the show.
It might actually work for you
because you have an agreeable face.
Good luck! See you.
Well, he has a point.
Advertise…
INVOICE FOR DAMAGES
TOTAL: 521,500,000 WON
- SILVERWELL LABORATORY
- 521,500,000 WON
- MAY MAINTENANCE FEE
- 171,180 WON
- JUNE MAINTENANCE FEE
- 250,380 WON
CURRENT BALANCE: 4,305,110 WON
THIS IS GOOD DESIGN
YOUR BUSINESS CARDS
HAVE BEEN DELIVERED
ATTORNEY HAN NA-HYUN
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
Worthwhile, my butt.
It must be hard on you.
But you should stay strong
at a time like this.
I'm here to help you--
Not again.
Excuse me?
You're all talk
when you won't even take responsibility.
"We need more materials.
Bring me crucial evidence."
You shameless people make excuses
only to raise the legal fees.
- No, I--
- Now,
I hate you people
more than that jerk who cheated on me.
I even shudder in my sleep
at the thought of lawyers!
Why's she taking it out on me?
I didn't do anything.
Nothing's easy.
Dad!
Hi.
Don't waste your energy
on meaningless thoughts, I-rang.
Mr. Bae?
I-rang? Long time no see.
Did you have a trial?
You seem busy.
I'm so tired. I have way too much work.
I'm dying to rest.
What's that?
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
I have no work,
so I'm out to advertise myself.
Don't feel embarrassed.
That's how it is for solo attorneys.
Want a case?
What?
I'm supposed to take it on,
but I already have my hands full.
What is it about?
I'm a little busy right now.
Hear it from the client in person.
I'll tell them about you.
SEONGMYEONG CONSTRUCTION
YOON HYEON-SEOK
You're the best. Thanks.
Don't mention it.
I can do this much for you.
I better get going. Bye.
Okay. I'll repay you for this!
Treat me to a drink some time.
Hello. If you need an attorney…
Please give me a call.
MY FAMILY WON'T RETURN,
BUT JUSTICE MUST PREVAIL
You're doing well.
Are you sure?
Make sure you eat well.
I'll wait for your call.
Thank you.
Cheer up.
Attorney Han Na-hyun?
No, you got the wrong person.
I know it's you.
Fair skin and a small face.
It is you, Attorney Han Na-hyun.
No, I'm not.
What? Yes, you are.
Why is he following me?
Attorney Han, why are you here?
Why are you wearing sunglasses?
What's with those business cards?
Did you get fired?
It's not your business.
Come on. Don't be so cold.
We had such amazing teamwork
when we caught Gu Hyo-jung.
Don't even mention his name.
It pisses me off.
- This is so embarrassing.
- Attorney Han, are you okay? Are you hurt?
Can't you just pretend not to know me?
How can I possibly turn a blind eye
when you just tripped over?
Anyway, did you really get fired?
Both Su-jeong and Mr. Kim Tae-jun
were found not guilty.
Wasn't that a good thing for Taebaek?
This is all because of you.
Because of you, my cases were a mess.
Because of you,
a win didn't feel like a win,
and I even ended up resigning, but now,
I'm going nuts with so much to pay for.
So don't talk to me ever again, got it?
If you follow me again,
I'll call the police.
Wait.
You can call the police
or even sue me, so hold on.
Sit here for a sec.
Let go.
Let me. Geez.
It snapped off completely.
There's a skilled cobbler's shop nearby.
I'll get it repaired soon.
No, just give it to me.
You can't walk in this.
It'll take only ten minutes.
Wait here a little.
Okay?
What are they doing?
Excuse me.
Hello.
Who are you?
Didn't you talk to a woman
in front of the courthouse just now?
A tall woman with sunglasses on.
Oh, yes. I did.
Your conversation ended in the middle
because of me.
If you're looking to hire an attorney,
you should really give that woman
a chance with your case.
She's such a competent attorney, you see.
I didn't know she was an attorney.
Excuse me?
She said she had done
a solo protest at the same spot
about a wrongful car accident
during her second year in high school.
She also said I needed
to be in good shape to keep fighting,
and so I should eat well.
I've never heard such a thing
from a complete stranger before.
It was so warm.
Her 2nd year in high school
was 13 years ago.
That's 2012.
YEAR 2012,
CAR ACCIDENT, SOLO PROTEST
DUI FATALITY CASE'S VICTIM
CONTINUES A SOLO PROTEST
CAN A LIFE BE REPLACED AT
THE COST OF TWO YEARS IN PRISON?
VICTIM'S YOUNGER SISTER…
IRRESPONSIBLE DRUNK DRIVING,
"IS THE LAW
REALLY ON THE VICTIM'S SIDE?"
I get it now.
I get that you love money,
but you shouldn't make use of others.
Those people are already having it hard…
even if not for the likes of you.
Now what?
DAD
Hello?
Hi, Na-hyun.
You're busy, right? Let me make it quick.
Your birthday is coming next week,
so your mom wants to make you
a homemade birthday meal.
Can you come over?
That'd be too much of a hassle.
Let's just dine outside.
Oh, should we?
S-Sure, why not?
Let's dine out
and celebrate the happy day.
How about Japanese food?
It's your favorite. I'll book a table.
Okay.
Thanks, Dad.
No problem. Bye.
Hello?
Is this Attorney Han Na-hyun?
Word says you're an outstanding attorney.
Will you be able to help me?
Yes, of course.
Please text me your address.
I'll visit you right away.
All right.
I gave you a special cut.
Thank you as always.
No news about ghosts yet?
No.
Are you disappointed?
Excuse me?
I've read the faces of followers
for over 20 years.
I can easily tell if one is happy,
sad, relieved, or disappointed.
You're as sharp as a needle.
Is I-rang aware?
Of what?
That you visited the shaman
at Unit 501 of the Okcheon Building.
He doesn't know and it must stay that way.
- Take responsibility!
Take responsibility!
Punish the scammers!
- Punish them!
- Where did our money go?
- Compensate the victims!
- Compensate!
Make amends!
- Make amends!
Take responsibility and make amends!
Take responsibility!
- Take responsibility!
I'm just as troubled, you know.
Everyone can be happy
if we just build the apartment.
But the landowner is insisting
on not selling the land.
There's really nothing I can do.
Didn't you advertise
as if the land had already been purchased?
No, not at all.
Oh, you'll know
if you take a look at the contract.
TERMINATION OF THE CONTRACT
The terms here are difficult.
The sentences are complex too.
It's incomprehensible even for me.
That's what a contract is for.
You just have to prove my innocence
with this ambiguous contract.
Can you do it?
Hi, Mr. Bae.
I-rang, where are you right now?
Me? I'm at my sister's restaurant.
Why do you ask?
Thank goodness.
You haven't visited
Seongmyeong Construction yet, right?
Do not go whatsoever.
What?
I'm sorry, I-rang.
The client I set you up with
turns out to involve a construction gang.
What? A construction gang?
Hello, I'm calling
because Attorney Bae Il-do referred me--
He already gave you a call.
I'm calling
to recommend you
an outstanding attorney I know.
Shoot.
Mr. Bae, text me the address.
What?
Text me the address now!
Attorney Han went office-hunting
and handed out her business cards
at the courthouse.
It seems she'll open her own practice.
And this morning,
she took on her first case.
Her client is Seongmyeong Construction,
a shady company that runs
a pre-sale fraud scheme.
ATTORNEY HAN'S POTENTIAL CASE
After all that big talk,
this is the case she takes on?
Good going.
It seems dangerous. What should we do?
Nothing.
I'll take this chance
to watch her high ego snap.
It's going to be fun.
Wait.
Just keep tabs on her in secret.
Yes, sir.
What's taking you so long to answer?
I can't do it.
What? You can't?
You must be mistaken.
I'm saying I can't do it
with this much info.
What does that mean?
You're so lucky, sir.
I'm very experienced
in pre-construction sales cases.
Especially, this kind of scam…
I mean, business is my expertise
because I'm so used to it.
So?
The essential condition of winning a case
is information.
The more information you have,
the more backup plans you can have.
For example, a fabricated document
of the land purchase.
Or an agreement you got
through blackmailing allottees.
I need all kinds of materials.
There's no such thing.
We do everything by the law.
Sir, you shouldn't
underestimate the prosecution.
One search and seizure is enough
to find everything like dominoes.
Once they start tearing you apart,
you're finished.
Your attorney has to
fight the prosecution for you.
Of course, I need to know everything.
If you get raided,
it'll all go down the drain, I tell you.
You'll be sentenced
to at least five years in jail. Too bad.
Good thinking.
Where's the bathroom?
It's at the end of the hallway outside.
Oh!
A glass of iced Americano, please.
I'm a bit thirsty.
The hell are you saying?
What are you waiting for?
She wants an iced Americano.
Prosecutor Kim?
Hi, Na-hyun. Are you sick?
What happened to your voice?
I'm well, and I have a favor to ask.
Do you know Seongmyeong Construction?
It's under investigation lately.
Yes, it's a vicious pre-sale scammer.
We don't have enough evidence
to indict them.
I'll get you that evidence.
Come straight to the address I text you.
Send the nearby police first
since there's no time, okay?
SEONGMYEONG CONSTRUCTION
Apologies. I drank a lot yesterday.
This should be enough
to make you rot for at least ten years.
- Rot?
- In prison, of course.
What?
You preyed on people's lifelong dreams
of owning a home.
That deserves punishment.
But sir, you're really lucky
because I'm going to give you a chance.
Turn yourself in
and give the money back to the victims.
Are you out of your mind?
You've got some nerve, don't you?
Why don't I mince you to pieces?
What's that noise?
Oh, dear.
The police are already here.
You should've reflected
on yourself sooner.
You crazy bitch.
Attorney Han!
You little punks!
How did you know I was here?
Are you okay?
What about the police? Where are they?
T-The police? What police?
What's with you people?
How fast can you run 100 m?
Fifteen seconds.
Run.
Hurry!
Get them!
Stop right there!
You bastard, stop!
Where did they go? Boys!
Go this way! And you guys, go that way!
I'm sorry.
Don't talk to me. I'm out of breath.
I didn't know they were dangerous people.
You gave him my number?
You got fired because of me.
I had to do something.
Why did you come alone, though?
You should've come with the police.
You're right.
I rushed here in case you got hurt.
Are you hurt at all?
Are you worried about me?
Of course.
There they are! Over there!
Hurry up! They're over there.
Run! Hurry up.
- Hey!
- Stop right there!
Damn it, boys!
- Get in there!
- Open up!
- You bastard!
- Unlock this door now!
- This is not good at all.
- Hey!
Give me back the documents,
and I'll let you go peacefully.
- Open the doors!
- Documents?
What are those?
Evidence to put them in jail.
You mean, evidence to get us killed?
We're not going to die.
We'll turn this crisis
into an opportunity.
What makes you that confident?
What now?
- I have a good idea.
- What?
Don't you come close,
or I'll scatter these to the victims.
- Wait.
- No.
What? Are you scared?
Are you scared? Are you?
Is that it?
- Damn.
- She startled us all.
I knew something was off.
Attorney Shin.
What now?
You're good at fighting, right?
What?
Kill them.
- Geez.
- Hey, come over here.
Come here.
Bring it on!
Hey.
Let go of her!
Move! Out of the way.
Attorney Shin!
Freeze and get down!
- Arrest them.
- Yes, sir.
Get down.
- Hands above your heads.
- Stand up now.
- Stand up.
- I hear you, okay?
You too. Stand up. Come along.
Walk faster. Move.
Attorney Shin.
Are you okay?
Pull yourself together.
I'm… okay.
You're not okay.
You shouldn't have come here alone!
Are you hurt?
TAEBAEK
So what happened?
Even the prosecution swooped in.
All the related scammers were arrested.
Not that, I'm talking about Han Na-hyun.
Is Attorney Han okay?
She almost got hurt,
but Shin I-rang rescued her.
Shin I-rang? What did he do?
Well…
The gang surrounded Attorney Han
and things were about to get physical
when Shin I-rang threw himself--
That's enough.
You're dismissed.
That guy isn't particularly
a strong fighter,
but he tried his best
to protect Attorney Han…
Go back to work, I said.
Yes, sir.
OKCHEON BUILDING
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
Attorney Han?
What are you doing here?
I went to your office
and you weren't there.
Apparently, everyone in the neighborhood
knows you.
I've lived here for a long time.
I see.
So what brings you here?
I forgot that I had plans.
Plans?
I'm supposed to meet Je-hun at the
playground. He's from Class Flower Petal.
Out of the blue?
Good luck!
What?
Da-bong!
Is it okay to drink?
You have an injured arm.
I'll just have sips.
Shouldn't you go home early?
Your daughter must be waiting.
My daughter?
Oh, you mean Da-bong?
She's my niece.
My dear beloved niece.
Doesn't she look a lot like me?
As if.
She looked cute, keen, and smart.
You think?
I saw you hand out your business cards.
Didn't you get any clients?
No. Not even one.
Work for other clients, then.
Those special clients…
who are visible only to you.
I don't have such clients.
How unusual.
You said you could see ghosts
like it was a bad habit.
I can't
see them anymore.
I see.
Anyway, why did you come to see me?
To apologize.
Apologize?
Oh.
I'm the one who sent you there.
I owe you an apology.
Not for your injury.
I had job interviews
after resigning from Taebaek.
I saw a red X mark on my name.
When I saw it, it really offended me.
It sure was shitty
going through it myself.
Let me apologize.
I'm truly sorry. I mean it.
That's okay. It's all in the past now.
No.
You should never have
been mistreated like that.
You're not at fault.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't meaning
to talk about your father.
It's partly my fault.
I knew my dad was a corrupt prosecutor,
but I insisted on becoming an attorney.
Don't say that.
It's all right. That's the truth.
I actually did wonder
why you chose the same kind of job
as your father's
instead of an ordinary job.
Perhaps,
I believed in my dad
all along.
Dad!
I-rang.
Did you wait long?
Did the trial take long?
It took me quite some time to bring those
who harassed good people to justice.
I want to be like you when I grow up.
Will you?
Sure thing.
- You'll get to work in there later.
- Or maybe
I wanted to believe in him.
I knew I shouldn't have taken this path
but I couldn't give up…
like a fool.
I'm not sure how you'll take this…
but I understand you.
It was actually
my older sister's dream to be an attorney.
It's going to be real fun.
I'm telling you!
We gotta hurry there.
Okay, we're already on our way.
The light turned green.
- Slow down.
- What are you waiting for? Come on.
Na-hyun!
So-hyun.
So-hyun!
No… So-hyun!
I MUST WIN EVERY TIME!
HAN SO-HYUN
LAW AND POLITICS
After my sister died in an accident,
I decided to become an attorney.
She died because of me.
I shouldn't be chasing a dream of my own.
So since then,
I've been living the life of my sister.
That must be why
you didn't know when to stop.
Did I not?
I can't be so sure,
but your sister
was probably proud of you.
You're always diligent
and precise.
And you're so…
down to earth.
Not really.
But thanks.
I kind of get the reasons
behind how you've behaved too.
You…
wanted to be like your dad,
who was your childhood hero, didn't you?
I think you're on the right track.
I must say,
you also have a great way
of interpreting things.
Anyway, thanks.
Careful.
Be careful.
The guy from the chauffeur service
will be here soon, so wait a bit.
- Did you call for a driver?
- Yes.
Right here, sir.
- Could I play some music?
- Sure.
THE LATE HAN SO-HYUN
WE LOVE OUR BRIGHT
AND RIGHTEOUS SO-HYUN
NAME: SHIN I-RANG
She died because of me.
I shouldn't be chasing a dream of my own.
Attorney Han, we're here.
Let me.
Wait.
Attorney Han, we're at your house now.
Your shoes. Take off your shoes.
Careful.
Attorney Han, wake up.
Attorney Han.
If you wake up in the middle of the night,
make sure you go to your room.
And…
I'm truly sorry
that my ghost-seeing ability…
put you through so much.
I'll go now.
It's a shame…
you can't see…
I wish I could see…
my sister.
SO-HYUN AND NA-HYUN
ON JUNE 8, 1999
HAN SO-HYUN'S 19TH BIRTHDAY
ON JULY 7, 2012
I-rang, what are you doing here
instead of sleeping?
Nothing. I'm just sitting here.
You aren't just sitting here.
Something's going on.
What's troubling you?
You were excited about not seeing ghosts.
Bong-su.
The truth is,
I know how to see ghosts.
- What?
- But…
I was trying to not see them.
I know helping ghosts is a good deed,
but I couldn't ignore
my family's concerns.
And it was nice to be back
to my ordinary everyday life.
I also thought it was right
to let bygones be bygones.
But then,
I realized something.
It's a shame…
you can't see…
I failed to understand
the desperate longing
to see a beloved one
one last time.
To them,
it's never over for them.
It can never be bygones for them.
I love you.
I love you, Dad.
But I simply thought it was all over
and it was meant to be let go.
I thought you were finally
starting to breathe again,
but I see you've got
a lot on your mind.
So,
what do you want to do?
If this is my destiny,
I will…
accept that destiny.
SEOUL
Thank you, sir.
- Have a good night.
- Bye.
OKCHEON BUILDING
I'm ready.
My doors are open for anyone now.
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
SEOUL
NA-HYUN'S MOM
Hi, honey.
Honey, did you have dinner?
What time are you coming home today?
I'm just about to head home now.
I feel a little down today.
Why? Did something happen?
Do you remember
when we went to Seocho-dong
after what happened to So-hyun?
Of course, I remember.
There's no way I can forget it.
I'm in front of that building right now.
The shaman's house is gone.
It's a law office now.
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
Wow.
The stars are beautiful.
They really came.
Excuse me. Are you…
HAN SO-HYUN'S 19TH BIRTHDAY
ON JULY 7, 2012
That's enough!
If you're drunk, keep on walking.
How could you use violence
against students?
Three boys were ganging up on one kid.
That bastard who beat you up
got an attorney.
It'll take no time for her
to find out what you've done.
- Stop.
- I'm going to kill him.
He's a diligent kid that will be happy
if he can just get over this hump.
- I'm going to do something about it.
- I'll kill you for real.
Why would I die?
It's your turn to die.
Jun-ho!
Subtitle translation by: Eunjin Erica Kim