EPISODE 11
- You're getting off work late, huh?
- I have a shoot tomorrow.
So I wanted to get ready.
- Um, ma'am.
- What?
When do you have a moment?
Why do you ask?
It might be a good time
for some new headshots.
You've been getting
a lot of media coverage lately.
We could talk about that later. Not now.
- [alarm blaring]
- [device buzzes]
[Seol-ah] The exit code is different.
[beeping]
[buzzes]
[door unlocks]
[breathes heavily]
Seol-ah. Seol-ah!
We have to go.
Oh, yes. This is where it belongs.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
[line ringing]
Hey, when will you be wrapping up?
Well, you better hurry up.
We have to finish
before the police end up finding them.
Are you okay?
The things you were looking for,
were they in there?
Yes, they are.
Taemyung's art, the ones
Chair Kim swapped out,
and my dad's painting too.
Everything burned up,
every single photo included.
But my family's last memories
are still trapped in there
[sighs]
I will never forgive Chair Kim for this.
I promise I'll make her pay.
I'm with you
whatever you decide.
Have a good time.
[attendees chattering]
Everything's ready, right?
[chattering continues]
SEARCH AND SEIZURE WARRANT
ARREST WARRANT
"Untitled" by Lee Soo-dam.
Sold to a bidder in the room for $270,000.
Congratulations.
This unpublished major work
believed to be the last painting
completed by the late artist Song Hwan-ju,
estimated at over $4.6 million
is expected to surpass
their most famous work, Cheong-myeong.
However, today this artwork
will not be going up for auction.
[audience murmuring]
Because it's not an authentic piece!
This piece was consigned
through unofficial channels...
What's she saying?
...at the direction
of Royal Auction Chair Kim Sun-ae.
The piece was submitted for appraisal,
since I questioned its authenticity,
- and the analysis revealed...
- What is she doing?
- ...that the adhesive used...
- Hey.
- What the hell are you doing, Ms. Han?
- ...was an industrial synthetic resin
rather than the natural glue that
artist Song Hwan-ju insisted on using.
ART AUTHENTICATION REPORT: FORGERY
[sirens blaring]
[Seol-ah] Even the signature is different.
SIGNATURE COMPARISON ANALYSIS
FORGERY - GENUINE
The character for "Hwan" in his name
is written incorrectly,
using the "child" radical
instead of the correct "fire" radical.
[in Spanish] You idiot!
[Seol-ah, in English] Therefore,
the appraisal agency has determined
that this piece is clearly
a forged artwork.
Get her. Drag her down. Okay?
Yes, ma'am. That crazy little...
We have evidence that the works
the Taemyung Cultural Foundation recently
lost in the fire were also forgeries.
Hey! Drag her out!
[Mr. Song] Shit. No photos. No photos!
[Seol-ah] So, where is the real one then?
[audience gasps]
- No way.
- There's the real one.
[Seol-ah] As you can see, she moved them
to her secret storage vault.
Inside is her collection,
all of which was gathered
through embezzlement, theft, and swapping.
[screams]
[reporter 1] How did you get this footage?
[reporter 2] When did you start planning
to blow the whistle on her?
Ma'am!
Is there more evidence that
this was Chair Kim Sun-ae's doing?
Artist Han Jin-woo, who painted this work,
was once celebrated
as a genius in the art world,
then was reduced to a mere forger
by Chair Kim.
I'd like to take this opportunity
to restore the honor of the artist
who died under a cloud of disgrace.
Even at this very moment,
another forgery orchestrated by Chair Kim
is likely being created somewhere.
I therefore request that
the police investigate this thoroughly.
[dramatic music plays]
Hey, do you think people would actually
believe that doctored footage?
- [door opens]
- [people gasping]
Ms. Kim Sun-ae.
You're under arrest
for embezzlement and fraud,
and for violating
the Criminal Proceeds Act.
At least the police seem to believe it.
- Ma'am, ma'am...
- Let go.
I did nothing wrong. How dare you...
You guys are making a mistake!
[sighs]
What is all this?
[Eun-gyeom] Wow, is this supposed
to be an art gallery?
How much money did she pocket this way?
[Gong] We've secured
all the evidence from your office.
What?
Who do you people think you are,
going into my office, huh?
Don't touch anything!
Don't touch anything! It's all mine!
Do not touch anything.
- They're all mine! Don't touch anything.
- Come on!
Hey, Han Seol-ah!
Hey! Han Seol-ah!
Let go!
Han Seol-ah!
They'll install locking devices
and restrict access.
Since there are so many high-value works,
the vault will be sealed until they can
be moved to a separate location.
We need to cross-check the evidence that
you submitted.
Could you verify them
before the expert appraisal?
You won't find this painting on the list.
The original artist is Han Jin-woo.
He was my father.
It can be returned, right?
- Make sure Seol-ah can get it back.
- Okay.
[Woo-seok] What is this?
It hasn't been unwrapped yet.
[gasps]
The Stiller.
The painting worth over $10 million?
No way. She swapped this one too?
It's the authentic Stiller piece
from the exhibition hall.
Does that mean
she's making a forgery of this too?
[tense music plays]
- Woo-seok, wait.
- I'll call you.
[line ringing]
You're still at the auction house?
Do you have a minute?
Get everyone to leave the worksite.
[sighs] I'll do the cleanup.
Just leave now!
Do as I say, you idiots!
Shit.
[door opens]
The hell?
You guys still haven't left?
Who's there?
It's been a while, Ju Hyun-su.
[sighs] Shit...
You were the investigator
in the Taemyung case?
You can't run anymore, you bastard.
Get ready to rot in prison.
I can just burn everything
and I'll be fine.
Do you want to die too, you bastard?
Goddamn it...
You just confessed, didn't you?
- Shit...
- That you killed Woo-hee!
My life got screwed up
after meeting that bitch!
If I knew her brother was a cop,
I wouldn't have touched her.
Shut your mouth, you bastard!
[laughs] She was crazy about me.
She begged me to take her in that truck.
That girl was so starved for affection.
- [laughs]
- I said shut up, you son of a bitch!
[Woo-seok screams]
[grunts]
[shouting]
[breathes heavily]
Come here.
She was so young
but she didn't want to be a burden
to her big brother. Did you know that?
That bitch's death, it's all your fault.
No.
No! No! No!
No. You son of a bitch!
- Die, you bastard!
- [Seol-ah] Hey, grab him!
- [Gong] Woo-seok, stop!
- Die!
[Woo-seok shouting]
- Stop!
- [Gong] Stop! Stop it.
- Woo-seok, stop. Stop, that's enough.
- [Gong] Hey!
Please.
- Hey.
- [grunts]
[Gong] Come on!
[breathing heavily]
Hey, it's all over now.
You can relax.
[sobbing]
[gentle music plays]
It was me...
I'm the one who made Woo-hee like that.
It was me.
[sobbing continues]
You said the same thing to me too,
that it wasn't my fault.
And now, I'll return those words to you.
It's not your fault, Woo-seok.
You always did your best.
Let me say that back to you.
[Gong] Ah, geez.
[sighs]
[Woo-hee] Please don't get hurt.
You know you're all I have, brother.
[chuckles]
[Hyun-su] That bitch's death.
It's all your fault.
[sighs]
[Gong] Your name. I know it's Ju Hyun-su.
STATEMENT
Your date of birth.
Hey. Think you can pull
that right to remain silent crap? Geez.
[sighs]
- What the hell...
- This is the file on the Cha Woo-hee case.
I couldn't throw it away
for six whole years.
When Woo-seok was
practically spitting blood,
saying you killed his sister,
I laughed in his face.
I told him he was just being emotional.
You already killed someone once,
so you expect us to believe you now?
Start talking, you bastard!
How far did Chair Kim go?
You killed Paek Jun-beom, right?
No! I didn't kill Paek Jun-beom!
Then who did you kill?
Did you kill Cha Woo-hee?
Did you kill Kim Yun-ji?
[sighs] Shit...
What is all this?
I wanted to prepare you something.
Oh, no. I'm fine. Thanks.
I-I mean, it must be hard for you
to use fire.
It's an induction stove,
I think I can handle it.
[exhales heavily] But you don't have to.
- Uh... Should I wash this first?
- Uh...
Go inside and get some rest.
You've already been through a lot.
You know, I'm not very good at cooking.
Especially when someone is watching me.
[chuckles]
CARROT
GREEN ONION
ADD THE BEEF
I can't promise it'll taste good.
This was my first time making porridge.
I just thought it'd be easier to eat
than plain rice.
Thank you.
It looks great.
Delicious.
I often thought about the meal
you made for me.
After the police interrogation,
when I broke physically and mentally.
That warm bowl of rice you made
helped me get back on my feet again.
But you didn't wanna see me anymore.
I was afraid...
that something might happen to you
if you stayed by my side.
And how about now?
I'm still scared, even now.
But I... I will give it a try.
You are the one who taught me that.
You told me not to run away
or to push you away,
to stay by your side and keep you safe.
I think now I understand
about how you're feeling.
But
we have to keep going.
I cant promise that
things will get better,
because
we'll carry this pain
for the rest of our lives.
Let's get through it together.
[gulps]
Hurry up and eat.
It's really good.
[chuckles]
[sniffles]
We analyzed Chair Kim's computer
and found chats with Kim Yun-ji
on the company messenger.
I think you should take a look at them.
ASSOCIATE AUCTIONEER KIM YUN-JI
[Ms. Kim] The painting my father bought,
you personally brought it in
from New York, right?
[Chair Kim] Why do you ask?
[Ms. Kim] Isn't this
completely crossing the line?
I introduced that painting to my family
in good faith.
[Chair Kim] Come up. Let's talk in person.
[Ms. Kim] Funny, isn't it?
The head of the Tax Investigation Bureau
has a daughter who's an auctioneer,
yet there's a forgery in his house.
What kind of nonsense are you saying?
I had two outside appraisals done,
and the results are the same.
If my dad finds out,
what do you think will happen?
Are you threatening me right now?
I'm saying we should try to sort this out.
What is it you want?
The main auction podium.
[scoffs]
You want me to get rid of Ms. Han?
This must've put
a lot of pressure on Chair Kim.
She already had plenty to worry about.
I thought it could be a motive
for Kim Yun-ji's murder.
[Seong-il] Taemyung's paintings
that supposedly burned in the fire
were found in your secret vault,
and you know nothing about it?
My client was simply storing the paintings
at the customer's request.
This is a matter of Taemyung's negligence
and an insurance issue,
not a crime committed by my client.
Then let's talk about this.
That Stiller painting
worth over six million dollars.
You just happened to swoop in
when the owner died, didn't you?
[gulps, clears throat] The same goes here.
My client simply kept the artwork
in the vault
until the inheritance process
was finalized.
That's standard practice.
But then why did you make a forgery?
Why all that trouble?
Your lackey, Ju Hyun-su, has been caught.
[moody music plays]
There is no point in keeping this up,
Ms. Kim Sun-ae.
[sighs]
The way you speak
is very rude.
Mr. Detective, do you even have an idea
of who I am?
Well, the mistake's already been made
and can't be undone.
Whether your career as a cop goes down
a flower path or a thorny one
depends on this moment.
Can't you feel that?
You should be worrying about yourself.
Insurance fraud, embezzlement,
selling forgeries,
and even incitement to murder.
You have a lot of nerve, you know?
How ungrateful can you be
to stab Chair Kim in the back?
What exactly are you really after?
Are you trying to become CEO
while she's away?
That's probably what you are after.
Who do you think
you're slandering right now?
Hey.
You think I'm you?
I'm just doing what I can
to sort things out from my position.
I should own what I started.
[scoffs]
Fine.
I don't know how long it'll last,
but good luck.
Chair Kim will be out soon.
[Tae-seok sighs]
Our upcoming auctions will probably
fall through, won't they?
We've already had
this many client complaints.
Most are canceling consignments.
[grunts] So annoying.
[Seol-ah] Give me the list.
I'll call them myself
and try to convince them to stay.
Ms. Han, you came to work?
Are you all right?
I owe you all an apology.
I know better than anyone
how much you all love Royal Auction,
yet I caused all of this.
That's why I'm really sorry.
Gosh, no. You did the right thing.
Honestly, we all think it's for the best.
We were unknowingly participating
in Chair Kim's fraud,
so it's actually a relief.
Ma'am remember you put your trust in us...
[client 1] They talked about
forgeries and embezzlement,
how can I believe you?
So we will take full responsibility
for every--
Do you think I'd be okay with it?
Send my paintings back right now!
I promise that I will visit you--
I don't care about compensation.
I'm done doing business with you!
[line clicks]
- [knocks on door]
- [door opens]
Um, Ms. Han.
Artist Han Jin-woo, he's your, uh,
family, isn't he?
Mm-hmm. He's my father.
I had no idea you were going
through so much pain.
I'm sorry that I couldn't be there
for you more.
Thank you.
I really appreciate the warm welcome.
I thought I'd be chewed out.
It must've been so hard for you.
Things will get harder for all of us.
I'll do anything.
I'm ready for what's coming.
I thought only Cha Woo-seok was sincere,
but Han Seol-ah is sincere too.
[sighs] Yeesh, it makes my head spin.
I can't imagine
what would have happened to you...
I had to make him pay for what he did.
Captain's even angrier than I am.
I think he feels so guilty towards you.
[sighs]
Have that bastard and Chair Kim
confessed yet?
We will make them.
Do you actually think Chair Kim
killed someone over a painting?
So far, she's the suspect
with the clearest motive.
Even if she didn't do it herself,
she could have ordered Ju Hyun-su.
He was out of the country for a long time.
And why would Chair Kim
mess with Han Seol-ah's men?
You know, I still suspect Do Eun-hyuk,
but he has an alibi.
[tense music playing]
The CCTV footage shows that he was
at his studio in Cheongun
when Paek Jun-beom was killed.
Let me see that.
You know I can't show you official files.
Well, there were records seized
from Paek Jun-beom's house,
of him stalking Han Seol-ah, right?
Including the photos taken in Cheongun.
[sighs]
Could you, please?
[ominous music plays]
[Gong] The cell tower data shows that
Do Eun-hyuk was at his Cheongun studio
when Paek Jun-beom was killed.
Now, I understand why
you trusted Cha Woo-seok.
I never imagined someone
like Chair Kim could actually be arrested,
and that's not something
I could've helped with.
I figured that's why you joined
sides with Cha Woo-seok.
No, not really.
We both had things we had to do,
and somewhere along the way,
we ended up having the same purpose,
so we worked together.
So it's a special connection.
Could it be fate?
Tell me what do you think?
You have a good eye for people.
[gentle music playing]
[gulps, sighs]
He's a person who belongs
in the spotlight,
confident and straightforward.
I'm the opposite.
Because I belong in the background.
You see, I've been deliberately
ignoring this...
but now I see it clearly.
Why would you think that?
[sighs] People...
live according to what's ingrained
in them.
Anyway, you've done a lot to get this far.
Everything will be fine.
I hope you get
Mr. Han's painting back too.
I'm still on edge.
You know, Chair Kim isn't the type
to go down quietly.
Don't worry.
It'll all work out the way you want.
[ominous music plays]
[knocks on door]
Ms. Han, Chair Kim is here.
They think there's no risk of escape,
for health reasons.
It's always the same, you know?
Damn, are these guys for real?
She brought in a big law firm.
Looks like their strategy worked.
[liquid pouring]
- [footsteps approaching]
- [slurps]
Sit down.
What's been going through your head
all this time, huh?
Have you been living
with such determination
to avenge your father?
Well, I learned it all from you, ma'am.
[scoffs]
My father was a theater sign painter.
I used to help him with painting,
and then I became an apprentice
to become a real painter.
But while watching your dad there,
I realized...
[sighs]
"Even a genius like him
can starve in this business."
So you made him paint forgeries?
It was to help him make a living,
so your family wouldn't starve to death.
Hey, is it my fault that naive man
took out loans
just so he could pay it all back?
Do you really think that's, uh, an excuse
for causing his death?
Who caused his death?
That was his own choice.
I was the one who called 119
when your house caught fire.
It was me! I saved you!
You should've let me die back then!
I wouldn't have suffered like this.
Because I survived at the cost
of my parents' lives,
I had to wag my tail like a dog
in front of you
and smile until my mouth split.
Even if you get away this time,
I will hunt you down
to the ends of the Earth.
[scoffs]
What more can you do?
The prosecutors and judges
are on my side anyway.
You know, a dog might bite
its owner's hand once,
but after that,
all it gets is beaten to death.
So if I bite your neck,
it'll be the end of it.
[chuckles]
Do you think you'll even get the chance?
Your neck will be the one on the line.
[laughs]
I guess we'll just have to wait and see...
as to whose neck is on the line.
[tense music playing]
[screams]
[breathes heavily]
[line rings]
Ju Hyun-su is getting out soon.
Take care of that bastard quietly.
If you fail,
then that bitch is going
to learn the secret
that you fear more than your own death.
[line clicks]
BOOKKEEPING LEDGER
[soft guitar music playing]
[humming]
[singing in Spanish]
[singing continues]
NONGHYUP LIFE INSURANCE
[mysterious music playing]
[Woo-seok] Something's off.
Everything's too perfect.
[sighs]
Where are you going?
Chair Kim's office.
She called you?
No.
I'm going up to resign.
Until the last auction... [sighs]
...I wanted to take responsibility
for all the mess,
- but Chair Kim...
- She wouldn't leave you alone.
Let's go together. I'm quitting too.
I told you, you didn't have to do that.
I'd like to focus on my own work now.
And to get back in the water.
[elevator dings, door opens]
[record player scratching]
[gasps]
[screaming, gasping]
According to the security guard,
he heard music playing all night long.
Han Seol-ah and Do Eun-hyuk
were the first to find her.
- Any foul play?
- Nothing yet.
There's a suicide note on her laptop,
but that's not enough
to conclude it was suicide.
The CCTV around her office isn't working.
[scoffs]
She had to move the paintings
to her vault in secret.
[sighs] In the end,
even her death became a secret.
HAN SEOL-AH
[voicemail] The phone you are trying
to reach is turned off. You'll be direct--
[tires squealing]
[doorbell rings]
[sighs]
This isn't the ending
that I was hoping for.
Chair Kim would never kill herself.
When I met her the day before,
she still showed no guilt
and was completely confident.
It looked like someone
had gone through her office.
It's strange that
she wrote the suicide note on her laptop.
She's the kind of person who still
keeps her ledgers written by hand.
That means Chair Kim was also...
It's all connected.
For some reason,
I think it's the work of one person.
So until we catch the killer,
nothing is over yet.
[Woo-seok sighs]
[Woo-seok gasps] Seol-ah.
Are you okay?
Wait, that's dangerous. I got it. Hold on.
[Seung-jae] Seol-ah,
I hope the day never comes
where you have to read this.
A woman came to see me
and said strange things about you.
To be honest, it shook me.
This is Seung-jae's handwriting.
He left a clue about the culprit.
[gasps]
- Are you okay?
- [gasping]
Seol-ah.
[sobbing, gasping]
INSURANCE APPLICATION FORM
INSURANCE AGENT: KIM MI-SUK
[door closes]
This is your parents'
life insurance policy.
Check the agent's name for me.
I think it might be someone you know.
INSURANCE AGENT: KIM MI-SUK
These photos were found
at Paek Jun-beom's house.
I skimmed through them back then,
but there were some with Kim Yun-ji.
That means she was in Cheongun
the day before Seung-jae died.
Until the next morning.
And this one here
was taken by the river that day.
So, Kim Yun-ji was a witness, right?
And she knew who murdered Seung-jae.
That's why she was killed.
[sighs]
You think this could serve as evidence?
Well, it may not be enough,
but the culprit will show up soon,
because I'm with Han Seol-ah
and I know their secret.
- If I don't take that chance--
- Oh, no.
I'm not going to be using you as bait.
I'm the only one who can get close
without raising suspicion.
- I'll do it.
- It's too risky.
Even Chair Kim is dead.
What's dangerous is always living
with anxiety and in constant fear.
I don't want to live like that anymore.
Then let's go together.
Together we'll get caught.
Woo-seok, isn't there something
you need to look into?
Let me know the route you're taking,
and I'll keep you in the loop
about mine too.
Be careful.
- [door closes]
- [engine starts]
[Gong] You know,
I still suspect Do Eun-hyuk,
but he has an alibi.
The CCTV footage shows
that he was at his studio in Cheongun
when Paek Jun-beom was killed.
["Fear Inside" playing]
CHEONGUN STUDIO
RECOMMENDED ROUTE
16 MINUTES
If I step on the gas the whole way...
BOOKKEEPING LEDGER
DO EUN-HYUK
[Woo-seok] As long as the road is clear,
it's possible to get
from Paek Jun-beom's villa
to the studio in under 15 minutes.
PHOTO EQUIPMENT PURCHASE
LIVING EXPENSES
DO EUN-HYE PRIVATE TUTORING EXPENSES
EQUIPMENT PURCHASE
DARKROOM & LARGE TANK INSTALLATION
SOUNDPROOFING WORK
[hammer cocks]
[Woo-seok] I'm going to Cheongun.
CHA WOO-SEOK
[Eun-hyuk] Don't worry.
It'll all work out the way you want.
Do Eun-hyuk.
[Woo-seok] If you fall in love
with Han Seol-ah,
you will die.
[people shouting, screaming]
I gained nothing at all.
No!
[Seol-ah] I only lost.
[Woo-seok] If the culprit
thinks I'm your boyfriend,
I'll end up dead,
or I'll find out who the killer is.
What if you really end up dead?
[Woo-seok] I said I don't care.
You can use me.
- [Seol-ah] So until we catch the killer...
- [screams]
...nothing is over yet.
[Woo-seok] But the culprit
will show up soon,
because I'm with Han Seol-ah...
- [grunts]
- ...and I know their secret.