"Sammy's Children's Day"
(Episode 9)
Xia Liuyi.
The truth is, I don't have
some emotional disorder.
I just...
like you.
I like you.
I really like you.
I... I'm sorry.
I have to get to work.
I forgot my glasses.
I'm back.
Brother Liuyi.
Fatty Seven.
I've got this pretty boy here.
He seems to know you well,
but he won't admit it.
So I thought I'd call and ask.
What the hell are you talking about?
Forgot him already?
You're a busy man, Brother Liuyi.
No worries.
I'll just ask him more... thoroughly.
Hey pretty boy, how long
have you been with Liuyi?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You don't, huh?
I heard you two are quite close.
Who knew he had a type?
You've got it all wrong.
I know Mr. Xia,
but I'm just his financial advisor.
You really have the wrong person.
We aren't close.
Xia Liuyi,
your pretty boy still won't talk.
Guess you didn't treat him well enough.
Maybe I should show him some kindness.
How about showing some sincerity
if you want your sweetheart back?
One finger,
or one storefront. What do you say?
He's just an accountant
who crunches numbers.
He's not worth that much.
To be honest,
he's the most useless guy I've got.
Stop wasting my time.
That damn cop wouldn't lie to me.
Fine.
This is getting interesting.
Kid,
either you're completely worthless to him,
or you're everything.
Seven.
Do we still cut him?
Just beat him.
Fatty Seven kidnapped He Chusan.
Check every single one
of Fatty Seven's hideouts.
I don't care if you have to
turn the whole city upside down,
find him!
Still won't admit it, huh?
Pretty boy.
Beat him!
Die!
Mr. Xie.
One of Fatty Seven's guys
kidnapped someone.
The victim's record is clean.
He has no history with Fatty Seven.
No connection at all.
It's strange.
Who did they take?
[At the] Kwai Chung warehouse.
He Chusan.
He Chusan and Xia Liuyi.
What's going on?
He Chusan and Xia Liuyi...
Mr. Xie.
It's me.
I'm here to deliver your gift.
I...
He Chusan.
What are you trying to say?
Don't play dumb with me, Mr. Xie.
Listen.
Xia Liuyi and Fatty Seven
are going to war tonight.
While they're busy killing each other,
you can swoop in and take the credit.
So get your men ready
to make the bust.
What war?
And what does He Chusan
have to do with this?
Impressive, Mr. Xie.
You're already getting intel.
He Chusan
is Xia Liuyi's lover.
Lover.
Do you understand what that means?
It's just like...
the relationship between you and me.
I pulled some strings
to leak that info to Fatty Seven.
Imagine how excited he must be.
Lu Guangming,
who gave you permission to do that?
Mr. Xie,
I'm trying to help you.
To close this case,
you need Liuyi and Fatty Seven.
I've even got the charges ready.
Two gang bosses murdering an inspector,
a bloody turf war,
all taken down by the OCTB's finest.
When that happens,
whatever evidence you need,
or any old cold cases you want to reopen,
it'll be yours with a single word.
I want real evidence!
I want lawful arrests,
not these underhanded tactics
that treat lives like garbage!
You're going to get an innocent
citizen killed!
Don't you realize that?
Innocent?
The moment he got involved with Liuyi,
he stopped being innocent.
Xie Jiahua,
drop the useless sense of justice.
This is your best shot.
Get out of the car.
Aren't you going to answer?
If I stay indifferent,
he won't dare to act rashly.
But if he knows I care about Chusan,
he'll never let go.
He'd probably cut off his limbs
just to threaten me.
Boss,
Liuyi still isn't picking up.
He won't learn until he sees a coffin.
An accountant, right?
The most useless lackey, huh?
Keep beating him!
Boss, we found him!
Where?
An abandoned warehouse in North Point.
Go get the men.
I'm heading there now.
Are you crazy?
The police are looking for you everywhere.
This is probably a trap.
It's too dangerous.
Let me go find the kid for you, okay?
I have to go, even if it is a trap.
This is the only lead
I have on He Chusan.
Xia Liuyi!
You're the head of the gang.
What happens to us if
something happens to you?
I can't lose him again.
Go back to the office.
If anything happens to me,
you take charge.
Let's kill them!
He Chusan!
Xia Liuyi!
Drop the knife!
Or else,
I'll kill him right now!
Boss Xia,
so high and mighty...
and yet here you are, in my hands.
Zheng Wu,
we can talk about this.
Whatever Fatty Seven promised you,
I can double it.
Look at Brother Liuyi, all anxious.
Offering terms before the
negotiation even starts?
You've already lost.
Zheng Wu,
my patience is wearing thin.
While you still have a choice,
I suggest you take the deal.
I'm a simple man.
I want you on your knees.
What?
Not interested?
Then the guy inside is as good as dead.
Fine.
I'll do it.
Kneel! Do it!
Get on your knees!
Hurry up!
I'm waiting!
I said kneel!
Did you hear me?
Kneel!
Boss!
We're here!
I'll leave this to you.
Don't move!
Chusan!
He Chusan!
Where are you?
Boss.
Ahao.
Give me my phone.
Seven.
My men had a run-in with Zheng Wu.
But he pulled a gun first,
breaking the rules of the street.
I'll take the blame too.
I should've kept my men in check.
How do you want to settle this?
Name your price.
That depends on how much
sincerity you have, Liuyi.
A year's worth of our shipments.
Did I hear that right?
That's all?
Let him go,
and I'll deliver it myself.
That's not nearly enough.
Too stingy.
The two biggest clubs in Mong Kok.
They're yours.
Still not enough.
How about your gang's old ancestral hall?
Fine.
You've got a deal.
Spoken like a man.
He's at the ferry terminal.
Oh, by the way,
he's wearing a bomb.
Better hurry, Boss Xia.
The ferry terminal.
Go! Now!
Got it!
He Chusan!
Kid!
This place is huge.
He Chusan!
Check over there!
Kid!
He Chusan!
Damn it.
I should never have met him.
Make a movie for me.
Write a story for me.
Love
is what happens
when someone risks everything
to save another person.
I have a gift for you.
He Chusan,
do you like it?
I do.
I don't care what happens to other thugs,
but I can't be
like that about you.
Have you ever
had someone worry about you?
My dream since I was a kid
was to take my father
out of this filthy, rotten gutter.
And now,
I want to take you with me.
He Chusan,
I want a place with an ocean view.
You'll have it.
Happy New Year.
He Chusan,
Xia Liuyi.
I'm so afraid of losing you.
I...
I should never have fallen for him.
Don't leave me alone.
Don't go.
Don't leave me all alone.
Trust me.
This is your new beginning.
What the hell?
What's going on?
Is this a pyramid scheme?
Get out, get out! Nothing to see here.
Move it!
Let's go.
What's the deal?
Move it, kid.
Don't ask questions.
Don't get in the boss's way.
Don't move!
Freeze!
Xia Liuyi,
you're under arrest for attempted murder.
It wasn't him!
Xia Liuyi!
It's okay.
Take care of yourself, kid.
Wait for me to come back.
Thank you.
Someone will be by later
to take your statement.
Xia Liuyi...
what will happen to him?
If he's innocent,
he'll be released.
But if he's...
I believe in him.
He Chusan,
you have a clean record.
Watch yourself.
Don't associate with the wrong people.
I...
Why do you bother with such
thankless work?
Lu Guangming,
you still have the nerve to call me?
You could've killed
three birds with one stone.
Excuse me, let me through.
You could've used the Inspector's case
to take down the two
biggest gangs in Kowloon.
With that kind of achievement,
you'd be the Chief Inspector by now.
And now look at you.
Did I ever say I wanted any of that?
What I want is...
to be a good cop who serves justice, right?
Brother Jiahua, don't worry.
I'll be just like you,
a good cop who fights for what's right.
What a cliché.
How disappointing.
I don't think so.
I bet
Tang Jiaqi taught you that too.
Mr. Xie,
you're so useless,
you can't get anything done.
But five years ago,
when the gangs and the cops killed Jiaqi,
his body
was left bound in cold chains all night.
Do you think he regretted it?
Regret?
He was just
a stupid cop who only cared about justice.
That "stupid cop"
was my brother.
I'm not as noble as you.
I know his death was a setup,
but you still want to talk about evidence.
I only know an eye for an eye.
Anyone involved in my brother's death,
I don't care what it takes,
I'll make sure they feel
exactly what true agony is.
You idiot.
Can I come in for a bit?
Officer Lu.
No way.
Is that it?
Let me go!
Ignore him.
Don't let it blow you up!
Let's be friends!
I'm serious!
Don't leave me alone!
Don't go!
It's going to blow!
Tell us how to make money.
As the saying goes,
the key to investing is the three Rs.
Do you know what they are?
Returns,
Risks,
and Relative Value.
Returns, Risks, and Relative Value.
Got it?
As their financial advisor,
I make them over three million a month.
Three million!
A stack of cash higher than this ceiling!
Today we sleep on the floor,
tomorrow we're the boss!
Be the boss!
Follow me and you'll make millions!
Do you believe in yourselves?
Yes!
Today
is your
new beginning!
Brother Liuyi.