Chen Haowei,
can you teach me math?
[Episode 3]
[A Confession from the Shooting Stars]
Sure.
Why did you draw sea turtles on the paper?
Drawing sea turtles makes me so happy.
Do sea turtles have this kind of use?
Then teach me how to draw.
Alright.
Let me teach you the easiest way.
First, draw a big oval,
add a spiral in the middle,
then 4 boomerangs.
Boomerangs?
Yes.
And the most important big head.
And a little tail.
Easy, right?
Big head and little tail.
This is so cute.
Thank you.
Now I know.
I've always wanted to ask you a question.
What is it?
Why do you keep smiling?
-Do I?
-Look.
You're smiling right now.
Isn't that good?
Not that. Don't you
ever feel unhappy
or sad?
I...
I don't know.
Well, how about
I teach you a new way?
Tell me then.
Say it in your heart:
"1, 4, 2, 8, 5, 7."
1, 4, 2, 8, 5, 7.
Don't you
feel calm?
Why these numbers?
Because they are
the most mysterious numbers in the world.
Some say they're numbers chosen by God,
while others say
they're the password in the universe.
But actually, they're just
cyclic numbers in math.
When you multiply it by 1 to 6,
the set of digits stays the same,
the sequence doesn't change,
and it's still
those same 6 numbers.
[Wishing Upon the Shooting Stars]
Aren't you a top student?
Chen Haowei, answer the phone, okay?
Please.
-Making such a silly mistake?
-I just want an explanation
about what is wrong with my money.
Just use Mr. Lin's money.
After all, we tried our best...
Yes, I know investment is risky.
But you were so sure,
and what happened?
-Do you want our efforts to go to waste?
-You said bonds were good, so I got them.
You said funds were good, so I got them.
1, 4, 2, 8, 5, 7.
-1, 4, 2, 8, 5, 7.
-The bank is scared to see me.
The bank won't lend me money.
-1, 4, 2, 8, 5, 7.
-I can't finance anymore.
What should I do?
Why don't you go tell him?
-1, 4, 2, 8, 5, 7.
-Help me, please,
Chen Haowei.
1, 4, 2, 8, 5, 7.
Excuse me,
are you going to check in?
Miss.
Pick one.
You really need direction.
Is He Xiangyong here?
I'm looking for him.
Bring the luggage in.
So you're the comics artist
that Xiangyong is in charge of?
May I ask,
how's our He Xiangyong
at work
in the company—
Xixi!
You...
You yelled so loudly.
You scared me to death.
How's our He Xiangyong
at work?
His attitude
and performance?
Why...
Why are you here?
Weird. You know her too?
Mr. He, you don't read comics.
She's really famous.
Like "The Hunter's Gentle Vacation,"
"Desserts, Seeds, and the Prophecy Diary,"
and "Goddess of Zandir,"
she drew all of them.
I love reading her comics.
Y-You're my idol.
But why are you here?
Do you have a room available?
-What do you want to do?
-Yes.
Our guest came here to stay, of course.
What kind of question is that?
No, Mr. He,
the vacant room
hasn't been tidied up
after the guest left.
Besides,
I haven't cleaned the toilet yet.
The vacant room also leaks.
I don't think it's...
suitable.
How many days are you staying?
Three days.
Well, listen,
our vacant room really leaks.
The floor is all wet.
Haowei.
Take her to check in.
Okay.
Gosh, Xiaoyou!
Take the guest's luggage to Room 201.
Room 201 won't leak.
Check in here.
Miss, this way please.
Sorry for that.
Dudu, come here.
Stay out of the sun.
What are you doing here alone?
I'm reading
and enjoying the view.
Is it because of Xixi?
What?
Why do you know Xixi?
I've read all her comics,
and my friend is her managing editor.
I don't need to report these
to you, right?
But when Mr. He asked her something,
why did you look so nervous?
Did I?
Are you afraid of a caterpillar?
What caterpillar?
I wasn't.
I wasn't nervous.
Are you hiding something
about He Xiangyong?
You're so imaginative.
What?
Have you dated He Xiangyong before?
Answer me.
Yes.
And we were inseparable.
We couldn't even be apart
even if we wanted to.
Inseparable?
I'm relieved now.
About what?
Since you said so,
it means you've never been together.
Boring.
Wait.
You said we should keep a distance
and stay away from each other.
Why are you suddenly so concerned?
What are you up to?
Nothing.
Just looking out for you as a friend.
Really?
The way you just asked
doesn't feel like concern
from a friend at all.
Instead, it feels more like…
Like what?
Like you were projecting.
What's going on?
Nothing.
We're fine.
She's asking if we're free.
Where do you want to go later?
Breathe.
Breathe?
She probably means
she wants to take a walk.
Am I right?
That's great.
I can give you a ride.
You rent one yourself.
I'm sure you want to ride one by yourself,
right?
What are you looking at?
Why do you know Xixi so well?
Maybe I'm just sincere.
Sincere?
I used to
watch the sea the most.
But I can only watch,
because I can't swim.
Whenever I listen to the sound of the sea,
I feel like I'm floating on the sea.
What do you think?
Let me take a photo for you.
One, two, three.
This is where you
can come whenever you're fed up,
need to let go,
or just feel like relaxing.
Just close your eyes by the sea
and count:
1, 4, 2, 8, 5, 7.
Seven...
Seven sevens are 49.
Eight eights are 64.
Nine nines are 81.
Or singing is alright.
After that,
you'll feel that everything
is not important
and that your worries will disappear.
Really.
It really works like magic.
Let me take another photo for you.
Here we are.
Li Wanzhe.
Three bowls of shaved ice.
Mung bean milk ice
and jelly ice.
This way.
For Xixi...
give her tri-color taro ball ice.
The tri-color taro balls
have to be cooked fresh,
so hurry up.
Hey, Angela.
Haowei.
Have you ordered?
Yes.
OK.
Xiaoyou.
You have a guest.
Xixi, let me tell you.
Wanzhe's shaved ice is super delicious.
No bad picks at all.
It's just that the tri-color taro balls
might take a little while,
because they're all freshly made.
So thirsty. It's hot today.
It's too hot.
Here comes the shaved ice.
Why is it so fast?
Li Wanzhe,
what is this?
Shaved ice.
Li Wanzhe!
He must have had heatstroke.
Wanzhe.
What is this?
I'll give you a gua sha massage.
Oh my god! I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Nothing, nothing.
I'll do it again.
Haowei, help me greet her.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Li Wanzhe!
One day,
the shell came home
and said—
I'm back (which sounds like "shell").
Why don't vampires eat spicy food?
Because they only drink blood
(which sounds like "not spicy").
Do you know—
Just get to the point.
What does that card mean?
What does "direction" mean?
Sometimes, cards
are just a reminder,
not an answer.
Here.
Thank you.
Not now.
Okay.
Put it away.
Yes, I wanted to put it away.
What?
Gua sha massage.
It hurts!
You feel pain now, huh?
Of course.
What play are you putting on now?
Because of Xiaohai?
Don't mention that name again.
I really don't know
why he keeps
confessing his feelings to me.
Didn't you say you wanted to date someone?
That kind of passionate love?
Now that love has come your way,
why are you overreacting?
Just accept his confession.
But
I didn't know my wish
would really come true.
You told me to accept it.
Fine.
Even if my wish has to come true,
Xiaohai can't be the one.
Xiaohai is my best buddy.
We play video games together,
and now we're gonna date each other?
Don't you think that is so weird?
This...
is impossible.
So,
we have to find a way to undo the wish.
That'll be rude.
Forget it.
Hello, good night.
Do you want to ask about He Xiangyong?
Our He Xiangyong
has gone missing after something happened.
I don't know where he is now.
Did he call you?
No.
I came here just to figure it out.
But he's gone. It's bothering me.
He didn't call you either?
This little brat.
Pick one.
He's probably in trouble.
What trouble?
If you want to know,
find the answer yourself.
Wait, you have to tell me
what the card says
and what kind of difficulties
or what kind of person he met.
I'm going to fulfill my mission.
Miss.
You haven't finished yet, you know?
Li Wanzhe!
I have something to tell you!
Come here.
I have something to tell you too.
Sit.
-Actually…
-Actually...
-I...
-You...
-You…
It's okay. You go first.
You go first.
Actually, I don't know
why I suddenly confessed to you.
-But I...
-Actually...
there's a strange legend on our island.
If there are shooting stars that day,
then...
then do something strange...
Shooting stars?
Yes, shooting stars.
I think
it's only because of the shooting stars.
You didn't like me at first,
but now you do.
Yes, that's it.
I really like you.
I really think
it's only because of the shooting stars.
Trust me.
Trust what I trust.
Trust the trust in what I trust.
You go back and sleep.
Everything will be fine
once you wake up tomorrow.
It's just...
just some weird power
that made you suddenly
confess to me on impulse.
Yes, that's it.
Yes.
I really like you.
You like me?
Okay, tell me what you like about me.
I like your cute eyes.
I like your high nose.
I like your thick lips.
I like your long legs.
I like how you're so good to your family.
I like that you're very considerate
to your friends.
I like that you're cheerful to everyone.
I like that whenever you make
shaved ice for me,
you always add tons and tons
of plums for me.
I like how you eat
with such big, hearty bites.
I want to eat a lot of delicious food
with you.
Okay.
Okay, I got it.
Then... how are you gonna prove it?
How do you want me to prove it?
I see.
Turtle-shaped cakes, right?
I'll buy some for you tomorrow morning.
Wait, wait.
Turtle-shaped cakes. Okay?
But...
I prefer pork knuckle rice.
Pork knuckle rice from Siping Street,
New Taipei, right?
How do you know?
Wait.
There's more.
I also want to eat
charcoal-grilled sandwich
from Yancheng District, Kaohsiung,
squid roll rice noodles
from Guohua Street, Tainan,
white vinegar cold noodles
from Wenhua Road, Chiayi,
Black Bamboo Chicken Feet Jelly,
stinky tofu from Heping Road,
jute leaf soup
from the Taichung Second Market,
Popiah from Hsinchu City God Temple,
and garlic pork thick soup
from Taishan Road, Yilan.
What do you say?
You can't do it, huh?
Let me think.
When you really do it,
let's talk about why you like me.
I don't think he can buy them.
Yeah, he surely can't.
Yeah, he can't.
He can't.
Jiao is so strange lately.
She keeps coming to my clinic.
She kept coming
even though she was doing fine.
Turns out
she came just to ask about you.
What's wrong?
Are you in a bad mood?
My son
must've gotten himself
into some kind of trouble,
which is why he quit
his job and came home,
and then, out of nowhere,
some college friend of his showed up
wanting to work for accommodation.
I don't know what he's up to.
I think something is off.
Could something have happened?
Why don't you go ask the publishing house?
He's all grown up.
Can't he solve everything himself?
All right.
Go on and act tough.
I remember Xiangyong had a high fever
when he was little.
You carried him halfway
across the island just to find me.
You even forgot to ride your motorcycle.
Do you know what you said to me?
What did I say?
You said,
"Worrying
is a lifelong lesson for parents.
No matter how old their children get,
parents
just can't let go."
Right?
I don't know why,
but everything you're saying
just makes me sick.
You'd better be.
Forget it.
He's all grown up now.
This was supposed to be my time
to relax and take it easy.
Your concern shows clearly on your face.
Instead of drinking
and moping here with me,
why don't you go get some clear answers?
You have to know what's wrong
before you can fix it.
You're the best at talking.
How long are you going
to keep folding that paper boat?
I'll burn it for you.
For me? Nonsense.
Just close your eyes by the sea
and count:
1, 4, 2, 8, 5, 7.
Wanzhe's shaved ice is super delicious.
No bad picks at all.
It's just that the tri-color taro balls
might take a little while,
because they're freshly made.
What's wrong?
I just wanted to throw my towel.
[Where Is My Home]
Zhong Xiaoyou.
I think something is wrong.
What?
When I brought breakfast to Xixi earlier,
she stayed in her room
and wouldn't come out,
and she was making
some really weird noises.
Like this, like this.
And she was smashing everything.
Did someone come to see her?
She should be fine.
That's what a comics artist does.
She's probably being urged to write.
So she locked herself up
and let her second personality take over.
But she can't lock
herself in her room.
What if something really happens?
How can we help her?
She'll be fine.
Excuse me.
I'll call Mr. He first.
Chen Haowei.
What's up?
Why don't you go buy something?
What do you want to buy?
Bitter melons and black tea.
Why me?
Fine.
Call Mr. He then.
When he comes back,
the room should be torn down.
You'll be responsible if anything happens.
Should the green tea be sweetened or not?
Black tea, sugar-free.
But Bitter melons
come in both white and green...
Whatever.
Go.
Weird.
What took him so long?
Hello,
this is Where Is My Home Guesthouse.
Xiaoyou.
I'm going to the main island.
We may have a group of fishing tourists
coming these days.
Remember to reserve 5 rooms
and avoid overbooking.
Call me if anything happens.
When are you coming back?
Hello?
You knew
there was a fishing tour group coming,
yet left the guesthouse
to two part-timers.
I'm back.
Did you buy it right?
Is it black tea?
Yes.
But I still bought
two kinds of bitter melons.
It's okay.
As long as it's a bitter melon.
I made you a cup of tea
and left it at your door.
What's wrong?
You also need to calm your nerves?
No.
I just want to see if it works.
Haven't you heard
that sweetness always follows bitterness?
The human brain
produces 4 happiness-inducing chemicals:
serotonin, dopamine,
endorphins, and oxytocin.
The bitter taste of bitter melons
stimulates the release of endorphins,
while the polyphenols in black tea
have powerful antioxidant effects.
That's why bitter melons
paired with black tea
helps relieve anxiety.
Really?
Really.
I read it in a book.
Do you read this kind of book?
Yes.
I don't have many friends.
I just read books when I'm free.
You usually go on and on in circles.
But you're pretty reliable when it counts.
You didn't lie to me today.
Did I lie to you a lot?
If I truly lied to you,
it was just one sentence.
Which one?
He said...
you were the last person
he wanted to remember.
The one on the first night,
on the rooftop.
At night?
So which line was it, exactly?
Forget it if you don't remember.
How about this?
Let's play a game.
We ask each other a question,
but we have to be honest, okay?
What do you think?
Go ahead.
Did He Xiangyong leave because of me?
No.
Really?
Really.
Your turn.
What?
Have you dated He Xiangyong before?
What exactly did you come to Xingpu Island
to find him for?
What is Chen Haowei doing?
[Epilogue]
Can't Chen Haowei quit dealing with
everything by himself all the time?
Does he think he's Kobe Bryant?
He might as well just play the whole game
by himself.
About today, I'm sorry...
Basketball is a team sport, okay?
He kept taking shots,
but he couldn't even make any.
What the hell?
I don't want to team up with him
next time.
Why are you here?
I'm fine.
It's just a game.
He Xiangyong.
This way,
no one will see how sad you are.
Do you know why I came to you?
I'm not sad.
I'm fine.
Can't you just laugh
and cry whenever you want?
You don't have to care
what others think of Chen Haowei.
Because as long as I find you,
I think I can find myself.
[Next Episode]
He!
Sorry to bother you guys.
You are He Xiangyong, aren't you?
You two aren't fighting,
just being stubborn and moody.
I said I wanted to see him
because I want to beat him up.
Surprise!
Xiangyong.
Your favorite watermelon candy.