Officail Website : dramacool.club  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Whether you're light or a lie,
I can't pull myself away ♪
♪ In this game,
truth or lie no longer matters ♪
[Queen of Darkness]
[Episode 15]
We finally meet.
Vincent.
You didn't have to come save me.
Unless you know me.
People rarely change their habits.
For example, when thinking,
you always like to play with a lighter.
Am I right?
Huo Xiao.
This hotel is one I acquired.
You probably understand
the current situation.
Master, Madam.
It wasn't me.
Inspector Huo.
I swear it really wasn't me.
You ran away,
and yet you dare come back?
♪ Are you ready or not ♪
♪ I'm gonna take it out ♪
Didn't expect you to find out this soon.
You're Vincent.
Before I became a cop,
I used that alias to invest abroad.
But very few people
knew about that identity.
So you were already working with Qian.
Weren't you?
She just told a truth disguised as a lie.
It's true that only I can save your group.
And you also passed my test
on your own merit.
Your solution matches mine.
Perhaps
this is called
tacit understanding.
Get lost.
Use one percent of shares
to secure steady hotel operations.
The future returns
could be dozens of times higher.
Plus, that debtor will protect the hotel
just to keep his own interests safe.
This deal's totally worth it.
You're more worth it.
Pleasure to cooperate.
Since you insist on sticking to the rules,
I won't push you.
Here's our
Valuation Adjustment Mechanism.
Repay when due.
If you can't pay on time,
then you'll be the interest.
I won't lose myself that easily to you.
You'd better drop that idea now.
Maybe one day...
One day what?
It's getting late.
I should head back now.
Sign it.
[Signature]
Can she really pay off that debt?
With what money could she repay it?
She's clearly overestimating herself.
So she'll end up being the laughingstock.
Time's almost up.
Why isn't she here yet?
Could it be she's
too cowardly to come?
Unworthy of the position,
misfortune will follow.
Being a homemaker suits you best.
This position
really isn't for just anyone.
Someone like Vice Director Song
doesn't deserve it.
Since I dared to come,
I naturally have the guts to sit here.
Qian.
[Equity Investment Agreement]
[Investor: Vincent]
What?
Vincent, the investment giant.
He took over
the group's 优酷剧集英语ed debts.
[Investment Amount] [Investor: Vincent]
Vice Director Song tried to meet him,
but couldn't even get an appointment.
Th... this…
How is this even possible?
This…
This contract must be fake!
Vincent, the investment tycoon,
[Vincent, the investment giant,
invested heavily in Longxing Group]
Strategically expands into
Longxing Group.
Rumors of the debt collapse
are proven false.
That's a big win.
That's a solid profit.
Exactly.
That's right.
No way, absolutely not!
[Longxing Group
Smuggling Controlled Drugs]
[Facing Full-Scale Investigation]
Take a look.
Just look at this!
The stock price has crashed.
We're taking huge losses!
You owe us an explanation.
This is all on you.
You dragged the group into this mess!
Things have come to this.
Resigning to take responsibility
and yielding the position
is your best choice.
You think that's enough to scare me off?
Then you really don't know me.
I'll carve out my own path
and show you
I'm no pushover for anyone.
As for the rest of you!
Every insult you threw at me today,
I'll make you swallow them
back word for word.
Just wait and see.
[Longxing Group
smuggles for personal gain]
[and seeks personal gain
through official positions]
[Relying on smuggled dirty money,
pretending here is shameless positions]
[Peaceful person is truly a snake with
a human face and a snake heart]
[Merchants' money is not so clean,
boycott Longxing Group]
A bunch of keyboard warriors.
Officail Website : dramacool.club  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Don't mind them.
I've already found out.
Your own people
are abusing their power to cover up.
Using the group's overseas trade line
to smuggle for personal profit.
[Trade Agreement]
[Seller signature: Fang Tao]
Sorry, the number you dialed
can not be connected.
Could it be him?
I suspect him too.
So I had Daming
track his location in advance.
[Karaoke Star]
He couldn't have pulled this off alone.
There must be
a customs officer involved.
Then what are we waiting for?
Let's move now.
If you go like that, you'll tip him off.
We need some cover first.
His last location pinged right here.
I'll cut the device power.
That way he can't erase anything.
Leave these guys to me.
We have to catch him
with the proof today.
Be careful.
They found me so quickly.
I'm right here.
Dad.
Hurry.
They must not get
this surveillance and evidence.
You must hold him off.
Check the power on the devices.
Where is he?
I have a way
to get rid of these two for good.
Dad.
You go out the back door first.
Leave this to me.
Then be careful yourself.
There's a hidden door
at the end of the hallway.
They're definitely hiding in there.
Let's go.
We're too late.
This is where they secretly meet.
Their computer must have
evidence of their plotting.
Seems it can still run.
Looks like the backup power kicked in.
The case is sealed shut.
No way to pull the hard drive directly.
A single fire will wipe it all clean.
The evidence,
and you along with it,
will all turn to dust.
No one will ever threaten
our Fang family again.
Hurry up!
A little faster.
It's stuck.
The fire's spreading fast.
All the doors are blocked.
How much longer?
Almost done.
What about you?
I can handle it.
If only one of us makes it out alive,
I hope it's you.
♪ Let me hold you tight before I fall ♪
♪ Let this expressionless world
shatter into breath ♪
♪ Rushed lies in endless time ♪
Dad, don't worry.
They must've burned to death.
Got it.
I heard on the news about
a man and a woman found dead.
That's when I dared to show myself.
What's taking so long?
Hurry and drive.
Didn't expect it, did you?
We're still alive.
Inspector, are you alright?
Check the surveillance footage.
Compile the clips of him meeting
with the customs official into evidence.
Got it.
Wait.
Since he wants us dead,
then we'll pretend to die for him.
Fake our death and lure him out.
Daming.
Get in touch with the media right now.
And put out a news story.
Yes.
Officail Website : dramacool.club  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
No way.
You dare treat me like this, you brat?
All these years,
you've been pulling these little tricks
and doing those evil deeds
behind the scenes.
Today I'll settle the score
with you properly.
Chairman An asked me to look into you.
And I had no idea till I looked into it.
Cooking the books.
Colluding with customs.
Smuggling and money laundering.
Instigating staff bullying.
Leaking the group's trade secrets.
All those dirty tricks of yours
just keep coming one after another.
Just a small token.
Then I'll gladly accept it.
You're quite straightforward.
Make sure that
shipment of ours stays safe.
Don't worry.
I admit it.
All of that was done by me.
I just lost my head for a moment.
Hand the footage to the media.
And issue a public statement.
Saying this was entirely a personal act.
It has nothing to do with the group.
Chairman An.
Please, just give me one more chance.
Please, one last chance.
Someone like you
doesn't deserve forgiveness.
From now on,
you're relieved of all duties in the group.
You'll handle the fines yourself.
All losses to the group fall on you.
You want to ruin me.
Then I won't let you walk away safe!
Let's go down together.
♪ Mist coils around the sleeping forest ♪
♪ Memories scattered
through cracks of darkness ♪
♪ How to escape this real-feeling dream ♪
♪ Lies reflect in water's gleam ♪
♪ Traces of existence
can never be erased ♪
♪ How to find the self I can't reclaim ♪
♪ Fly away, hear she says ♪
♪ She'll fly out from
thorns of woven lies ♪
♪ Pierce the fog,
shatter this dream tonight ♪
♪ Burn like fire ♪
♪ Just burn like fire ♪
♪ The maze in the abyss starts to clear ♪
♪ Yet night keep on whispering ♪
♪ Surrender to fate,
no clear direction ahead ♪
♪ She will rise as the dawn
that breaks the darkness ♪
♪ Never slowing down,
for tomorrow cannot be stopped ♪
♪ Surrender to love and find the way ♪
♪ Even if fate tries to forget her ♪
♪ Never despair,
for the heart burns with endless light ♪
♪ Waiting for dawn ♪
[Copyright of this short drama
belongs to]
[Shanghai Chuqi Weishi
Culture Media Co., Ltd.]
[and Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[Co., Ltd.]
[Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[holds exclusive global online
and broadcast rights]