[Name: Du Cong]
Look at these big fruits.
How nice.
I told you so, didn't I?
They're all nice fruits.
Yes.
You'll be in charge of grocery shopping
from now on.
I'd rather stay out of it.
Absolutely.
Dad,
Mom,
I'm such an unfilial son.
This parting could be...
♪ The stars twinkle, the moon curves ♪
♪ A gentle breeze
sways the willow branches ♪
It's the two of you again.
♪ The two of us, working late at night,
sneak up to the base of the wall ♪
The same bad thing
could happen once or twice,
but not three or four times!
[Do not trample on the plants]
♪ Sneaking around, peeking through ♪
"Never cave in to reality."
Never cave in to reality.
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 19]
[Forensic Lab of Sanjiangkou
Municipal Public Security Bureau]
The substance found at the scene
last night
[Physical Evidence Examination Report]
is human blood.
Judging from
what we know of now,
the dead
is most likely Liu Bei.
So, now, our primary goal
is to find
Liu Bei and the killer.
Alive or dead, there has to be proof.
That is to say,
all the vehicles and people
passing by the intersection
near Xiangji Temple must be
looked into.
It is the evening rush hour.
The traffic conditions
at the intersection are complex,
with a large flow of people.
Chief Zhang,
we need more manpower.
Li Qian,
give them a hand.
It's temporary.
You'll only spent
a couple of days with them.
Just obey the order.
You are a girl.
Chief Zhang had no other choice.
He just caved under pressure.
Where was I?
We need to find Liu Bei and the killer.
Liu Bei and the killer. Right.
We propose to merge
this case
with Zhou Rong's case.
What do you think?
Human blood was found,
but how do we prove
it's Liu Bei's?
Even if it is Liu Bei's,
how do we prove he was killed?
The surveillance footage
shows that Liu Bei
came in carrying a suitcase.
So these are his footprints.
But the man who left was not Liu Bei.
This is a mark left by the suitcase wheels
when this man went away.
Pay attention to this trail.
It's deeper.
There is only one possibility.
That is, the dead
was in the suitcase.
And this dead man
was Liu Bei.
But there are barely
any signs of a struggle at the scene.
The killer took his target down
with only one move.
With Liu Bei's skills,
who could be so capable
as to kill him instantly?
There must be someone as strong as that.
Who?
Yeah.
Finding out who it is
is what we are going
to do next.
Right?
Chief, please go on.
We watched the surveillance footage
near the crime scene this morning,
and found a suspicious vehicle.
This car also has a fake plate.
In the past few days, this car
got in two traffic accidents
with cars owned by Rongcheng Group.
Li Qian,
when your car
rear-ended
that Rongcheng Group's car that day,
the car that fled the scene was this one.
Were all the incidents
just coincidental?
I don't think so.
These two people were highly likely
in cahoots with Liu Bei,
so they also sneaked into
Zhou Rong's manor.
This provides an answer
to Li Qian's question just now.
It is true
that Liu Bei was a great fighter.
But what if he was
caught completely off guard?
What if he was killed by an acquaintance?
This is my guess:
it was these two people
who robbed Zhou Rong
and beat up Lang Bowen.
Suppose they were indeed
working with Liu Bei,
then that phone and the suitcase
must be in their hands now.
I suggest we treat these two people
as our primary targets now.
I agree.
-Agreed.
-I agree.
If you all concur with me...
I beg to differ.
Why?
It doesn't seem to me that Zhou Rong
was robbed by these two people.
I've seen those two guys.
Hadn't you been knocked out by then?
I woke up later and got
a blurry glimpse of them.
They don't look like the robbers.
Didn't you say their faces were covered?
That's why I said
they didn't look like the robbers.
Li Qian just made
a rather good point.
Everyone, try to collect
evidence in this regard.
Got it.
Before new evidence is found,
these two people
are still our primary targets.
Agreed?
Agreed.
Find out who they are.
I just did.
The driver is Mao Hongwei,
nicknamed Mao.
The other man
should be a fellow of his, Xia Tinggang.
They operate a scrap yard
[Building 2]
near the chemical industrial zone.
Have you...
seen a dead body?
N-Not when it's so close.
Y-You go take a look.
No, you do it.
L-Let's do it together then.
What are you doing?
What is this?
This is...
the murder weapon.
No, it's not.
Didn't you see that guy's
slit on the neck?
It must be caused by a knife.
Let me venture a guess.
The killer first knocked out
the dead with this,
and then slit his neck
with a knife.
Otherwise, why would
this thing
be placed beside the body?
I bet the killer meant to
dump the body
and throw away the weapon later.
Right?
Quite smug, aren't you?
Dump the body, huh?
I sent you out to snatch money.
Why did you bring back
a dead body instead?
W-Who
would've known this could happen?
That man looks...
just like Sakuragi Hanamichi.
Who would know he is a murderer?
How was I supposed to know
there was a body in this suitcase?
Would I have known that?
You didn't expect it, did you?
I didn't expect any of this.
Didn't expect this?
Why were you so careless?
How could you be this ignorant?
What's this for?
Now see what you've started.
Instead of money, you brought
such grave trouble back.
Let's call the police then.
K-K-Keep your voice down.
[Taxi]
Call the police, huh?
It's true
that we didn't kill this man.
But for driving this fake taxi
for robbery,
we'll still be put in prison, won't we?
Which will keep you
behind bars longer,
driving a fake taxi
for robbery, or killing a man?
[Taxi]
No, we didn't kill this man.
And I didn't borrow that money.
Why should I be put in jail with you?
Driving a fake taxi
for robbery
was your idea.
-I told you to keep it down!
-I can prove that!
I should have a say in this!
C-Come over here and talk.
I won't hit you.
Come and talk to me in a lower voice.
What if you hit me?
I...
If I hit you,
I'll die without descendants.
Alright?
Tinggang,
let's throw the suitcase away.
Where?
Anywhere is fine.
The farther the better.
Never cave in to reality.
They've been disturbing
all the neighbors.
They should've been caught long ago.
They should've been dealt with long ago.
See, you guys waited so long to do so.
Where have they gone?
Chief,
Captain Wang,
those two guys were seen
driving a car away half an hour ago.
Hand out photos of them.
Notify all checkpoints.
Don't let them leave Sanjiangkou.
Got it.
Listen,
Team 1, Team 2,
follow me!
My little grandson
took one yuan with him
and went to buy a popsicle.
But those two men robbed him
just as he reached that alley entrance.
He's just a six-year-old.
See,
in this neighborhood,
all women—
each and every woman—
would never hang
their washed underware outside.
That's right.
Or it'd be stolen.
What kind of person would do that?
Thank you all.
The clues you provided
are helpful for our investigation.
Just hurry and arrest
those two scumbags.
Yes, arrest them.
We will. Rest assured.
Thank you.
Thank you too.
Thanks a lot.
They'll be caught sooner or later.
They're never up to any good, are they?
Exactly.
Such peace destroyers.
Are they really the culprits?
[Name: Hu Qinghua]
Money solves every problem.
One million US dollars...
It's equal to over 60 million yuan.
We can each take more than 30 million.
With your math skills,
it's a shame you're not an accountant.
One million US dollars
is equal to over 7 million yuan.
Only 7 million yuan?
"Only"?
How much is that God of Wealth statue
you moved?
In your entire life,
have you ever seen 7 million?
I...
Splitting 7 million
between the two of us...
We'll each have only a little
more than 3 million.
That's not even enough to get a wife.
It costs that much to get a wife?
Then this woman can't be your true love.
You made a good point.
Listen,
do you think true love exists
in this world?
When I'm about to dress as a woman,
don't ask me
any questions about romance.
Okay, got it.
Hey,
I'd like to go for
a different makeup style this time
as a breakthrough.
A breakthrough, huh?
I'll help.
Take a look
at these two men. Have you seen them?
Well...
No, never.
Did you look carefully?
Take a closer look.
Sir, careful. The floor is slippery.
I really haven't seen them.
Show me the registration record
of guests then.
Well, I...
What? Hurry!
Sorry for that.
There isn't even a photo.
How do I understand any of this?
Gosh. Look.
Such messy handwriting.
H-How can I read this?
Do you know what it says here?
You're disguising as a blind man now.
Acting like this will blow your cover.
Give it to me.
Watch me.
You have a try.
Is it passable?
Come on, give me a hand.
I'm blind now.
Those two bastards.
Where have they gone?
I just sighed. Did it affect you or what?
No.
The car is out of gas.
Then go get some gas.
Why did you pull over?
It's completely out of gas.
Did you step on
the gas pedal too hard?
This car is even older than me.
I wish I could do that.
What do we do?
We'll have to push the car.
I pulled over at the perfect spot.
The sign here says
there is a gas station
800 meters to the right.
Get out and push the car now.
I guess it's the only option.
Join me.
But I have to stay in the car
to spin the steering wheel.
You can do it and push the car
at the same time.
Just keep that door open.
No.
-You can't drive.
-Then use this arm to...
I...
So you don't know.
For safety reasons, both hands
must be on it.
You really are...
Fine then.
[Gas Station is 800 meters away
on the right]
Come on.
Push!
Push.
Quick.
F-Forgot to release the handbrake.
[Diesel Oil]
Ma'am,
500 yuan, pump No. 3.
Please pay inside.
Thank you, young man.
How much in gas?
Two hundred yuan.
Are we out of RMB notes?
See,
I'm blind now.
I can't stand on my feet now.
What is it with you?
What now?
Take out your money, alright?
Wait. You don't have money?
No, I don't.
I only have 2 yuan left.
Only 2 yuan in my pocket.
Hurry.
What's wrong?
They don't take US dollars.
Are they crazy,
for rejecting US dollars?
Where are you going?
Come back!
What are you going to do?
Hey, ma'am, I have a question.
-Why don't you take US dollars?
-Alright, stop it.
My husband is grumpy.
-Sorry.
-We don't take US dollars.
Why not?
Give me what you earned by selling junk
yesterday.
This is all I have.
What? But I asked for
200-yuan worth of gas.
Why that much?
Gas is expensive now.
The key's in.
-What kind of attitude is this?
-Let's just go.
This is China.
We don't take US dollars.
What's the point
of saying all that?
Where is your manager?
I demand to see your manager.
The car! Our car!
This isn't over.
You haven't paid!
Get out of my car, you bastards!
What do we do?
Get in this taxi!
♪ The sun is setting ♪
Sir, 200 yuan.
Pay up!
You haven't paid up!
What a nice car.
So luxurious.
Leather interiors.
Look at this sunroof.
How very nice.
-That scared me.
Darn it!
Eyes on the road!
No.
How is it...
back to us?
P-Please stop
saying that.
Are we...
being haunted or what?
Bro, drive faster.
Faster, please.
I can't see those guys anymore.
This is the car we abandoned.
This is as fast as it gets.
Bro,
there is a suitcase.
It looks identical to ours.
Bro,
the content is completely different.
Tell me something I don't know.
What should we do?
Find those two bastards first.
Zip the suitcase!
You go open it.
See what's inside.
No, I refuse.
You go do it.
I already did it last time.
You...
Just go do it!
Go!
Gosh.
What? What is it?
Another dead body?
A real surprise.
Gosh.
Take a look.
No way.
You have to!
Look!
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
We're rich now, bro!
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
These are US dollars, right?
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
We have to go.
Why?
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
This car is too conspicuous.
We can't drive this.
Then how do we go home?
By bus.
Okay.
Let's go.
♪ Get your head in the game,
we're all smart people here ♪
♪ Don't drag your feet,
even gold slips through slow hands ♪
♪ I beat it, I beat it ♪
♪ Aye aye aye aye yo ♪
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
[No parking on the pavement;
violators will be fined 500 yuan]
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
Get out of the car.
What's wrong?
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
You want to be arrested?
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
[No parking on the pavement;
violators will be fined 500 yuan]
[Pull up here for a check]
[Temporary checkpoint
for major quarantine forest pests]
Chief Zhang.
How is it going?
No finding so far.
Let's go to the next spot then.
Okay.
Keep a close eye.
Got it.
Good work.
Understood, Captain Wang.
[Temporary checkpoint
for major quarantine forest pests]
Xing, pull over.
What's up?
Xing, go check out that car.
Uncle!
When will we go fight Zhou Rong?
Now.
Everyone, come down and follow me!
What's this for?
For fighting Zhou Rong.
To fight Zhou Rong,
we'll use this.
This?
Zhou Rong took away
the ninth piece of bianzhong.
Don't you think
he craves the remaining pieces?
Of course he does.
How will he get them?
He definitely craves them.
So he's waiting
for a call from us?
Exactly.
What should we do?
Give him a call!
It's hard to find a buyer.
It's no easy job to find a seller
either, right?
We will tell him explicitly
that the deal is off.
Let's see what he is going to do.
He has to double the price,
or we won't sell anything to him.
Agreed.
Mr. Fang, why a new ride?
Well,
just trying to keep fit.
[Protect the environment,
safeguard our home.]
[Chief Huang]
Get ready for a study session
at the Party School in a few days.
Last 3 lifts.
One.
Mr. Zhou,
I...
Shuang,
would you leave the room?
Mr. Zhou,
a call from Fang Yong.
P-P-Pick it up.
Hello, Mr. Fang.
It's me.
What?
Please don't.
That was just a little accident.
He...
Okay, I'll tell Mr. Zhou then.
This is...
No way.
Hello.
Speak up.
Help me...
Hello?
You failed such a trivial task.
What's the point of keeping you around?
Fine. G-Go ahead then.
Take your time.
I'm listening.
That's it.
Mr. Zhou!
Mr. Zhou.
You almost got me killed.
I was asking you
to pick up the barbell, not...
Sorry, Mr. Zhou.
I thought you were asking me
to pick up the phone.
What happened?
Fang Yong called,
cancelling the bianzhong deal.
Why?
I don't know.
Wait.
Zhu Yifei just refused to sell,
and he immediately said he wouldn't buy?
Could it be a concidence?
Besides, Li Penggai called just now,
saying he couldn't find those two guys.
In Sanjiangkou,
is there anyone I can't find?
Mr. Zhou,
the happenings in recent days
are so weird.
Is the person after us
really that powerful?
I mean...
When those two people are caught
and their phones checked,
there's nothing we can say to help.
Mr. Zhou,
it's time you took medicine.
I once went a week
without taking this medicine,
and I didn't have a relapse.
Do you believe it?
I've told you about it.
I spent an entire week
on that small island Gondwana.
I didn't have to think about
anything there.
I did nothing but eat and sleep every day.
I didn't take a single pill,
and I didn't have a relapse.
I swore at that time
that one day I'd stop taking this medicine
for good!
Jianren,
it is high time
for me to do so!
So you're planning
to go to Gondwana?
What if you have relapses again?
Nonsense!
As I said, relapses won't happen
again when I live in Gondwana!
Yes, right.
You'll be fine.
Where am I going?
Gondwana!
I got it, Mr. Zhou.
I'll skip town with you.
I've done all the preparation.
What preparation?
I learned English
for only one purpose:
by the time I'm with you,
there won't be a problem with communition!
You're insane.
People in Gondwana don't speak English.
Seriously?
Bro,
I feel so itchy.
Am I allergic to this?
Don't worry. You're not.
It's made from eco-friendly materials.
We only have these two IDs now.
What about the others?
In my suitcase.
This doesn't look like me.
And this even looks less like you.
What if we're identified
and reported to the police?
We'll have to take a gamble.
[Ruihao Boutique Hotel]
A standard room.
You IDs?
A deposit of 500 yuan.
Forgot to exchange for RMB.
I'll get some tomorrow.
Remember to do that.
Room 209.
Sorry about that.
Isn't that the blind man
I bumped into before?
[Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau]t
Li Qian.
Captain Wang.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to make a report to the chief.
Weren't you assigned to help
investigate Liu Bei's car?
[Police Visit Record]
[Visit Record]
Why would you work on this?
I think it's of great importance.
I know it's important.
So is obeying orders.
Get back to your work.
I will hand this over to Chief Zhang.
[Police Visit Record]
[Scrap yard]
Chief Zhang.
This afternoon near Dongxian Road,
we found an abandoned car
again, a Land Rover.
[Scene Investigation Record]
The car has been examined.
It's Lin Kai's car.
That taxi from before
was the Xiali sedan that ran over Lin Kai.
These two cars were both
tinted and modified.
Any clues in the car?
Four sets of fingerprints were found.
They're being compared one by one.
Four people?
What is this?
The stuff we found
in the trunk of the Land Rover.
A big box of makeup products,
plus many
fake IDs.
And this.
Today, Li Qian visited
the scrap yard
[Police Visit Record]
and nearby residents.
According to them,
Xiao Mao and Xia Tinggang
are just two street loafers
who can hardly count as hooligans.
They couldn't have committed
robbery and murder, right?
Chief.
Chief,
I really don't think
Xiao Mao and Xia Tinggang
are the murderers.
The killing was likely done
by two other people.
Should we expand
the scope of the investigation?
[That young man named Li Penggai often
comes collect scrap materials at my home]
It says here that when Li Penggai
[He seems honest]
first arrived at Sanjiangkou,
he worked for over a year
with Mao and Xia Tinggang.
Is it true?
It's known to all the old neighbors.
[Xia Tinggang]
After spending only a bit over one year
learning from these two men,
he managed to become the most favored
[Hu Jianren] [Lang Bowen] [Mei Dong]
security team leader
in Zhou Rong's company.
Are Mao and Xia Tinggang really
just street loafers?
Right now, we're looking everywhere
for them in the city.
It's been a whole day,
yet there isn't a trace of them.
Could ordinary street loafers
such strong
counter-reconnaissance skills?\
[Xia Tinggang] [Mao Hongwei]
[Suspects of the jewelry store robbery]
Such sadness in the eyes.
I can't read your mind.
Before new findings are made,
our focus is still on Mao
and Xia Tinggang.
[Xia Tinggang] [Mao Hongwei]
[Suspects of the jewelry store robbery]
That said, we truly
need to expand the scope of search.
Don't think of them
as ordinary street loafers.
Check all the inns and hotels.
I have a hunch that these two people
are experts in disguise.
Besides
their photos,
distribute pictures
of this suitcase as well.
Carry out a thorough investigation
whenever two men are found carrying
such a suitcase.
Got it.
Captain Wang.
You and the Chief can't treat me
like this.
I should be the one saying that.
Li Qian,
what's wrong with you?
You do the exact opposite
of what the Chief says
and you keep picking on him.
What are you trying to do?
I do it because you and the Chief
plan to transfer me off the front lines.
Who's planning to do that?
You and the Chief.
Did the Chief assign me
to watch surveillance footage
because Director Gao wants to keep me
from the danger on the front line?
Don't think I'm unaware of it.
Who told you that?
It doesn't matter.
Just tell me if it's true or not.
No, it's not true.
Chief Zhang only told everyone
to try to keep you safe.
This has nothing to do
with you being assigned
to watch surveillance footage.
Really?
Really.
See, you're actually
brilliant.
Why not use
your brain for cases instead?
When anything comes up, try looking
for the cause in yourself.
You think there are 4 suspects.
Is there enough proof?
Who are the other two? Where are they?
Why did they do it?
Can you explain all that?
Listen,
based on the current clues,
Chief Zhang's deduction is correct.
Don't make trouble out of nothing.
Just go watch surveillance footage.
Yes.