Run!
- Oh, dear!
- This way!
Go! Run quickly!
- Where is he?
Let's go!
Uncle, where is Vibhu?
What are you saying?
I brought you to this room
to save you from him!
And you're looking for him!
I'm sorry, uncle. Force of habit.
We left Manmohan behind!
Help! Help me!
Uncle, why did you lock the door?
Please let Manmohan come inside.
I locked the door for a reason.
If Khachedu comes inside
along with Mr Underpants,
he will bite one of us.
Why don't you get it?
Perhaps, this is what God wanted.
Angoori, stay strong.
Open the door, Bhabhi Ji!
No! Go!
Open the door! Let me in!
Go away! Fetch!
Why did you leave me alone outside
and lock yourselves inside the room?
If we hadn't left you outside,
you would've bitten all of us.
Uncle, try to understand
what I'm saying.
Vibhu, you need to understand
what we're trying to say.
We can't come in front of you.
Anu, of all people,
I thought you'd stand by me.
Your divorce is final.
You need to throw this man
out of your life, Bhabhi Ji!
Anu!
Oh, dear!
What if he breaks open the door?
Say positive things!
- Positive things.
Oh, God!
Please open the door!
Do it for my sake!
Anita, he asked you to open
the door for his sake.
I don't believe
in all that, Angoori.
It's a wife's duty to do something
if it is for her husband's sake.
Please! Don't leave me alone.
At least, don't leave me alone
when I'm in this condition.
Why are you so scared of me?
I'm Bharbhuti.
Anu, I'm your husband.
Come on.
- No.
You are neither.
You are 'desi ganna ras' for us.
I think you mean 'dangerous'.
You got it right!
Bhabhi Ji, move aside!
Come on! Untie me.
I am not an animal.
You're not an animal.
You're a werewolf!
Mr Tiwari!
I know he's behaving
like a werewolf.
That doesn't mean you call him one.
Anu!
- What?
Bhabhi Ji!
I didn't say anything
when he bit me.
But he bit my wife, too.
That is wrong, Bhabhi Ji.
Mr Underpants, why don't you get it?
Don't say that word.
Listen, Khachedu.
We won't say 'Bhabhi Ji'.
This is getting out of control.
That is because you keep repeating
the same word.
Which one?
- Bhabhi Ji!
Stop it!
Oh, God!
If you stop saying this word,
I won't bite you.
You don't understand
the trauma I'm going through.
What an irony!
Our day used to start
with this word.
Now, we're not allowed
to say that word.
Oh, God!
Bharbhuti is in a lot of pain.
I think we should untie him.
Look. He's 'bleeding' a lot.
If we let him go,
we'll be the ones left bleeding.
You mean to say 'pleading'.
- You got it right!
You keep your mouth shut!
Let this man rot here!
Mr Tiwari!
Sorry, Bhabhi Ji!
Stop it! I'm fed up!
What is wrong with you, Mr Tiwari?
Anu, untie my hands.
I'm very hungry. I want to eat.
No! Don't untie him!
He is not hungry for food!
He's hungry for a bite!
Don't let this werewolf go,
Bhabhi Ji!
What is wrong with you?
Why do you keep saying it?
You won't understand, silly girl.
Drop it.
You need to drop it.
Bharbhuti, I'll get something
for you to eat.
I knew it. I was sure
that in this cruel world,
you are the only one
who has a kind heart.
You are so sweet!
Bharbhuti, my dad says
God blesses us if we feed dogs.
I will get something for you.
I will help you.
Let's go.
Vibhu, don't worry.
I will find a cure
for your condition.
Mr Tiwari.
- Yes.
Stay with Vibhu and look after him.
I will make a few calls.
You... You take care.
So!
Bhabhuti!
Do you remember
how we used to go
to each other's house
all the time in Modern Colony?
Do you remember
what we used to say?
What did we say?
Try to recall.
Is Bhabhi Ji home?
Go on. Bite me now.
You gave me so much pain.
Now, I'm going to make
things very painful for you.
Bhabhuti, do you remember that song?
The song that we used to sing
and dance to in Modern Colony?
Try to remember that song.
What song?
Try to recall.
"Bhabhi Ji! Bhabhi Ji!
Is Bhabhi Ji home?"
"Bhabhi Ji! Bhabhi Ji!"
"Bhabhi Ji!"
What's wrong?
What are you doing here?
We came here you show you something.
I will give you a slap!
Get your mind out of the gutter!
We came here to show you this.
Look.
What is this?
Can't you see?
Can't you see what this is?
We were... We were...
Vibhuti has turned into a cannibal.
He doesn't see us as humans.
He thinks we're live kebabs.
We're lucky that we're here.
Otherwise, we'd be getting digested
in Vibhuti's stomach right now.
Oh, God! Vibhu has spared no one.
Luckily,
we're still alive, Bhabhi Ji.
We want compensation.
Compensation?
Why should I pay you compensation?
Bhabhuti bit you, not me.
Excuse me, sir.
Your manager attacked us
when we were on duty!
What if Tillu and Malkhan
contract rabies because of that?
They're not even married yet.
We have been attacked.
You have to compensate us,
as our boss.
Yes, you have to pay us.
Hang on a minute.
Where is it written that I have
to pay you a compensation?
The one who bit you will pay you.
The animal who bit us
is your manager!
Malkhan, don't call Vibhu
an animal.
Well...
Sorry, Bhabhi Ji.
Oh, dear! Did you all hear
thunder rumbling?
It is not the thunder.
Bhabhuti is growling.
Don't say that word.
Don't say Bhabhi Ji.
We will never say that word.
We will get ourselves treated.
I gave you Rs 10, didn't I?
Use it to get treated.
Excuse me, sir.
Roll up the ten rupee note
and put it in your back pocket.
Bhabhi Ji is right here.
Sir, we were attacked.
We want compensation or else,
we'll quit.
He's right.
No, wait. Boys.
Mr Tiwari. Vibhu's condition
is quite serious.
If they quit their jobs,
you'll have to do
the work of five people.
Hang on a minute.
I will pay the compensation.
What proof do you have
that Bhabhuti bit you?
What kind of a question is that?
Do you expect us to gather evidence
when we're being bitten?
Do you mean
we should have asked him to wait
when he was about to bite us?
Did you expect us to click a selfie
with him as he was biting us?
Is that what you want?
I need proof that Bhabhuti bit you.
If you got bitten by a stray dog,
and claim that Bhabhuti bit you,
does that make me
liable to pay you?
You have bitten me so many times.
Hey! What did you say?
What do we need to do?
Tell us what we have to do.
You have to gather evidence
to prove that Bhabhuti was the one
who attacked all three of you.
I will pay the compensation
immediately.
We will bring you proof.
Let's look for evidence.
We can check the CCTV footage.
Tika.
- Yes.
You may be thick-skulled, but
your pea-sized brain still works.
I got a dog bite
instead of a love bite.
Mr Tiwari will have
to compensate for it.
You did the right thing
by untying Vibhuti.
Mr Tiwari will have
to believe us now.
He has to pay the compensation.
Be ready to be bitten.
You're right.
Come on, Mr Tiwari.
What took you so long?
Take a look!
'Meet the TV that has it all!'
'VZY TV! TV time is back!'
Bhabhi Ji you praise VZY TV a lot.
Every other smart TV works
the same way.
What's different about it?
VZY TV has so many smart features!
If I ask you to bring about
that many changes in you,
it will take you ages to do that.
Really?
- Yes.
What are those features?
With VZY TV you get
one year entertainment subscription.
It's worth Rs 10,000.
More than 22 OTT apps
are included in it.
And it also includes
more than 390 TV channels!
Really? Does that mean we don't
have to pay extra for subscription?
Not at all!
Wow, that's a magical thing!
Look at its bezel-less
and monolith design.
You can hardly see the border
of the television.
It makes the screen appear bigger
and gives it a modern look.
VZY TV is a class apart.
Moreover, it even has karaoke.
Wow, that's great!
I'll put on karaoke and
serenade you with lovely songs.
You can serenade me later.
Think of a way
to boost our business.
Our business will grow
by leaps and bounds,
because VZY TV won't let our guests
leave the resort even for a second.
But for that we need guests.
When will we have guests?
They will come for sure.
As soon as we put up VZY TV,
they'll start coming in hordes.
Oh, dear! That's Manmohan screaming!
Why did he scream?
Bharbhuti, what happened?
Why are you crying?
- Bha...
Do you have coal?
Yes, I do. Why do you ask?
Bhabhi Ji, burn a coal
and give it to me. I'll swallow it.
No, I don't have it.
I've run out of coal.
Do you have kerosene?
- Yes, I do.
Please give me some.
Why? - I'll put it in my mouth
and set fire to it!
No!
I've run out of kerosene, as well.
When will my pain end?
Bharbhuti, how did you get released?
Who untied you?
I just heard Manmohan scream.
How come?
Actually, I bit his buttock again.
Oh, dear!
Why did you bite him?
Because Manmohan was saying
that word again and again.
The word that triggers me
into biting everyone.
Bharbhuti, I can understand
your pain.
What should we do
about your condition?
Bha... No. I won't say it.
I bit Mr Tiwari so many times
on his buttocks
that it looks like a couch
shredded by a dog!
I didn't even spare my own uncle.
I bit him, too!
And I bit you, too!
It's okay, Bharbhuti.
What can we do?
I can understand your situation.
You have no idea
what I'm going through.
I can't say the very word
that was my life's purpose.
I have wreaked havoc
by biting everyone.
I am not a cannibal, Bha...
I'm not a cannibal.
I am not doing this on purpose.
It happens involuntarily.
You know that I would
never hurt anyone.
I'm someone who spreads love.
I'm a lover.
Please love me.
What did you say?
Please help me. Help me out.
Bharbhuti, will you do as I say?
I always do, Bha...
I'll do as you say.
Alright. I'll be right back.
I think she has gone
to get something to eat.
Bharbhuti,
I have 'chased' this for you.
Did you chase a dog in the park
and snatch it from him?
No, I bought it!
You want to say 'purchase'.
- You got it right!
If you put this muzzle on
your mouth, you won't bite anyone.
Even if you hear that word,
you won't be able to bite anyone.
Who knew it would come to this!
How do I look?
You don't look good,
but you should wear it.
You really need it.
Where did Vibhu go?
We had tied him up.
How did he slip away?
Where will I find him?
It's courtesy of those boys,
Bhabhi Ji.
They untied Bhabhuti.
Bhabhi...
Bhabhi Ji, your dear husband
has given me a lot of pain.
The moment he gets a chance,
he bites my behind.
Did he bite you again?
He bit me not just once,
but thrice.
Oh, God! Mr Tiwari, are you okay?
Are you really asking me that?
I can't tolerate this pain.
I'm bruised all over.
I feel as if I might die.
Why are you saying this?
Vibhu's bites won't give you rabies.
Forget about rabies. Right now,
I can't bear the pain, Bhabhi...
What a predicament!
I can't say the word
that brings solace to my heart.
Mr Tiwari, you're mumbling
even when you're in pain.
Say it aloud.
I can't bear this pain!
I'm scared I might die!
Mr Tiwari, don't say that.
Can I help you get relief
from this pain?
Now, you've come to the point.
- I'm sorry?
What's the point, Bhabhi Ji?
I don't think you can do it.
I'm missing my mom.
Every time I was in pain,
my mom would put my head
in her lap and caress it.
She would sing to me.
And my pain would go in an instant!
Mr Tiwari, I have an idea.
Why don't you call your mom?
She can sing for you
and that will relieve your pain.
I think you didn't hear me.
She used to put my head in her lap
and caress my forehead
while singing.
That's how my pain went away.
She can sing on the phone.
But who will caress my forehead.
You're right about that.
What should we do?
- Why don't you
caress my forehead and sing to me?
No! I mean... I can sing.
I can't caress your forehead.
Bhabhi...
Mr Tiwari, don't get frustrated.
Try to understand my situation.
The oil you put in your hair
will make my fingers sticky
and singing.
It's out of the question.
My sari will be ruined.
Get rid of the sari.
- What?
I mean... Forget about the sari.
I'll wash it for you.
For now...
Let me put my head in your lap
and please sing to me!
Please don't cry.
Oh, God!
Mr Tiwari, please don't cry.
Let's give it a try.
By the way, which song did your mom
sing to you?
"My beloved says something to me."
"But I don't know what it is."
"My heart dances with joy!"
"But I don't know why."
Wow!
I mean... Your mom used to sing
romantic songs to relieve your pain!
Haven't you met my mom?
Does she look like someone
who would sing a lullaby?
She used to sing what she knew.
You can sing whatever song you know.
Alright.
Come on. Let's give it a try.
Let's go.
He's here!
- Run!
Why are you scared?
I won't bite you.
I'm wearing a muzzle.
Hi, sir.
Greetings, Vibhuti sir.
Hello, everyone!
Hey! What's wrong?
Why are you scared?
He won't bite you. He doesn't bite.
Sir.
Vibhuti sir, I'm sure
this muzzle is uncomfortable.
You have no idea.
I feel as if someone has
trapped my breath in a cage.
In that case, we will
free you from this misery.
What did you say?
Are you threatening to kill me?
No, sir.
Actually, you are
very important to us.
So, we are ready
to take off your muzzle.
But we have a special
offer for you.
Why are you being so nice to me?
Because you can do something
for us in return.
What do you want me to do?
We don't have any proof that says
you were the one who bit us
the last time. - I see.
Our boss will pay us compensation
only if he gets proof.
Our only request is
that you bite us gently.
Consider us your cute little pups.
- Right.
We will make a video.
We will show it to Mr Tiwari
and get compensation from him.
I will get 50%.
- He wants...
Excuse me! Why would you get 50%?
Why should we give you a share?
Because I will bite your
dirty and stinky skin
with my well-brushed
and well-cared-for teeth!
That's very unhygienic.
What if I contract an infection?
What will happen to me?
I don't even have insurance.
It's okay, sir. We're ready.
I will remove the muzzle.
You be ready.
I'm ready.
Say it.
Vibhuti is useless!
You live off the scraps
that Bhabhi Ji throws at you!
Oh, God!
Please bite gently!
Tika... Are you okay, Tika?
Tillu!
He is going to bit off
a chunk of my thick skin!
Gently! Gently!
We got the video.
Was the shot okay?
- It was great.