A wyvern?
It looks like a mage is controlling it.
What do you think, Chancellor?
Wyverns are fundamentally pack animals,
so one would never attack
a village on its own.
Plus, that mage is present.
There could be another threat nearby.
Think this is the work
of the Kingdom of Yelenetta?
Most likely.
Yelenetta's attacking this village?
Baron, there's a good chance this wyvern
has a small group of elite knights in tow.
Be careful.
Right.
Although at that altitude,
ballista bolts won't reach it.
That leaves one option.
We'll deploy the prototype.
EASYGOING TERRITORY DEFENSE
BY THE OPTIMISTIC LORD
EPISODE 10: A SECRET WEAPON'S
VILLAINOUS ATTACK ON THE HOMELAND
We'll soon be in enemy territory,
Your Highness.
The wyvern is already scouting
Seatoh from above.
I can't believe they made me lead
the invasion of such a remote village.
I'm Prince Unimog Yelenetta, eighth son
of Yelenetta Kingdom, for pity's sake.
The king commanded you to lead
this operation due to its importance.
Yelenetta Kingdom has long been rivals
with the neighboring Kingdom of Scuderia.
However, it is now time to settle things
with Scuderia once and for all.
You have been entrusted to lead
our glorious vanguard, Prince Unimog.
Conquering a remote village like this
will be a walk in the park.
We should be there soon.
- Whoa!
- What is that?
Wh-Why is there a fortress city here?
How did they build something like this
in this remote region?
You imbecile!
There's no way they could've constructed
a fortress city so easily!
They've merely built a facade
that makes it look like a fortress city.
We will advance and take their land.
- H-Hold on.
- Huh?
What if that fortress is the real deal?
You dare to defy me, you insolent oaf?!
I'm telling you it's all for show.
F-Forgive me.
Now, go destroy those ramparts!
We've barely made a mark on it.
I-Impossible. That can't be true.
Good afternoon!
I'm Van, the lord of this village.
That child?
What brings you all this way
from the Kingdom of Yelenetta?
Y-You imp! How did you know
we're from Yelenetta Kingdom?
So my guess was right.
I was just bluffing that I knew,
but you were quick to admit it.
This village didn't have ramparts
like this before.
How did you turn it into a fortress city?
Oh, the villagers and I worked together
to make the ramparts and facilities.
D-Do you take me for a fool?!
Get down here now!
Don't expect me to go on easy on you
just because you're a child!
My wyvern can attack you
from the air, you know!
Your ramparts won't save you!
Send a message to the mage
controlling the wyvern.
Get him to attack them.
But there's a chance
he'll be attacked in return—
Imbecile!
Wyverns are dragons!
There's no way it'd lose!
R-Right.
Now, it's time you learned
just how terrifying dragons can be.
Lady Panamera. If you would.
Huh?
Fire!
Wh-What the...
Those are shuriken.
They're thin and light, so I figured
I'd stuff them inside a bomb of sorts.
This was your "prototype"?
Yes. That's the first time we've used it,
but it seemed moderately successful.
That was a ridiculous amount of force.
That could prove to be as much
of a threat as an elemental mage.
Y-You.
You're the king of Scuderia.
Wh-What's the king doing
in such a remote village?
Now then, do you all want to continue?
You bunch of cowards!
What are you doing? Protect me!
What's this? You have plenty
of fight left in you, huh?
Lady Panamera?
- Whoa.
- The next one won't miss!
The baron is full of surprises.
You said it. Marquis Fertio
has sired one incredible son.
If I remember right, I heard the marquis
drove the baron out of his home.
I doubt he ever imagined someone
with a low-ranking magical aptitude
would be capable of such feats.
When we return to the capital,
we'll have to reconsider
our research into magical aptitudes.
Now then, Your Highness.
Might you tell us what your strategy was?
There's no way I'm telling you.
Well, that is unfortunate.
Viscountess Cayenne?
Should I rip out your fingernails
one at a time or gouge out your eyes?
Which would you prefer?
Please don't! Okay! I'll talk! I'll talk!
Yelenetta Kingdom has been planning
this invasion for several years now.
Oh?
We start by conquering this village
in Marquis Fertio's lands.
We assumed taking control of
this remote village would be easy.
Yet you were bested here.
How embarrassing.
Were you planning to invade
other territories as well?
At this very moment, a separate force
is attacking the city we're truly after.
Which one would that be?
The fortress city of Scudet.
My threats got the information out of him.
I see. So Scudet is their target?
I believe Your Majesty and I should
hasten back to the royal capital.
We should marshal our knights at once
and ride to the defense of Scudet.
I'm broadly in agreement.
But allow me to add one request.
What is it?
Baron Van Nei Fertio.
I request you join us
in our defense of Scudet.
Huh?
You're against the idea, boy?
Normally, I wouldn't be able to say no
in this situation, but I won't yield.
Because I want to hole up in this village.
I am greatly honored by your request,
but leaving this village while it's still
developing is akin to abandoning it.
Even though it possesses weapons
capable of firing holes in wyverns
and defenses that can fell
armored lizards and dragons,
you claim it is still "developing"?
Yes. I've barely completed
a tenth of what I envision.
There's much more
I'd like to make for it.
You really are amusing, boy.
I can't wait to see what you make that's
even more incredible than all of that.
However...
You should accept this request.
Every noble must come to
the nation's aid when it's in danger.
That's essentially the covenant you forge
when you become a noble.
Very well.
If it's a noble's duty, I'll participate.
However, I still have
my responsibilities as a lord.
Please allow me to organize
my troops myself.
You may do as you wish.
I finally got the village's
defenses all set up,
and now I'm being told to leave
the village and go fight.
At any rate, can I ask you to protect
this village as its acting lord, Esparda?
Of course, but will you
be all right without me?
Well, I am a bit anxious about that,
but only someone with your ability
can serve as lord in my stead.
I understand.
Dee, you and the Seatoh Chivalric Order
will come with me, right?
Yes, sir.
Till and Khamsin, it'll be dangerous, so—
I'm coming, too!
I'm coming with you, okay?
I'm coming, too.
Oh, right. Understood.
But will this be enough?
People in the royal capital won't claim I
showed up with too few troops, will they?
This will be more than enough
to those who know your might,
but to those who don't? Hard to say.
Excuse me.
Do you mind if we accept
a quest to guard you?
Huh? You'd do that?
Normally, we'd have nothing
to do with any wars.
But we don't mind accepting
a quest to guard you.
Ah, I'm glad to hear it!
Then, could you reach out
to the other adventurers, too?
Tell them I'll pay one large gold
and five gold per person.
You'll give us that much?
You're risking your lives, after all.
Thank you for this.
I'm sure everyone will gladly accept.
You're coming with us, right, Kusala?
You're forcing me to do stuff again?
To be honest, it's because I don't
have a suitable scout among my knights.
Well, that's true.
But if it's a quest, I'd at least like
to be asked whether I'll accept it or not.
Huh? But if you don't accept the quest,
you can't come to the barbecue.
What?! I'd miss out on the barbecue?!
Then, sure, I'm coming! Of course I am!
Boy.
I'm returning to Count Ferdinatto
to report all of this,
but after, I'll round up my troops
and head for Scudet at once.
Then, we might see each other there.
What weapons are you taking?
I'd like to take some
of my creations with me,
but I can't bring any ballistae
as they are right now.
In that case...
I'll bring my marionette.
Your marionette?
Wait, you mean...
This will be the Seatoh
Chivalric Order's first campaign.
Our mission is to defend our largest
neighbor, the fortress city of Scudet.
Our foes are knights from
the Kingdom of Yelenetta.
They've tested our nation's borders
countless times,
and unlike us,
they'll be very experienced.
However, there's nothing to fear.
We won't be going to the front lines.
What does he mean?
So how do we defeat the enemy?
Because our goal is for everyone here
to return to this village, safe and sound.
As your lord, I'm responsible for
the lives you're entrusting me with.
I'll do everything in my power
to protect all of you.
So cherish your own lives as well.
Then, once we're done with this battle,
let's develop this village together...
and enjoy another barbecue!
Scudet's been attacked?
Yes. The Kingdom of Yelenetta
has dispatched soldiers.
But Scudet's impregnable.
It won't fall that easily.
We'll marshal the troops
and ride out immediately.
Yes, sir.
Send emissaries to the neighboring lords
to request troops from them as well.
The village governed by your son,
Lord Van, is near Scudet, so should we—
That village won't have
any troops to dispatch.
They can barely earn enough to eat.
Still, according to the merchants
who came to the royal capital,
Lord Van has earned the title
of baron for defeating a dragon.
Drivel.
Van doesn't possess elemental magic.
There's no way he could defeat a dragon.
That may be true,
but Lord Van isn't a normal child.
He might have done
something extraordinary—
Just hurry up with the preparations.
We're heading to Scudet at once.
Yes, sir.
FORTRESS CITY OF SCUDET, SOUTH GATE
Impossible. Scudet's impregnable
ramparts have been...
Damn that Yelenetta,
employing so many wyvern squads...
We're withdrawing to regroup!
Yes, sir!
Scuderia's reinforcements are here!
Take this!
What's that weapon?
Lord Jalpa! Our forces
have nearly been wiped out!
Wh-What?
Is this the end?
They're leaving without finishing us off?
What in the world is going on?
FORTRESS CITY SCUDET'S WEST GATE
Wh-What is that thing?
Hurry up and summon
all of our wyverns here!
Yes, sir! At once!
Automaton: Uno!
Damn it.
Hurry up and crush that thing!
Arte, you're incredible!
I can't believe you can do that!
Who would've believed Scudet
could get conquered so easily?
They must have used those wyverns
and that new weapon.
It seems the damage on
the south gate side is huge.
Scuderia's knights should be
responding over there.
Although they'll probably be forced
to retreat with Scudet in this state.
I don't want to overdo it,
but if we draw the enemies to us,
that'll provide some support, right?
All right. Let's keep this up
and buy the knights some time to retreat.
- Yes, sir.
- There they are! Over here!
I'll protect you, Lady Arte!
I'm firing!
We're going to fight, too!
Yeah!
Aim for that group!
Whoopsie. Can't let you go doing that.
Sorry, but we can't afford to lose.
I feel bad for you.
Good work, everyone.
Thank you, Arte.
Damn it.
Crush them with all of our forces!
Ah, we lured a lot to us.
Well, I think we've bought them
enough time to escape.
Everyone, it's time to pull back.
Are we really running away?
We might actually win this, you know.
Remember what I said at the start?
Our number one goal is for everyone
to make it home in one piece.
If anyone dies, I won't be happy
at all, even if we do win.
Or does anyone here have a death wish?
Then, let's all run away
as fast as we can.
Yes, sir!
Lord Jalpa, what's our next move?
We must retake Scudet.
We'll reorganize our knights.
Make the arrangements at once.
Yes, sir.
Still...
I'm surprised we made it back alive.
What in the world happened?
Father.
Murcia? You're late. Where were you?
My apologies.
Marquis Jalpa Bul Ati Fertio.
You're making the youngster
cower, you realize.
Your Majesty, I apologize
for that unseemly display.
Marquis, you may rise.
What's the situation in Scudet?
Scudet has fallen.
Fallen, you say?!
Our knights were attacked by
their new weapon and nearly wiped out.
How did you manage to get away?
Well, for some reason, their wyverns
suddenly stopped pursuing us
and headed for the west gate.
They were most likely drawn there
by Baron Van's reinforcements.
- Huh?
- V-Van?
I suppose we haven't sent word
to your march yet.
Baron Van has developed that
remote village and defeated a dragon,
earning himself a title at a tender age.
But Van isn't an elemental mage.
There's no way he could have—
Marquis, are you suggesting we're lying?
N-No, I would never.
So Van has earned a title?
Young man, are you frustrated your
younger brother earned glory before you?
The opposite.
I'm very proud of him.
Ah, that certainly wore me out.
Lord Van, what are you
planning to do next?
I'm not sure.
I think I've fulfilled my duty as a noble,
but if Scudet isn't retaken, it means
leaving a threat nearby long-term.
Lord Van. This was my first time
actually witnessing war,
but to me, it felt like a terrifying place
where even innocent people are sacrificed.
I don't want to go there again
if I can avoid it.
Still, we're allied with Lady Panamera
who's involved in this war,
so I think we'll have to provide
some form of aid.
All right.
Let's develop a new weapon.
Next is the catapult.
Deliver some to the battlefield, and we
can claim we provided plenty of support.
It's rather big, isn't it?
How many are you planning to make?
I think twenty stationary ones
and five mobile ones should suffice.
Oh, but I guess it'd be difficult
to transport that many to Scudet.
The roads there were
in pretty bad condition.
Oh, right. I can just make them on-site.
That's right. That's an option, too.
Now, let's start our strategy meeting
in preparation for tomorrow!
TRANSLATION: JOHN PICKETT
TIMING: ANDY ELLIS
EDITING: SMR
QUALITY CONTROL: RILEY DALTON
TRANSLATION CHECK: REI MIYASAKA
NEXT EPISODE: THE ULTIMATE SQUAD'S
PROUD COUNTERATTACK