YUMI'S CELLS 3
EPISODE 10
RUDOLPH
Hey, Jang PD.
- We just arrived at the hotel.
- Ms. Kim!
Hi, we're at a pub. You should come.
- A pub?
- Yes.
It's close to the hotel.
Yu-mi? Tell her to hurry up.
The Chief Editor says to hurry.
- The chicken is here.
- Yes, come with Shin PD.
Okay, I'll ask him.
Let's go, let's go.
This is a chance to get closer
to Soon-rok while drinking.
Yes! Let's get some chicken!
They said there's chicken.
Your room is on the fourth floor.
The Chief Editor is at the pub now
and wants us to come.
Would you like to go?
I can take you there.
- What about you?
- I have some work to do.
If you come down after unpacking,
I'll take you there.
Forget it. Why go without Soon-rok?
You're not eating the chicken?
I'm tired too. I should rest.
- Do you want to do that?
- Yes. Please tell them I'm resting.
Sure.
You're not eating the chicken?
But I want to eat chicken.
Fourth floor. Door closing.
Where is your...
We're on the same floor.
I'm sharing the room
with the Chief Editor.
Oh, really?
That must be uncomfortable.
Such is the sorrow of a junior employee.
Silence again.
Isn't it strange?
The silence that was so unbearable
just a few days ago...
Why does it feel so sweet now?
- Shall we go?
- Yes.
Well.
Have a good night, Ms. Kim.
Yes, thank you for your hard work.
The sweet silence.
Soon-rok smells so good.
I wonder what cologne he uses.
Is Soon-rok's hair naturally curly?
SWEET SILENCE
IS SOON-ROK'S HAIR NATURALLY CURLY?
Soon-rok, take off your glasses
and wear contacts.
But it's Soon-rok's birthday.
Soon-rok's birthday isn't over yet.
We were together all day on his birthday.
- Should we just let it pass?
- Yeah.
We already got him a birthday cake.
Come on, that was the one Na-hee bought.
Isn't it too late to send a gift?
Wouldn't it be weirder
to just stay quiet and move on?
That's true.
Right. Doing nothing is weirder.
It'll seem like I'm still mad.
Something that he won't feel
uncomfortable to receive.
Like this one.
Is this too cheap?
Then...
This one's better.
But if a perfume isn't his taste...
he won't wear it, right?
This one is a bit much.
No, not this one.
But he doesn't drink...
at all, or does he?
Picking gifts is so hard.
What? There are only ten minutes
of his birthday left?
Let's just send anything.
It'll be meaningless to send it
after 12 o'clock.
Gosh, what should I send?
Right.
This one's the best.
It's safe. Let's pick the safe one.
SEND TO SHIN SOON-ROK
Hold on. What if you're just
waking a sleeping person needlessly?
And isn't he sharing a room
with the Chief Editor?
What if the Chief Editor sees it
and gets the wrong idea?
That's...
That's not right.
The wind feels nice.
- It's Soon-rok!
Soon-rok is awake.
The Chief Editor isn't with him either.
The timing is perfect!
What time is it?
It's 11:57 p.m.
There are still three minutes left.
- Yu-mi, let's send the gift!
I'm sending this
before your birthday is over...
Happy birthday.
- Press it!
Press it!
- He's reading it.
He's writing a reply.
Soon-rok is writing a long reply.
No, he's deleting it.
He must be thinking about it.
He's writing again.
He replied!
What did he say?
Thank you.
I'll enjoy the coffee.
Have a good night.
He sent a smiley!
It's a smiley, everyone. See?
That means you like them.
- Right?
- Right!
That night, a smiley moon
rose over the village.
This is crazy.
I feel good.
It's been so long
since I've felt this way.
It feels like my heart
has gone soft.
Chief Editor Ahn.
- Oh, Yu-mi.
- You're up early.
- Yes, please have a seat.
- Okay.
Ms. Kim.
Why didn't you come yesterday?
I was so tired yesterday.
I really wanted to go,
but I just couldn't.
That was a good call.
You drank a lot yesterday, right?
No, I've cut back a lot.
Ida gives me such a hard time about it.
- Ida's scary about that, right?
- Tell me about it.
- Would you like some coffee?
- Yes. I'll have an iced Americano too.
Thank you.
Gosh, the weather is so nice.
By the way, Ms. Kim.
- Were you just somewhere?
- Sorry?
It looks like you were outside somewhere.
Oh, no. I came here right after waking up.
Oh, it's just that...
you look so radiant.
I see.
You! I told you not to do this!
- What did I do?
- Look tired in front of the Chief Editor.
Don't you know the basic rule for writers?
Judging by your condition
it looks like
your manuscript is going well.
Oh, that's strange. That's not it at all.
I guess it's because I slept so well.
The water in Busan must be good.
I went to the sauna this morning too.
Don't I have a bit of a glow?
You're absolutely glowing.
Oops.
By the way, Shin PD...
said you're sharing a room...
Yes. I tried to wake him
but he said he'll sleep in
and skip breakfast.
- I see.
- He's a night owl so he skips breakfast.
Oh, I see.
- Let me have some too.
- Of course.
Sushi. The sushi's good.
Got it.
I got all dressed up in my
"effortless style" for nothing.
Since Soon-rok isn't even here
let's eat till we burst.
Ms. Kim.
Did you have a good night?
It's Soon-rok.
Glad I chose the "effortless style."
He's so cute.
Look at his messy hair.
His T-shirt is so casual.
- He has great taste!
- Jeez!
He just looks like he woke up.
What's the fuss?
You must like sushi, Ms. Kim.
Oh, the Chief Editor said
the sushi here is good.
I see.
But I don't like sushi.
So Soon-rok likes sausages.
He likes chicken too?
He doesn't eat vegetables.
He has the palate of a kid.
Even his taste in food is cute.
Is the chicken good?
I recommend it.
Even the way he speaks curtly is cute.
Gosh, what a cutie.
- Got it?
- Yes.
Let's go.
Hello.
Where's he going?
Oh, to buy some sandwiches.
For the people who skipped breakfast.
I think everyone will wake up late
- so let's have free time until lunch.
- Sounds good.
What will you do, Ms. Kim?
I'm going to take a walk.
I arrived late last night,
so I didn't get to see anything.
You should.
- You should enjoy the ocean view.
- I will.
I'm going to get some sleep.
Of course, go ahead.
I missed him. Darn it.
But he's nearby. Look for him.
Found him! I found Soon-rok!
Oh, there you are.
Ms. Kim.
I came out to buy coffee
and take a walk too.
I see.
- What would you like?
- No, I...
No, I'm buying for all the writers.
What would you like?
Then...
a light Americano.
I'll add one light Americano.
Yes!
That was very natural.
- The gift you gave me...
- Yes?
That café is in the spot
with the best view.
Over there.
- I see.
- I'll visit before going to Seoul.
In that case...
why don't we have a drink together?
- You were going for a walk, right?
- Yes.
I'll show you a good route for your walk.
I found a great course last night.
Do you like walking at night?
Yes.
I especially like the ocean at night.
I like the ocean at night too.
Then why don't we...
take a walk together tonight?
Rudolph.
- Rudolph, your order's ready.
- It's ready.
What?
His nickname is Rudolph?
Because his name is Soon-rok?
How insanely cute. Rudolph?
Even his nickname is cute.
That morning
Rudolph the Reindeer appeared.
- So cute!
Give me a break.
Yu-mi! Get a grip!
How old are you?
Why act like this over one emoticon?
Thank you.
Let me get that for you.
By the way, may I ask...
when your birthday is?
- Sorry?
- Your birthday...
Oh, my birthday?
Yes.
If you don't mind me asking.
There's no need to be so formal.
You can just ask casually.
But you're much older than me, aren't you?
If I may ask...
your age?
STRAWBERRY CREAM PUFF
EPISODE 11
THE ROAD TO SOMETHING MORE
Oh, my birthday?
Yes.
If you don't mind me asking.
There's no need to be so formal.
You can just ask casually.
But you're much older than me, aren't you?
If I may ask...
your age?
BIRTHDAY
AGE
Hey, did you all hear that?
He asked about her birthday formally
like she's an old lady.
And her age, too!
Do you get it now?
How Soon-rok thinks of Yu-mi?
A relationship? Yeah, right.
Isn't that just what you say
to a writer who's older than you?
If you have manners,
you should ask formally about birthdays.
And I think it's the same for age too.
And Soon-rok is very professional.
Oh, please.
So you're saying it's okay?
That's the first time someone's asked
for my age like that.
It's not like I'm a grandma or something.
Right...
I was going to ask how old you were
- but that didn't seem right either.
- Why won't that be right?
We're not that far apart in age.
Really?
Then, what year were you born?
Say how old you are proudly!
Take a guess.
As far as I know....
It's 199...
- There you are, Shin PD.
- Mr. Kim.
Hey.
He's here.
What a relief.
We've changed the subject.
If she can't even tell him, it's hopeless.
How can she date him
with that little confidence?
Hey, do something about him.
He's such a killjoy. It's so annoying.
I didn't see you come yesterday.
When did you get here?
I arrived around 11:00 p.m.
- I see.
- Did you sleep well?
I couldn't sleep.
I was drinking until late last night.
- Wait.
- You know her, right?
This is Writer Kim Yu-mi.
Yes, of course I do.
- Gosh, hello.
- Hello.
This is Writer Kim Ju-ho.
- Writer of The Invincible Baseball Team.
- Oh, hello.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I've only seen your pictures,
but seeing you in person...
- You're so beautiful in person.
- Oh, thank you.
I'm not just saying that. I'm serious.
I was curious about you, since
The Invincible Baseball Team is popular.
That's all in the past.
I'm planning to stop.
- I see.
- It should've ended a long time ago
but I need the money, so I'm stuck.
- Would you like some coffee?
- Yeah.
- I'll have an iced Americano.
- So this is where you were.
- You want coffee?
- No, I'm full.
- Just have one. Two iced Americanos.
- Okay.
- Ms. Kim, this is Kim Ju-ho.
- We've already met.
Shin PD is in charge of this team.
- Oh, I see.
- That's right.
You worked Soon-rok so hard
that he was taken off Yu-mi's team.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah. You should apologize.
Yu-mi is already so busy,
and you even took her PD away.
It's okay if you take him.
Let me know if you need him.
The writer's manuscript comes first.
- Really?
- Of course.
I've been writing this for so long
I can write it with my toes now.
- Bring him back!
- Then...
- Ms. Kim.
Don't believe him.
He gets generous only
when he doesn't have a deadline.
But later, he'll make a huge fuss,
asking who took our Shin PD.
Jeez, honestly. Good grief.
- Bingo!
- Goodness, stop doing that.
- What's with that guy?
Over here.
Gosh, I like our Shin PD so much.
- Thanks.
- But does Shin PD hate me?
Have some.
Ju-ho is so fickle
catering to his whims can't be easy.
Hey. Shin PD doesn't cater to anyone.
He just goes his own way.
He just plods along silently.
Look at him.
That's Shin PD's strong point.
He's got a strong backbone.
- Chief Editor Ahn?
- Yeah.
Let's go in ten.
- Everyone's at the lobby.
- Okay.
We'll be leaving in ten minutes.
I see why Soon-rok is expressionless
when he works.
I want to snatch Soon-rok away.
So Ms. Kim...
You said you both
went to the same school, right?
- Yeah, we went to school together.
- I see.
So you're from our generation then?
Sorry, but what year did you start school?
Sorry?
Wait. Why would you suddenly ask that?
Change the subject!
Well, didn't know we were alumni
and I found out at the publishing house.
Oh my, that bread looks so delicious.
Should I buy some?
When I got out of the army,
she was a freshman...
So a three-year gap.
Then we're only four years apart?
- Right.
- Hey...
For someone who looks so young,
you're surprisingly a bit old.
- Jeez, cut it out.
- Oh, what?
The three of us can just be friends.
What?
Friends with a four-year age gap.
- What is he talking about?
- Never mind that, look!
Soon-rok is...
counting Yu-mi's age.
Is he one of those Gen Zs?
No, that's how you mess up
the whole social hierarchy.
Jeez.
That writer talks too much.
It's draining my energy.
The age gap is pretty big.
Right? It is.
Okay, I admit it.
Is this even possible?
Even five years is already a big gap...
You can't fall asleep, Yu-mi.
You can't afford to sleep.
Why did you come all the way to Busan?
It's not time to despair yet.
Love.
You didn't know he was younger?
I'm asking if you didn't know.
Our Yu-mi
isn't an amateur anymore, right?
Yu-mi is a pro.
She may have gotten older
- but she has experience and wisdom.
- And also...
her invincible, youthful skin.
What you do with Soon-rok today
can lead to something, Yu-mi
- Right? That's true.
- There's a chance.
With confidence,
let's go for flirting stage!
- Flirting stage!
Should I text him and see
what he's doing after the meeting?
Hello?
Hello, Ms. Kim. This is Kim Ju-ho.
Sorry?
Oh, right.
- Hello.
- What are you doing now?
Right now?
Nothing much.
I see.
Well, we're not having lunch
until one o'clock.
We have a lot of time left, you know.
So for research, I was thinking
of going to Bosu-dong Book Street.
Would you like to go together?
Bosu-dong Book Street?
Yes. We should have
just enough time if we take a taxi.
Let's go together and just browse.
There are a lot of books there.
I'm sure you'll like it there.
Well, I'm not really...
Shin PD.
Two hours is enough
to look around and come back, right?
Yes, two hours is more than enough.
Wait, Soon-rok is going too?
If you go, who's going?
Me, Shin PD...
Dae-yong said he's busy, so he can't go.
- I see.
- Great!
Let's go!
Come on, let's go together.
You might get some ideas.
- Who is he talking to?
- Ms. Kim.
In that case...
should I?
I didn't have anything else to do anyway.
And I've wanted to visit Bosu-dong.
All right.
- See you in the lobby in ten minutes.
- Okay.
Great! We're meeting again naturally.
But Mr. Kim is in the way.
It's more natural
to have someone else there.
You need a third party
during the "flirting" phase.
That's experience and wisdom for you.
Shin PD, you should get a taxi.
Yes, I'm booking one now.
- She said she's coming.
- Really?
Yeah.
Hey, you're sure Ms. Kim
doesn't have a boyfriend, right?
No. She's my wife's best friend.
I'm positive.
Okay.
Wait. Get the taxi.
I'm just going to my room for a second.
- Work hard.
- Yes, I'll see you later.
Shin PD.
Ms. Kim.
-Where's Mr. Kim?
-Getting his camera.
He'll be back soon.
By the way, aren't you tired?
- Sorry?
- You got in late and got up early...
If you're tired, you don't have to
force yourself to go.
No, I'm fine.
If you feel obligated to go,
I can talk to Mr. Kim for you.
Please, no need.
It's just that I think
it would be good to go.
- I can use it in my manuscript.
- Busan?
Is Busan in your manuscript?
Yes, well...
I think it will be soon.
What happens in Busan?
I'm still thinking about it.
The female lead goes on a trip
to Busan by herself
Even though
she has a travel phobia?
Can you please stop prying so much?
Stop nitpicking.
Because I want to be with you, okay?
Do I really have to spell it out?
Well...
The taxi's here.
Shin PD!
Hello, Ms. Kim.
- Is that our taxi?
- Yes.
Let's go.
Go, go.
Ms. Kim.
Do you come to Busan often?
No.
I think I've been here
about three or four times.
I used to come here really often
when I was young.
My town had no baseball team
so I liked Busan's Cougars team.
- Right.
- Gosh.
I wanted to watch baseball back then,
but I had no money.
I couldn't take the Tongil-ho train.
I had to take the Bidulgi-ho.
The Bidulgi-ho must've taken forever.
Exactly. We'd kill time
talking with friends on the train.
I knew it.
- Sorry?
- I knew we were kindred spirits.
You know about the Bidulgi-ho.
I bet Shin PD doesn't know about it.
Do you know what the Bidulgi-ho is?
- The Bidulgi-ho?
- You don't, do you?
Is it the name of a ship?
See? His generation has no idea.
We were the last generation
to ride the Bidulgi-ho.
Was that around the year 2000?
It went out of service around then.
See? We're kindred spirits.
Friends, right?
Friends.
Bidulgi-ho?
Gosh.
We're totally contemporaries.
Not really.
Hey, that writer is so annoying.
Why does he put me in his generation?
Especially in front of Soon-rok.
Don't get swept up in this.
If he brings up the old days again,
let's just not respond.
- Guys, we're in big trouble.
- Why?
The place we're at right now...
is a haven for nostalgia.
Gosh...
This is Bosu-dong Book Street.
There are so many books here.
This place is amazing.
Look at these magazines. Gosh.
Oh, look at this! Gukjin Bread! Ms. Kim.
You know what this is, right?
Gukjin Bread.
Wow, I really loved Gukjin Bread.
You know, right? We'd take stickers
and ditch the bread.
Of course, I do.
I bought so many just for the stickers.
And you'd always get the same sticker
over and over again.
But wait, does Shin PD know this?
I've never seen it before.
Is it bread made
by the comedian Kim Gook-jin?
Kim Gook-jin?
See? He has no idea.
I'm telling you,
his generation's different from ours.
But...
I don't know either.
What? No way you wouldn't know.
No, I really don't know.
Was it popular in your generation?
We're from the same generation.
We're different.
We're obviously different.
Come on.
We're from the same generation. Ms. Kim!
Let's just browse quickly
and get out of here.
If we stay, I'll be stuck in this
hell of forced generational bonding.
MORE PEOPLE ARE MADE BY BOOKS
THAN BOOKS ARE MADE BY PEOPLE
I really like this street.
The atmosphere is great.
It would've been so nice
if I'd come here with just Soon-rok.
But where's Soon-rok?
You know this, right?
Guiyeoni.
Wow, they have this book here.
I mean, Guiyeoni is practically
our foremother, isn't she?
Well, I don't really know.
Come on, don't lie. No way.
I told you
we're from different generations.
But where did Shin PD go? I don't see him.
Shin PD left early.
- What? Where to?
- He had to go and left.
- But...
- Ms. Kim, you must be hungry.
Should we grab a quick
and delicious bite nearby?
- Well...
- Huh?
- Hello?
- Where are you?
I'm on my way back to the hotel.
- All three of you?
- No.
It's just me.
Just you?
He told me to go.
Gosh, that guy. All right.
Hello? Hey Ida.
Why are you calling?
Are you resting well?
- Are you having fun?
- Fun? I'm tired.
By the way.
You met that writer, Kim Ju-ho, right?
How is he?
What do you mean, "How is he?"
Dae-yong says Kim Ju-ho is a fan of yours.
He's apparently been asking
to be introduced for a long time.
- You met him there, right?
- I did.
How was he? How was he?
I've met him a few times.
He's fun and likable.
- Did you all conspire against me?
- What?
It looks like you all plotted
to set me up with him.
He suggested we do some research
but then the PD just disappeared.
- Oh my.
- So we had lunch and coffee alone.
- On our first meeting, like a date.
- Really?
You? Just the two of you?
Why is everyone so desperate
to set me up with someone?
Come on, what are you talking about?
He earns good money
your ages are compatible
and since you have the same job,
you'd understand each other well.
That's what we were thinking.
I see.
Your ages are compatible.
You're compatible in many ways.
Since it seemed like we're
compatible in many ways
the PD also made himself scarce.
That's what it is.
So...
- You don't like him?
- It's not that I don't like him.
Never mind.
Who am I to say whether I like him or not?
All right then.
Okay, bye.
Gosh, why did I come all the way to Busan?
Jeez.
Yes, Jang PD.
Ms. Kim, I haven't seen you all day.
I know. I was a bit busy.
Come on down.
We're going to dinner soon.
Yes, I'll be right there.
Well, I've got to eat.
They were together all day
and just came in a little while ago.
I wonder if it's going well.
What? Are they talking about me again?
Why is everyone acting like this?
I mean, he was just so excited.
Really?
The nerve.
Who does he think he is?
But don't you think
they look good together?
Not really.
What?
They don't look good together.
You don't think so?
Why? Don't they look good together?
EPISODE 12
IS THERE A CHANCE?
They don't look good together.
You don't think so?
Why? Don't they look good together?
No.
They don't.
Why? What is it?
What about them doesn't match?
Chief Editor Ahn.
- Oh, you're here?
- You're here.
How was fishing?
- Hi, Yu-mi!
- Jang PD.
Gosh, it's so hard to see you.
No, I was just looking for you.
Say hello. This is Writer Kim Yu-mi.
And this is Writer Bae Woo-joo.
- Oh, hello.
- Hello.
- I'm a big fan.
- Thank you.
- Everyone's over there. Let's go.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Hello.
- Oh, you're here?
- Oh, it's nice to meet you.
- Writer Bae Woo-joo.
- Say hello.
- It's our first time meeting.
- Ah, so it is.
- Yes.
It's big here.
Right this way.
- What about the other teams?
- They're all here.
- The restroom...
- It's one floor up, Ms. Kim.
Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Sure.
Coming to Busan was a good idea, right?
Of course. It was a great idea.
It was.
Oh, come on.
Hey, Ms. Yu-mi!
Over here.
Ms. Kim, come over here.
Wait, that seat looks dangerous.
Ms. Kim, this way.
There's a seat here.
It's dangerous.
They're from a similar generation.
- I'll sit here...
- Come on, go ahead.
This is by the door,
so we'll be going in and out.
Over here, Ms. Kim.
- Yes, come here.
- This way.
Hey, Ms. Kim is here.
I was waiting for you
and saved you a seat.
This is the seat of honor.
Thank you.
Hello, Ms. Kim.
- Hello.
- I'm so happy to finally see you.
But this is strange.
He definitely said
it was the seat of honor.
It's not the seat of honor
it's the old-timers' seat, isn't it?
Bingo!
This is a seat for people
who remember the Bidulgi-ho train.
What a load of nonsense.
- Kids don't know the Bidulgi-ho?
- They don't.
Besides the four of us, no one knows.
This is crazy.
The hell of generational bonding
has begun again.
Oh, really?
Thanks for your hard work.
- It was nothing.
- You worked hard.
- Let's cheers.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'd like to...
say a few words.
It's not easy to get all you writers
together in one place
so today is truly a moving day.
Of course, while some of you
know each other well
there are those
who are meeting for the first time
even though we're from the same publisher.
So I'd like to introduce
everyone one by one.
Who should I start with...
What about the order of
when we entered college?
- Sit down.
- Okay.
Okay, then let's start with Isabelle.
That guy, he's starting again. I'm so mad!
If we go by this order, Yu-mi is fourth!
Why me again?
I won't go first
unless it's for a beauty ranking.
Why are we ranking people
all the way here?
Let's just do it freely, freely.
Just freestyle. Freely.
Freely?
I'll just go first.
Hello, I'm Writer Kim Yu-mi.
It's a real pleasure
to meet you all like this.
Ms. Kim is so cool.
So you are an only daughter?
Yes, an only daughter.
I'm the youngest of five siblings.
I have three older sisters
and one older brother.
Oh, I see.
But how did you go from working
at a noodle company to writing?
I originally studied creative writing
so I wasn't good at anything
other than writing.
But if you were in finance
isn't that a bit far from writing?
It's a long story
and it's a boring one.
You know how it goes.
- Ms. Kim.
- "How it goes."
Do you remember that time? You know.
After that play in Daehangno
the Chief Editor, you, and me,
we had some drinks.
We went home
- on all fours.
- This isn't it.
It's too far to get close.
Today's a lost cause.
Let's give up.
Everyone, wouldn't it be better
to just go to sleep?
Yu-mi is so tired.
-I walked on two feet.
-You were like a puppy.
- A dog.
- Oh, come on.
Wait, where are you going?
- I'm just going to the restroom.
- With your bag and everything?
You're quite interested in my business.
Oh, yes. Go ahead.
- Cheers.
Ms. Kim.
Where are you going?
Well, I...
Is it okay if I slip out?
Oh, are you going to the hotel?
Yes, I've said my hellos
and I'm so tired
from walking around all day.
Go ahead, then.
Everyone's going for round two.
I think they'll be a while.
- Oh, then I'll take you.
- No, it's okay. It's right there.
But still.
It's fine.
Jang PD, you'd have to come back alone.
I want to walk. Have fun.
We're together, but we can't be together.
This is hard.
There's no chance
to even make eye contact.
Because Soon-rok isn't looking.
He's not looking at Yu-mi.
Because he's working.
Soon-rok is strict about separating
his public and private life.
Separating public and private life? Sure.
If he's so strict, would he leave
just because Ju-ho said to?
Didn't you hear him say
they don't look good together?
He said that because they don't.
Don't you know Soon-rok?
He's the type to only state facts.
Can't you just be quiet for a bit?
You're the one who should watch yourself.
It's just a one-sided crush anyway.
It's a relationship that will end
before it even becomes anything.
What do you know?
Hey, Yu-mi is a romance writer.
Don't you know the formula
for romance novels?
They have to give you an opening
to get past a one-sided crush.
Watch closely.
In a one-sided crush,
if they give some hope
it evolves into a flirting stage.
but if they don't
it just stays a one-sided crush.
- An opening?
- Yes, an opening.
Look at Kim Ju-ho!
If you're not hungry,
how about just a cool drink then?
- His attitude when they're alone.
- A cool one.
Ms. Kim!
- His effort to sit beside her.
- Come over here.
So you are an only daughter?
His curiosity and questions about Yu-mi.
That's exactly what an opening is.
The kind of things Kim Ju-ho gives.
Has Soon-rok ever given you
something like that?
Has he?
His attitude when they're alone.
It's all right.
My seat is over there.
I couldn't get seats next to each other.
His effort to sit with her no matter what.
Oh, I see.
Oh, right.
Yes.
Oh, I see.
His curiosity and questions about Yu-mi.
Has Shin PD ever done something like this?
Has he?
He hasn't. Not even once.
Right.
It means Shin PD isn't interested
in Yu-mi as a woman.
He said they don't look good together
because they don't.
- So we don't have a chance...
- Ms. Kim.
Sh... Shin PD.
Jang PD was worried
that you left by yourself.
But I'm almost there.
I know.
I was too late.
It's right around the corner.
Still, it's nighttime.
This is an opening.
It's not an opening.
It is an opening.
Ask him.
It's an excuse, right?
Didn't you volunteer to escort me
because you wanted to leave?
Well...
I can't deny that.
See?
The writers here are heavy drinkers
so it's a bit overwhelming.
I understand. It is overwhelming.
Yes.
Let's go.
Okay.
- Going up.
- Please get some rest.
Aren't you going up?
No, I can't sleep.
What are you going to do?
I'm thinking of watching a movie.
There's a theater right in front.
- What movie...
- Thomas' Game.
I was planning to see it
because it's a James King original.
- I really like James King too.
- I see.
I can't focus in crowded theaters,
so I planned to go before it ends.
But it turns out today
is the last day it's showing.
I see.
Well, enjoy your rest.
- Thank you. Enjoy the movie.
- Thank you.
Door closing.
Isn't this a real opening?
He's explaining the movie
in too much detail.
- Does he really need to do that?
- That's true.
Doesn't that mean it's okay
to go with him?
Let's ask to go with him.
Say that Yu-mi wanted
to see that movie too.
Isn't that too obvious?
But what if it's not an opening...
I told you it's not an opening!
There's no need to listen to cowards.
We have to be brave
when faced with an opportunity.
If Soon-rok gave you an opening,
you have to respond.
- Hello?
- Shin PD.
- It's me.
- Yes, Ms. Kim.
Did you arrive at the theater?
I'm on my way.
I see.
I came back to my room, but I can't sleep.
I wanted to...
see that movie too.
Should we watch it together?
I...
prefer to watch movies alone.
He wasn't interested after all.
-I knew this would happen!
-Hey!
You guys! What did I tell you?
Take it back! Just take it back right now.
Right?
It's more comfortable
to watch movies alone.
I was about to go, but I'm lazy now
and I might fall asleep.
Well, enjoy the movie.
Let me know if it's good!
- Okay. See you tomorrow, Ms. Kim.
- Yes, see you tomorrow.
Oh, how embarrassing.
You said he was interested...
I was a bit hasty, I admit.
So much for your experience.
You just keep getting it wrong.
I'm a mess.
How do you start dating again?
It's been so long,
you've lost your touch, Kim Yu-mi.
Oh, what now?
WRITER KIM JU-HO
NUMBER OF TICKETS
- Yes, Mr. Kim.
- Hey, Shin PD.
I heard you left with Ms. Kim.
Well...
- Yes, since it's late.
- I see.
She's probably not asleep yet, right?
But she's not answering her phone.
Bring Ms. Kim and come over here.
- Sorry?
- We're moving to a better spot.
You know the food stall
by the beach, right?
So bring Ms. Kim and hurry over.
Seems like Ms. Kim
can't drink much, though.
It's not about the drinking, okay?
Anyway, both of you come. Okay?
I'll text you the address.
Come together.
You must.
Ms. Kim can't make it.
Why?
She went to the theater to watch a movie.
It started. It's two hours long.
What?
- What movie?
- So don't call Ms. Kim.
She won't pick up.
Okay.
Yes, I understand.
NUMBER OF TICKETS
I wanted to...
see that movie too.
Should we watch it together?
I said I'm not going.
Just enjoy yourselves.
Ms. Kim.
You're not asleep yet, are you?
No.
Why?
Do you want to
watch the movie together?
He's showing interest, right?
He's not interested.
You said it's more comfortable
to watch movies alone.
DO YOU WANT TO WATCH A MOVIE TOGETHER?
YOU SAID IT'S MORE COMFORTABLE
TO WATCH MOVIES ALONE
Do you want to watch the movie together?
YUMI'S CELLS 3
It's still in the early stages.
But if it keeps growing
it becomes love.
Look at that, behind you!
Do you like me?
I want to date you.
I'm sad.
I haven't felt this fluttered
by Soon-rok in a long time.
This is so unlike Soon-rok.
Why are you interfering?
Ms. Kim, you're so cool.
If Shin Soon-rok feels the same
that's when the relationship starts.