Monitor,
do you want to go to the cinema
with me and Maomao?
I heard that action film
is thrilling and touching.
Don't miss it!
Didn't you agree
to play basketball with us?
What basketball?
Why didn't you guys
arrange it ahead of time?
Wait.
Didn't you promise to stay
and decorate the classroom with me?
Go to the cinema!
Play basketball!
I bought everything!
Go to the cinema!
How about this?
I'll decorate the classroom with you
from 5:30 p.m. to 6:30 p.m.
Then we'll play basketball
from 6:30 p.m. to 7:30 p.m.
After that,
I'll go to the cinema with you.
Okay?
Of course.
Besides, it's Saturday tomorrow.
We can play all night!
Late-night snacks!
You must be thirsty.
How about I buy you drinks?
Sure.
Thank you, monitor!
You're the best!
What movie?
What do you want to watch?
Chen Haowei.
I want to go to the cinema
with you tonight.
How did you know?
I'm in the same group chat
with Maomao and the others.
But they haven't sent me
the time and place.
I can tell you.
Send me a message.
I'll friend you.
I have a question.
What's the name of that student
in your class?
Just an outcast in our class.
He's a weirdo.
He always gets the last place in exams,
trying to draw our attention.
So, what's his name?
He Xiangyong.
Thanks.
I'll send you a sticker.
Check it out.
Okay.
[Wishing Upon the Shooting Stars]
What exactly did you come to Xingpu Island
to find him for?
Actually...
Who did it?
Who made this bitter gourd black tea?
You said she came alone.
Who are you?
Only He Xiangyong knows
I drink bitter gourd black tea
when I'm stuck.
How do you know?
Actually, I struggle with anxiety.
When I'm anxious, I'm like...
And I read in a book once that
bitter gourd black tea
can relieve anxiety,
so I decided to make you a cup.
I get you.
You're Xixi, right?
Wait...
You're wearing...
What's wrong?
You saw it!
Calm down!
No, we didn't see anything!
Chen Haowei, listen to me.
Did you just see a grumpy,
angry-looking girl?
I did.
That's right.
Did you see a girl running around
in plaid boxers?
Well, she...
Look at me!
Now, answer my question.
Did you see a messy girl with no makeup
who looks just like Xixi?
No, I didn't!
Great.
No!
That's good.
I think
Xixi might be hungry when she comes out.
Let's go to the kitchen and see
what we can prepare for her, okay?
Good idea.
Yes, let's go.
I have some ingredients.
So...
Well...
It's okay.
I'm okay.
Is she really Xixi?
Yes.
How long does she usually take
to get ready before going out?
[Stairway Corner Ice]
That's odd.
There is internet.
He hasn't contacted me for days,
and he hasn't come for shaved ice either.
I thought my phone was broken.
What are you thinking?
Is your phone broken,
or is it your brain?
You've been playing with your phone
all morning,
you know?
I'm not playing.
I think there's no signal.
No signal? Let me see.
The signal is great, full bars!
Okay, I got it.
Who's call are you waiting for?
I'm not waiting for anyone's call
or message.
Didn't I tell you
that
you can't just wait
and expect customers to come
but look for customers.
And this
also applies to
other situations.
You should take the initiative.
Understand?
Did you take the initiative?
Every time Xiaohai comes over,
I always greet him warmly
and friendly,
right?
Right.
He hasn't come
for days, right?
Who cares?
It's not my business.
I see.
Did you have a fight?
Stop...
Stop gossiping!
Just do your own things.
I'm already busy!
It was me.
I know.
Your phone is not broken,
but the tapioca pearls are going bad.
Hurry up!
Okay.
I'm going bad too!
Only He Xiangyong knows
I drink bitter gourd black tea
when I'm stuck.
How did you know?
Really?
1, 4, 2, 8, 5, 7.
What caterpillar?
You're still up?
Reading.
Did you put it there?
Oh, it's my collection.
Why is it there?
Aren't you scared?
Why should I fear a caterpillar?
Remember to turn off the lights.
Why are you trembling?
I just took a cold shower.
It's fake.
It's not real.
You've got this.
It's fake.
It's not scary at all.
But Chen Haowei is really...
really troublesome.
I'm such an idiot.
What am I thinking?
How could they be the same person?
Watch the stairs.
Welcome to Xingpu Island.
Wish you have a good time.
Did you forget anything?
"A Promise Beyond Time."
What promise?
The publisher likes
straightforward titles,
but my managing editor and I
prefer the one we came up with together,
"Desserts, Seeds, and the Prophecy Diary."
She's very famous.
She has a lot of great works,
like "The Hunter's Gentle Vacation,"
"Desserts, Seeds, and the Prophecy Diary,"
and "Goddess of Zandir."
I love reading her comics.
Y-You're my idol.
You're He Xiangyong, right?
Yes.
No!
I'm his friend.
He once told me about
the book you just mentioned.
I heard they sell well.
Congratulations.
No matter how someone's
appearance changes,
their soul remains the same.
As you know,
I care about my privacy a lot.
I'd never tell others about these things.
What happened to you?
Why do you look different?
I don't know how to explain.
But
do you believe that shooting stars
can make our wishes come true?
Interesting.
I want to hear it.
Anyway, I made a wish,
and it really came true.
The next day,
no one recognized me.
I'm also trying to figure out what to do.
So,
you can't change back?
Have I changed?
I think I'm still the same person
I used to be.
What was I like
when I was in the publishing house?
By the way, how did you recognize me?
The gift.
Thanks.
Thank you.
I don't like socializing.
Being my managing editor is hard,
but you've never complained.
You're just like Xingpu Island,
full of energy and warmth.
More people should know about
Xingpu Island.
And you,
He Xiangyong,
also deserve to be seen.
Stop here.
Goodbye.
[Only when you embrace the broken pieces
can you become a better person]
Zhong
Have you seen Xiaohai lately?
Who?
Xiaohai.
Have you seen him these days?
He took leave several days ago
and hasn't come back.
I need to find someone.
Took leave?
How's that possible?
Mr. De,
we're here for the beers.
Xiangyong.
Have some candies.
Your favorite watermelon candy.
Hong,
you've mistaken me for someone else.
Hong.
Do you also think he's He Xiangyong?
Plum candy.
Take it.
No need.
Answer my question.
You also think he's He Xiangyong, right?
Thanks, Hong.
The shooting stars in Xingpu Island
are very beautiful, right?
They have magic.
They can make your wishes come true.
Do you know what will happen
after that?
The person will...
But love will remain.
No watermelon candy?
Thanks, ma'am.
Thanks.
See you next time!
Hey, Mr. Li.
What big business
have you been dealing with?
I haven't seen you all day.
No business. Someone went missing.
I can't find him.
Missing? Then you should call the police.
I...
What if...
What if he doesn't want to see me?
I'll be so embarrassed.
So annoying. It's annoying when he comes,
and it's more annoying
when he doesn't show up.
Well, if you have a choice,
will you see him
or not?
Of course I want to see him.
Congratulations.
You like him.
No way!
I'd never like Hama-chan!
Hama-chan...
You two aren't fighting,
just being stubborn and moody.
Mom, you misunderstood.
I want to see him
because I want to beat him up.
I don't like him.
Fine, go beat him up.
He's waiting for you at home.
Here's your shaved ice
with green beans and tapioca pearls.
He's back.
Hamaguchi Aomi,
I'll beat you up!
Hamaguchi Aomi!
Hamaguchi Aomi
Yes!
Welcome!
Have a seat.
Here.
Sit down.
charcoal-grilled sandwich
from Yancheng District, Kaohsiung,
squid roll rice noodles
from Guohua Street, Tainan,
white vinegar cold noodles
from Wenhua Road, Chiayi,
oyster fritter from Wanggong Fishing Port,
Changhua,
jute leaf soup
from the Taichung Second Market,
Popiah from Hsinchu City God Temple,
and pork knuckle rice from Siping Street,
New Taipei.
These are all your favorites.
Are you crazy? You bought all of them?
I didn't buy all of them.
I also made some.
The jute leaf soup
was sold out,
so I begged the shopkeeper
to sell me the ingredients,
and then I made it myself.
Eat up.
This is why you took leave these days?
How did you know?
So, you care about me, right?
I don't.
I've never seen someone so heartless.
You just vanished.
You went to buy food,
not like falling into a black hole.
I'm sorry.
There were many cities to go to,
and the schedule was tight.
Most importantly,
I wanted to surprise you.
Try it.
Is it good?
It's good.
Okay!
[I like you.]
You...
I was trying to stump you.
Why did you take it seriously?
Whatever you want
to drink
or eat,
or wherever you want to go,
just ring this bell,
and I'll show up immediately!
Here.
As long as it's about you,
I'll try my best!
Idiot.
Then...
Did I pass the test?
You missed
Black Bamboo Chicken Feet Jelly,
stinky tofu from Heping Road,
and garlic pork thick soup
from Taishan Road, Yilan.
Sorry.
I'll make it up right away.
What's wrong with you?
Yes!
How can I help you?
Oh, water! No problem.
Hurry up. I'm choking.
Okay.
Sorry.
Have some water.
Thank you, sir.
Anyone here?
Hello.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
-Hello.
Mr. Jin?
Yes.
I need to check your ID.
Okay.
Thanks.
You can take a look around.
Chen Haowei.
Why are there guests?
I invited them.
What's wrong?
Didn't you see my note?
There's a fishing group coming,
so we can't take any new guests.
What note?
Where's my note?
My sticky note.
Why can't I find it?
Where is it?
It's here.
It fell down.
Honey, you're so good at picking places.
That's why I booked it.
Mr. Jin, Mrs. Jin.
Yes.
I'm so sorry.
We made a mistake.
We're fully booked today.
What does that mean?
We can't check in now?
We booked it a long time ago.
What do you mean by fully booked?
Why can't we stay...
Actually, you can.
But we booked it a long time ago.
You can.
Wait a minute.
I checked with him.
I called him,
and he said yes.
Then where should we go?
Let me contact
our friendly guesthouse for you.
They must have rooms.
Wait a minute.
But we want to stay here.
Sorry.
[Guest, Mr. Lin]
We're fully booked today.
But we booked it a long time ago.
Hello, Auntie Jiao.
This is Where Is My Home. I'm Xiaoyou.
Do you have an empty room?
1, 4, 2, 8, 5, 7.
Great.
We have two guests...
Aren't you a top student?
How could you make such a stupid mistake?
Just use Mr. Lin's money.
1, 4, 2, 8, 5, 7.
Chen Haowei, my money!
You're supposed to be responsible!
We've been looking forward to it!
We booked it a long time ago!
Chen Haowei.
Yes.
Didn't you see my note?
There's a fishing group coming,
so we can't take any new guests.
Go 50 meters straight,
then you'll see a yellow sign on the left.
1, 4, 2, 8, 5, 7.
It's settled.
Chen Haowei.
Chen Haowei, where are you going?
Chen Haowei, where...
Chen Haowei.
Chen Haowei!
Stop running!
Where are you going?
Chen Haowei!
I'll tell Mr. He
I'll be responsible for the loss.
No need.
You didn't mean to do this.
We'll shoulder it together.
I'll bear my own mistakes.
This is my principle.
Fine.
You should take a day off tomorrow.
Stop smiling.
It's okay to be sad.
You don't have to keep smiling.
I'm really fine.
Let's go to sleep.
By the way,
why did you run away?
Actually,
I have a panic disorder.
You're just pushing yourself too hard.
But
I didn't expect
you'd carry so much burden,
because you've always been so optimistic
in front of us.
I thought my life was miserable.
But after listening to your story,
I think I'm lucky.
However,
is there any other way
to deal with your symptoms
besides taking medicine?
Running.
I don't think about those things
when I run.
What if you get a cramp?
Are you serious?
I'm talking about
something painful in my life.
Do you realize
what you're saying?
Alright.
Let me tell you another one.
Listen,
when I was working,
there was a colleague
who would cry every single day.
I felt so sorry for him.
Eventually, I'd put
a box of tissues
wherever he might go.
Was he depressed?
Yes.
I have a panic disorder.
I'm not depressed.
That's right.
Listen,
depression is a constant low mood,
whereas panic disorder just hits you
all of a sudden.
Do you understand now?
Got it.
So,
don't stop me when you see me running.
But you almost ran into the sea today.
I was going to turn back!
Forget it.
I shouldn't have told you.
Alright.
Then
let's not talk about this.
Maybe I can tell you a joke.
Do you know why guards
are always chuckling?
Why?
They're standing at
the chuckling (checking) point.
It's not funny.
Listen,
Judy,
what illness does Judy get
if she works too hard?
Overwork?
Jaundice (Judy's) disease.
Let me tell you a joke.
One day, Xiaoming and Xiaohua
were riding horses.
Halfway through, Xiaoming shouted,
"Rein in! Rein in!"
Then Xiaohua said,
"It's not raining."
Then he fell off the cliff.
Isn't it funny?
Why do penguins always look so smart?
Why do they
look so smart?
Because
they're always wearing suits.
What a bad joke!
Do you know the color of toilet paper?
Why did the phone go to therapy?
Depressed?
Because it had
too many hang-ups.
He!
Chen Haowei.
Turn off the alarm.
Sorry, it's mine.
Well...
Sorry to bother you.
Have you seen Mr. He?
You just woke up. How could you see him?
I'll look for him.
Wait, Uncle Hua.
It's okay.
It's not what you think.
I know what happened.
Maybe it was too cold last night.
Be careful.
I never came.
Bye.
I'll brush my teeth.
I've been looking for you.
Why did you drink so much?
Didn't you go to the main island
to find your son?
Did you have a fight again?
If he knew I made a decision,
he'd come back to quarrel with me.
What decision?
Tell me.
I'm going to sell my house.
[Epilogue]
I'm bad at playing basketball.
I always lose.
I was lucky this time.
Maybe you'll win next time.
Having fun is all that matters
when playing with friends.
Winning is not that important.
You're right.
Besides,
your hands
aren't meant for playing basketball.
You have a pair of Takehiko Inoue's hands.
Give me a hand.
Okay, wait for me.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Chen Haowei!
I forgot something.
What did you forget?
I can help you.
It's okay. No need.
I'll go back to get it, okay?
Caterpillar?
Are you afraid of caterpillars?
What caterpillar?
Look at the cockroach!
Why did you lie to me?
I need to pay 5 million TWD?
[Next Episode]
Sir.
Sorry, I'm the president.
Take a photo of this dangerous building
and see if there's any place to change.
Do you know this is an ancient relic?
You know nothing, huh?
I don't think you should
invest in real estate.
I finally found you.
I won't let you go this time!
He Xiangyong!