(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
Damn it. Seriously?
CHOI TAE-HO
MR. OH, HWANG YANG-JUNG
LEE DU-YEONG, HYEON-JU
- Aren't you going home?
- I was just house-hunting, sir.
Man, it's not easy
buying a house nowadays.
Taking a honeymoon?
My wants us to go to Paris,
but I don't think we'll go with COVID.
Ugh, goddamn COVID.
How come you're here so late, sir?
So, something big came in.
I've been keeping tabs on a loan shark
for about half a year now,
and this fucking asshole
takes videos of people,
so he has something to threaten them with.
And today I happened to receive
a list of all the asshole's victims.
I'll share it with you.
I'll organize the data,
and we can dive into it together.
Sounds good, sir.
- Get back to searching.
- Will do.
Mm.
He said he got the list today.
He probably didn't do it alone.
Find me the asshole who helped him,
and I'll pay you 100 million per person.
Yes, sir.
When will you get Oh In-muk's location?
I think I can find
his credit card locations
of the last seven days…
probably by tomorrow morning.
I'll pay you as soon as I receive it.
Good luck.
A hundred million.
What's up?,
The only person who knew
where hard drive was, was Jang-do.
The asshole must have snitched
when President Choi nabbed him.
The fuckers who were with him
teamed up with Hong. Fucking shithead.
Oppa.
You said there's only one hard drive?
There's only one hard drive.
But everything's backed up on a laptop
that we use to transfer the videos
to the drive.
Oh!
For now, we should just stay put.
If we release that video
at the wrong time,
then that son of a bitch, Hong,
is going to hit us with a tax audit.
Stupid motherfucker.
Oppa,
wouldn't it be better to let them know
you still have the video?
You need to scare them.
You're a smart cookie, aren't you?
A toast!
- And cheers!
- Cheers!
ADDRESS, MART
GAS STATION, RICE STORE
GOHEUNG GROCERIES
Have you seen this person before?
Uh, I'm not sure.
Our customers walk around in masks,
so it's hard to tell.
Oh, yeah? Is that so?
Ah, fuck me.
Right, take another look.
Oh.
I really don't know.
You think this is funny?
- Excuse me?
- Do you think this is fucking funny?
Uh, no, that's not what I--
Goddammit.
Eyes down, shithead.
Look. Do you know him?
I… I don't know.
Yes or no, you little fuck!
Get up, get up, get up!
- Do you know him or not?
- I don't know him.
Do you know him or not, you piece of shit?
I said look at him. Look.
Speak up, you fucking shit.
Ah, fuck this.
Look at the picture.
- Hello, sir.
- Oh, hello. Welcome.
- I'd like to ask you something.
- Okay, okay.
I'm looking for someone.
He's a friend of my dad's.
Oh, yes, I know him.
- You know this man?
- I do, but what's this about?
Well, I'm getting married,
and I'd like to send him
a wedding invitation.
Oh.
Do you know where he lives?
Of course. After all,
I deliver rice there every month.
Could I get an address from you?
Oh, sure. I'll get it for you.
BLOODHOUNDS
He's here.
Kang In-beom's profile.
His info right, right, right here, guys.
Ah.
You work fast.
Every second counts
in situations like this.
- Thank you very much.
- All right.
- It's done.
- Yeah.
This is it?
Huh?
Ah, so you don't know?
Normally, when you make
someone do something like this,
- You give a little token of thanks.
- Oh, right. How much should we give you?
You know, a one piece.
I mean, we're… we're a team and family.
A big one will do. Yeah!
- Okay, all right.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Hey, call me whenever you need something.
- Will do. Have a nice day.
- Good night, then.
Mm.
Fuck, man. I meant a million won.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
KANG IN-BEOM
She told us not to use it though.
We have to look at it on a big screen
to get a better look at his neighborhood.
Right. What if Da-min comes in
while we're at it.
She won't. We got caught before
because she was passing by.
It was bad luck.
- "Gangdong-gu, Seonggu-ro."
- "Seonggu-ro."
I told you she'd come.
Turn it off.
Oh, God.
Uh, what are you doing?
It smells like lonely men in here.
Why are you using the computer again?
I told you not to.
We're sorry.
Also, sorry about the lonely man smell.
Damn.
Whatever. This room is ruined.
It's ruined.
Da-min!
- What is it?
- I'm also sorry about today.
I'll take care of this putrid smell.
How will you?
A diffuser.
A diffuser will get rid of
this sad old-man smell.
Really?
First of all, to get rid of a bad smell,
you just have to find
an opposing good scent.
This sad old-man smell is
basically a blend of a thick, musky odor
with slight, unintentional undertones
of rotten wood.
To get rid of it,
we need the opposing scent.
Something floral and fruity.
I use Baies, Baies from Diptyque.
- I like that one.
- Well, all right.
Then we're in luck!
The fresh sweetness in the Baies
will cancel out
all the sad old-man smell here.
We'll get you one
when we leave this place.
- A gift.
- Yeah.
We'll get you one for the ground floor,
one for the top bunk.
Bathroom too.
Okay, three it is.
Deal.
Dude, how does Kang In-beom
know my number? He's calling now.
Whoa, no way.
Something must be wrong here, right?
Oh god.
What's wrong with Grandpa?
Who did this to him?
Uh…
No!
Come to Incheon's
Four Garden shopping mall in one hour.
Call the cops, and the old man dies.
You're fucking dead.
Uh…
Uh, Da-min, you should tell us
what he said too.
He said to come to Four Garden mall
in an hour.
He said if we call the cops,
he'll kill Grandpa.
Come on.
There's not much time.
Gun-woo.
- How many do you think will be there?
- Uh, at least 30.
They'll probably have weapons.
and, uh, Kang In-beom and Mr. Jung
will probably be there.
Do you think it would be a good idea
to call Gang-yong?
No, that would put Mr. Oh
in too much danger.
- What about our senior?
- Which senior?
You know, Mr. Moon.
But he hurt his arm, right?
Wouldn't he help in any way that he could?
Uh, that's true, but…
You two ready?
Yes, but Da-min, what's the bow for?
For rescuing Grandpa.
Uh, no. There's no way.
We'll go just the two of us.
It's too dangerous for you.
Move over.
Da-min, why would you--
Whoa!
I also know how to fight.
I'm coming, so don't try to stop me.
What are you doing? We don't have time.
Hey, she's a good shot.
Hey,
I think she'll be useful.
Hello, sir, it's Woo-jin.
Mr. Oh…
…has been kidnapped.
Can you, uh, help us in any way?
I'm also indebted to Mr. Oh.
Don't go in without me, no matter what.
That's an order.
MOON GWANG-MU
734TH CLASS SENIOR
My Junior Marines, you're finally here.
- Yes, sir.
- Wow, sir, you've really gone all out.
Oh, yeah, I had this lying around.
It really itches. I think it's pretty old.
Should probably take it off soon.
Through the underground parking lot,
I'll--
Wait, who are you?
I'm here to rescue my grandpa.
She's Mr. Oh's granddaughter.
Oh. Oh, right.
Your faces are similar. I can see it.
It's almost been an hour.
Right, right.
And what's in the bag?
It's a compound bow.
A guobaorou?
Compound bow.
Guo--
Sir, it's a competition bow.
Uh-huh.
Oh, right.
Koreans are really good at archery, yeah.
Is she a good shot?
She is.
All right, so Archer and I will take
the stairs from the parking lot
and make our way
to the top of the building.
Our two Marines,
you charge in through the front gates.
We'll cover fire from the top. Understood?
- Yes, sir.
- Let's move.
Go.
- Follow me.
- Okay.
- This way.
- Right, okay.
Where is Mr. Oh?
Kill them!
One, two, three!
Wow.
- Good job.
- Get them.
Where? Who is it?
What is it?
Where is it coming from?
Hey, hey!
Up there!
Get the black one. The black one.
Who is it? Who's doing this?
The blue one there. There, the guy there.
Damn it.
You keep helping out the juniors, okay?
Oh, fuck. Fuck!
Hey there, blue boy.
Are you on the track team or something?
Fucking shit!
Get lost!
What are you doing? Get up.
Shit.
Shit!
Guess you need a knife to beat me,
huh, tough guy?
Then pull it out, asshole.
Come on.
You've got pride, after all.
Let's go.
Oh, hey, are you…
…are you all right?
Not really.
One, two, three, four!
All right. Track guy.
Hey! Hey, hey, hey, asshole. Wake up!
Come on. Up, up, up!
Up!
So where's Mr. Oh?
Look at this asshole.
Does he think he's being a tough guy
or something?
- Hey, Archer, give me an arrow quick!
- Huh?
I'll give it back.
I just need it for a second.
All right, let's see
what a loyal bloodhound this guy is.
I was like you, you know?
Well, back when Mr. Choi was alive.
But do you know what becomes
of a bloodhound that's lost its master?!
It becomes a filthy stray
that mauls everyone in sight.
Oh!
Oh, no. No!
This isn't pain that you're feeling.
It's just shock.
The real pain comes
when I pull this bad boy out!
Hey guys, could you…
please cover Archer's ears for a second?
You married, shithead?
Because the important thing
in the whole world is family.
But without this, buddy,
you'll never be able to make one.
So, work or family?
You better choose wisely.
I gotta admit, you choose work right now,
that's gonna make you a real pro.
But obviously, in that case,
I'm gonna have to puncture your balls.
"Why?" you ask. Because I'm also a pro.
All right.
You got three.
Three,
two,
one.
- Wait!
- What? Why, why, why?
I'll talk, yeah.
Tuck down, asshole.
Get inside, hurry!
I said fuckin' tuck down.
Uh, sir, we'll go
and save Mr. Oh right away.
Can you hold on to Kang In-beom
in the meantime?
What are you talking about?
I'm coming with you guys.
We're gonna do it ourselves.
Your arm's in bad shape, sir.
Fuck me.
Uh, sir, Kang In-beom knows
where Kim Myeong-gil's slush funds are,
plus the location
of the safe containing those funds
and Mr. Choi's gold.
Please get all that information out of him
using your Marine tactics.
We need you, sir. Please.
All right.
You got it.
You just get him back, okay?
- Yes, sir.
Let's go. Da-min.
NATIONAL POLICE AGENCY
Here.
What do you think?
Sir, I've seen him this prick
standing next to the chief of staff.
The chief of staff?
Yes, sir. The hooked nose and those ears.
I'm positive.
Why would a scummy loan shark bribe
the presidential office?
I bet he sticks his nose everywhere.
Or he could be a bigger player
than we actually realize.
HEAVY DRINKER GUN-WOO
What's up?
Hey, man, sorry for calling you
at such a late hour,
but we didn't know what to do
in this situation, so we had to reach out.
- What?
- Kim Myeong-gil, he kidnapped Mr. Oh.
So I'm heading to Seoryeong
with Woo-jin right now.
Just the two of you?
Why the hell
are you only telling me this now?
I'm sorry,
but they told us that they'd kill Mr. Oh
if we said anything to the cops.
Hold on.
Did Kim Myeong-gil call you himself?
No, no. We managed to capture
one of his thugs.
He's the one who told us.
So, you don't know for sure
if Kim Myeong-gil will be there?
No.
Send me the location. I'll head over now.
Don't go in. Just wait for me, okay?
Okay.
- Dude, text him the info.
- Okay.
Sir.
Jae-min,
come down to the meeting room right now.
All right, sir.
Hey, listen here. Call in some backup.
It's Buseong-myeon in Seoryeong.
It's about that thing
I mentioned last time.
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
When did you see them?
About a month ago.
LIEUTENANT KIM JAE-MIN
Mm.
MR. KIM MYEONG-GIL
The cops are on their way.
Okay, got it.
Yo, the cops are comin'. Clean up!
All right.
Check if there's a back entrance.
- Come on, quick. Quick, move out.
- Hurry up.
Turn off the engine.
Sorry.
Hey, we'll see what's going on inside.
Wait here.
We just searched the place.
There's nothing here but a flatfish farm.
Oh…
Maybe this guy will know something.
Who the hell is this asshole?
Kim Myeong-gil's thug.
The one who stabbed me.
I'm a cop, and I've got some questions
you need to answer.
You prick, nod your head.
Is Seoul Fish Farm the right place?
Did anyone know that we were coming?
Gang-yong.
This guy's crew gave us the slip
in the middle of the fight.
They might've given them a heads-up
before we got here.
Let this guy out and leave now.
You guys weren't here. Is that clear?
- Okay.
- Are you hurt?
- No.
Han-gu.
Where is Grandpa?
We need to wait a little more.
The detectives should get back to us.
We don't have much time.
We have to find him.
No matter what it takes.
The safe! Where's the safe?
Come on, you fuckhead.
Where's Kim Myeong-gil's safe?
Damn it! Come on!
Listen, asshole, if you keep this up,
you're gonna end up dead, you hear me?
Okay, give me a cigarette.
You piece of shit!
- Hit me!
- Fuck him!
Hit me harder!
BEST PORK
BEOMSEUNG DISTRIBUTION
How'd it go?
Why isn't Mr. Oh with you?
Uh, we couldn't find him.
I think his thugs caught on to us
and took him somewhere else.
Damn it.
That gym rat say anything?
That's one stubborn fucker in there.
He won't say a word.
Having fun, huh?
- You want fun? I'll show you fun.
- What the hell are you gonna do now?
Shit!
Sir! That idiot, he bit his tongue.
- Fuck!
- Come on, sir!
Goddammit! Fuck!
- Hey! Hey!
- Fuck.
- Hey, Kang In-beom, snap out of it! Hey!
- Damn it!
- Dude, call an ambulance now.
- Okay.
Uh, wait! Wait, wait!
If we just send him off,
how will we find Kim Myeong-gil's safe?
Still, we can't just stand here
and let a person die, sir.
If he dies like this,
we still won't be able to get to the safe.
Okay, give it to me quick.
- You gotta let me get him down.
- Fuck!
Okay. Come on.
Sir! Sir, are you all right?
Sir, wake up! Are you okay?
Hello.
- Hello.
- Where's the owner?
Oh, yes, she went on vacation.
Oh.
I'd like an iced hand-drip coffee
with Ethiopian beans.
All right.
- Here you go. It'll be right out.
- All right. Thank you.
MY HAPPY FAMILY, I'LL KEEP YOU SAFE
CEO KIM MYEONG-GIL
ATTACHED FILE: 1 VIDEO FILE
Oh shit!
Hey, Min-beom.
Kim Myeong-gil still has the video of me.
He just sent it to me.
Uh, but how?
Hello?
- Gang-yong?
-
- Hello?
Damn it!
Fuck.
Motherfucker.
Salt.
What?
Salt!
Someone's been hit by a car!
What happened?
Oh my God! I think someone died.
MR. OH
Gun-woo, hurry. Look.
Hey, shitheads.
Why make a big problem out of nothing?
What do you want from us?
Come to the fish farm today at 9:00 p.m.
If you decide to call the cops again,
I'll grind up the old man
and feed him to the fish.
You got it?
I've gotten rid of Min Gang-yong
and all his cronies,
so there's no one else to help you.
Oh, and one more thing,
if you mess around, your mom's next.
See you there.
GANG-YONG
How'd he get to Gang-yong? He's a cop.
Dude, I think things
might get really dangerous.
We should really go alone this time.
Excuse me?
How long have you been there?
The whole time.
Don't even try to leave me out.
I'm going to rescue Grandpa.
Come with me.
Listen, Woo-jin,
if something bad were to happen
to Mr. Oh right in front of us,
Da-min's definitely going to
break down like Hyeon-ju did and I…
I never want to see
something like that happen again.
But Gun-woo,
one thing that's different from back then.
You know what that is?
Back then,
the invincible Marine duo were apart.
That's not the case now.
And we're stronger. A lot strong.
You remember, right?
One, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three, four, five!
Look,
let's work together,
so we can save everyone.
Mr. Oh, Da-min,
the people that Kim Myeong-gil hurt.
Ack?
Ack!
Why'd we stop?
Woo-jin and I are gonna head in first.
Keep a look
until you find a good spot to shoot from.
That's when you move in.
Sounds good.
You should get out.
They could've dropped me off closer.
- Good thinking.
- Hm?
Dropping Da-min off far away
so that she doesn't get hurt.
Uh, I just didn't want her
to end up getting caught.
Was it too far?
It'll take her ten minutes.
Then let's get this over with fast.
Okay.
Kill them!
Get 'em.
These guys have a shit ton of weapons.
Dude!
Son of a bitch!
I'm gonna fuck you up, man!
Oh shit.
Hey.
You can't even get rid of two kids?
I'm sorry, sir.
Sorry isn't fucking good enough.
Now then.
Come on!
Now,
you punks come any closer,
and I'll slit the old timer's throat.
You understand me?
Too bad. I wanted to do it.
Hurry up and kill them, you stupid fucks!
What are you waiting for?
Do I have to kill them? Huh?
You sons of bitches are just unbelievable.
Hey, duck!
You fuckin' son of a bitch!
Come here, you fucker! Come here!
I told you to hurry up
and kill them, you assholes!
What are you doing? Let go, motherfucker!
I said let go of me!
Kill them! Come on!
Grandpa!
Grandpa, are you okay?
It's me, Da-min.
Oh.
You pulled out my eyebrows.
Mr. Oh, are you all right?
Thank you.
Hurry up.
- What's this?
- All right. All right, come on.
Come on, get on it.
Hurry up and untie them.
Who is it?
Delivery.
Ah, what the fuck.
Stay still, you fucking asshole!
Do a full sweep,
including the interior!
- Scour every inch!
- What is this place?
I found it! Everyone over here!
Oh, God.
What the hell? These guys are psychopaths.
What were they doing here?
Ma'am, we from
the Serious Crime Investigation Division.
I have a search warrant.
As of right now, your property
will be subjected to search and seizure
We'd appreciate your cooperation.
Let's go.
Come on. Hurry up.
Mr. Kim Jae-min?
You're under arrest
for murder, bribery, kidnapping.
Fuck me. This is so fucked up, man.
Let's go.
- Sir, check it out.
- Wow.
NATIONAL POLICE HOSPITAL
Luckily we got the warrant quickly
and went into Kim Myeong-gil's house.
A bunch of cell phones were found
in his closet.
We traced the numbers.
And they all belonged
to dead or missing individuals.
This crazy asshole.
He was storing the phones
that belonged to the people he killed.
He can't escape this.
Not even the American president
can help him.
Could go overseas.
He's a wanted man now. It won't be easy.
Criminals frequently go to China
on cargo ships, don't they?
Kim Myeong-gil is
a grade-A wanted criminal.
We'll be focusing surveillance
on potential stowaway routes.
He won't get out of Korea that easily.
But it's not completely off the table.
You all seem to think this is all over,
but I'm really on edge right now.
That bastard still has that video of me.
If he releases it at any time,
it's all over for me.
Brother.
I really have to see
that maniac behind bars.
Min-beom.
I understand.
But just look at Han-gu's condition.
And Tae-yeong is still in a coma.
We just need some time.
We're gonna help find him.
It's not over till it's over for real.
Um, is there any way you could find out
where Im Jang-do might be?
Why do you need Im Jang-do?
Im Jang-do's probably in hiding somewhere
trying to stay away from Kim Myeong-gil.
I think maybe Im Jang-do may know
where Kim Myeong-gil might run off to.
That's right.
Im Jang-do may have given him tips
on how to smuggle himself
out of the country.
He mentioned earlier
he was in charge of stuff like that.
All right, I'll look into it.
- All right, how much in cash?
- I think I can give you 18 million.
Im Jang-do hasn't used
a phone or credit card under his name
in the last six months.
He's avoided anything
that might give us a lead.
So we don't have anything?
Well, so far all we've found
is his bank account number.
And apparently, he did a cash withdrawal
last March in Suwon.
Can't you follow that?
We could, but we'll have to check
a few months' worth of security footage,
which would take some time.
Do you think
we could get his account number?
IM JANG-DO
JOHAN BANK
This prick is super strapped for cash,
so wire some money into that account,
and when you send it,
put down your phone number
under the sender's name.
Then he'll contact you
straight away for sure.
- How much should we send him?
- A big one should do.
Ten thousand won?
I was wondering
if I should mention this last time,
but in this line of work,
"a big one" differs by the situation.
That big one
from when I got you Kang In-beom's info,
that was supposed to be a million won.
A million won?
It's cool. It's cool.
I'm not asking for that money now, okay?
I'm not some greedy asshole.
We're family, after all.
Okay, in this case,
how much are we talking about?
He'll laugh at a million won.
Ten million.
He'll bite right away.
Your wounds aren't healing
because you keep drinking alcohol--
- Doctor.
- Yes, sir.
- Do your job.
Shit.
Sixty-six,
sixty-seven,
sixty-eight, sixty-nine.
Dude, someone's calling.
There's no number.
Hello?
You.
The kid that was with Mr. Choi, right?
Yes.
And the cops told you my account number.
Why?
Why did you send the money?
Because Kim Myeong-gil is running away.
Why?
Police have raided his house
and found substantial evidence
that he killed several people.
- When was that?
- Two days ago.
You know where
Kim Myeong-gil will run to, don't you?
I do.
Listen.
We have to catch him.
Please help us find out where he is.
How much will you pay?
Uh, a big one.
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
- I want a billion.
- A billion?
I trusted President Choi
and got royally fucked over.
I deserve at least a billion.
Okay, but we don't have--
Within a few days,
Kim Myeong-gil will flee overseas
using the method I taught him.
You know my account, right?
Think it over.
That it so fucked.
How will we ever get a billion won?
Should we ask Mr. Oh
if he could do anything?
Mr. Oh doesn't have money.
The money he gave us back then
was all he had left.
Hold up.
How much do we have in there?
I think around 300 million.
It's nowhere enough.
Should we ask Min-beom
if we could borrow some money?
Im Jang-do's the one
who took that video of Min-beom.
You think he'll help us with this?
I don't know.
But I think Min-beom's the only one
who could help us in this situation.
Let's try asking him just once, mm?
Sir, here they are.
Do you guys trust Im Jang-do?
Uh,
we do think that he can help us find…
everything that we've been looking for.
What if he pockets the money
and goes overseas?
Then what do we do?
If he does that,
if Im Jang-do breaks his promise and runs,
we'll chase him down and catch him.
This much I can promise, sir.
You have my word.
Keep that promise.
- Great.
1,000,000,000 RECEIVED
- Okay, looks good. Move along.
- Okay.
You can go.
UNKNOWN CALLER
Write this down.
The day after tomorrow at 1:00 a.m.,
a cargo ship called the Nike
is going to depart for Ho Chi Minh City.
Kim Myeong-gil gave political donations
to a high-ranking Vietnamese official.
He's going to take off
with all of his slush funds.
The container number is 9004230.
There will be a cargo truck
with all of his slush funds hidden inside.
Should we move in
when Kim Myeong-gil's getting on the ship?
It won't be easy to find
because it's a big ship.
How will we find it?
You guys get on the ship with him.
You mean we should get on the ship
and go to Vietnam?
Well, that's up to you, right?
- Bye.
- Wait, wait, wait.
What should we do then
if we decide to board that ship?
I'll text you a contact of mine.
Tell him I sent you
and try to work out a deal.
Also, he really likes cash.
That's the text.
I didn't know what you'd need,
so I brought a little bit of everything.
Thank you, sir.
You two take care.
Yes, sir.
Okay?
Yes.
Let's go up.
You go on ahead.
I need a minute.
Okay.
Thank you so much for your help.
No, we should be thanking you.
Da-min, see you soon.
- See you.
- Up you go.
Oh.
You have my number?
Mm.
Let's go.
- Hello.
- Hey, you're on your way there?
Yes, we're on our way.
Don't get hurt, okay?
Okay.
Me and Gang-yong
will take care of the rest.
Drive safe.
Yeah.
Let's hurry along then.
- Just a second.
- We'll be right back.
Dude.
Okay.
Set sail.
- Okay, go check out the inside first.
- Got it.
Kim Myeong-gil!
Uh-huh.
Oh!
If you ever show your face again…
I'll kill you.
Gun-woo.
Are you all right?
What is it?
Dude.
I've become a bloodhound.
Gun-woo, have you forgotten
about the heart of a boxer?
All we have to do is find our way back.
Hm?
Let's go back together.
Mm-hm.
Let's go back.
Here.
Whoa! Dude!
Ah, yes!
Hey.
- Hey, man, where are you?
- I'm almost there.
Gold bars, did you find them?
Yes, we found them all.
And the phone?
I'll go get it.
- Oh, dude, here. Here.
- Oh, oh, oh! Let's go!
Right!
How'd it go?
I finally got the phone.
They did good.
I asked Interpol for backup.
They'll be waiting in Vietnam.
It's all over.
You really went through a lot, kiddo.
Thank you.
What would you guys like to do with this?
Hm.
Well, Mr. Choi always wanted to help
those who were too poor
to get proper medical treatment,
so I'd like this money to be spent
in accordance with Mr. Choi's wishes.
What do you think about that idea?
Don't you want the money for yourself?
Uh, of course, I do.
But this isn't my money.
To be fair,
I'm just trying to pay back Mr. Choi
for his kindness
and make I sure I keep the promise
I made to him.
Mm.
Guys.
We have a total of 168 golden bars,
and each one would give us 500 million,
putting us at 84 billion in total.
If you want, I'll take this
and start a welfare foundation
all under Iil Group.
Through that welfare foundation,
we'll be able to provide
medical assistance to people who need it.
On top of that,
I should just have our company
add some money to the pot,
set up a hospital while we're at it.
- Well, that sounds like a great idea.
- Right?
It does.
I think my dad will like it too.
And it'll help
with our company image as well.
Besides, we'll do the world a lot of good.
I'll get started
as soon as I'm done with the hotel.
One last thing.
Could you maybe include Mr. Choi
in the hospital name?
- What was his name?
- His full name was Choi Tae-ho.
To be honest,
I don't think it'll be that easy,
but I'll definitely consider it.
Thank you so much.
Huh?
I'll cover the missing amount
with my own money.
Think of it as a bonus
for a job well done.
Um, it's all right.
We're really good.
That Mr. Choi would have done the same.
Take it.
What, you don't know
what to say all of a sudden?
A thank you would do.
- Thank you so much, Mr. Choi.
- No.
I'm the one that should be thanking you.
Thank you so much!
Let's get the ball.
Come on. Stop her!
There, right?
Oh!
Gun-woo, is that you?
What? Where are you?
Gun-woo!
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
Oh, my son.
Ah!
Oh!
Woo-jin.
Oh my gosh, look at you.
What happened to your face?
God, you went through so much.
It's all over, Mom. Let's go home now.
All right. Okay.
Oh God, I'm so proud of you!
Ah!