ALL NAMES, PLACES, AND PRODUCTS
ARE FICTIONAL AND DRAMATIZED
AND DO NOT REFLECT REALITY
Did you remember?
Yes. After Lee Seo-jin appeared
on Grandpas Over Flowers with a biker bag,
it sold really well for some time.
It was out of stock then,
so I stuck it out for years.
I was finally able to buy it
when Returns aired.
That's where I met that woman.
That show aired in 2018,
so it was five years ago.
Do you remember her name as well?
Yes, her name was…
It's not Mok Ga-hui, is it?
It is! How did you know?
Hey, it's not here.
It's not?
This is driving me nuts.
Why didn't I recognize her at once?
She had a face that's hard to forget.
Damn it.
Because she was pretty?
For a different reason.
I found it!
2018 EMPLOYEE EXCLUSIVE SALE
We will begin entry shortly.
Please have your invitation
and employee ID ready for a smooth entry.
We will begin entry shortly.
Please have your invitation
and employee ID ready…
- Let's start there.
- We should've come sooner.
- It's fine--
- What the…
- Ouch!
- What the hell?
- She cut in…
- What's she doing?
What's with her?
- She should apologize.
- It's fine.
She has no decency.
- Let's take it this way.
- Okay.
One, two, three!
Hey, my face looks so big!
- Okay, we'll move up.
- You come to the back.
- Oh my!
- Oh my gosh!
What are you doing?
- You took my picture. Delete it!
- We weren't taking your picture!
- Why are you doing this?
- What a crazy bitch!
Why are you doing this?
Keep back.
Your boyfriend bought you that!
Hey, what's she doing
with your cell phone?
What's with her?
Hey!
This is a Van Cleef!
The Sweet line isn't available in onyx.
Did your boyfriend buy you a fake,
or is he a fake too?
Excuse me! You can't just walk off!
It's fine.
- Seriously?
- I'll get it serviced.
She's totally crazy!
Hey, are you okay?
- Just because she was in…
- Are you okay?
None show her face,
so they're not very useful,
but I sent them anyway.
No, they mean a lot.
Doors closing.
- What the…
- What's that smell?
Thank you for visiting Samwol today.
- He smells like trash.
- I know, right?
How can he go to a store like that?
- What's he doing in a department store?
- God, he stinks!
THE ART OF SARAH
MOK GA-HUI
Sir!
Here.
Mok Ga-hui worked right here
at Samwol Department Store five years ago.
According to Woo Hyo-eun,
Sarah Kim was pushing
to get a spot in this place
up until she was murdered.
And the sewer where the body was found
is also connected to this place.
What does this place have to do
with the murder?
That's what we're here to find out.
What if it's a person, not a place?
What is?
Where the arrow points.
Doors closing.
The police requested information
as part of a voluntary investigation.
So Samwol isn't obligated
to provide the requested documents
and may be selective in what we submit.
So I was told.
I understand you have a lot to lose.
After all, you own more
than anyone else in South Korea.
"Samwol Department Store
chairwoman Choi Chae-u
even tricked into signing
a lease agreement by con artist."
The lease agreement in question
was reviewed and deemed invalid
by our MD Team.
We've already addressed the issue
by disciplining the employee responsible,
per our internal regulations.
So I was told.
If that's the case,
it means you were aware
that Sarah Kim was a con artist.
The security footage
could help identify the suspect,
but they won't share it.
They're a major company.
We need irrefutable evidence
for things like a summons
or a search warrant.
From this moment on,
we're tracking down Mok Ga-hui,
who worked at Samwol five years ago.
The more connections with Choi,
the better.
Wait, Mok Ga-hui?
Don't tell me it's that Mok Ga-hui?
It's here somewhere…
Who's "that" Mok Ga-hui?
I shared an office
with the cybercrime team
when I was stationed at Namdaemun.
I heard that name endlessly,
so I remember it.
WANTED FUGITIVE
She was hiding right here.
REWARD UP TO 5 MILLION WON
WANTED FUGITIVE FOR FRAUD
PERSONAL INFORMATION: MOK GA-HUI (F, 26)
TATTOO NEAR ANKLE
Are you looking for this?
The Cheongdam Goddess scam case.
She listed luxury goods as second-hand
and built trust with buyers,
then took the money and vanished.
She swindled a whopping 500 million won.
Are these all the documents you have?
What about fingerprints or DNA evidence?
It's like I'm being audited.
You're from Violent Crimes, right?
What's going on?
We suspect Mok Ga-hui to be
the victim of a recent murder.
I think you're mistaken.
Mok Ga-hui died five years ago.
She committed suicide by jumping.
It was for a common reason.
Financial hardship.
She was heavily in debt to loan sharks,
apparently from buying hordes
of luxury goods.
She left the place a total mess,
but soaked her suicide note in perfume.
It was downright insane.
See the shiny thing she's holding tightly
as she jumps?
That's a limited edition too.
The damn thing must've been dear to her.
She couldn't let it go, even in death.
- Was the body recovered?
- No.
She went missing,
so the case was suspended.
That means it became a cold case,
so why did you conclude she was dead?
The reason and circumstances were clear,
and a suicide note was found.
Most importantly,
there was no evidence she was alive.
Even if someone lives like a ghost,
they still leave traces
like hospital visits, bank accounts,
or delivery-app records.
But there was nothing.
CHEONGDAM GODDESS SCAM CASE
SUICIDE NOTE
Could they really be two different people?
Similar physical description
and criminal offense type.
Do you think that's all a coincidence?
We have no evidence she's alive,
but none that she's dead either.
If she had been impersonating Sarah Kim
for the past five years,
it makes sense she was declared missing.
Do you know The Cuckoo's Calling
by Robert Galbraith?
No.
Right after the book was published,
an anonymous Twitter user
claimed Robert
was just J.K. Rowling's pen name.
After some debate, it was revealed
that the two were the same person. How?
By the book's prologue.
"Unhappy is he whose fame
makes his misfortunes famous."
Because of the quote by Lucius Accius.
Lucius is Malfoy's father's name,
and who's the classic case of fame
making one's misfortune famous too?
Harry Potter!
Even language has fingerprints.
All we need is one sentence.
No, we just need one word.
- But Mok never wrote a book.
- She did write something else.
The suicide note!
Wait, did you steal that?
What do you mean by "steal"?
I found it on the floor.
I'm giving you fair warning.
We'll make countless enemies
the moment I open this.
We'd be attacking the errors
of the case team, the courts,
and the prosecution.
So if you want out, now's your chance.
I tend to be quite daring.
We're not leaving until we find a lead.
Yes, sir.
People trust others
knowing they shouldn't,
trust themselves,
believing they'll be different,
believe the world,
thinking it'll be different this time,
and believe in lies
even while knowing everything is a lie.
Mok Ga-hui?
You're 27?
Usually they don't hire such old newbies.
Do you have this one size up?
What do you think?
Who's going to buy anything
from a salesperson who's a large?
Don't ever use the client bathrooms.
The same goes
for the elevators and the escalators.
That can trigger complaints
for causing discomfort,
so don't even hint at it
in front of the clients.
Just say you're on a break.
These are this season's new releases.
Learn them by this weekend.
I don't need until the weekend.
- I've already memorized them all.
- But they're not even in Korea yet.
I just like how knowing more
lets you see and understand more.
You won't last long here.
People who talk like that
always disappear and quit.
No.
I'm here to stay for good.
Fellow Samwol family members,
we will be ready to serve
our valuable clients in ten minutes.
Please complete all preparations.
Announcement from the control room.
Fellow Samwol family members,
thank you for your hard work today.
Please unplug all devices in the store
and turn off the power before you leave.
Please ensure all high-value display items
are properly secured.
Please report any issues
to the control room as soon as they occur.
Ga-hui.
What are you doing here?
How do you think the rich became rich?
Well, they were born that way,
don't you think?
You know, I have a dream now.
I want to become a person
who suits this bag.
That might be possible
if you had one meal a day for ten years.
Well, let's think about that
after we close up, shall we?
Come on. Hurry up.
God, this is seriously driving me crazy.
Something big is coming. Something big.
Are you all religious?
Pray. Even if you're not.
Please let it be anyone but me.
Why? What's going on?
Regardless of the reason,
any inventory discrepancy
is considered a loss.
And we make up the full amount.
That's Samwol Department Store's policy.
So pray.
October 14th.
Who closed up that day?
- October…
- Fourteenth…
OCTOBER 14, SUNDAY
CLOSING SHIFT: MOK GA-HUI
Misfortune struck without warning,
like a disaster.
Why did you leave your station?
Was it something important?
It had better have been
something very important.
At least then you'd feel less wronged.
I was on a break.
Couldn't you have held it in?
I'd been holding it in all day.
This wouldn't have happened
if staff could use client bathrooms.
It's a long walk through the back hall
to the staff bathroom,
but even then, there's a line.
The basement one is less crowded,
but I have to take the staff elevator,
which is also around the back hallway,
and it stops on every floor, so I have to…
Damn it.
I have to wait through the long ride.
Going to the bathroom was such a struggle.
I mean, it's just the bathroom.
It was only once.
What can I do? That's the store policy.
You know that we can't recover the items
even if she's caught.
I swear it's a better world for criminals.
Just think of it
as an expensive life lesson learned.
How
much do I have to pay?
Fifty million won.
Ouch.
Where did things go wrong?
- Add one A!
- Okay.
Five, you said? Add two more.
Got one more B.
All right. Dessert served to table two.
Get the sauce ready.
Two steaks going out to table four.
Where did things go wrong?
Didn't know you smoked.
I started.
I figured this was my only way
to get breaks.
Here.
The girls and I all pitched in a bit.
It's not much, but I hope it helps.
See you later.
Where did things go wrong?
Are you sure you won't regret it?
We can't pay you even if it bombs.
Just make sure you pay me properly.
Okay, I'm practicing script tattoos.
Is there a specific phrase you'd like?
Where did things go wrong?
After thinking it over,
I found my way back to when I was born.
TO BE OPERATED
BY AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Ma'am, are you going to the employee sale?
It coincides
with my in-laws' ancestral rites.
- Oh no!
- Damn that husband of mine.
- It's supposed to be the best ever.
- Don't ever get married.
Oh my.
Yes, perfect!
Ga-hui, would you like to earn some money?
Sorry?
There's going to be an employee sale
for store staff.
Luxury goods at those prices are a steal.
If you manage to make purchases
on my behalf,
I'll compensate you generously.
Mok Ga-hui of Samwol Department Store.
You may enter.
Lee Hyeon-suk of Samwol Department Store.
Samwol Department…
Bags!
Please be careful.
At that moment,
I saw a ray of hope for my life too.
What are you doing?
I'll buy it. Wait, hold on.
No, I'm buying it!
- I grabbed it.
- What's with you?
PLEASE ENTER YOUR NICKNAME
CHEONGDAM GODDESS
JOIN
WELCOME TO NOBILITY
SELLING CHEAP DUE TO CIRCUMSTANCES
NO WEAR AND TEAR
OPEN TO NEGOTIATION
POST
COMMENTS
Samwol Department Store's First Lounge
ensures that our most valued clients
can relax comfortably while shopping
by offering various services…
NO COMMENTS
MANAGER OH SEON-JEONG
ON A BREAK?
HURRY, THE BOSS IS HERE
I'm about to burst!
Hurry!
So gross.
Why are you going
to the bathroom so often?
I feel better now.
It's because I took enzymes.
It's a group-buy item from Gemma,
and it sold out.
Really?
Should I get some too?
You know, this vintage Chanel bag
Gemma carries is sold out.
Where did she get it?
I can't seem to find it anywhere.
Yeah, that one's pretty.
She takes good pictures.
They urge you to buy it right away.
She has over a million followers.
That's understandable.
Her posts make you want to buy the items.
GEMMA
SELLING SINCE I GOT THE SAME BAG AS A GIFT
THIS ITEM IS HARD TO FIND THESE DAYS,
SO I'VE ADDED A PREMIUM
POST
I'LL BUY IT. I CAN PAY NOW
IS IT NEW? PRISTINE CONDITION?
AUTHENTIC? ALL COMPONENTS INCLUDED?
I'LL BUY IT! PLEASE!
I REALLY WANTED THIS ONE
PLEASE MESSAGE ME!
FOR EXECUTIVES, EMPLOYEES,
AND PARTNER COMPANIES
SAMWOL GROUP YEAR-END SALE
FOR EMPLOYEES AND EXECUTIVES
God, where did my employee ID go?
Did you happen to see my ID?
No, I haven't seen it.
Please have your employee ID
and invitation ready in advance.
MOBILE INVITATION
TRANSACTION COMPLETE
PRETTY IMPULSE BUY
NOT MY USUAL STYLE
- All good upstairs?
- Yes, things look absolutely fine.
I'm sorry for the delay.
What is this?
Fifty million won.
What?
I'll get changed.
I mean, this is…
Oh, you got a tattoo.
What does it mean?
Splendid melancholy.
"Splendid melancholy"?
It's like "miserable rich"
or "beautiful trash."
Right now,
I feel like miserable, melancholic trash.
What if money made money?
50 million becomes 500 million,
then 500 million becomes 5 billion.
The one choice
That will change your life
They say the jingling sound
of the charms brings you luck.
Do you think it suits me?
Of course. It's perfect for you.
I'll take it.
We don't have any in stock for now.
It may take a while for you to receive it.
Would that be all right?
Why ask?
What will you do if it's not okay?
I apologize.
Never mind. Here's the deposit.
Yes. Please wait just a moment.
I'm afraid you can't purchase these.
Sorry? Why not?
You can only purchase
up to two million won per person.
Since when?
The brand implemented a purchasing limit
due to illegal invitation issues.
Apparently, dealers were caught
reselling the items recently.
So, would you like to buy
up to the two-million-won limit?
REMINDER FOR MOK X-HUI
PRINCIPAL DUE: 01/07/19
PRINCIPAL: ₩50,000,000
RATE: 24%
THE ONE CAPITAL
It's 50 million won.
Come on. Damn it.
There's money missing.
That's 50 million won.
I brought the principal right back.
Exactly.
Why only bring back the principal?
What about the interest?
Well, you see…
Something came up,
so I can't pay it back right away.
Whatever it takes,
I'll have it by next month.
Will you be okay with it?
By next month,
you'll have more interest to pay.
Look, why don't you just pay it off now?
I'll lend it to you.
Hey.
Here we go.
Give me your thumb.
- Ouch!
- Okay, relax.
That's a good girl.
Here you go. Come on, take it.
Here's me lending you the money,
and me receiving it.
Thank you again
for using our services today,
Mok Ga-hui of Samwol Department Store.
Interest piled up,
and 5 million became 50 million,
then 50 million became 500 million.
Pay back the money!
Listen, everyone.
A bitch who refuses
to pay back the money she owes
works in the luxury section
of the Samwol Department Store.
Mok Ga-hui!
Hey! Damn it!
Stop right there!
Out of the way!
Mok Ga-hui!
Hey, Ga-hui. Mok Ga-hui.
Fucking hell.
You really think she's in there?
Hurry up!
No matter how hard I try to escape,
I find myself in a deeper abyss.
Take care of the inventory for now.
And don't let me catch sight of you.
Where there is light, there is darkness.
Why did I have to be the darkness?
VALUED CLIENT MOK GA-HUI
YOUR BAG IS READY FOR PICKUP
Please!
Fuck.
What did I ever do that was so wrong?
Why are you doing this to me?
Why?
You've got to burn to shine.
MOK GA-HUI
Run.
This is not a place for you.
I have decided to kill myself today.
MOK GA-HUI
But before I died,
I wanted to prove that I had existed.
Where the hell is Ga-hui?
- Seon-jeong, aren't you her friend?
- Well, I…
- I can't reach her.
- You what?
Try calling her.
That little…
- Oh God!
- I'm sorry.
How would you like this handled?
Just put it down as a disturbance
caused by a sprinkler malfunction.
Processing request.
Your transaction is complete. Please…
Though I will be shattered,
I shall do so brilliantly.
MOK GA-HUI
"Fuck it."
"I love you."
Luxury goods?
I really do like you.
Yet I really hate you.
Still…
I love you.
Even so, I hate you.
However,
I want to possess you.
But I hate you.
Nevertheless,
I want to be with you forever.
I wonder how you really feel?
Do you think it's a love-hate thing?
It might be surprisingly human.
Professing love and hate
without using conjunctions.
Ugly but beautiful.
- This is more human.
- It doesn't contradict what we know.
It's complex and ever-changing,
exactly like Sarah Kim.
I mean, like Mok Ga-hui.
She gets 500 million won overnight
and then commits suicide?
Now there's a contradiction.
Where did all the money disappear to?
But no matter how many times I read this,
not a single sentence suggests
Sarah Kim wrote it.
What if we flip it…
and try to find Mok Ga-hui from Sarah Kim?
There have to be traces of her,
even if she pretends to be someone else.
A rose will still smell like a rose,
no matter what name you call it by.
LUXURY GOODS
SPLENDID MELANCHOLY
What if we look for Mok Ga-hui
among these?
Luxury goods.
Splendid melancholy. Handbags.
Maybe it needs to be more intuitive,
or maybe it's where the three overlap.
A luxury bag
that introduced her
to a feeling of splendid melancholy…
Do you recall the bag Mok had
when she committed suicide?
Yes, the really shiny one.
I found it, sir.
It's the 2018 Lady Dior Collection.
YOU GOT TO BURN TO SHINE
THOUGH I WILL BE SHATTERED,
I SHALL DO SO BRILLIANTLY
The phrases match the suicide note.
What date did you say
Cheongdam Goddess posted that?
Wait, give me a second.
I GOT THE LUXURY BOUDOIR BAG LOVED
BY EUROPEAN ROYALS FOR 100 YEARS
December 26, 2018,
the day Mok Ga-hui committed suicide.
And when was Sarah Kim first seen?
According to Jeong Yeo-jin's statement,
that was also December 26, 2018.
Now we know what happened to the money.
Mok Ga-hui didn't want to die.
She wanted to live differently.
No matter how hard she tried,
her reality never changed.
She clung to the illusion of luxury goods
until she fell down the abyss.
That's when she decided.
If she couldn't change reality,
she would change herself.
Just as J.K. Rowling became
Robert Galbraith,
Mok Ga-hui became Sarah Kim.
And the Lady Dior,
which was hugely symbolic for Mok…
became Boudoir.
I told you to catch a killer,
not go around wasting your time.
And what's all this about Dior?
Are you saying
a dead person has come back to life?
A sloppy investigation
has turned a living person
into a dead one.
- What?
- It wasn't concrete.
The evidence only hinted at Mok's suicide.
They never searched the reservoir.
It's not too late to search and confirm.
If a body is not found,
we can prove Mok didn't commit suicide.
And this suicide note will serve
as justification for the search.
If they do find a body,
what will you do then?
Tell me.
After rallying people in this weather
to make a fuss
and mocking another team
by reopening a closed case, huh?
There's no chance a body will be found.
It's unfortunate when an investigator
decides the outcome from the start.
Did you give up on everything
after being passed over?
I'm hanging on to this case
because I haven't given up.
So why the hell are you hanging on
to this case and not me?
I'm the one who makes personnel decisions.
That suicide note gives me justification.
That's enough. You can go now.
Have you ever seen this person?
I can't say. We get a lot of customers.
FUCK IT. I LOVE YOU
Fuck it.
I love you.
Fuck it. I love you.
FUCK IT. I LOVE YOU
MY LOVE DAMNED IT ALL
WITH JI-HWON
It's all there in the notebook.
The secrets, tastes, and even minor habits
of the VIPs I managed.
A REGULAR AT A MALE HOST BAR
FELL FOR MALE ESCORT KANG JI-HWON
MADE HIM HER PERSONAL ASSISTANT
It wasn't Choi Chae-u.
It was Kang Ji-hwon.
Did you bring a warrant?
No, but I brought something else.
Sarah Kim and Kang Ji-hwon.
It turns out they were former lovers.
Are you saying
they conspired to deceive me?
Well, we'll find out once we investigate.
And to do that, we need your cooperation.
If you want the security footage,
you're too late.
We've replaced the system.
Never mind that.
I noticed you own an aquarium as well.
Would you mind giving me a fish?
Sir!
Where have you been?
You've been out of reach since yesterday.
Fishing.
What? Seriously?
This is no time for hobbies.
What did the section chief say?
Will he let us search the reservoir?
No. I'm going to drop that.
What?
That's it?
You're just accepting it without a fight?
What do you expect me to say in protest?
Do I say, "I haven't found anything yet,
but I'd like to keep investigating"?
That's all the more reason to prove it!
In times like these,
you should listen, not defy.
I'm not defying you.
But I won't listen either.
You should at least do one of the two.
Then you might find something
instead of whining.
You're right.
That's why I plan to do things my way.
Is that what you ordered from Coupang?
- What is that anyway?
- Isn't that an oxygen tank?
Is that doing things your way?
Jumping in blind?
Where are you going, kid?
He's defying me, right?
Hey, bring it over here!
Right there. Yes.
Bring it here!
Hurry!
Yes, we've got it.
Excuse me, sir,
but this area is off-limits to the public.
Please leave.
What's going on?
Last night, a fisherman reported
seeing piranhas in here.
We're draining it.
Please leave.
Are you done wasting time?
This way!
What's all this?
Coffee.
Piranhas in the middle of winter?
Are you behind all this?
Justification.
Keep sending it over.
Over here!
Quick! Hurry up!
I wish I could be born again.
Where did things go wrong?
Excuse me.
Subtitle translation by: Yung Un Choi