[Fenglinwan]
Here is my bank card.
The PIN is your birthday.
This is an accident insurance policy.
You are the beneficiary too.
Yibo.
What happened?
Can't you tell me?
You've been restless these past 2 days.
Qi,
please don't ask me, okay?
Just remember,
everything I've done
is because
I love you too much.
We must meet tonight.
I have just one question for you.
Why did you come so fast?
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 6]
[Loyalty]
[Forensic Lab]
Our forensic doctor's surname is
Chen, right?
Yes.
Just call him Mr. Chen.
Okay.
He's a nice guy.
Very easygoing.
Okay.
Mr. Chen.
On Ye Jian's body,
[Forensic Lab]
there are a total of 6 major stab wounds.
The murder weapon
is a dagger-like knife.
In addition, his ribs
were fractured
due to multiple impacts.
Judging from my experience,
Ye Jian should have been
hit by a vehicle first,
and then stabbed by a dagger.
However,
the cuts on his body are very strange.
There are both upward
and downward directions
for the blade marks.
It doesn't matter if there is one murderer
or multiple of them—
this doesn't make sense.
I have been
a forensic doctor for nearly 20 years,
and this is the first time
I dare not make a complete conclusion.
Do you need the Provincial Department
to send a forensic team over to help?
Chief Zhang.
What do you mean by that?
I...
I have been a
forensic doctor for nearly 20 years.
In 1995,
I became a forensic doctor
right after graduating from college.
Do you know how hard it was
to get into college back then?
It was like millions of soldiers
crossing a single log bridge.
Let me tell you,
my grades back then.
Chinese.
-My Chinese language grade—
-No.
I'm not doubting your ability.
I'm just thinking they could
come and assist you.
Because I saw your leg seems...
It's not my leg—
it's my waist!
It's a lumbar disc herniation.
Does it have anything to do
with the autopsy results?
Mr. Chen.
Say no more.
We are all on the same side.
Chief Zhang is also doing this
to solve the case.
Right?
Yes.
Chief Zhang has his own way
of solving cases.
I am greatly inspired.
No wonder the media says
you are a brilliant detective.
But if you ask me,
solving Ye Jian's case
will truly make you
a real brilliant detective.
His self-esteem is quite high.
That's his only flaw.
East New Town
will issue the tender within this month
for 33 acres of land.
Half will be for office and commercial use,
and the other
half is for residential facilities.
The base price
for the bidding is 600 million.
There are financial subsidies too.
According to
the financial department's calculation,
the profit from selling
the residential buildings alone
can cover the cost.
As for the remaining
office and commercial buildings,
the hundreds of millions
of rent every year
are basically free money.
Jianren.
Rongcheng's recent accounts
don't look very good.
If we don't get that land,
things won't be easy for us either.
So have you found out
where Fang Yong lives?
Yes.
But what should we give him?
Doesn't Fang Yong
call himself a man of culture?
We need to deal with him
in a cultured way then.
Start with antiques and calligraphy.
Zheng,
you're late today.
Traffic was a bit heavy today.
Is that so?
I'm leaving.
Bye-bye.
Ren!
How do you have time
to come here?
Open the door.
Ren,
have some tea.
I want to buy a calligraphy piece.
By whom?
Gan Yueran.
You mean Yu Yueran?
That's about right.
On the market,
there are many of Yu Yueran's
calligraphy works—
there are fakes and there are real ones.
Expensive ones cost 500,000,
while cheap ones are only 5,000.
Brother Ren,
which kind do you want?
I want the 500,000 one.
[A stone at the scene
with "Yi'ang" written on it]
[Zhang Yi'ang]
Chief.
Hasn't this case been cleared up?
[Informant?]
It has nothing to do with Chief Zhang.
Why is his photo still there?
Take it down right now.
[Zhang Yi'ang]
Don't, don't.
[Ye Jian's murdered]
Just leave it there.
Because this is our
only clear clue right now.
Just leave it there.
Yes.
Come.
Yi'ang.
You will be
in full charge of this case.
How to solve it
is up to you.
[Police]
I...
I think...
The...
The most important
clue should still be at
the crime scene.
We have already investigated
the scene several times.
We found footprints along the way,
but we can't be sure yet
if they belong to the suspect.
[Lu Zheng car accident]
[Informant]
Good.
[Paid murder]
[Ye Jian's murdered]
Before Captain Ye passed away,
did he have any conflicts
before he died?
It's possible.
As far as I know,
no.
Okay.
Then what about his
computer,
phone,
apps, WeChat...
His files, WeChat, QQ,
and Taobao browsing history—
we've checked them all.
There was nothing special.
What else have you done
related to this?
From the time Ye left the station
to his murder,
there were 5 hours.
He appeared
[Ye Jian's body location] [Ye Jian's car]
at this intersection at the end,
and couldn't be traced afterwards.
Yi'ang.
Are you giving a test?
These guys
are better than interns
from the police academy, right?
Yes.
They know the basics.
Of course.
I...
I didn't mean that.
Chief Zhang,
time is running out.
Since we're
going to work together,
let's be clear.
Okay.
You are a brilliant detective.
We can't compare with you.
Don't say that.
Then tell us,
what should we do next?
And what exactly?
You can't possibly not know.
[Ye Jian's murdered]
[A stone at the scene
with "Yi'ang" written on it]
[Yu Xiaofei] [Paid murderer]
[Lu Zheng car accident]
[Informant] [Report letter]
Chief.
Before Captain Ye was murdered,
he requested the files of a case
handled by Chief Lu.
To investigate Captain Ye's case,
[Ye Jian's murdered]
we have to start with Chief Lu's cases.
[Lu Zheng car accident]
[Informant] [Report letter]
Okay.
Investigate Chief Lu's cases?
How?
We have to start with Captain Ye's case.
You mean
the two cases are connected?
It's obvious
that this is a closed loop.
As long as we can find
the connection point of this loop,
we can
move both cases at the same time.
[Lu Zheng car accident]
[Ye Jian's murdered]
I understand now.
You want to merge the cases, right?
Merging cases requires evidence.
Have you been to Ye Jian's home?
Have you?
This is a very important clue.
Yes.
I led the team there.
You went there personally?
Of course.
When I went there,
I was in deep sorrow.
If you go there again,
you might find something different.
Right.
[Ye Jian's murdered]
Is he out yet?
Should be soon.
This is Fang Yong's neighborhood.
There's only one gate here.
If he goes out,
we'll definitely see him.
Mr. Rong.
Do you think it's appropriate
for us to wait for him like this?
[Fang Yong, Director of
East New Town's Administrative Committee]
He's here.
Mr. Fang.
You are...
Rongcheng Real Estate's
Zhou Rong.
Hello.
What's the matter?
It's like this.
I
just acquired a piece of calligraphy
by Master Yu Yueran
from the Republic of China era.
I heard you're an expert in this field,
so I wanted to ask you to authenticate it.
I wanted to visit you at your office,
but I was afraid it might not look good.
So I tried my luck here.
And I actually ran into you.
Yu Yueran's calligraphy?
Where is it? Let me see.
In the trunk.
Hurry.
This way.
Okay.
Please.
Slowly.
[Yu Yueran]
Not bad.
The frame is not bad.
It's from Rong Bao Zhai.
The calligraphy is fake.
Fake?
Yes,
it's fake.
As expected
of an expert.
Mr. Fang,
since this calligraphy is fake
and worthless,
you can take it back
and hang it on your wall.
It really is fake.
If I hang a fake
on my wall,
people will call me crazy.
It really is fake?
It's obviously fake.
Ren,
which kind do you want?
I want the 500,000 one.
But
I only brought 5,000.
Look at this,
the characters are nothing like his.
How dare one write Mr. Yu's name
on this.
It couldn't be more fake.
Where did you get something so fake?
Mr. Fang, well...
I just don't know much
about calligraphy and painting.
It would be great
if I could have the opportunity
to learn more about this
from you.
You stopped me halfway
just to ask
if this is real or fake?
I also wanted to ask about
the development policy
of the East New Town.
Rongcheng is bidding too.
See.
I knew it.
I hate you
businessmen the most.
You think you're smart
and play all kinds of tricks.
I tell you,
I, Fang,
don't buy this.
Mr. Fang.
Mr. Fang!
Mr...
[Fake Yu Yueran calligraphy]
Mr. Rong, he's gone.
I bought a fake
for 500,000,
and I almost gave it
as a first meeting gift.
Well...
I'll go settle this score
with Zheng Yongbing.
What's the use of looking for him?
Jianren,
I normally turn a blind eye
when you play your little tricks—
forget them.
But this is something important.
How could you fool me with a fake?
Mr. Rong.
Drive.
Mr. Rong,
I haven't gotten on yet!
Mr. Rong!
I...
Mr. Rong.
The trunk is open!
Ye is 39 this year.
He's single.
He was assigned an apartment in
the Public Security Bureau's
family compound in his early years,
and has lived here ever since.
You must have found
the key clue to Chief Lu's murder.
You might not even realize it yourself,
but it must be there.
Where is the clue?
On the second floor.
On the second floor?
Ye's house is on the second floor, Chief.
Okay, let's go.
Here.
♪ Burning on its own
somewhere between haziness and clarity ♪
♪ In the careless detail,
he touched the color ♪
Why are you all following me?
I'm just looking around.
♪ The show starts getting interesting ♪
♪ I wonder who's the real onlooker here ♪
♪ Find the onlooker ♪
♪ The chance is waiting patiently
in the bowl ♪
Thanks.
Put it on.
♪ Who covered my eyes ♪
♪ I'm full of ideas ♪
♪ Oh, god ♪
♪ Please give me some guidance ♪
♪ Find the sleepy poet ♪
♪ They are all guests ♪
What are you doing?
This is an important clue.
As soon as Chief Zhang came in,
he pulled it right off the wall.
Even the nail was pulled out.
Right, Chief Zhang?
Chief Zhang.
What's important
about this photo?
Chief Zhang,
are you looking for
something that shouldn't be
in Captain Ye's house?
Yes.
What I am looking for now
is something
that Ye Jian wouldn't normally have.
Chief Zhang,
how did you know Ye...
Shut up.
Chief Zhang.
Captain Ye was an upright person.
He never made
any disciplinary mistakes.
How could there be
anything that shouldn't be here?
I can guarantee this:
Captain Ye is absolutely
not that kind of person.
There's definitely something going on.
Did you find something?
He's definitely never used it.
Let me have a look.
Bring it.
We found this
when we searched the place last time.
This card has no credit limit.
But we checked the records,
and it hasn't even been activated.
He's a very cautious man.
He rarely even attends
drinking gatherings.
Why didn't you mention it last time?
I was afraid if word got out,
it would be bad for his reputation.
Fenglinwan?
[Spa Card]
[Fenglinwan VIP Exclusive]
The slightly shorter one
in the back
is Lu Yibo.
He's the manager of the biggest hotel
in Sanjiangkou.
Only by finding out the truth
can we clear Ye's name.
Captain Wang.
Chief Zhang is amazing.
He's got something.
[Out of service;
do not climb]
My poetry; my distant horizon.
[My Poetry, My Faraway]
Is this the highly corrupt official
we went through so much trouble
to find?
He's still riding
such a shitty bike in this day and age?
Can't even afford an electric bike?
That's such a sad life.
Is this what
a highly corrupt official looks like?
You are too inexperienced
to see through their disguise.
I'll teach you.
Don't let his shitty bike fool you.
This fatty is East New Town's
Director of the Administrative Committee.
The East New Town is known to be
the next Sanjiangkou.
This fatty is
on an equal footing
with the mayor of Sanjiangkou City.
The neighborhood he lives in—
I checked the housing prices.
It's at least 3 million.
Well.
At his age,
buying a house with a mortgage
of 3 to 4 million
is quite normal.
Besides, if he bought it
a few years earlier,
he wouldn't even need half of that.
Then let me ask you:
everyone with a status
has a car.
Given his status,
is it normal for him to be riding
a shitty bike to work?
Yeah.
This fatty is trying to lose weight
by riding a bike.
Then why
does he ride a shitty bike
instead of getting a new one?
He's used to it.
He doesn't want to change the old one.
Like me—
I've been wearing this underwear
for 5 years
and haven't changed it.
I'm still wearing it.
Don't show me your underwear.
Look at the photos in the back.
This is first-hand information I got
from the newspaper publisher.
Open your eyes wide and look carefully.
Are the bikes he rides
the same one?
Bro.
There's a game called spot the difference.
They really are different.
Over the years,
he has changed
at least 3 different bikes.
A bike doesn't cost much.
Those 3 shitty bikes
are worth even less.
The problem is,
why does he
always change to shitty bikes?
And where did he find
3 shitty The Forever bikes
from decades ago?
He always rides a bike.
He's always riding a shitty bike.
Even if it's broken,
he changes to another shitty bike.
Ordinary corrupt officials
don't need to
disguise themselves to this extent.
Look again.
From 10 years ago to last month—
whenever there's an interview,
what does he emphasize?
"I don't want to be an official.
I am a scholar."
Pretending to be so humble,
how much money must he have embezzled?
Does it make sense?
It does.
Let's get him.
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
Park in the parking lot.
Parking elsewhere is a fine of 200.
Sorry.
Bro,
doesn't he live here?
I know.
Bro,
can we find him?
I am well-prepared.
Bro,
will our plan work?
When God closes a door,
he opens a window.
[Fenglinwan Nightclub]
[Fenglinwan]
Stop the car.
[Fenglinwan Hotel]
She's here.
Zhou Qi,
the PR Manager of Fenglinwan Hotel.
She'd intervened to mediate
a few fights here,
so we've met before.
Ms. Zhou
knows what to say and do.
Okay.
Hello, officer.
Hello, Wang.
Mind your manners.
Hello, Officer Wang.
This is Chief Zhang.
Hello.
We're here today
because there are some situations
we want to ask you about.
I'll definitely cooperate.
Have a seat.
[Zhou Qi,
Fenglinwan Hotel's PR Manager]
Chief.
What we're asking you
today
must be forgotten
or kept a secret.
Understand?
I'll 100% keep it a secret.
I understand the rules.
Whatever you ask,
I'll answer honestly
and fulfill my duty.
Good, good.
Chief,
go ahead.
Do you know Ye Jian?
Captain Ye?
Yes.
Has Captain Ye been
to Fenglinwan Hotel
or your nightclub recently?
Are you sure?
I didn't see him anyway.
Anything else?
If not,
officers, I'll head back first.
Wait.
If you think of
anything suspicious,
report to us anytime.
Of course.
Done asking?
Do you have anything to ask?
N-No, I don't.
Neither do I.
She looks like
she came prepared.
I want to see Lu Yibo.
Make an appointment for me—
right now.
Can you still see anything?
Can you find him?
Got it.
Can you hear me?
Found him.
Is it the guy in the garden?
Chief Huang.
The signal at my house was bad just now.
It's fine now.
Go ahead.
Fang,
we are getting older.
It's time to step back
and take care of our health.
Don't you like doing cultural stuff?
Switching to an easier job
would make you happy, right?
How's that?
Are you so happy that
you can't speak?
Well...
Why?
We mainly considered how
you've been diligent
and hardworking all these years—
it hasn't been easy.
N-No, Chief Huang.
I can really work for another 2 years.
I've been fighting for a chance for you.
And I finally got it this time.
Why bother, Chief Huang?
What are you talking about?
You only have work in your heart.
So I can't not have you in mine.
Fang,
wrap up your work nicely
and get ready
to go to the provincial capital
to do your cultural research.
Fang?
Why aren't you laughing?
All right, all right.
No need for
words of gratitude.
That's it.
What is he doing?
Looks like Five-Animal Exercises.
He cares about his health.
Bro,
let's go.
I'm hungry.
Knowing where he lives is enough.
We have to
keep watch here tonight.
That way, when he leaves tomorrow,
we can make our move.
Makes sense.
Chief Zhang,
how should we ask him later?
Do you like
listening to Guo Degang's crosstalk?
Yes.
Yes?
I heard that sometimes
when he's on stage with Yu Qian,
they don't
follow the script.
Improvising?
Right.
All right then,
as long as you deliver the setup,
I'll play along.
You sure? Okay.
Please.
What a luxurious office.
It's converted from a presidential suite.
Have a seat, officers.
Sit.
If you're standing, we...
I'll sit.
Officers,
what can I do for you?
Well, we just saw each other recently
at Captain Ye's memorial service,
didn't we?
Mr. Lu,
guess why we're here.
I don't know.
I am a police officer!
Listen to me!
Don't run this way now.
You, get out of the way.
Don't go that way!
Move!
Go around! Go around!
Don't take it out.
I've been prepared for this.
What's meant to come will come.
You can take it out and see for yourself.
Chief Zhang,
a leader from the Provincial Department
assigned to this special case.
He came with clues,
so it's all down to your attitude now.
I wrote the report letter.
You wrote the report letter?
I didn't write it?
You did.
You aren't here for this?
That's exactly what we are here for.
This file...
Your report letter
has too many typos.
You kept striking off
and writing over—it's illegible.
We have to verify it
with you in person.
Yes.
I was really
too agitated at the time.
Who killed Lu Zheng?
I don't know.
Then who did you report?
You should at least remember that.
The person I reported is...
Who was it again?
Let me tell you.
I'm giving you a chance right now
to make up for your crimes.
If we didn't know the actual situation,
would we come looking for you?
If you don't want to talk,
we can talk at the station.
Mr. Lu is our witness now.
He is the key
to helping us solve the case.
We can't treat witnesses
like criminal suspects.
You...
Tell us yourself.
Who is it?
Chief Zhang.
I need to think about it again.
Can you give me some time?
Yes, absolutely.
We protect witnesses.