( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
Hey.
What are you still doing here?
I'm sorry. I thought you were my friend.
Let's go. Everyone's here.
Wait. Why is he leaving?
So it wasn't him?
Mi-rae!
Ms. Choi?
Su-ji, a college friend.
What?
The campus is so big. I still get lost.
I almost lost you on my way back
from the bathroom.
Let's go!
Go where?
What? We said we would go together.
Over there.
Yay, we're here!
Isn't it great?
"Freshmen"?
WELCOME, FRESHMEN!
I'm not a freshman, am I?
No way.
How much is this?
STUDENT COUNCIL
It's so pretty. Can I have this?
Thank you!
-You there!
-I got this.
Freshmen!
You gotta be shitting me.
Let's go. That's awful.
Join us in the near future.
Never.
Not you!
Go away!
Take a look.
Check it out. It's fun.
Come check us out.
-This way!
-Come this way.
-Take a quick look.
-Check out what we're all about.
-We have cameras.
-Show us your kicks!
-We're offering free photos!
-Free pictures!
Why is this line so long, Ms. Choi?
Hey!
Don't call me that.
You're weirding me out.
I know, right? Girl, that was so weird!
They must be lining up to get tickets
for the kumdo match today.
I heard in the bathroom earlier
that it was sold out.
Are they waiting
to get canceled tickets or what?
The kumdo club must be really popular.
I heard it's even more popular
than the soccer and hockey teams here.
No way! You got tickets?
Where did you get these? That's insane!
I'm supposed to go here, aren't I?
You have to go.
Come along now.
It's this way.
He's here!
13TH KUMDO FRIENDLY
HANSAE VS KOSAN
What's going on?
Didn't I tell you not to stand here?
Why not?
You're blocking the view!
-Damn it!
-What did you say?
Who are they?
Part of a fan club or something?
I guess so.
The Hansae-Kosan kumdo friendly match
will begin soon.
Hansae University!
EUN-HO, WE LOVE YOU
-Hansae University!
-Kosan University!
Begin!
Head strike!
-Seo Eun-ho of Hansae University has won.
-Eun-ho!
In the next match,
Park Myeong-seong of Hansae University
will be facing
An Hong-mo of Kosan University.
Please remain seated.
So cool!
He's amazing.
Congratulations, Ms. Seo Mi-rae,
on meeting your second date!
I knew it.
It was you.
EPISODE 3
FIRST LOVE 101
HANSAE KUMDO CLUB
Are you guys joining because of Eun-ho?
No.
It's okay. That's why we joined too.
-You want to get to know him better, huh?
-Yes!
Then you'll have to get past us first.
Is Seo Eun-ho really that popular?
How could he not be?
I'll bet all the girls here
wish he'd go on
to earn his master's and doctorate
and become a professor here.
Good thing the architecture program
is five years long.
He's not a PE major?
Wow, he's in architecture.
He must be smart too.
Eun-ho's good enough to run a country,
not just a company!
Totally!
So the most popular guy on campus
likes me?
That's a decent plot.
-Why are you laughing?
-What?
It's nothing.
Introduce myself?
I'm Seo Mi-rae, a freshman.
Looking forward to it.
Where am I now?
He's so handsome.
All right, freshmen.
It's our first time seeing each other.
Say hello.
-Hello.
Hey.
What are you still doing here?
It's the girl I saw earlier.
Hey, isn't the club president
just gorgeous?
She is.
Kumdo is the best sport
for training one's body and mind.
We will help you enjoy every aspect of it,
from the basic stances to sparring.
Since it's your first day,
let's start with the basic footwork.
Any volunteers?
Who wants to give it a go?
Good. Come on out, then.
Sorry?
No, I'm good.
Come out. It's okay.
Get out there.
What was your name again?
It's Seo Mi-rae.
It would be nice
if someone could help out.
All right. Help us, will you?
They probably all came to see you anyway.
Shall I?
Is that okay with you?
Yes.
Hi.
Hello.
Have you tried kumdo before?
No, I haven't.
Here.
Hold it like this.
Right foot, forward.
How is it? Comfortable?
Yes.
High stance.
Head strike.
And this is the middle stance,
which will be your basic stance.
Want to give it a go?
Yes.
Go ahead.
Head strike.
What was that?
Is this really your first time?
This is my first time.
What just happened?
I usually have two left feet.
You're really athletic, huh?
Let's try that again.
Okay.
Wasn't she a blur just now?
What did I just see?
No way.
Mi-rae, you've really got talent.
Come on.
Eun-ho was obviously going easy on her.
I wasn't.
Great job.
I'll be looking forward to it.
Okay.
-Head strike!
-Head strike.
-He's just so cool.
-One.
-I know!
-Head strike.
-Look how stable he is.
-Middle stance.
He's just so insanely buff!
You know it!
Like you're walking. Watch me.
One!
Head strike!
Very good.
Mr. Ko?
Why are you guys just standing here?
Is something wrong?
Jung-pil, kumdo club senior.
Actually…
What's your name?
-It's Su-ji.
-Su-ji?
-Yes.
-Su-ji, come over here.
Okay.
-The key to kumdo is smooth movement.
-Okay.
Head strike!
That was so smooth.
You try.
Head strike!
Hey, keep an eye on everyone.
Sure.
Head strike!
Eun-ho.
-Where are you off to?
-The library. Why do you ask?
Would you like to have lunch with me?
All together?
No.
Just the two of us?
Yes.
You're quite impatient, huh?
Next time, once we know each other better.
-What?
-Take care.
Eun-ho?
Hey, Eun-ho!
Where are you going? Let me come.
Let's go eat.
Weren't you supposed to have
fallen for me?
Why should he?
He should be into me.
This is Boyfriend on Demand, after all.
I think you may have gotten
the wrong idea.
Wrong idea?
Did you think that all 900 guys here
would be chasing after you from the start?
But…
Choi Si-woo liked me from the--
That's just how that scenario was written.
SPRING, AND YOU
You don't look it, but you've got
a pretty bad princess complex.
Are you saying Seo Eun-ho
might not ever end up falling for me?
There's no telling that.
Some dates are more difficult than others.
If I have to work for it,
how's it any different from reality?
Would you rather date another guy?
Shall we move on?
No, wait. Hey!
Hold on a second.
If you're not feeling it, just move on.
You don't have much time.
I know. My time…
Time?
Jesus.
Kyeong-nam.
Man, look at her.
You want coffee?
PlanC had a decent first episode as well.
But Yun Song's tough, right?
I knew what we were up against.
Did you really ask to be moved to Fridays?
No.
Ms. Seo didn't seem to think so.
Obviously. She doesn't like me, after all.
Don't you?
What?
Yes?
Come in.
Did you want to see me?
I just got off a call with Yun Song.
What? What was it about?
What else would that woman call me for?
Honestly, I want to end this series.
I'm so sick and tired of it!
Please save me.
You don't mean
she's thinking about quitting?
-She said she's quitting?
-What?
-No.
Damn it.
Then why did she…
She wants two weeks off.
Otherwise, we'll be attending her funeral.
Ms. Yun has been through a lot recently.
Great work.
-Sorry?
-I liked it. Keep it up.
-I don't get why you were whining so much.
-Please…
While Yun is on her break,
think about the next episodes.
You approved her break?
Seo Mi-rae is free on a weekday?
It smells so good. Hurry up.
So you'll be free for two weeks.
Should we go to Jeju over the weekend?
Jeju? Don't even think about it.
I have other authors to take care of.
I've always thought that being a producer
is not worth the grind.
Not worth it at all!
It looks so good!
Hey, Ji-yeon.
Say you could go back to being 20.
What would you want to try?
Sex.
Not that kind of stuff!
What's this out of the blue?
What would you do if you went back?
I'd want my life to be
completely different from this one.
The exact opposite.
-The opposite?
-Yeah.
You know, if I fell for someone,
I'd just go straight for him.
Come what may,
I'd be way more proactive
about pretty much everything.
Hey, you're cracking me up!
What's so funny?
You were super proactive when you were 20.
I was?
Yes!
Se-june had a crush on You-mi,
and you kept trying to win him over
until you made him yours.
You forgot, didn't you?
You-mi sure was popular back in the day.
Not as popular as me, but still.
You're right. I was like that.
So how did I end up like this?
I guess dating him for too long
changed you.
And you got older.
I feel like
we had a really good thing going
in the beginning.
Yeah, you really did.
I envied you guys back then.
Seo Eun-ho, I must say,
is not an easy one.
You were super proactive when you were 20.
Should I just go for it?
Temples in classical architecture
can be classified by the number of columns
in the front and rear facades.
It's called "distyle"
when there are two columns,
"tetrastyle" when there are four,
and "hexastyle" when there are six.
When it comes to the hexastyle…
Hello.
Hi.
Can I sit here?
Be my guest.
Can you move over?
Just a sec.
Go ahead.
So you're going to keep that up, huh?
The columns of a temple can be classified
according to their forms…
Since I decided to go for it,
I'm going to pull out all of my old moves.
Where are we right now?
Thank you!
Sorry about that.
Hey.
Yes?
Are you feeling unwell?
No.
Okay.
Let's focus on the lecture.
Eun-ho, you're off to practice,
aren't you?
I'm going to the library.
Good. I was also on my way to the library.
Come to think of it, I have practice.
Me too. I have practice too.
Should we get started first?
What's he doing?
Oh my God!
Has he fallen for me?
Don't you…
go easy on me like last time.
Give it everything you've got.
This is bad.
Put it on.
I hurt his pride.
Mi-rae, hi!
Hello.
What's going on?
Did you two have a practice match?
The thing is,
Eun-ho…
It was my idea.
And? How did it go?
MI-RAE, EUN-HO
Wasn't I supposed to be a campus queen?
They turned me into a full-on swordsman!
WIN, LOSE
No way.
You lost?
I don't believe it.
Is it true?
I'll go wash up.
Let's go!
Umchichi, umchichi, umchichi, umchichi!
-Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny!
-Carrot, carrot!
It's been so long since I've felt
this excitement, this youthful energy!
Carrot, carrot!
Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny!
-Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny!
You got it wrong, Jung-pil! Drink up!
Drink up!
I'd like to
take one for him.
-Hey! Give us a penalty drink!
-Penalty!
Okay!
Here comes the drink.
Mi-rae!
-Mi-rae!
-All right, mix it up.
Get ready.
Even soju?
All right. Here's your penalty drink.
Mi-rae, just
what kind of life have you had?
I got carried away.
Is that how you do it?
Eun-ho!
-Hello, Eun-ho.
-Eun-ho!
-Hi, Eun-ho.
-Come sit down.
-Sit here.
-Hello, Eun-ho.
Why are you so late?
-Assignment.
-Have a drink.
Bottoms up! Yeah!
Su-ji, that's enough.
No. I know you're a lightweight.
Cheers.
I'll drink it.
I knew I didn't like that girl
from the start.
She oddly reminds me of Na You-mi.
You have something on you.
Jung-pil!
No, don't push yourself!
You're going to feel sick tomorrow.
By the way, Mi-rae,
have you done any sports before?
Not at all.
Oh, you're an art major.
A talented artist and a skilled athlete.
You've got it all!
Please! You flatter me.
Too much humility can hurt you, you know.
What are you talking about?
Being humble is a good thing.
Eun-ho's right about that one.
It can get a bit annoying
when someone takes it too far.
Yup.
Excuse me.
What?
Not you.
Do you hate me?
What?
I don't hate people.
Sorry if you felt that way.
That's a relief.
-Mi-rae?
-Mi-rae.
Where are you going?
Because I like you, Eun-ho.
-What?
-I think she's drunk!
-Come on!
-Stop cutting in line, Mi-rae!
You know, we've just met.
What?
You don't know me that well.
Kids nowadays sure are bold,
don't you think?
Jung-pil, you've got some pie on you.
Man, that's embarrassing!
Cutie-pie.
-So cute.
-Is she mad?
Hold on.
-Cheers.
-Sounds good, Jung-pil!
-Here you go!
What the heck?
You're the best.
-See you. Bye!
-Bye-bye!
-You want to get in this one?
-May I?
Yeah. Get in.
Thank you.
You should get in too.
Where are you going?
To campus.
Oh, you live in the dorm.
Are you going to campus too?
Yes, to the library
to finish my assignment.
You might as well just walk next to me.
I don't want to feel
like I'm being chased.
-Eun-ho.
-What?
Do you like the club president?
What?
Maybe that was too direct.
Fine. Where is your hometown?
What's your type?
Are you into video games and stuff?
What's up with you?
You said I barely know you.
I want to get to know you quickly.
Eun-ho!
Run!
You can't go to the library
all soaked like that.
I have dry clothes in my bag.
You should dry them off a bit.
LAUNDRY ROOM
Someone's doing their job!
I'm sure they'll dry off in a bit.
Take care.
Wait!
There's a way we can dry your clothes.
Thanks for letting me in here.
This takes a while, doesn't it?
Yeah.
You should go change too.
Don't want to.
I want to stay here with you, Eun-ho.
You're one of a kind.
You're really bold, aren't you?
I didn't see this coming.
Se-june.
Here. Eat up.
Mi-rae, why are you so bold?
What did I do?
Do you like me?
Yes.
Why is this jerk
suddenly invading my thoughts?
Eun-ho.
You'll catch a cold.
Dry your hair.
And I don't like her.
I'll be in the reading room
while the laundry finishes. See you.
Wait…
Don't catch a cold.
What was that? So annoying.
General You-mi only lets me post
flattering photos of her.
I'll let it slide since she's cute.
Hashtag, soon to be taken.
What's this? You posted a photo?
What? I don't like this photo.
You don't?
No. You should have asked me first.
Only you look good.
I posted it because you told me to.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you snapping at me?
I only said that because you didn't have
any photos of us dating.
Okay. Sorry. You want it down, is that it?
Never mind. Just leave it.
BLOCK
I'm doing fine too, you know.
I'm happy too.
Then again, there's no rule saying
I have to be doing fine in the real world.
Let's go eat.
Okay, Eun-ho!
I heard the architecture program
is super hard.
Jung-pil told me that, by the third year,
your blood is basically coffee
from all the all-nighters.
But I don't think
I've ever seen you drink coffee.
Don't you like coffee?
Oh, I'm guessing
caffeine doesn't agree with you.
Want to go to a café after this?
Love it. I like lattes.
You like lattes?
All done.
What do you think?
You nailed it.
Like trying to paint over
old memories with new ones…
I immersed myself in Boyfriend on Demand.
Eun-ho.
How did it go?
The exam?
I blew it.
Because of you.
Is it true that a kumdo practitioner
could beat anyone with just chopsticks?
-Drinking game?
-Let's go!
Bunny bunny?
Not even. Don't be ridiculous.
Why not? You can stab people with them.
-Aim for the vital spots.
-Bunny, bunny! Carrot, carrot!
Stab!
Carrot, carrot!
No thrusts allowed until you're third dan.
Why?
Why are you outside by yourself?
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
To you, am I still…
just an upperclassman?
Why did I quit being an author?
Kim Baek-chun, the author, said to me,
"Hey, kid, you should give up
on being an author."
That's why I quit.
That's how tight we are.
What's wrong with you?
Wow, you're indebted to him.
-What was that?
-You're indebted to him. Indebted.
What? There wasn't any rain
in the forecast.
You came to a company dinner.
How unlike you.
Yeah, it felt kind of awkward
to go home for dinner.
I see.
Are you heading home?
Yes, I am
not.
You're not going home?
-Then back to the office?
-Seriously?
Does he think I have nowhere else to be?
Oh, well, I have a date, you see.
I see.
He'll be picking you up?
Yes.
Enjoy your date, then.
A date, really? Have you lost it?
I'm freezing.
VISUAL DESIGN CLASS GROUP CHAT
NA YOU-MI
Here is our mobile wedding invitation.
You are cordially invited
to Se-june and You-mi's wedding!
MOBILE WEDDING INVITATION
SUNDAY, NOVEMBER 23, 2025
KIM SE-JUNE, NA YOU-MI
Oh my God, you two look great together!
Congratulations, You-mi and Se-june.
You-mi, you look so pretty.
You'd better treat her well, Se-june.
JI-YEON
Is she out of her mind?
She totally knew you were in this chat.
Hello.
It's me. Did you have my number?
No.
At least you recognized my voice.
Why did you call?
Well, it's just, You-mi…
Damn, the thing she posted on the chat
is bothering me.
Did you see it?
Yeah.
You guys look happy.
I'm sorry.
About what?
For making you see that.
It…
It wasn't so different
from any other invitation.
Right. I'm glad you're okay with it.
Yeah.
I'm hanging up now. Take care.
NOTIFICATION
Ms. Seo Mi-rae, four hours remain
until your subscription expires.
Today, of all days?
I'm so sorry, but I love you
It's all a lie
I had no idea, I finally get it
I need you
Sorry, but I love you
Those piercing words
In the heat of the moment
I ended up letting you go
I'm so sorry, but I love you
It's all a lie
Together now!
Mi-rae.
You can't just walk away like that.
I did because you were talking nonsense.
-Let go.
-I can't.
If I let go, you'll just leave,
and you'll blame yourself
for letting our last moment end like this.
I'll deal with it myself. Let me go.
I said let go!
Why?
You broke up with me.
Why won't you let me leave?
Who do you think you are?
Just who do you think you are?
I may have brought it up first,
but we both already knew
that things had changed.
That's what you think.
I never changed.
Mi-rae.
We all change.
You've also changed.
If I can love you
for who you've become,
that would mean
we can be together forever.
But I…
I'm not sure if I can do that with you.
-Wow, look.
-It's beautiful.
-What is this place?
-Amazing.
-Let's take pictures.
-It's lovely.
Is something wrong?
I don't know what's going on,
but get some sleep
and just clear your mind.
You know what?
Ever since we broke up,
I've never once thought back
to our early days together.
-Cheers!
-Finish it off!
Se-june!
SEO MI-RAE
Don't I look good?
For your first day at work.
Thanks!
Got some sleep?
You had a long day.
Because you had changed anyway.
Because we were over anyway.
Because I hated your guts so much.
But
being in here brought the memories back,
and strangely…
I don't hate you now.
HANSAE KUMDO CLUB
FRESHMAN WELCOME TRIP
We're here. Let's get off.
Over there.
It's a shooting star.
Want to see it up close?
Is there something here?
You'll see.
Eun-ho.
Do you like me now?
Still not there yet?
Eun-ho.
If you end up marrying
someone other than me,
will you forget about me?
What do you mean?
It's not like you lose your memories
when you marry someone.
I'm sure I'll remember everything.
My heart may forget…
but the memories will remain.
How will you remember me?
The way I was in the end?
Or
in the beginning?
It's all you.
I'll remember it all.
The beginning…
and the end.
Okay.
That will do.
Have a good life.
You too.
You sound like you're about to go away.
You must be cold.
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon