Sorry!
- Sorry, sorry. - No, it's okay.
Those are very important client files.
I’ll do anything to make it up to you. I’m really sorry.
Anything?
Yes, anything.
Do my house in Tagaytay.
Attorney!
Here’s a package for you.
It’s from Valeria Construction.
Return those to Architect Luna Valeria.
I would rather have you repay me
through your professional service, Architect Valeria.
Sevi,
will you be my engineer for
- Kalix’s house project in Tagaytay? - You’ll accept the project?
Luna?
You’re Luna, right?
- Yes. - I’m Kio,
Kio Martinez.
Kio?
- Yes. - Kio!
Mom’s looking for you.
Isn’t Luna still very pretty?
You got the telescope back?
The moon looks so beautiful.
Yes, beautiful.
Luna.
What?
Are you hitting on me?
If yes…
so what?
I mean,
we’re both single.
You still haven’t changed, Attorney.
You’re still a flirt.
What do you really want?
Huh?
I’m just looking out for you.
Jeez!
I know what you’re doing.
If you’re not being serious, don’t—
I have never cheated on you, Luna.
Never.
You’re good.
You’re actually a good actor.
So good.
This is why a lot of people believe in you.
Because you know how to act.
I’m telling the truth.
Truth?
Are you serious?
So, what did I see then?
Was I just seeing things?
Just my imagination?
You know, Kalix,
I was stupid then.
But I wasn’t crazy.
You’re drunk
and we should just talk about this when you’re sober.
I’m drunk?
I’m not drunk
and we have nothing to talk about.
Okay?
Luna, where are you going?
Mind your own business.
Luna!
Luna, are you okay?
Hey…
I don’t ask help from cheaters like you.
Luna, you shouldn’t drive. You’re drunk.
And you shouldn’t have followed me.
Listen, it’s best if someone sober can take you home.
What if something happens—
Okay? Stop.
Stop acting like you care.
But I do care.
Don’t.
Okay? Don’t. I can–
I can take care of myself.
Take care of yourself?
You can’t even walk straight
and you think you can drive a car?
Why do you care?
Luna, where are your friends?
There has to be someone sober that can drive you–
Bastard! Okay?
- Luna, I’m justtrying to help you. - Fuck you.
Why did you even come back to my life?
Do you just want to apologize for all the fuck ups you did before?
Is that it?
Fine, let’s do this.
So you can finally relax,
here it goes.
I forgive you.
Okay?
Happy?
Now, go.
Go.
- Out of my way. Go. - Luna…
- What? - You shouldn’t drive.
Quit it–
Leave me alone!
Luna, listen please.
Please, please!
Go away.
All right, slowly.
Slowly…
Hey!
Luna?
Hey.
Are you okay?
Okay.
There, on the couch.
Watch out, careful.
All right.
How’re you feeling?
You okay?
Drink this.
Okay.
Thanks.
I’m okay.
I’m glad you’re not hurt.
Your car was towed already.
Huh?
Did I bump into—
Yes, don’t worry about it.
They’ll fix it ASAP.
Thanks for bringing me home.
No problem.
I’ll–
I’ll pay for your...
time and for your gas.
No need.
I’ll call my secretary and tell her to send you the payment.
Okay.
About...
what we were talking about—
Forget about it. Not now.
You need to rest.
We can talk about it some other time.
Okay.
Are you sure you’re gonna be okay by yourself?
Yes.
Should I text Kierra?
No, no, I can handle myself.
Okay.
The key is by the door, okay?
Why did you get yourself so drunk last night?
Now you’re regretting everything you said to Kalix.
Take note,
she’s regretting what she remembered she said.
What about what she said that she can’t even recall?
Stop reminding me, please.
This reminds me of our time in college.
Didn’t Kalix also bring you home when you were drunk then?
This might just be the start of your love story again.
#LuKal.
It’s going to be #LuKa-Luka
if she’s crazy enough to fall for him again.
Honestly, why are you guys always missing when I’m drunk?
No, Luna, we were just there.
Yes, the club was jam-packed
and you just couldn’t find us.
And it’s always Kalix who finds you, right?
Is the universe working overtime to get you two together again?
¡Es un tramposo!
Isn’t Kalix a cheater?
You better be careful, Luna.
I can’t take it if I see you crying again.
Or maybe we just also assumed that he cheated?
Yes and he’s not even together with Amethyst.
And he did not represent Miguel.
So, you’re saying they’re both single right now
and they’re even working together?
So what?
It’s just work. He’s my client,
I’m his architect. That’s all there is to it.
What if he tries to win you back?
So, are you going to give him another chance?
If he cheated, it’s a pass.
If not, go ahead.
Whatever your decision is, Luna, I’m all for it.
You know what’s best for you.
Question is,
do you still want him, Luna?
Oh, come on.
It’s too early for this kind of interrogation.
Let’s wait ‘til my hangover passes.
Mommy, let’s go!
Okay, Avi, let’s go.
I’ll go ahead, girls.
I need to bring her to school.
Luna, you know what you gotta do.
Flirt responsibly and… maturely.
No flirting is gonna happen, okay?
And hurry up,
your daughter will be late for school.
Besides, I gotta go, I don’t have a car today.
Bye!
- Bye! - Bye!
Good morning, Architect.
I had your car fixed last night.
I felt bad because
I think I’m partly to be blamed why you crashed the car in the first place.
Thanks.
Thank you for having it fixed.
Sorry, you had to take a rental today.
It’s okay.
Wait!
- Attorney! - Yes?
Glad you’re here. I need your signature.
I can sign them now.
There’s your daughter? Architect!
Mrs. Chu! How are you?
Oh my gosh!
How are you?
How are you, my dear?
What brings you here?
No, I just brought a thank you gift for you.
I really love the design you did for our Clark house.
You listened to all my requests and made it great.
I’m really glad that you liked my designs.
And because she liked it,
she told me she wants to do another project with us.
Yes, yes, yes! It’s for my nephew.
He just came home from California
and he plans to settle here for good.
Since he’s having his own house done,
I recommended you because
I know that you’re the best architect for residential projects.
I’m so excited, Mrs. Chu. Thank you very much.
You know, Architect,
my nephew is still single.
Nate, Lorice, sorry, sorry. I just have to say this because–
because, you’re so beautiful,
you’re even successful and—
and it’s baffling to me that you’re still single.
Well, I think guys are scared because I’m overqualified.
No, but kidding aside,
I’m not ready to settle down yet.
Actually, Mrs. Chu, there’s a lot of guys who want to go on a date with her.
But none of them have passed her standards. Right, Dad?
That’s so true.
Mom.
Better to be sure
than to settle with a jerk and a cheater.
That’s why I’m hoping that you’ll meet my nephew.
Not only as an architect but also personally.
He’s handsome and kind.
Wait, wait, wait.
Do you have any specific type?
Someone—
Someone loyal and honest.
Oh my god, this is perfect.
Oh wow! Great. I think I can vouch for my nephew.
And I think you guys would be perfect together.
He definitely fits your standards.
So, so what,
are you interested?
Who knows,
you might get along with each other.
I’m so excited.
Why didn’t you accept Mrs. Chu’s offer?
Her nephew might really be handsome
and he might even fit your standards.
I don’t need someone handsome, Ke.
What I want is someone loyal.
Besides, there’s nothing wrong with focusing on work.
That’s too bad.
It’s been so long since you fell in love.
You’re getting older but you choose to focus on working.
Age doesn’t matter when it comes to love.
Besides, I can do all things a guy can do for me.
If someone comes, I’ll welcome him in.
If there’s no one, then I’ll be fabulous on my own.
Architect?
Oh, someone did come.
Sorry, what’s that?
Attorney, come in.
Architect Valeria,
you might have a hangover and these may help.
Architect Ynares, please, have some too.
Attorney, thank you. This is so sweet of you.
Luna, aren’t blueberries your favorite?
This mango is my favorite since it’s so sweet.
Anyway, I’ll get going now. I’ll leave you two.
Thank you, Attorney.
You may sit.
Attorney,
you don't have to do this every time we have a meeting,
It’s not part of the contract.
I know.
I brought you these fruits ‘cause I want to.
Do you like the designs?
Why did you choose the royal blue tile?
Bachelor’s pad for your master’s bedroom.
Oh, it’s definitely not gonna be a bachelor’s pad.
Like I mentioned before,
this is gonna be a family home.
I’ll be sharing the master bedroom with my future wife.
If you don’t like royal blue, hold on.
Maybe you can choose some colors here.
So…
light copper would work
or green tree,
or green river.
What color do you prefer?
I told you to design it the way you want it.
Not the way you think I want it.
All right then.
I’ll send you the revisions through email.
Thank you for the trust.
It really meant a lot.
This makes the job easier.
I’ll be waiting.
Please make sure that the delivered materials are correct.
And follow up with our suppliers.
We need to meet the deadline. Okay?
- Yes, Architect. - Okay, thanks.
Oh! Perfect timing.
Are you sure we’re not closing off the veranda?
I like it as it is.
This place is special to me.
The—
Do you have your pegs for the guest bedroom?
You can send them to me through email
so that I can discuss it with the interior designer.
Or, Architect,
we can always text.
It’s just faster that way.
I don’t have your number.
I did not change my number.
I deleted your number.
Oh.
Okay.
Give me your phone.
Huh?
Give me your phone, so we can exchange numbers.
Oh, okay.
Here.
Okay, uhm---
I’ll just text you regarding any updates with this house.
Here you go.
By the way, I sent you a follow request the other day.
Really?
Sorry, I haven’t been checking my socials recently.
I’ve been busy.
Are you active in social media now?
Not really.
I just like to keep up with the people I care about.
Oh, because I’m your architect.
You’d wanna know what’s happening in my life.
Maybe you’d want to see the master’s bedroom since
they’re putting up the wallpaper already.
Sure.
Are you okay?
Yes, sorry. I’m just dizzy.
Architect, you might be hungry or
dehydrated or even fatigued. Sit down.
- Kuya, chair please. - No, no!
No, it’s okay. It’s okay.
It’s just a slight migraine. I can manage.
No.
Let’s take a break first. We can continue later.
- There’s no need. - Thank you!
- I’m all right. - Sit down.
Sit down.
Okay.
Everyone, let’s take a break. I bought some food.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
Go ahead, don’t be shy. Eat up.
Come on, you guys can sit here.
Guys, sit here.
I bought some food.
I’m not hungry, but thanks.
Eat up, Luna.
You shouldn’t waste Attorney’s treat.
Thanks, Attorney.
The boys are grateful.
No problem, Engineer.
Eat first.
Let me.
Lucky you.
I’m on it.
I'm about to eat.
Hello?
What?
Mom…
You’re coming here?
So, what do you think, Mom, Dad?
I like it.
It’s simple and practical.
Yes, I agree, Dad.
The first time I saw the design, I really did like it.
Is this it?
This is the design?
What do you mean?
I mean, it’s just…
I expected more.
You know, simple is different from simplistic and this
is simplistic.
I feel it’s too plain, it’s too bland.
We’re still at 60% of construction, Mom.
It’s not yet finished.
But I’m sure that once everything is done
and everything is set in place,
you will see how amazing this house can be.
Amazing?
I’m not sure.
I mean, judging from the layout,
I think I like how the house looked before.
I’m sorry, who are they again?
Mom, Dad,
Architect Luna Valeria, Engineer Sevi Camero.
Hi.
Good afternoon.
Luna Valeria?
Are you—
Yes.
Wow!
You were just an architecture student when we first met you.
It’s good to see that you are practicing your profession now.
Thank you.
Dear, I’ll be blunt.
Is there a way for you to fix this, maybe improve it?
I just feel that it’s too open,
you know, like there’s no privacy.
And your design, by the way, is too common. You know?
This minimalist design that you got going here
it’s just not working for me.
I have to disagree with you, Mom.
The design is perfect.
It’s a huge improvement from the previous design of this house.
This feels more homey.
Where a family can actually live in.
I don’t want too big of a house and closed off where family
members can’t even see each other anymore.
Like ours.
Just to add, Doc,
I designed it this way to let more natural light in.
And to have a better view of this beautiful landscape outside.
We wouldn’t want to waste it, right?
We should maximize the beauty of nature here in Tagaytay.
And to be honest,
the original walls made the house look small and constricted.
With this open floor layout,
people can see more of each other.
Plus,
the layout is flexible so it’s easy to reconfigure the furnishings.
Kalix do you really like it?
Yes, Mom. A hundred percent.
Every design element of this house is well-thought of.
Architect Valeria did a really great job.
Fine.
If you say so.
You’re the one who’s gonna live here anyway.
What happened earlier was really intense.
Kalix’s mom is really scary.
What are you going to do when she becomes your mother-in-law?
Are you crazy?
But it’s good that he finally defended you.
Feeling giddy now, aren’t you?
What do you mean? I’m actually confused.
He’s been very sweet this week and
his comments seem to have an underlying meaning to it.
That makes me think that he and I still have a chance, like we can still be—
I don’t know anymore, it’s just annoying.
What if there really is a chance?
Stop assuming things.
This is just work.
Jeez! You never change.
Besides, this is my first time seeing a client who keeps visiting the site.
This is out of town, you know?
I wonder why.
Kalix just might be a hands-on client.
Or… he just wants to come see you.
That’s nonsense.
Stop putting meaning into this,
we are strictly professional.
Strictly professional or–
Just strictly professional!
You hear me? Okay? Happy now?
This is just work, strictly professional.
Okay, okay.
Answer it.
- What? - I need to go home. ‘Cause…
- ‘Cause…? - I can’t be late.
- I don’t wanna be in trouble. - Is this work?
- I’ll go ahead. - Or are you going on a date?
- Bye. - Okay, I’ll go home soon too.
This jerk…
Luna!
Can we talk?
Okay.
Sorry about what happened earlier.
Personally, I really like your design.
It’s fine, don’t worry about it.
It’s normal for some people not to like my designs.
But, thank you.
I appreciate it.
By the way,
Adonis is inviting you for dinner.
Dinner?
It’s his birthday.
He says he wants to invite all of his closest friends.
And he asked me to give you this.
Dear Architect, you better come to my birthday. I’ll be really sad if you don’t. Love, Adonis
So what do you think?
Are you coming?
Okay.
Great.
I’ll tell Adi.
I’ll see you tomorrow night?
Okay.
I’ll go ahead.
Yeah.
Architect!
You’re here.
Happy birthday, Adi.
Wow! Thanks a lot.
You even gave me a gift.
Help yourself out.
Architect, glad you came.
So glad that you made it, Architect.
Am I early?
No, you’re right on time. We’re complete now.
Is it really your birthday, Adi?
It's my birthday tomorrow.
This is an advance birthday celebration with my best buddies.
You’re one of them so thank you for coming.
Excuse me, we’re just gonna go ahead.
We left something.
Come on guys, that’s just lame.
I know you are planning a surprise for me.
All right then, go ahead, I’ll pretend like I have no idea.
Don’t be too full of yourself!
Let’s have a drink?
Sure.
Seriously, thanks for coming.
I really appreciate it.
Of course, I don’t want you to sulk just because of me.
You’re such a nice person. Just like Kalix.
But so scary at work.
Especially when we were both in that firm where we handled criminal cases.
Adi, can I ask you something?
Sure.
Didn’t Kalix leave his old firm?
Yes, since he didn’t have a choice.
Why didn’t he have a choice?
Our boss said that
it’s either he’s gonna resign or he’s gonna take a certain case.
What certain case?
The one about that mayor’s son, about–
Miguel Villaflor?
Yes! Yes, that one.
After our boss gave him that ultimatum, it didn’t even take Kalix an hour to decide
and give his letter of immediate resignation.
He decided that quickly.
He took cases worse than that
but that was the only one he rejected.
I didn’t really get it.
He could’ve won easily.
They said he was going to be paid four times his salary.
But Amethyst took the case, didn’t she?
Kalix asked her to take it.
How come?
No idea.
That was also Amy’s first loss.
Happy birthday, Adi…
Happy birthday, happy birthday…
Make a wish!
Thanks, guys!
- Yes sir, to many more years, brother. - Finish this.
Cheers!
Yo, let’s take this champagne later?
Yes, let’s do it!
Bro, do you wanna smoke?
Sure, let’s go.
- Excuse us. - Excuse us.
Would you like some wine?
Kalix, can we talk?
I heard you resigned because of Miguel’s case.
Yes.
Why?
Because that’s the right decision.
I couldn’t work with them anymore.
Adi said that you could have easily won that case.
Why did you leave then?
I didn’t want to defend an abuser.
Maybe they offered a lot of money,
but they couldn’t buy my principles.
Alleged, remember?
Innocent until proven guilty.
You’re learning something.
You said your opinions won’t matter in court.
It’s only the court who’s going to decide if someone’s guilty or not.
So why did you reject the case?
For you, Luna.
I knew it was important to you.
For me?
Why?
I knew it was important to you and Kierra.
I didn’t want to disappoint you, Luna.
I don’t understand.
I wasn’t even in your life when this all happened.
You were never gone.
Many years have passed and you were never really gone.
Even after all these years have passed?
It was hard to forget what we had, Luna.
And I told you,
I would give up anything for you, Luna.
I wanted to keep my word.
You shouldn’t have sacrificed your job for me, Kalix.
If I had taken that case,
you would’ve hated me forever.
You would have never talked to me again.
And I can’t ever live with that.
Sorry, I have to take this call.
- Dad? - Luna,
sorry for the short notice.
Can you drop by the office tonight?
There’s just a rush revision needed.
Okay, Dad.
You have to leave?
Architect Valeria…
Take care.
You too.
You were never gone.
Many years have passed and you were never really gone.
Luna, it means moon.
Now you’ll remember me everytime you look at the moon.
Like a curse.
More like a tattoo in my brain.
A beautiful one.
One that I’m never gonna forget.
I can see it! The moon looks so beautiful.
Yes,
beautiful.
I spoke with the landscape designer
and they said that bay fencing and wood decking
would match the outdoors to the interior.
If you have any concerns, let me know.
No, that sounds good.
Why, Kalix?
What?
Your post.
Your caption.
What about it?
The caption you had is my name.
I posted it because it was special to me.
Special?
Because we got to talk things out.
Things I should’ve said earlier.
I’ve been thinking recently.
About,
regrets.
I regret failing that semester.
So many things changed after that.
Your dreams?
Everything, Luna.
Everything started falling apart at that time.
But most especially, the future I dreamt of.
If I could go back in time
and change something, I would go specifically to that one semester.
And do anything to not let you think
that I cheated on you, Luna.
Because I didn’t.
I really didn’t.
And I would be willing to explain everything to you
as long as you’re ready.
As long as we’re both ready to listen to each other
with an open mind.
How about you?
Do you have any regrets?
That one night
when I said I didn’t love you—
I didn’t believe you.
But it stopped you.
You gave up.
I didn’t give up on you.
On us.
You just felt like you wanted to get rid of me so badly
that you even have to lie about your own feelings.
So why are you back, Kalix?
Why are you even telling me all this?
I was doing great already.
Because I want you back, Luna.
You are the future I dreamt of.
And trust me I regret every single day of the past years…
that I just walked away from you.
That I did not fight for us.
A lot has happened, Kalix.
So many things have changed.
I know.
I know we’re not the same people anymore.
But my feelings for you never changed.
I meant it when I said that my feelings for you were never gone.
I want you to understand, Luna, that I’m really trying.
And I want you to give me a second chance.
I know I’m asking too much but if you could only give me one more chance.
Just to prove myself to you one last time.
If you still don’t want me after that,
I promise
you won’t see me ever again.
I’m scared.
I don’t know if it’s still worth it for us to try again.
Use this Boracay trip to relax and think about it.
Hello, Kalix.
Hey! I just arrived here in Malaysia.
Enjoy your stay in Boracay.
I guess it’s good that we’re on separate trips so that we can think clearly.
Again,
I’m not pressuring you to give me an answer right away.
I’m willing to wait for it
and work hard for it.
I know he already knows what he lost after you broke up.
But, let’s show him more.
Let’s show him what he missed out on.
You look great, as always.
You just reminded me of our time in Boracay.
There’s someone at the door.
I’ll be back ‘cause my phone is charging, okay?
Give me a second.
- Okay. - What’s up?
You know my room number, right?
- Yes. - You should stop by.
Let’s have some fun.