[theme music]
[suspenseful music]
[growling]
[Joon-seong whimpering]
Stay back, stay back.
Stay away!
No way we're going to heaven now.
We're alive, so this is heaven.
[yelps]
[upbeat music]
[zombie growling]
2ND GRADE 5 CLASS
[growls]
JUNG YONG-HYEON
[thudding]
I heard that in some countries,
they mourn adults
more than they do with children.
[somber music]
[Nam-ra] And in others,
children more than adults.
Which do you think our country is?
What do you mean?
When kids die, you lose hope but…
when adults die, you lose their wisdom.
-[Joon-yeong] Hope and wisdom.
-[helicopter whirring in distance]
Which do we value more?
Hmm?
[helicopter whirring in distance]
[Nam-ra] They've been flying
all over the place since yesterday.
They would have already saved us
if they really wanted to.
But even if they do come to save us,
we won't get out first.
We're just not important enough for that.
[somber music]
We're students. That's it.
[helicopter whirring in distance]
[helicopter pilot] We're coming in.
Set to control, steady.
Prepare for landing.
Okay, roger.
[helicopter pilot] Landing pad is clear.
We're touching down.
RESCUE HEADQUARTERS
[whirring]
[helicopter whirring]
[ominous music]
We have everyone on board.
Heading to the quarantine camp now.
[whooshing]
[anchorman] Around 11:00 a.m.
this morning,
the government announced
the declaration of martial law
in an effort to control
the crisis in Hyosan.
Starting sometime yesterday afternoon,
a strange epidemic began to spread,
which lead to an evacuation order
-and a city-wide lockdown.
-And a city-wide lockdown.
It's the first time in 41 years
that martial law has been declared.
[anchorwoman 1] Last time was
the Democratization Movement
on May 18th, 1980.
I repeat. Martial law has been declared
in order to control the Hyosan--
[anchorwoman 2] The sense of panic
caused by the Hyosan epidemic
has sent markets into a death spiral.
Sidecar investments were activated
for both KOSPI and KOSDAQ
which came as volatile
market respondent to Covid-19…
[male protester] No refugees from Hyosan!
We don't want them!
[protesters] We don't want them!
[male protester] No refugees. Go back!
Go back where you came from.
[preacher] We are the Lord's people
who receives salvation.
People will die as people,
and demons are going to perish
as all demons must.
[members] Amen.
Get away!
[screaming]
-Look out!
-[zombie growling]
[screaming]
[crowd clamoring]
[male protester] You're killing us.
[protesters] Go home!
Come on, Zuki. It's okay, okay. Thank you.
-Why won't you let us in?
-Get the hell of me.
-[protesters] Send them back. Go home!
-[tense music]
-Please. You have to help us!
-[protesters shouting indistinctly]
REMOVE THE GOVERNMENT!
[preacher] Our Lord Jesus Christ
will not ask whether you are his son
or the son of the Devil.
No. He won't.
EVERYONE WILL DIE!
[preacher] A person
who does not act righteously.
A person who does not love
their brothers and sisters…
REMOVE THE GOVERNMENT!
…that is not one of God's people.
[all] Amen!
-We're so gonna break a million views.
-[all laugh]
[crowd clamoring]
[anchorwoman 1]
A false rumor recently surfaced
claiming that Hyosan epidemic
has spread to Seoul,
as a result, the number of people
leaving Korea through Incheon Airport
-rose to 228,000 in a day.
-[YouTuber] Hi, everyone. I apologize
to the people, to all the viewers
we scared with our zombie skit
we did on the subway.
[sucks teeth]
Today, I'm on my knees
begging for your forgiveness…
[inhales]
…for accidentally misleading everyone
about the crisis in Hyosan…
Is this what you expected? Really? Really?
[laughs]
SUBWAY ZOMBIE PERFORMANCE
APOLOGY VIDEO
[prime minister] We have to expand
martial law to control the media.
There are rumors that radiation
from US nuclear bombs created the zombies.
That the heads of Korea's
top 30 corporations fled the country.
Most of the media are spreading fake news
and sharing it online
without verifying sources.
It's contributing to all the chaos.
The government
should not control the media.
The people themselves
should control the media.
And our citizens
have enough power to do that.
No expansion in martial law.
[prime minister]
Let's focus on containment
and rescuing the uninfected.
Those are our priorities.
-[Dae-su] Su-hyeok.
-[Wu-jin] Hey, Bare-su.
-[panting]
-Are you okay?
Where's the phone?
And Cheong-san?
[breathes nervously]
[On-jo] Su-hyeok.
Where is he?
[suspenseful music]
We got separated in the teacher's office.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
Are you serious? Oh, shit!
I'm sorry…
for coming back alone.
[sighs]
[grunts]
-[growls]
-[groans]
Come here.
[Gwi-nam] Come here.
[tense suspenseful music]
[growling]
[grunts]
[grunting]
Were you bit? You were bit, right?
No, I--
[gasps]
[groans]
[whimpers, screams]
-[growling]
-[screaming]
[tense music]
[growls]
[grunts]
-[grunts]
-[growling]
[breathes angrily]
[grunting]
[snarling]
[growls]
[pants]
[Gwi-nam grunts]
[both panting]
Cut it out.
Give me the fucking phone.
You killed the principal.
You're a murderer.
You made me kill him. You shit.
-You wanted proof I wasn't a coward.
-You're insane.
[tense action music]
[Gwi-nam grunts]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
[growls]
-[growls]
-[groans]
[growling]
[both grunting]
[zombies growling]
[Gwi-nam] Get off me.
-[grunts]
-[shatters]
[growling]
Should I save you?
-[Cheong-san grunting]
-What do you say?
[Cheong-san grunting]
Beg for your life. Come on.
Screw you.
[grunts]
[Gwi-nam gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[grunting]
[Cheong-san whimpering]
-[thuds]
-[Gwi-nam grunts]
[screaming]
[breathing heavily]
-[Gwi-nam groans]
-[growling]
[Gwi-nam screams]
-[grunting]
-[growling]
[zombies snarling]
Damn it.
Shit! Help me!
[growling, munching]
Cheong-san!
[Gwi-nam] Cheong-san!
Fuck!
Oh, please!
[whimpering]
-[screaming]
-[growling, munching]
[zombies munching]
-[ominous music]
-I'll kill you.
I will kill you.
Fuck you.
[breathing heavily]
I'll…
I'll kill you.
-[banging]
-[glass shattering]
-[shudders]
-[banging continues]
[whimpers]
[sniffles, sobs]
[munch, growl]
[breathes heavily]
[tense music]
[Cheong-san grunts]
[panting, grunting]
Whoa!
[grunts]
[snarls]
-[grunting]
-[wood creaks]
[growling]
[zombies growling]
[zombies snarling]
[growls]
[tense music]
[Cheong-san grunting]
[zombie snarls]
[grunts]
[growls]
[panting, grunting]
[tense music continues]
[panting]
[growling]
[thudding]
[snarling]
[growling]
[grunting]
[grunts]
-[grunting]
-[growling]
[grunts]
[panting]
[Mi-jin breathes heavily]
[sighs]
Shit.
None of them are normal. All infected.
-[zombie growling]
-Hey! He's coming!
[Mi-jin] Oh, Shit. Shoot, shoot!
[sighs in relief]
Oh, shit.
We're gonna die
before we ever find your brother.
[clattering]
[sighs]
Let's go, okay?
[suspenseful music]
[breathes heavily]
Oh, shit.
[whimpers]
Oh, seriously--
[door closes]
[glass shatters]
[foreboding music]
[breathes nervously]
[tense music builds]
[Mi-jin] Shit.
[both sigh in relief]
[sighs]
I told you we should just
stay put, didn't I?
How are we gonna find your brother
in the middle of all this?
And it was just as crazy
to have come with her.
-I told you--
-Hey. Hey!
-[Mi-jin] What?
-There's a computer.
[Mi-jin] Oh, yeah. Turn it on.
Post on Instagram or Facebook for help.
[Mi-jin sighs]
Oh, shit.
-[computer chimes]
-[sighs]
ADMIN
[growling]
[thumping]
[Seon-moon] Martial Law Command
has acted swiftly and thoroughly.
We sealed off the entire Hyosan area
to prevent the situation
from spreading to other regions.
[gasps, breathes shakily]
If you live outside the area
under martial law,
please stay calm and return
to your normal lives.
Currently, Martial Law Command
is doing its absolute best
to quarantine those infected
and to rescue and protect
those who are not.
EMERGENCY CALL
We continue to operate, as always,
in strict compliance with the law
and Federal regulations.
EMERGENCY CALL
CONNECTING
Fake news about the Hyosan epidemic
is spreading fast.
Almost like a separate contagion.
Martial Law Command will sensor
all unconfirmed rumors, simultaneously,
in the interest of operational efficiency,
-all cell phone services…
-[phone line busy tone]
…landlines, internet services,
-and all communication originating…
-Why it isn't working?
-…in Hyosan will be terminated…
-[Min-jae] Huh?
What's wrong?
-…from this point on.
-[reporters murmuring]
-[camera shutters clicks]
-[indistinct chatter]
[phone line busy tone]
[clicking rapidly]
That's so weird.
The internet cable's plugged in.
-I'm trying to refresh it.
-Hey, get the phone over there.
Okay.
[beeping]
[phone line busy tone]
[sighs in annoyance]
Shit. Fucking assholes.
They cut off the phones and internet.
We at Martial Law Command,
and its advisory council,
are doing our best
to suppress the continuous spread.
[Seon-moon] Moreover,
we are focusing all of our resources
to rescue the people
who are currently trapped.
If you live in Hyosan,
and you're watching this now,
please try to stay hopeful and wait
in your location to be rescued.
NO SIGNAL
OCTOBER 21, THURSDAY
[suspenseful music]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[gasps, breathes heavily]
[phone chimes]
[phone line busy tone]
[grunting]
[suspenseful music continues]
[groans]
[phone line busy tone]
[screams frustratedly]
[breathes angrily]
[sobbing]
[sobbing continues]
WATER FLOW DETECTOR
[growling]
What do we do?
On-jo and Cheong-san are really close.
[Ji-min] They're going out.
But On-jo told me they're not.
I'm telling you they are.
[Ji-min] They're always together.
[Hyo-ryeong] Really?
NAM ON-JO
Poor On-jo.
[sighs deeply]
[sentimental music]
[sniffles]
[sighs]
I'm sure Cheong-san is fine.
You know how fast he is.
I don't know why he never listens.
Ever since we were kids,
he's just never listened to me.
I told him not to go,
but, of course, he did.
I'm sorry.
I should've brought him back here.
[sighs]
Where do you think…
he is now?
I'm pretty sure
he's in a safe hiding spot.
[helicopter whirring in distance]
[whirring]
Joon-yeong. Didn't you mention
that your science club made a drone?
Yeah. You want to look
for Cheong-san with it?
-Could we?
-Well, yeah. But it's in the science lab.
We can go get it.
How would we get it?
It's crawling with zombies out there.
That.
[foreboding tense music]
[Joon-yeong] You want me
to climb up on that?
But there are zombies
in the science lab too.
There weren't any
in the supply room. Right?
That's true, but…
We have to find Cheong-san.
There's no one else besides us
to start looking
and rescue people.
[sighs]
Yeah.
It would be good if we had the drone.
We can find Cheong-san and then
we can see how things are outside.
[Nam-ra] We might even be able to send
an emergency message and ask for help.
Sure, that would be really great.
But who's gonna go?
I wanna go.
I took a fire rescue class,
and I've climbed ropes before.
No, I'll go.
You already went out there.
[On-jo] You can't keep
putting yourself in danger.
The drone isn't finished yet,
we need to find
a few more parts to run it.
Do you know what to get?
[ominous music]
[Joon-yeong sighs]
Then I have to go anyway, I guess.
I'll go with On-jo.
No way.
I'm actually going this time
so stand back.
But you can't.
He can't.
[chuckles]
The rope won't hold you.
It was fine when I came down.
But it'll snap if I climb up, right?
-Yeah. Right.
-[Dae-su] Yeah. It'll snap.
[Wu-jin] Right. Good boy.
Joon-yeong, come with me.
Mm.
It's too dangerous.
I'll go.
[Joon-yeong groans]
Thank you.
But I don't want you…
to be put in danger anymore.
[Joon-yeong] I'm going.
[groans]
I'm going.
[grunting]
[breathes nervously]
[Ji-min] Be careful, On-jo.
Be safe. We'll be watching, okay?
[suspenseful music]
[grunts]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Hyo-ryeong] Do you think…
it's really safe out there?
I'm sure it is.
Like you said,
there are soldiers and cops, right?
I wanna go to my dad's factory
and my mom's sundae place.
[snorts]
Whatever.
You hate the smell
of leather and sundae anyway.
[sniffles]
Yeah, I do.
I just want my mom's sundae soup.
[scoffs]
So you finally grew up?
You should have said that earlier.
Now, it's too late.
[sighs]
[zombie growling in distance]
[quirky music]
[Jae-ik] Hey. Hey, look.
I bet there's a key in there, right?
[sighs]
I don't think so.
Shouldn't we just hide somewhere safe
and wait to be rescued?
Hey.
He said the solution
is on his laptop at the school.
We have to hurry and notify
Fire and Disasters HQ.
The people who have important information
need to survive, am I right?
So doesn't our survival come first?
Why do you keep acting
better than everyone
like some elite leader of society?
You're from Seoul University?
-Yeah.
-Huh? Wait?
You really went there? Serious?
Well, I haven't graduated yet.
I'm going back.
Oh, grad school?
-No. I'm a sophomore.
-What?
Your exams? You retake?
Uh, few times. Yeah.
I went after high school.
Oh, wow. I guess you must really
had your nose to the crime stuff, huh?
Your face says it all.
Hey. Apparently, you're smart,
so I'm gonna say this once.
Be quiet and follow me.
[splutters]
Wait.
[grunts]
Shit!
[screams angrily]
-[zombie growls]
-Whoa!
[panting]
[engine creaks]
-[growls]
-[Jae-ik] Shut the door. Shut the door!
-[growling]
-[grunting]
Why won't it start?
[screaming]
[Ho-cheol] Hurry up!
Please spare me!
-[Jae-ik] Come on. This way.
-[Ho-cheol screaming]
[Ho-cheol] Wait.
-[Jae-ik] Let's go! Here.
-[bell chimes]
Hurry!
GOOD LUCK WITH YOUR NEW BUSINESS
[growls]
[Ho-cheol] Oh, my God.
It's a zombie, sir.
[growling]
There's a zombie in here.
[both panting]
-[baby crying]
-[zombies growling]
-In there?
-Yeah.
Shit!
[Hee-su growling]
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
-It's all right. Come on.
-[zombie growling]
Sure?
She's tied up. it's okay.
A student should be in school.
Why is she in a chicken place?
And why she tied…
Oh, my gosh!
-What? What? What?
-[spluttering]
Right there. There.
What? What is that?
Oh, shit.
[Ho-cheol] Is… is it okay?
Is, is the baby a zombie?
No. It's alive.
[growling]
[somber music]
[baby coos]
[growls]
Why don't you go check the fridge
for some milk or something?
Why? Are you thirsty?
It's for the baby.
We need to feed this baby somehow.
It's very dehydrated.
What if there's no milk?
Can you just check first?
Check the fridge,
and if there's no milk, come back,
and we cross that bridge
when we come to it, okay?
Uh, yeah. You're right. Yeah.
-If there's no milk, maybe I should bring?
-Just check first. Can you do that?
[Jae-ik] Check. Damn it.
[croaking]
What do we do now?
What else can we do? Back to HQ.
What about that?
It's hard enough with just us.
Are you gonna bring it along?
[clanking]
[chuckles]
[panting]
[grunts]
Oh, careful.
The drone and the bag are right there.
[suspenseful music]
[object clattering]
[zipper zips]
[Joon-yeong] Okay. Where was it?
Where is the battery?
[sniffles]
[sighs]
[objects clattering]
[suspenseful music continues]
I can't stop thinking
about this one thing.
What?
If eventually everyone in the world
but us ends up turning in too?
No way.
But if that were true?
Nah.
Then we'd be the minority.
And all minorities
have a way of going extinct.
[sighs]
We're not the minority.
But what if that actually happens?
You think you could make it through this?
[pensive music]
I don't know.
But I don't wanna be a zombie.
[Su-hyeok] You don't recognize anyone.
And…
I won't even recognize you.
In case I do get bitten,
I have a favor to ask.
No.
Don't get bit.
-If by chance--
-No.
Don't get bit. You can't.
[Su-hyeok] Don't even think about dying.
THIS DOOR DOES NOT OPEN FROM THE INSIDE
Shit.
[suspenseful music]
[sighs]
[breathes shakily]
[metal clanks]
[grunts]
[suspenseful music continues]
[metal clanks, creaks]
-[grunting]
-[metal creaking]
-[grunts]
[grunts]
-[grunting]
-[metal creaking]
[growls]
[metal clanks]
[growling]
-[breathes heavily]
-[metal clanking]
[metal clanks]
-Eat up, I-sak.
-Thanks.
[laughs]
On-jo. Which do you like better?
-Mm, they're both good.
-Is that right?
[laughs]
[reflective music]
-[breathes heavily]
-[metal clanking]
Is it better like this?
Or like this?
[metal clanking]
[laughing]
Why?
-[croaks]
-[laughter echoing]
[whimpers]
-[sniffles]
-[metal clanks]
[breathes heavily]
-[grunts]
-[growling]
-[grunting]
-[metal clanking]
[growls]
-[groans]
-[tense music]
-[grunts]
-[growling]
Fuck this.
[screams angrily]
[zombies growling]
-[snarls]
-[panting]
-[gasps]
-[growling]
[loud thuds]
[panting]
[groans]
-[growling]
-[grunts]
MUSIC ROOM
INSTRUMENT STORAGE
[breathes heavily]
[Joon-yeong] Hey, be careful.
Take your time. Take your time.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
[breathes nervously]
HELP, WE'RE IN THE BROADCASTING ROOM
IN HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
[chimes]
[drone chimes]
Does it work?
Is it working?
I think it will.
[pensive music]
[drone whirring]
Ooh.
[whirring]
[gasps]
[Dae-su] Holy crap.
That thing's crazy fast.
I'll take it outside
after I find Cheong-san.
If I find any rescuers out there,
I'll land in front of them.
Okay. Okay, okay.
[drone whirring]
-Wait a second.
-[suspenseful music]
They say when people know
their situation is hopeless,
that's when they despair.
Sweet saying.
But what does that mean?
Even if everyone in the world
but us turned into zombies,
we can't fall in to despair.
Ahh. So that's what that means?
Nam-ra.
It's best to make a plan
and try to stick to it,
but we're not all top students,
and we can't be as smart as you.
Being logical isn't part of human nature.
In a crisis, it's better to be logical.
We need hope more than logic.
Don't you think that's best right now?
Hey. I think…
flying the drone
is what we need right now.
-Okay. Try it.
-Here goes.
-[Dae-su] Mm.
-[drone whirring]
[tense music]
[tense music continues]
[gasps]
Oh, no.
Everyone's zombie.
[music fades]
[sighs]
I shouldn't even bother studying.
Shit.
I can't take my CSAT anyway.
Shit. I'll never studying again
as long as I live.
Can you please be serious
for once in your life?
I'm dead serious right now.
What are you gonna do?
Keep looking for your brother?
The archery center has an emergency phone.
It automatically connects
to emergency services.
-Really?
-Yeah.
We got a hotline installed a while ago
because of some injuries.
And if it doesn't connect?
All the phones and internet are dead.
It doesn't matter.
That's where all the arrows are anyway.
I have less than 20 left.
We'll need more
if we wanna leave the school alive.
-I think, uh--
-Okay, let's go.
Go to the archery center
so we can get your arrows.
Then we should probably go home
or maybe go to a supermarket.
You know. In most zombie movies,
the ones that go to supermarkets
always manage to survive in the end.
And they have cigs.
I think that we--
[Min-jae] The dumpsters
are right under these windows.
I think it's better to jump
than use the stairs.
[sighs]
Yeah. Let's jump.
Falling from the third floor is way better
than falling your exams, right?
Hey, let me get a word in!
Hey, Min-jae.
Go down first and shoot any
that come running.
[Min-jae] Okay.
Then you two go down
and help him out as much as you can.
I'll cover you out in the hallway
and bring up the rear.
Mm.
What do you wanna say?
Uh, I think we should just stay here.
The adults will rescue us.
If you wanna stay, be my guest.
But I don't trust adults.
Ahh, shit. She's just so my type.
[Joon-seong sighs]
I'm too scared to stay here alone.
Hurry up.
[suspenseful music]
[zombies growling in distance]
[zombie shrieks]
[breathes heavily]
[panting]
[suspenseful music]
[growling]
[groans]
-Look out! Behind you!
-[growls]
Move.
[shrieks]
[gasps]
[growling]
[whimpers]
Oh, shit. Why are we so high up?
-Jump already.
-All right, I'm going.
[screams]
[groans]
Shit.
[pants]
[growling in distance]
[growling]
[drone whirring]
No one in the infirmary.
Joon-yeong, go somewhere else.
Wait. Hold on. Stop right there.
[Wu-jin] Is that an arrow?
-Where?
-This.
[Dae-su] You're right. It is.
Why? What?
My older sister.
She had a competition today.
[music fades]
[dramatic music]
Where the hell did Cheong-san go?
[breathes heavily]
[dramatic music continues]
-[metal creaking]
-[thudding]
[screeching]
[drone whirring]
It's Cheong-san!
-What room is that?
-Cheong-san!
He… He can't hear you.
-[Wu-jin] Be quiet.
-[suspenseful music]
-Hey, Cheong-san!
-He can't hear you.
On-jo, it's okay.
[gasps]
Cheong-san is alive!
[Su-hyeok] Cheong-san is alive!
[breathes heavily]
Ah…
What's he doing? Where's he going?
[Dae-su] Look this way! Over here!
Where are you going, you stupid moron?
He can't hear you, Dae-su!
[Wu-jin] Be quiet, will you?
You're so damn loud.
[Dae-su] My bad. My bad.
-Didn't you say the battery was low?
-[Joon-yeong sighs]
Yeah. I couldn't charge it,
so it's almost dead.
Now that we know for sure
where Cheong-san is,
let's go look somewhere else.
You wanted to check outside
and ask for help?
On-jo, is that okay?
Mm-hmm. Now that we know he's alive.
Okay. Here it goes.
[drone whooshes, whirring]
[Dae-su] Whoa.
It's totally Zombieland out there.
I think we should look
outside of the school grounds.
Let's take it outside.
Okay.
[suspenseful music]
[drone whirring]
[zombies growling in distance]
[Ji-min] Wait a minute.
What is it?
Wait a sec.
[breathes shakily]
Just… wait.
[Ji-min gasps, sobbing]
-[sobbing]
-What?
[Hyo-ryeong] Wha, what's wrong, Ji-min?
Wait a minute.
[whimpering]
I-I can't…
[sobbing]
What? What is it?
[Ji-min sobbing]
This…
-[whimpers]
-[somber music]
That's my dad's car.
[whimpering]
[Joon-yeong] Which one?
The white one? The black one?
[Ji-min cries]
It's this truck.
[sobs]
It's my dad's car.
[whimpering]
Don't worry.
I'm sure there are lots of cars like that.
[Ji-min crying]
-Hang on. I'll check.
-[Ji-min whimpers]
[wailing]
[sighs]
[Ji-min crying]
[somber music continues]
-Ji-min.
-[crying]
[crying, breathes heavily]
[growling]
[drone beeping, chimes]
[zombies snarling]
[wind whooshing]
[helicopter whirring]
[ominous music]
11:47 AM
ABANDONED PRISON IN THE SUBURB OF HYOSAN
[helicopter whirring]
[whirring continues]
[ominous music continues]
[whirring]
[male announcer]
Attention, citizens of Hyosan.
Please proceed calmly…
-Where are we going? Where are we going?
-…to the first quarantine.
-Do you see us--
-Don't you!
-Hey!
-We're not animals!
-We've been waiting here for hours!
-Please cooperate
with the tests to determine
whether or not you are infected…
[indistinct clamoring]
…will be returned to you
at the later stage.
I repeat.
Please proceed calmly
to the first quarantine checkpoint…
and surrender your personal belongings.
This is for your safety,
and the safety of those around you.
We appreciate your continuous cooperation.
EXAMINATION ROOM
Thank you for your service.
Where's the control room?
As per Martial Law,
you have to quarantine
until you are examined.
Why in the world
would she have to quarantine now?
She just came back from a battlefield--
-It's okay. That's enough.
-Unbelievable.
So, where is the control room?
[soldier 1] You have to be examined first.
I'm not refusing to be examined.
[soldier 1] Please follow the protocols.
Hyosan Fire Station.
Rescue Team One, Captain Nam So-ju.
I was responsible for them
from mobilization until rescue.
[soldier 1] Enough!
Does it sound like
I'm asking your opinion?
-[soldier 1] Take them to the exam room.
-[soldier 2] Yes, sir.
[dramatic music]
[Eun-hee] What is this place?
This isn't an examination room.
[soldier 2] There are lots
of people in line for exams,
you have to wait your turn.
Then you should've explained the situation
and asked her to wait somewhere else
and then escorted her.
What the hell is wrong with you?
[soldier 2] There are plenty
of other people outside
who are sitting on mats
on a concrete floor.
We're trying to make you
as comfortable as possible
because you're an assemblywoman.
The wait time
for an examination is 12 to 72 hours.
Wait a minute.
My daughter is at her school right now.
It may be too late if we keep waiting.
Please request a rescue.
[soldier 2] We're doing the best we can.
Wait here for now.
[clattering]
[suspenseful music]
[insect buzzing]
[buzzing continues]
[buzzing]
[gasps]
[foreboding music]
[breathes]
[gasping]
Oh, shit.
Did I die?
Am I dead?
[growling]
[gasps]
[flustered gasping]
[growling]
[Gwi-nam whimpering]
[breathes heavily]
Hey.
-[growls]
-[gasps]
Aren't, aren't you gonna eat me,
you zombie bastards?
-[growling]
-[Gwi-nam whimpers]
I gave them serotonin injections
for a week,
but it had no effect whatsoever.
The moment an antivirus enters the body,
the virus mutates
and stops attacking its target.
[Mr. Lee] The only explanation
is that the cells learn and evolve.
If this virus…
manages to learn human consciousness…
-[thuds]
-[squelches]
…a new species of humankind could be born.
[thuds]
[growls]
Cheong-san, you son of a bitch!
I'll kill you.
[breathes heavily]
[metal clanking]
[tense music]
[screeching]
[tense music continues]
[screeches]
[zombies growling in distance]
[growling]
What the fuck?
[sighs]
That means…
ONE HEART
…I'm God.
[screaming]
Hey, Cheong-san!
[zombies growling]
[closing theme music]
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.