"Episode 9"
"Love in The Air"
The sky after the rain stopped,
a rainbow unexpectedly appeared.
In fact, the order of the colors of
the rainbow was already determined.
Whether it was a coincidence or not,
is there any fateful meeting
like the rainbow?
A fateful meeting like the rainbow?
Of course there is.
There's only one.
It all started on
the night the storm came.
No way! What's going on?
Huh?
Please start!
Ah, damn it! I give up!
Yes?
I'll take a look at the engine.
Open the hood of the car.
Huh? Really?
I can't help, so
this is the least I can do.
Hold this.
I was really stuck.
Thank you so much for helping me.
It's an old car.
It's my father's most important car.
If you're going to keep driving it.
Next time, handle it yourself.
Since then, many things have happened.
Hey! Don't hit me!
Even my parents never did that!
Before you start designing houses,
you need to design your own life first.
We went through things that were
the first time together.
If that's not destiny, then
there's no destiny,
that's definitely destiny.
Even so...
A fateful meeting like the rainbow,
huh?
It's annoying to say
but there's only one person.
He's my boy.
My apologies.
Can we talk for a moment?
Do you know that this is
a dangerous place where outsiders
are not allowed to enter?
Anyone who sneaks in
doesn't leave unscathed.
What should I do?
Depends on the offer,
but if I get to choose...
You understand, right?
What you need to trade
to get out of here.
Just kidding.
Not everyone could resist
someone as cute as you,
but luckily I can.
Don't come to such a dangerous...
I will do whatever you want.
That kind of terrible meeting,
even though I thought
we would never meet again.
Good morning.
I came here because you
didn't give me a reply.
A present.
Before I knew it,
I was interested in him,
Just seeing your cute smile is enough.
I like him.
(I'm worried about you)
"Porridge with egg, orange jelly."
Stop it! Stop it!
"A player but takes racing seriously."
"A narcissist, but undeniably charming."
"Annoying, but makes me smile."
I love you.
I really love you.
I hear you.
And I'm obsessed with him.
I'm afraid of more happiness.
Then, I will make you so happy
that you forget the fear.
I will make Kai smile all the time.
Kai, the car is fixed.
Ah, amazing. Thanks.
Well, I learned a lot from Arashi...
Oh, then let's continue.
The mountains at night are cold.
Fuma-san...
Told me...
Dammit, I really want to forget.
I want to forget, but why do
I keep thinking about him?
Okay, from now on,
let's not think about them anymore.
Agreed, "I don't know anyone like that."
"I don't know anyone like that."
Let's get them out of our heads.
- Because we... - Because we...
- are angry! - are angry!
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love-"
(Friday)
What's wrong with you, Rei?
You're not cheerful at all.
- Want to tell me about it? - No.
I have more life experience than.
Don't be shy.
I don't want to discuss
my life experiences with senpai
who only live with kouhai.
Hey, you!
Hey.
Dammit, this guy...
Ah!
Oww!
That hurts.
What's that?
This is...
It's the fox god that has been
protecting us since ancient times.
The fox god?
- Then we have to apologize...
- It's too late.
Huh?
You've now...
- been cursed! - Whoa!
- Don't do that! - You were so scared!
It's all because of Arashi.
Huh?
There's something like Tanuki
in a place like this?
What "something like Tanuki"?
Huh?
Umm, I'm sorry.
It's too late.
That's somehow scary.
It's all because of Fuma.
What's wrong?
I'm the one who wants to ask.
You sighed before me.
I did?
Hmm... Then I win. Tell me.
How annoying.
You have a problem with Fuma, don't you?
No way.
Is that so?
Kai is usually kind.
But he's this irritated.
Only Fuma who can make him like this.
I...
- am kind? - Mm, a lot!
So Fuma is at fault, right?
Mhm... That's right. Hey, listen to me.
I'll listen. You'll listen to me too.
- I knew something is bothering you.
- Of course.
Gosh,
I get irritated just thinking about it!
Then you speak first.
You go first.
Rock, paper, scissor!
Dammit!
(Thursday)
Hey, Arashi.
Have you thought about the contest
you mentioned the other day?
What about?
Huh?
Didn't you say you'd think about it?
Haven't you thought about it yet?
Hmm...
If I remember correctly...
Ah, the fashion contest?
It's a Japanese costume contest.
I think it'll definitely suit you.
Well... I suppose.
Right?
I want to see Arashi win.
It might be more suitable for Rei.
Stop saying that.
I'll think about it.
People who don't think like to say that.
Playing games is good.
But why don't you do
something more useful?
It's fun and a great way to kill time.
You're right.
But you've played too much.
Never mind that,
finish your work quickly.
Then we can go out to eat.
You should look at me
more than the game.
Hmm?
I'm more interesting than that game.
The guy who's going to eat
with you is rushing with his work.
Even if you top up, you find one.
I think
if I just watch Arashi,
it will be hard to work,
so I play games.
You can watch.
If you watch me, I will try even harder.
Because I want you to see
only the good side.
Of course I would want to watch.
It's really annoying.
Huh?
You're mad about that?
That's right.
Then what's Kai upset about?
I...
(Thursday)
Oh, right.
What's wrong?
I just thought you'd look good
in a Japanese outfit.
I told you I wasn't going to compete.
Please.
I wanted to do what you asked for.
But I don't want to spend my luck
on anything other than work.
Luck is unrelated, I think you'll win.
I sincerely apologize this time.
But I must refuse.
Why did you suddenly start
working out while I'm here?
And why can't I do it?
Don't people usually do it
when others aren't around?
Do you want to do it together?
Did you hear what I said?
I'm not working out.
Then just watch quietly.
It's obvious that he was inviting me.
So confident.
And really charming.
Oh gosh. I'm so irritated.
Are you mad about that?
Then what if Arashi
works out in front of you?
I wouldn't be able to stand watching!
And what does Fuma look like
when he's working seriously?
- I want to watch him forever.
- Right? And then...
What makes it even more annoying is...
What is it?
No matter what happens,
don't stop playing games.
Is the work done?
Promise me, no matter what happens,
you won't stop playing games.
Huh?
Fine.
I'm gonna die. Please stop.
You mean your game?
Or is it because you feel good?
Game...
Keep playing your game.
Wait a minute.
Keep playing.
I'm still playing but
what did you suddenly do?
I'm done with work.
Then let's hurry up and go eat.
Hmm?
Then should we stop?
No...
No need to stop.
A good thing about you is...
Your words are true to your heart.
Oh no.
I can't take it anymore.
You promised you'd continue
playing your game.
You're right.
This is pure hell.
It's hell on earth.
The game is long dead.
But the game of negotiation
just started from there.
It's obvious that you lost.
- Yay! - Yay!
But sometimes I wonder if
the reason I'm being bullied
is because I'm younger.
Haa...
Can I wipe my sweat?
Go ahead.
What are you doing?
I'm wiping it.
It's dirty.
So mean.
It's just sweat.
You used to say that
you liked me with wet hair.
I didn't say that.
If it's dirty or uncomfortable and
you really don't like it,
you can tell me to stop.
Oh.
Your shirt is wet.
You have to take it off.
Geez...
What nonsense are you talking about?
You'll catch a cold.
Aren't you cold?
Just a little cold.
I told you it was sweat...
But it's warmer than before, right?
You want to start sweating now, yes?
Haa...
Having a boyfriend who's too
charming is really stressful.
I totally understand.
But actually...
Tomorrow we're going on a three-day,
two-night hot spring trip.
Huh?
Tomorrow I...
have a date at the beach.
- Haa... - Haa...
- So stressed! - So stressed!
- Yay!
- Gosh, I'm not looking forward to it.
Yay!
I am so surprised
to hear that you'll listen
- to what I have to say. - Arashi.
Once we return, please listen to me.
Of course.
Fuma-san
is wearing it for me.
You've gotten much better at wearing it.
It suits you.
Thank you,
it's all thanks to you.
You've been helping me all this time.
Hello, Rei.
- Let's go out! - Let's go out!
(The sky in the rain is full of worries)
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love-"
He doesn't pick up the phone.
Arashi, you really don't know
where Kai is?
Sorry, I don't know.
Actually, I haven't been able to
contact Rei since yesterday.
Actually, today we have
a date at the beach.
Huh, me too.
We have a date to go
but we can't contact them.
Arashi.
Kai just contacted me.
- Said he wanted to cancel the trip. - Huh?
Oh, I also got my date canceled.
Why did it suddenly turn out like this?
There's no clue at all.
Same here.
But it's good that they're safe.
Which onsen were you going to?
It's an inn belonging to
an acquaintance of my father's.
Huh?
Making a new reservation?
Then it's clear where those two are.
- Okay, time to hunt. - Okay, time to hunt.
Even Kai was cheated on?
Even if he apologizes,
I won't forgive him.
Yeah, let's go.
Forget everything
and just travel together.
- Hey, Payu. - Hmm?
How are Sky and Rain doing?
- Huh? - Huh?
Huh? Did you just call us?
Rei and Kai?
Hi.
What's going on with these two?
They look a little like someone else.
Oh, man. I really want to forget.
This time, it's just the two of us.
Let's have fun on our getaway!
- Yay! - Yay!