(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 29=
How nice to be young.
Duan Xu is so fearless
and stubborn that he won't turn back.
He's quite like me in my younger days.
Actually,
you didn't have to do all this.
Ziji,
these past ten years,
as one so high above,
you stay by a mortal like me.
It must've been hard on you.
In the past, I was young, defiant,
and angry at the world,
but now I have let it all go.
You should return where you belong.
All that you have done
is meaningless.
As you know,
I won't live long.
I know what I'm doing.
Drink the medicine.
If you truly want to save me,
get me some elixir instead.
Mortals should take mortal medicine.
By order of His Majesty,
the Minister of War is suspected
of horse graft
and has now been detained.
The remaining evidence against him
is here in the 5th Prince's Mansion.
Any documents tied to this case
are to be taken back
to the Judicial Review
for investigation.
- Yes.
Your Highness,
for the time being,
please stay in the mansion
until His Majesty finds the truth.
Something's happened to my father.
Duke Pei
has stopped caring for us two.
That is a mortal matter.
It has nothing to do with me.
We still have one last chance.
I can take you to the palace.
I can make you Emperor.
You can have anything you want.
No.
Do not make me enter the palace again.
He Simu left a magical artifact there.
Song Xingyu,
I am right here.
What a fine thing.
It sealed away at least
the lifelong spirit power
of three mighty sorcerers.
No wonder it could block
Great Ancestor's spiritual aura search.
We have a pact.
If you want to live, come with me.
I'll leave matters
in the Mortal World to you.
No problem, Great Ancestor.
Do not come near me.
You are too filthy.
You're nothing
but a sickly fraud living off others.
How do you have such power?
Your Grace,
to be honest,
back then, Master Qingxuan,
out of pity for Great Liang
with only half its land left,
wished to keep the imperial clan safe.
After repeated requests,
I reluctantly agreed
to leave Starhaven Sect and come here
to serve as your Prophet.
Times have changed.
People these days
have actually forgotten
that my family name
is Hejia.
Your son died
a month ago.
For power and glory,
you forged a pact with an evil spirit
to keep up the lie that he lives.
The obsessions on you
are far too heavy.
Why not let me take them?
Song Xingyu,
you truly are something.
You dared to control a prince.
Do you mean to rule the Mortal World?
What joy is the Void alone?
The Mortal World is far more fun.
The ruler of the Mortal World
controls everything
that mortals have.
Not a bad idea.
Who told you to do that?
(Forbidden)
You made a pact with that person.
The pact binds you,
so you can't speak his name.
I understand.
I...
I know the former Sovereign
didn't die for love.
In the Sovereign's Hall,
there was another spirit.
Tell me.
Who was it?
Do you think I don't know
something's off with my father's death?
My father loved my mother
and me.
He promised to stay by my side,
so he'd never have left me
with a chaotic, unfamiliar Void
and die for love.
Great Ancestor,
he just said
the former Sovereign...
I'll take Consort Yu back.
Let's go.
Ziji,
how old are you this year?
Twenty.
What's your zodiac sign?
You can't even remember
your own zodiac sign?
Are you truly only twenty?
You're like me.
You're not a mortal.
In fact, I don't care who you are.
Fengyi has grown up.
He doesn't need me to decide for him.
Whatever you are,
he must've kept you by his side
for a reason.
Fengyi has never been
an easy child to raise.
He's deeply curious,
but frail in body,
plagued by illness.
He may not live long.
The road ahead is his to walk.
I only hope that by his side,
you can look after him.
In the Shunzhou horse graft,
Sun Changde,
Registrar of the Imperial Stud,
has changed his testimony.
He says he was ordered
to frame Sun Zi'an, Minister of War,
and Li Li,
Minister of the Imperial Stud.
The one who ordered him
is Duan Xu, Court Counselor.
Duan Xu,
do you have anything to say?
Your Majesty,
I did no such thing.
the horse craft has indeed festered
for ten years.
By Your Majesty's command,
I have investigated this case.
The chief culprits
are Sun Zi'an, Minister of War,
and Li Li,
Minister of the Imperial Stud,
not the Court Counselor.
So, it is true.
The proof must be solid.
According to Sun Changde,
Registrar of the Imperial Stud,
several months ago,
he found 3,000 warhorses
drawing false pay
in Shunzhou's horse ledgers.
So, he prosecuted
Sun Zi'an with evidence.
But after the inquisition,
Sun Changde was coerced by Sun Zi'an,
changed his testimony,
and falsely claimed it was done
by Duan Xu, Court Counselor.
This case
involves the Ministry of War
and a prince.
The Ministry of War was in it.
This...
By Your Majesty's order,
I searched the Sun Mansion
and the 5th Prince's Mansion.
I found all the solid evidence
in the horse graft.
Now, the 5th Prince,
ashamed before the realm,
has taken his own life in apology.
Good!
Your Majesty, please calm your anger.
And you,
Qin Huanda.
Yes, Your Majesty.
As Marshal of the Three Armies,
were you truly unaware?
I beg your wisdom.
I've long been tied to wars,
with no time for papers.
Horse administration has long suffered,
but war was graver.
Forgive my oversight.
Your Majesty,
Marshal Qin makes it sound easy.
I can't agree.
Before Yunzhou was retaken,
we had no natural pasture.
Any horse ranch we built
took land from the people's fields.
The land for one horse
could feed 25 people.
3,000 horses
means 75,000 people.
Corrupt officials have killed
those 75,000 people
due to their greed.
I was at the front, short on warhorses.
The cavalry couldn't form ranks.
We'd only send surprise troops
instead of facing the foe head-on.
Every victory came at a grave cost.
Our troop losses doubled.
Did Marshal Qin not see any of this?
How can we defend the realm?
- You...
- Your Majesty,
as the Marshal of the Three Armies,
Marshal Qin is good
at driving the foe away.
He reclaimed our lost land.
If, over one brief oversight,
we place false charges on him,
I fear the army's hearts will grow cold.
If not for Duan Xu,
who struck Yuzhou and Liangzhou
with a few thousand against many,
crossed the Guanhe River,
and pushed on into Shuozhou,
taking command in the darkest hour,
and reclaiming Yunzhou and Luozhou,
would Qin Huanda have won
such towering merit today?
Your Majesty,
horse administration is tied closely
to military administration.
Marshal Qin failed to spot its flaws.
That was a neglect of duty.
Though his merits are great,
he should still be punished.
Duke Pei,
what do you think?
I've spent
half my life in military administration,
yet I failed
to remind Marshal Qin of it.
I failed
in my duty to detect it.
Please punish me.
In the horse graft,
Han Mingxuan is now dead.
His co-conspirators,
Sun Zi'an, Minister of War,
and Li Li,
Minister of the Imperial Stud,
misused their power
and took vast illicit wealth.
That is unforgivable.
They shall be beheaded.
The other officials involved
will be tried by the Judicial Review
and dealt with by the law.
I'll keep
the military tally for now.
When war comes in the future,
I'll make arrangements.
Duan Xu.
Yes, Your Majesty.
From this day on,
the horse administration
will be in your charge.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Just now, you were
in high spirits at the court.
The case was handled well.
Thanks to my two
steadfast supporters.
Even the 5th Prince was involved.
Indeed.
It is truly shocking.
Mr. Wang,
may Great Liang know
no injustice under your lead.
What puzzles me is
how you learned
the remaining evidence was hidden
in the 5th Prince's Mansion.
An immortal told me.
You're about to marry.
I offer
my congratulations first.
How about this one?
What about this?
These are all too ordinary.
This one.
This is Radiant Cyan Brocade.
It gleams with shifting colors
and fits the body on its own.
Perfect for Mr. Duan's wedding robes.
Ugly.
This one?
I spent a hundred years
finding this Wandering Ice Pillow.
Its color is bright and lustrous.
Rest on it, and all the isles and lakes
will fill your dreams.
It's just right for Mr. Duan
sleeping beside his dear wife.
Well?
How dull.
The air is dry. Beware of fire.
Someone has died again.
(Erudite and Determined)
Your instinct
is still as sharp as ever.
Is it you?
You said
that if disaster struck
or I needed help,
once I called your name,
you would appear.
Did you hear
my heart calling for you
and come?
What would you like?
Your Grace,
I like you.
That won't do.
There is something on my mind.
You never ask why I love you.
Perhaps it's because
too many adore you,
and you are used to it.
So, you're not curious
about my reasons.
You drew me in.
With the tenderness beneath your cold,
the loneliness above all spirits,
and your love for this world,
you drew me in.
And I took the bait
willingly.
Will you miss me?
Since I left the Void until now,
I have missed you often.
Every day, in every little thing,
you come to my mind.
That day, I met you on the street.
You asked me who I was.
Though I knew
you were playing dumb,
I still thought
that perhaps one day,
you might forget
my name,
my appearance,
and me.
By the time that day comes,
I will have long turned to dust.
I will no longer be able to hold you
and tell you who I am.
I think that would be unfair.
You must rarely think of me.
That is why you forget so easily.
If only you missed me as I miss you,
♪Spring comes; ice and snow thaw♪
you'd remember me
for at least 100 years.
♪In the season at its fullest♪
♪Light the lamps
to pierce the old night♪
♪Borrow mortal warmth to ease the cold♪
♪Warm winds bring fragrant blooms,
savoring wine and graceful dances♪
♪Let me love with all my heart♪
Simu,
are you still here?
♪Still shining bright♪
♪With you by my side♪
Have you left?
♪Falling into your gentle smile♪
You don't even talk to me.
♪In your eyes♪
♪If you'd let me know how tell♪
Foxy,
I am quite busy.
♪Love and worry♪
But I do miss you sometimes.
♪Borrow mortal warmth to ease the cold♪
♪Warm winds bring fragrant blooms♪
I often think of you.
♪Savoring wine and graceful dances♪
♪Let me love with all my heart
in youthful grace♪
♪With light, carefree words♪
I still do not know
what wedding gift to give you.
♪A pot of wine in fleeting dreams♪
♪A brief life dares seek eternity♪
(Half a month later)
♪May I roam drunk in dreams
and never forget♪
♪Please ferry me once♪
(Duan Mansion)
(Joy)
♪I see a ray♪
He's out.
(Duan Mansion)
The Duan clan gave me
a wedding invitation.
It's more official
than your hair ribbon.
And now, I can only stand here
with you,
watching the bridegroom from afar.
I can't even join the fun below.
Go attend the wedding feast.
I didn't ask you to be here.
Since this is
your first time
at a wedding,
I'll keep you company.
They're coming.
They're fetching the bride.
The folks in the streets
gain nothing from it.
What makes them so happy?
They are sharing in the wedding joy.
To share in happy news,
or let others share it,
is a blessing.
(What does a wedding truly mean?)
(Why did you insist on making me)
(attend your wedding?)
Congratulations, Mr. Duan.
♪Touched memories linger like shadows♪
♪Scattered reflections
sink into my heart♪
♪If I could softly call you like this♪
♪As gentle as a fleeting embrace♪
♪Though apart, my thoughts still swirl♪
♪A lifetime is given
for a name to be remembered♪
♪There are passions and pains♪
♪Hope we'll experience them together♪
♪Before we forget or grow apart♪
Foxy,
you look stunning
in red.
♪What would come of it?♪
♪I care for no one but you♪
♪I'll come near and run to you♪
♪To heal the deepest wounds♪
(Simu,)
(did you see it?)
(I want the first thing you see)
(to be me in wedding attire)
(in this vibrant world.)
♪Though apart, my thoughts still swirl♪
♪A lifetime is given
for a name to be remembered♪
♪There are passions and pains♪
You helped him.
Blessed flowers can stir the Pearl
to trade the five senses.
Just now, he gave me
the sense of color.
♪Grows dim and fades away♪
Heaven as my witness,
you made that pact yourselves.
You set the terms yourselves.
As for me,
I merely did
a little catalyzing.
So,
this was your plan.
But now, with color,
you're far too beautiful.
Great Ancestor,
what did you say?
He gave me his sense of color.
Now, all he can see
is black and white.
Then how will he see his bride?
True.
- Good.
- Mr. Wang.
Come this way, please.
From now on, we're family.
Please, please.
We're family. How nice.
Assassin!
Guards, hurry!
What happened?
What's going on?
Let go of Miss Wang!
- Milady!
- Stand back.
Let go!
(Wang Mansion)
All of you, step back!
What do we do now?
If anyone moves, she dies!
Don't move!
Move aside!
Go!
Milady! Milady!
What are we to do?
- She was taken!
- Report it!
The Chong people are in Nandu!
They seized the bride!
Shut the gates. Seize them!
- Yes.
- Go!
Follow that bride and the assassin.
Isn't that a bad idea?
Do as I say.
This doesn't concern spirits.
Let's not meddle in this, then.
If I still had spirit power,
would it be your turn?
Did you forget
how I lost my spirit power?
All right.
Where did they go?
He Xiaoxiao.
Miss He.
I am Prophet Hejia.
Are you well, Miss Wang?
Prophet Hejia, please spare me.
Get up.
Suyi.
Suyi, get up.
Given the situation,
I alone will bear all the blame.
Seize me if you must.
You are a fragrance maker
at Yueran Fragrance.
So, this man
is your beloved?
Xuan and I are devoted to each other.
But bound by our different stations,
we dared not make it public.
Prophet Hejia, please help us
and let us leave.
Great Ancestor,
this.
Duan Xu knew
you wanted to marry him,
so he cast aside his pride
and staged this whole farce
to make it happen for you.
Mr. Duan arranged it with me
to help Xuan and me carry this out.
He said
he'd seen too much
of so-called mutual respect
and fake affection.
He found it unbearably dull.
He, too, had someone in his heart.
He also said
she was the girl he loved most.
Perhaps
that girl would never marry him.
Then he would
remain unmarried all his life.
Miss Wang and Xuan
are in love.
Xu had us put on
such a grand performance.
He helped Miss Wang,
as well as himself
and the one he loves.
You should understand
his intention.
Go.
Where is he?
(Duan Mansion)
(Letter of Challenge)
The bride
was seized by Chong spies.
I heard it was because Duan Xu
drew too much notice
on the northern battlefield,
so the Chong spies took the bride
to get even
and shame him.
They've gone too far.
Mr. Wang nearly fainted from rage.
His daughter is the true victim.
That's right.
Xu,
how is it?
Have you found the bride?
- What to do?
- What do we do?
Those North Chong spies.
Those wretched North Chong spies.
They are truly vile.
- Gentlemen.
- Since you're here,
please bear witness for me.
The Chong people stole our land,
enslaved our people,
and harmed my kin.
Now, they've seized my bride
and sent a letter of challenge.
I will never
forgive them for this.
Wang, bride of the Duan clan,
is virtuous and gentle.
Today, she suffers this calamity
all because of me.
I can't face her
or my honored in-laws.
If she returns safely,
I will never take a concubine.
If she can't return,
and we can't fulfill our bond,
I swear
by Duan ancestors' honor:
For as long as I fail to drive
the Chong people from Great Liang,
I won't take another wife.
How could he?
How can he do this?
If I break this oath,
I shall meet a tragic end.
He can't live without an heir.
Exactly!
Why go this far?
Utterly unfilial.
North Chong
has gone too far!
(Duan Mansion)
I never expected
Mr. Duan to be
so devoted to Miss Wang.
Such a harsh oath.
Mr. Duan
was so distraught.
I fear he truly meant it.
But Duan Xu
is the Duan clan's only heir.
If he truly never marries,
won't the Duan line end?
Exactly.
♪I go alone in the night without end♪
♪I can't remember the seasons
or the passing years♪
♪Wishful thoughts creep onto my brows♪
♪Whose face is it♪
♪Through cycles of time, we get to meet♪
♪Snow on sunny days♪
♪Countless wayfarers roam the world♪
♪Luckily, I share a fate with you♪
♪I hold a lantern to draw the moon♪
♪Light up the night that haunts you♪
♪I have simple wishes, but I fear♪
Simu.
♪You always stay with me♪
♪See the world I've never seen♪
♪However the years may wind♪
♪I wish I could live in your heart♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪