[Fenglinwan]
Hello.
Have you seen these two men?
They're skilled at disguises,
so they may not look the same as
in the pictures.
This is the suitcase
they've been carrying around.
If you see them,
call the police immediately.
Okay.
[Fenglinwan Hotel]
[Delivery]
They're skilled at disguises,
so they may not look the same as
in the pictures.
This is the suitcase
they've been carrying around.
If you see them,
call the police immediately.
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 20]
Only the Weinan District is left.
I'll lead the search there myself today.
At most, one day.
One way or another,
we'll track those two punks down.
T-Then, we're about to
wrap up the case, right?
Pretty much.
-Chief Qi.
How was the meeting
at the Provincial Department?
Very smoothly.
How's the evidence gathering
against Zhou Rong going?
We've already located
the vehicle used by the two suspects
and have locked onto them.
Have they been arrested?
No, why?
Yi'ang,
I'm not trying to pressure you here.
After the meeting yesterday,
Director Gao specifically called me in
and said
the deadline for case review
was approaching.
He wants a specific deadline.
I think we need to move quickly
and try to wrap up within the deadline.
Within a week,
we'll do our best to secure
evidence against Zhou Rong.
Given Director Gao's temperament,
since he asked,
he won't let us drag it out that long.
Chief Zhang is indeed the one
who knows Director Gao best.
I know my mentor's temper
too well.
He's an impatient man,
especially when it comes to cases.
By noon tomorrow,
we need to have evidence in hand
to formally open the investigation.
And that time
is what I fought hard for
with Director Gao.
Thanks, Chief Qi.
W-What's there to thank him for?
Chief Zhang.
By tomorrow noon?
That's way too tight.
By Director Gao's logic,
Zhou Rong is now
basically like a sitting duck.
As long as we catch those two
and get the phone,
we can move in and arrest Zhou Rong.
Is it really that simple?
Chief!
Chief.
Officers from the local precinct reported
that last night,
people from Rongcheng Group
booked tickets at Sanyang Travel Agency
for Zhou Rong and Hu Jianren—
a noon flight today
from the provincial capital to Gondwana.
Why go to Gondwana?
They're trying to flee?
Wang, I need you to make a trip.
Where? Gondwana?
To the airport.
And play it by ear.
Without criminal evidence,
what reason are we gonna use?
Just play it by ear.
Yan,
it's Zhang Yi'ang.
I need your help with something.
Two people are trying to flee
by plane from the provincial capital
at noon today.
Can you help me
intercept them?
Thanks!
I owe you one.
Criminal suspects...
They are suspects,
but
we don't have enough evidence yet.
Aren't you familiar with border control?
See if you can figure something out.
How could I joke about this?
Chief.
The ones who robbed Zhou Rong
and beat Lang Bowen
really weren't Mao and Xia Tinggang.
It was these two.
Can't see their faces.
What should we do now?
Let's not jump to conclusions yet.
Try to find a way
to get clearer photos
of them.
[Police]
[Lu Zheng Car Crash Case]
Did you bring the medicine?
Yeah.
Let's go!
Thai beaches,
Hawaiian beaches,
Caribbean beaches—
none of them can compare to Gondwana's.
Gondwana has nudist beaches.
Wonderful.
Mr. Zhou.
There's been a coup in Gondwana.
What?
The flight is canceled.
No, why did you come over here?
I-I'm going to make a call.
May I... I...
I... I...
Excuse me?
Yeah, it's me!
You can call me Peter.
I want to find...
find...
What's the man's name?
Vanuatu!
V-Vanuatu!
What?
Mr. Lu! Mr. Lu!
Someone from the Municipal Bureau
just came.
What for?
They told us to keep an eye out
for these two people.
And they specifically mentioned
that those two are carrying this suitcase.
[Never Bow to Lite]
The Gondwana military government
has announced that it will confiscate
all illegal assets
belonging to foreign colonizers.
Do I look like a foreign colonizer?
No.
Then why are they confiscating my money?
And "Never Bow to Lite?"
What the hell does that even mean?
[Never Bow to Lite]
Mr. Zhou,
I think...
Hello?
There's hope.
Lu Yibo called.
He said the police are
looking for two people
carrying a black suitcase.
Based on the photos the police provided,
those two are not the ones who robbed you.
So the police
can't possibly get the phone
from them.
Let's stay in Sanjiangkou.
We might still have a chance
to turn this around.
Turn around, my foot.
That one seems to be
"Never Bow to Life."
Isn't it "Lite"?
Close enough.
Go back.
And track down those jerks
who screwed me over.
Chief.
The HD photos
of those two are in.
It was indeed not Mao and Xia Tinggang.
Should I notify everyone?
[Lu Yibo] [Report Zhou Rong]
Bring Lu Yibo in first.
Okay.
Chief Zhang.
Zhou Rong didn't manage to leave.
He went back to his villa.
Good!
Justice won't let him go.
Good.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
Good.
I'll go report to Chief Qi.
Zhou Rong's not getting away.
Absolutely not!
He can't get away this time.
He's done for this time.
Zhou Rong didn't leave?
What happened?
What's that for?
Drop the act.
What are you talking about?
The two-man con.
What two-man con?
Are you crazy?
I know
everything now.
The Chief knew all along
that Mao and Xia Tinggang
weren't the ones who robbed Zhou Rong.
Pursuing them was just
a smokescreen to keep Zhou Rong off guard.
Why did the Chief do that?
If you were Zhou Rong
and the most damning evidence against you
went missing
while the police were searching for it,
what would you do?
Find it before the police do.
Wrong.
The safer move
would be to run immediately.
Just like Zhou Rong tried to do.
Yesterday, when you said
Mao and Xia Tinggang
weren't the real culprits,
the Chief had already believed you.
But why did he still ask us to distribute
their photos everywhere?
To keep Zhou Rong calm and in place.
But how would Zhou Rong see
the photos we distributed?
I just came back from Fenglinwan.
The Chief specifically emphasized
distributing them
to hotels and restaurants.
Would punks
like Mao and Xia Tinggang
ever go to places like that?
Still denying it?
Then how did you figure out
the Chief's plan?
Don't think you're the only smart ones—
keeping everything from me like that.
But I'm diligent.
Yesterday, the Chief recited a poem:
"Sorrowful eyes,
unable to see through your heart."
That's from a piece he published
in the Provincial Department's
monthly journal four years ago.
The title is
"I Won't Let You Leave."
Who didn't leave?
Zhou Rong didn't leave.
I've carefully read every poem
the Chief has ever written.
Hello, the task force.
Really?
How did you find them?
Okay.
What happened?
They found the two real suspects
at Ruihao Boutique Hotel.
Are you sure it's them?
We haven't even sent out the photos yet.
It was a delivery worker
who recognized the suitcase.
See?
It was also the Chief's idea
to send out the photos of that suitcase.
Li Qian and Song Xing
are already on their way.
Tell them not to go in yet
and wait until we get there.
Okay.
[Loyalty]
Stop, stop.
Chief Zhang.
Let him go in and wait!
[Ruihao Boutique Hotel]
How about I go in
and scope out the situation first?
Let's wait for the Chief and the others.
What if it's not them?
You stay here and keep watch.
[Ruihao Boutique Hotel]
Hello.
What?
[Police]
Officer?
What's the matter?
Let me see the surveillance video.
What happened?
Well...
Chao,
I don't want to pretend to be blind today.
I also wanted to give you a new look.
But do we have anything?
Would we be in this mess
if you hadn't caused trouble yesterday?
Chao.
I think you're better at
acting blind than I am.
Today you'll be the blind one.
I just want to get a room
with my girlfriend.
Can we do it without an ID?
No problem.
Honey, did you bring
my disability certificate?
Did you bring my disability certificate?
No.
Let's go back and get it.
What's wrong, Chao?
I think that guy's a cop.
What do you want?
We go all in.
[Shiweixuan Restaurant]
All in.
Hello?
I've trapped the suspects
in the room.
Requesting backup.
Chao, this pillow is too small.
I'm afraid we'll sprain our ankles.
Idiot,
when jumping from a height,
the most important thing
is to protect your head.
I...
Hurry! They ran away!
Where is the back door?
Chao,
why are we taking the back door?
There must be an ambush at the front door.
Freeze! Police!
You brat, you can still sit up?
Let's go!
Freeze! Police!
Are you okay?
Never mind me, go after them!
Suspects spotted.
♪ He ♪
Requesting backup!
♪ A rusted flower etched
across his chest ♪
♪ Oh, he ♪
♪ Says your worldview's still too small ♪
♪ A rat that steals rice—
humans call it cunning ♪
♪ A human who steals honey—
calls the bees hardworking ♪
♪ Absurd, greedy—
self-proclaimed superior beings ♪
♪ Hypocritical, wasteful, hollow ♪
Freeze!
Stop!
[Professional Bicycle Repair]
This way.
When we were coming this way,
we didn't know what was going on.
Boom! It just exploded.
Yeah, scared the hell out of me.
This is so gross!
Well...
It's everywhere!
How are we supposed to get through?
It stinks!
Why didn't you wait for us?
Why did you act on your own?
I didn't act on my own.
I just wanted to go in and confirm
whether it was really those two.
I didn't even give away my identity.
I don't know why,
but they just ran away.
Song Xing,
this isn't the first time
you've screwed up.
What exactly do you want?
Had enough of being
a criminal police officer?
Want to go push papers
at the Household Registration Office,
huh?
Go to the hospital first.
Chief, I'm actually fine.
Stop arguing!
Go to the hospital!
Chief Zhang.
Captain Wang.
The way those two blew up the sewer
is identical to
the provincial capital explosion case.
Let's go to the hotel first,
collect biological evidence of those two,
and take it
to compare with the one
from the explosion case.
Yes, sir.
Chief Zhang.
It's already noon.
Can we still make it
by tomorrow at noon?
Can't we?
Can we?
Right now,
these are the people involved:
me,
you,
Zhu Yifei,
Lang Bowen,
and Lu Yibo.
Lang Bowen is the most suspicious.
But even if he wanted to drag me down—
he took care of Lu Zheng himself.
There's no way he'd just sit in a hospital
waiting to be caught.
As for Zhu Yifei,
he's an outsider.
He has neither the motive
nor the influence to mess with me.
Mr. Zhou.
Whoever I might suspect,
it wouldn't be you.
Mr. Zhou, Ren!
Um...
This morning,
Lu Yibo went to
the Municipal Public Security Bureau.
What did he go there for?
No idea.
But the people at Fenglinwan said
he definitely went.
I've underestimated you.
You go right now
and wait outside the Municipal Bureau.
As soon as he comes out,
bring him here!
[Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau]
Officer,
when will Chief Zhang
be able to receive me?
"Receive?"
No, question me.
"Question?"
What's the proper term then?
I can't just wait here
forever, right?
The Chief went out on official business.
Just wait patiently as you were told.
If you don't want to wait,
you can leave right now.
Chief.
Life is
full of ups and downs.
You have to endure the quiet times
before you can embrace the glory.
Am I really going to be
transferred away from the frontline?
Who said that? No.
Then why are you
saying all that to me?
I just think...
You don't need to comfort me.
Just tell me the truth.
Am I really being
transferred to
the Household Registration Office?
You can't go there.
Their staffing quota is already full.
Then where am I going?
Nowhere.
You're staying with the task force.
Why aren't you disciplining me?
Think about it yourself.
Unless I didn't do anything wrong.
Is that it, Chief?
You could interpret it that way.
I understand now.
Chief Zhang!
Captain Wang!
You're like
a completely different person now.
What did the Chief say to you?
The Chief
told me everything.
Understood?
Understood.
Understand the Chief's intentions now?
I do.
No more mistakes from now on.
Yes, sir.
Chief Zhang.
The fingerprint match results
for Liu Bei's killer have come back.
Huo Zheng.
[Wanted Person Registration Form]
He's also a hitman,
a wanted criminal.
He was there to protect the seller.
Find him.
Why are you still standing here?
Go issue the wanted notice.
Yes, sir!
One more thing.
Lu Yibo is still waiting for you.
He's still waiting?
Let him go back.
He's been waiting here all day,
and you're not going to see him?
Well,
we almost caught the suspects today.
What
could we possibly
get out of him at this point?
Let's focus on the important work.
Send him home. Let him go.
Alright.
Doctor.
Doctor, could you
take a look at this for me?
I'm off duty.
Come back at 1:00 PM.
Sorry,
but could you just take a quick look?
Lately,
I've had no appetite
and constantly feel tired.
[Sanjiangkou People's Hospital
Laboratory Test Report]
[Test Item] [Sex Hormone Panel]
I want to know
if I have an endocrine imbalance.
Based on your hormone levels,
you're pregnant.
That's impossible.
Nothing has happened.
Nothing what?
It's only been a few days.
Go get
a beta-hCG test.
Even if it's just a week into pregnancy,
the test can pick it up.
Thank you.
[Test Item] [Sex Hormone Panel]
I'm pregnant?
Get in.
Ren.
Where are we going?
Mr. Rong wants to see you.
What's it about?
Hello?
Hello, Yibo.
I have good news for you.
You're going to be a father!
Let's talk when I get back.
What's wrong?
Where are you?
I'm in Ren's car.
Where are you going with Ren?
Mr. Zhou needs me for something.
Why does he want to see you?
Stop asking.
I have to go.
So, what did you
talk about with Zhang Yi'ang?
Rong,
I really didn't get to see him.
Then who did you see?
I didn't see anyone.
They just had me waiting
i-in a meeting room the whole time,
a-and then let me go.
The world shouldn't be like this.
People
shouldn't be like this either.
Mr. Zhou,
if I'm lying to you,
I can die right now!
How?
Could you bear to?
What?
Getting desperate enough
to do something rash?
Rong,
if you don't believe me,
I'll jump now
and drown myself!
If you don't let me up,
I won't take a single breath!
Yibo!
You're serious about this?
Come up here and explain yourself clearly.
No need to be so drastic about it!
He can't hear you.
I have experience.
When I had an episode last time,
you were shouting outside,
and I couldn't hear a thing,
no matter how loud.
How long did I stay underwater
in that fish tank?
Two or three minutes.
If he's still alive
after three minutes,
pull him out.
What if he can't hold it
and comes up early?
What comes after
is yours to handle.
We grew up together.
I can't bring myself to do it.
Understood.
[Alarm] [3:00 minutes]
Mr. Zhou!
Ren!
Um,
Zhou Qi is here.
Mr. Zhou!
Mr. Zhou.
Where is Yibo?
Yibo...
is swimming.
Yibo!
Mr. Zhou.
I'm begging you.
Please let him go.
Please spare him.
Qi,
Yibo is playing a game
with Mr. Zhou.
He's doing it willingly.
No one's forcing him.
Yibo!
If we die, we die together.
The three of us die together!
Yibo,
I'm coming!
Yibo!
-What a couple those two are...
-Yibo!
She just said "the three of us."
Who's the third?
What are you doing?
Qi,
why are you here?
I was worried about you!
Mr. Zhou,
two minutes, fifty-nine seconds.
she didn't know anything
about me coming to the police station!
Mr. Zhou,
should we fulfill their wish?
No, no, no!
I'll go back to drowning.
Please,
let her go, okay?
I'm pregnant.
She's carrying my child.
W-Who...
W-Who is pregnant?
What kind of question is that?
He said she's pregnant.
She's the only woman here.
Who else could it be?
No, he...
How would I know?
Rong.
Mr. Zhou.
Please, let my child
have a chance to live.
Mr. Zhou,
I'm begging you.
Please let us go.
Our child can't grow up without a father.
I...
Lu Yibo, I...
Which word of yours
am I supposed to believe?
You told me you couldn't...
You told me you'd never touched her.
Just that one time.
Please believe me.
After leaving your place that time,
I finally managed to do it.
Rong.
You really didn't say anything
to Zhang Yi'ang?
I really didn't even get to see him.
I'll trust you one last time.
Is it really yours?
Yes.
It is mine!
Well,
shouldn't you at least
do the math on the dates?
No need.
It's Qi's,
then it's mine!
Are you insane?
Your dying here
would still be an embarrassment to me.
How could I have a friend like him?
Ren, can I come up now?
Ren!
Qi,
why did you come?
I was worried about you!
Be careful with our baby!
I can't live without you!
[Crime Scene Fingerprint Record Card]
The fingerprints have been matched.
These two
[Fingerprint Comparison]
are the suspects
in the provincial capital explosion case.
One is called Fang Chao,
and the other is Liu Zhi.
Let me add something.
Because these two
are skilled at disguising themselves,
the Provincial Department's task force
never managed to obtain
their real photos.
Li Qian found these,
which allowed us
to confirm their identities.
Catch these two men.
See if we can uncover
evidence against Zhou Rong from them.
Once we have it,
none of them will get away.
Before noon tomorrow,
we might be able to do it.
Chief,
thumbs up.
No.
The credit goes to Li Qian.
Everyone, thumbs up!
Chief Qi called for me.
I need to go report to Director Gao.
Chief Zhang!
Two thumbs up!
Thumbs up!
Alright, get back to work.
Get back to work.
I'm going back to work, Captain Wang.
I'm out.
Xing?
Xing? You're back.
Song Xing, you're back.
What's with that expression?
Song Xing, you're back!
What's with that look?
He's mad.
Who wronged him? He looks so aggrieved.
What's wrong?
Laugh.
Just keep laughing.
Soon enough,
you'll know
who the biggest contributor
to this case really is.
Fine, it's you.
No!
It's the Chief and me!
Yes.
What do you even know?
Today was a trap set by the Chief.
He intentionally let
those two suspects escape.
It wasn't me who screwed things up!
Yes, yes.
I'm telling you,
don't doubt me.
Think carefully—
haven't we been unable to find evidence
against Zhou Rong this whole time?
But in Zhou Rong's villa,
Li Qian
overheard those two
planning to make a deal with Zhou Rong
over the phone.
So if we catch them in the act
when they make the deal,
wouldn't that give us evidence?
If today
I had caught those two,
how would they still be able to
make a deal with Zhou Rong?
Get it now?
The Chief let them go on purpose!
Is what you just said true,
or are you talking nonsense?
Of course it's true.
The Chief explicitly hinted at it to me.
Who else
did you tell this to?
What's wrong?
Can you make it by tomorrow at noon?
[Police Internal Video Communication System]
As long as we can catch
the suspects
we've already identified today,
tomorrow should be no problem.
Yes.
But just in case
we fail to catch Zhou Rong,
please don't blame me.
Work hard.
Don't embarrass me.
Director Gao.
Yi'ang is now
making his big move
after lying low for a while.
He's really spread his wings.
Director Gao,
[Police Internal Video Communication System]
please come over.
Hold on a sec.
Chief Qi.
What's wrong?
S-Something's wrong.
Director Gao knew he was claiming
that Chief Zhang...
Zhang Yi'ang.
Here.
Was it you who told Song Xing
to deliberately let
Fang Chao and Liu Zhi escape?
[Police Internal Video Communication System]
What?
Did you ask him to let them go?
No.
Still denying?
Word has already reached
the Provincial Department,
saying you privately told Song Xing
that in order to catch Zhou Rong,
you deliberately
let Fang Chao and Liu Zhi go.
No wonder you dared to promise
that you would definitely
catch him by tomorrow noon!
[Police Internal Video Communication System]
Turns out you resorted to dirty tactics.
Director Gao, this matter...
Chief Zhang, don't admit it.
Just say there was no such thing.
Chief Zhang.
If you admit this,
Director Gao will discipline you.
If you say it was Song Xing's own doing,
we'll handle him internally.
That gives us more room to maneuver.
Now is the critical moment
to solve the case.
We must abandon the rook to save the king.
Sacrifice the part to save the whole.
Chief Zhang,
I shouldn't have
leaked your plan.
Just sacrifice me.
Well...
We're in the middle of a meeting
with Director Gao!
What are you doing?
Get out. Out.
Director Gao,
sorry about that.
The connection just dropped.
Where is Zhang Yi'ang?
[Police Internal Video Communication System]
He stepped out.
Get him back here!
[Police Internal Video Communication System]
Okay.
Yi'ang?
Yi'ang!
Yi'ang.
Pin it on me.
Director Gao.
He's here.
[Police Internal Video Communication System]
Zhang Yi'ang,
did you instruct Song Xing
to deliberately
let Fang Chao and Liu Zhi go?
Tell me!
Don't admit it.
Director Gao,
the connection is a bit laggy...
Director Gao!
I am now the Deputy Chief
of the Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau
in charge of criminal investigations.
This case falls under our jurisdiction.
If anything goes wrong, it's on me.
[Police Internal Video Communication System]
Everything we've done
is for the sake of solving the case.
Now
is not the time to pursue the details.
Zhang Yi'ang,
haven't seen you for a few days,
and you've grown.
[Police Internal Video Communication System]
Those are suspects
of the provincial capital explosion case!
How dare you!
You have to risk something
to catch something.
[Police Internal Video Communication System]
Screwing things up
is nothing new for you!
If they get away,
can you take responsibility for that?
R-Responsibility...
I'll bear it together with Yi'ang.
I'm the head of the Sanjiangkou Bureau,
the first person accountable.
If you want to punish someone,
punish me first.
[Police Internal Video Communication System]
Director Gao,
we're at a crucial stage
of the investigation.
Just let Yi'ang handle things his way.
I'll give you until noon tomorrow.
If you haven't caught them by then,
you'll answer for it.
Thank you.
Uncle Yifei,
why hasn't Zhou Rong contacted us yet?
Who do you think is
more anxious, him or me?
Z-Zhou Rong.
Exactly.
Uncle Yifei,
when are we eating?
Soon.
Alright.
You're as fat as a pig,
and you're still thinking about food?
Get lost!
Zheng,
I can see you're getting restless.
Why don't you go for a run
and buy me a bottle of fish sauce?
Later,
after we finish checking
these few households,
let's go check somewhere else.
Okay.
Sir,
you just moved here, right?
Yes.
Hello.
We're from the subdistrict office,
conducting a census check.
May I see
your ID card?
Sure.
My ID card.
[Name: Zhu Hao]
Is it just you living here?
We're in the transport business.
There are a few other workers as well.
Then please
have them come out.
We'll register everyone together.
No problem.
[Jiangping Community Resident Registration Form]
[Name: Zhu Hao]
Chubby!
Come out, all of you!
Bring your IDs!
Registration check!
Stand properly!
[Wanted]
[Suspect Photo: Huo Zheng]
[Suspect Photo: Fang Chao]
[Wanted]
[Suspect Photo: Xia Tinggang]
Sir,
that vehicle out front is yours, right?
Yes, it's mine.
Then, when you have time,
bring your vehicle registration
and driver's license
to our office.
We'll issue you an entry-exit permit.
Okay.
Okay, thank you.
Alright, we won't trouble you further.
Okay. Alright.
Sir!
Well, you haven't told me
how to get to your office.
Building 27, ground floor.
There's a sign by the door.
Huo Zheng!