[Would you like to join Spirit Fingers?]
♫ A heart that remains
unchanged through time ♫
♫ Our eternal story
that will last forever ♫
[This drama is fictional, and any similarity
with reality is purely coincidental.]
[Production guidelines were followed
when filming children and animals.]
You'd pop up out of nowhere at school, at
the study room, even in front of her house.
U Yeon said that.
Why should I know
everything that happens to her?
So?
You scared?
I'll
just wait.
I feel like I've been pushing too hard.
You grew up?
No, no.
Don't grow up, Gi Jeong.
Don't be like that.
Why are you really doing this?
Hey, Gi Jeong.
Our Gi Jeong shouldn't mature.
Our Gi Jeong shouldn't grow up.
[Episode 12] Kids, Dad's home.
Welcome back.
He doesn't look happy, so
don't say anything unnecessary
and read the room.
Try this too, grilled patty.
Give it to the kids.
Where's U Seok?
He went to meet a friend. He's late.
U Yeon, you...
You're not distracted these days, right?
No.
She's working hard on
tutoring and doing well.
U Dol,
let's eat kimchi.
I'm done.
What are you talking about?
You need to eat well so your brain works. The
math competition is right around the corner.
Song U Dol.
Come sit here.
Pick up your spoon.
Song U Dol!
Why? You're scaring him.
You're the problem.
Why do you keep hovering
over the kids? Seriously?
Not just one, both of them.
I can't take this.
Is something wrong?
When you scold kids, you need to be firm.
You could have just said it nicely.
Did something happen at school?
You're wondering if I failed
the tenure appointment again, right?
What? Why would you say that?
I didn't say anything.
Don't I know you?
You ask the same roundabout question
every year. It drives me crazy.
I'm frustrated because every year you
get so close, yet it keeps slipping away.
You think doing social life is
as easy as you make it sound?
Is it that easy?
Well, I guess someone who stays
home all day wouldn't know.
Just focus on the kids.
And stop stressing me out.
I'm sorry.
Dad was mad at me,
but he wrongly took it out on you.
No,
Mom told Dad to do that.
What?
It's all because Mom is
controlling him from behind.
I really hate Mom.
U Dol, don't say that...
You don't like Mom either.
Why pretend you do?
You haven't seen Geu Rin lately, right?
You two still haven't made up?
We have.
Geu Rin said she wants to meet
after she settles something.
What is it?
Acaprio.
Huh?
Maybe I should've said I'd take care of it.
You don't trust her?
No.
Of course, I don't like it. How could I?
Whatever the reason is, why would I
be happy about them meeting?
I guess she's just trying
to tie up loose ends.
Maybe that's something she needs.
U Dol, let's hurry. We'll be late.
Why rush so much?
Just to get used to the test environment.
U Dol.
Let's go, let's go.
Oh, U Seok, heading out?
Yes, to the library.
I'll be back.
I'll drive you to the library.
No need.
Look at your brother.
Don't you realize anything?
U Dol, let's go together.
Your classes end early today?
Dad's coming home
early. Come straight back.
- Hey, Song.
- Se...
Why didn't you call me?
No, I was about to call you anyway.
I did it first.
No, I called first. I even got to 'Se.'
That means I started first.
You didn't finish my name.
That's unfair.
You shortened mine to just 'Song.'
Then call me 'Sel' or something.
You guys are so childish, seriously.
Picking a fight on purpose
doesn't really work, huh?
Hey, let's go. Come on.
Germany?
Why tell me now? Why am I
the only one who didn't know?
- You didn't tell me either.
- Hey.
No, scratch that.
I was going to tell you.
You were already so upset
because of your mom, so I put it off.
I'm sorry.
I genuinely knew nothing about this.
Hey, don't cry.
I already cried everything out earlier.
If you start over, I'll have to cry again.
What am I supposed to do?
What do you mean?
Do I have a terminal illness or something?
It's not like I'll live there forever.
We might not adjust and
come back in a month.
No.
I feel like you'll end up marrying some
German guy and living there for generations.
What? Why would I live there?
I'm a descendant of Dangun, you know.
I just want to try living with Mom.
I'll live with her as long as I did with Dad.
By the time this passes,
we'll be adults, right?
Able to make our own choices
and take responsibility for them.
Yes, Se Ra.
Until then, avoid boys!
I mean it, no dating!
Just focus on studying like now.
- Just studying.
- Yeah.
You guys need to study more.
[U Dol's Teacher]
Yes, teacher. Hello.
What? He didn't show up? What do you mean?
But I
clearly saw him enter the exam hall.
What happened?
- Mom.
- U Yeon.
Did you see U Dol on your way here?
Huh? U Dol?
They said U Dol never
entered the exam room.
What?
U Dol!
Where have you been? Huh?
Where were you all this time?
U Dol.
Explain everything to me.
You wouldn't do this without a reason.
I don't want to talk about it.
Was it that Min Ho again?
Did he bully you again? Hit you?
This won't do. Let's go to the hospital.
Why?
Afraid I'll get brain
damage and can't study?
Worried I'll embarrass you?
That's all that matters to you, isn't it?
U Dol, what's wrong?
What do you mean?
He learned this all from you.
- Me what?
- You as his older sister,
talk back to me, lie,
sneak around, and join weird clubs.
That's good behavior?
You're the one who lied first.
What?
Why? What's going on?
Uh, it's nothing.
Your ballet career was all fake.
You're the fraudster, so why blame me?
And,
you will abandon me
if I fail studies, right?
Like how you tore U Yeon's drawing,
you'll discard me too, right?
How could you say that, U Dol?
Song U Dol.
How dare you speak to Mom like this?
Honey, don't shout at the kids.
You, move aside.
Apologize to your mom right now.
Now!
You have no right to scold me.
You ignore us and constantly blame Mom.
- What did you say?
- Let's go inside, U Dol.
I read about guys like you in books.
Because they're looked down on in society,
they act scary at home
and take out their anger on family.
You're a coward.
This punk, seriously.
Calm down, Dad.
U Seok, move aside.
- Move aside!
- Stop this!
Ah, these darn kids, seriously.
Honey. Stop, why are you doing this?
All this time, I thought that without me,
our family would be perfect.
That was
my perfect delusion.
Everyone was wearing masks.
Even my
seemingly perfect brother.
I'll be back.
What? He's not here yet?
Anyone here?
Director.
What's with that look?
Don't you remember?
It's the outfit I wore when we first met.
Rin Rin's favorite.
I told you not to call me that.
- Where is the Director?
- The Director
is stuck in traffic and running late.
Oh, he's late?
While we wait, let's catch up
and reminisce about old times.
You can talk about old
stories all by yourself.
Even though I knew it was all talk,
the reason I came willingly was...
Wait.
Let's rewind to the past.
It was all my fault. Forgive me, okay?
It's okay. Anyone
could've made that mistake.
Will you
forgive me too?
For what?
You still cut people off, huh?
Anyway, let me finish.
Even though I knew it was all talk,
the reason I came willingly was
to reassure my man.
- What?
- I didn't date Seon Ho out of loneliness.
Even when dating you,
Seon Ho always came first.
Then and now, you can't beat Koo Seon Ho.
Hey, Nam Geu Rin.
Hey, Nam Geu Rin!
Koo Seon Ho, what are you doing here?
I'm on emergency standby.
Come here.
I'm here. What now?
I missed you.
Me too.
I did as Pink said.
I proudly declared that I
came to reassure my man.
I was really pathetic, huh?
Why did I act that way?
So embarrassing.
I'll keep it to myself.
But seriously, why did you?
Unlike your usual self.
The sorrow of unrequited love, I guess.
Unrequited love?
You've gotten bold, Koo Seon Ho.
I've liked you for a long time.
What?
Hey, why didn't you come yesterday?
You can't skip out like that.
Yesterday was my dad's memorial.
Oh, the memorial...
What?
My father passed away last year.
You...
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Why are you crying?
Liar.
I'm sad too.
It must've been harder hiding your pain.
I'll take better care of you, Seon Ho.
Hey, I said don't cry.
I think that's when it started.
When I
started liking you.
Why? Why didn't you say anything?
Why would I?
I was afraid you'd reject me.
- What?
- You get it now, right?
It's been a long time for me.
U Seok!
I wanted to take photos.
Huh?
I want to go to Africa
and photograph zebras and lions,
and in the desert, the stars too.
What's this?
You know National Geographic?
Getting my photos published there
was my dream.
I thought
you'd be the first in our
family to gain freedom.
Because
I'm the least capable one.
No one is incapable.
You just are yourself.
Do what you want.
But be smart about it.
Why aren't you meeting your boyfriend
who acts like a friend?
Did you fight?
Not exactly...
Whatever it is, don't drag it out too long.
Or it might really end that way.
I'll head to the lab.
You go ahead.
U Seok.
Take care.
You'll come next week?
Yeah.
U Dol.
Huh?
U Dol!
U Dol, are you there?
Huh?
Mom.
Yeah, why?
Where's U Dol?
He's probably in his room.
He's gone. He's nowhere in the house.
It's so noisy, ugh.
Hey, Gi Jeong.
Hey, it's an emergency.
- What's wrong?
- Something's up at your girlfriend's place.
The kid ran away.
What?
Bong Gu...
Hello?
Brother-in-law!
What?
Uh, well...
There's something I need to tell you...
Lies.
You called after hearing about me, right?
I'm not coming back, so hang up.
You don't have to come back.
Just hear me out, okay?
What is it?
About U Yeon!
If you leave home,
I might have to break up with U Yeon too.
Why?
She'd be better off without me.
No, that's not true. You know?
Let's meet up real quick.
Can you give me some advice before leaving?
Brother-in-law, huh?
At least give me a word
before you go, right?
Fine.
I'll text you, so come there.
But
don't tell anyone, okay?
Of course, no problem.
You're busy too, right?
10 minutes. Just 10 minutes.
Okay.
You were spouting nonsense. Did it work?
Yeah, luckily it's not far. I'll be back.
Does that even make sense?
It actually worked?
The subscriber you have dialed is not available.
You'll be connected to the voice mail.
His phone's off. Even
the tracking app's disabled.
Did you find him?
Not here.
No, he hasn't come home yet.
Yes.
What did Dad say?
He's checking the next complex.
Twice a day? What's going on?
Who's U Dol's best friend?
U Dol.
Bong Gu.
Why do you keep falling?
It's an unknown number.
Don't answer those.
Okay.
They hung up.
Huh?
[Slide to power off]
Here.
What?
The subscriber you have dialed has powered
off. You'll be connected to the voice mail.
It's off.
Where's Bong Gu's house?
U Dol.
Why did you run from the exam?
I hated it.
I hate exams too.
Bong Gu.
I came to say goodbye.
I'm leaving home.
Who'll take care of you?
I don't need anyone.
I'm smart. So I'll grow up on my own.
I can do it.
But...
Just anywhere but home.
I hate seeing everyone.
Wanna come with me?
Huh?
No. Grandma would be sad.
I was just saying.
Why isn't he coming?
I need to hurry.
Who?
Giant creep.
He says he wants to discuss
something about my sister.
Try it. It's fun.
So childish.
But don't tell anyone, okay?
Ugh, this little punk.
Alright?
More! More!
One,
two,
three!
Bong Gu!
Are you okay, brother-in-law?
He's okay.
It's just minor bruises.
He fainted from shock briefly.
Bong Gu's grandma said he's fine too.
Because of me, Bong Gu...
It's not your fault, okay?
Let's go.
Bong Gu is waiting.
Come.
This darn kid, seriously.
U Dol.
I'm sorry.
It's all because of my kid. I'm sorry.
It's alright.
Kids can get hurt while playing.
But
he was really shocked earlier.
His face turned completely pale.
U Dol.
We are not scolding you.
Come here, okay?
U Dol, Song U Dol.
U Dol.
U Dol, Mom was wrong.
I won't do it again.
Come to Mommy, sweetie.
Mom.
I'm sorry for hurting you.
By the way,
where did that boy go?
That tall student who saved the kids.
Oh, right. Where did he go?
We didn't even get to thank him.
- Grandma.
- Yes?
He's not just the tall student,
he's U Dol's brother-in-law...
Huh?
We could've been in
big trouble without him.
He even took them to
the hospital. We're so grateful.
I should thank him.
Exactly.
Did he just leave?
(Watch on www.kisskh.at to support Admin)
U Yeon, where are you going?
Go. What?
What are you doing?
Oh.
Huh?
Mom, Dad.
He's not just some passing student.
He's my boyfriend.
- What?
Gi Jeong, say hello.
These are my parents.
Oh.
Hello.
I'm Nam Gi Jeong.
Brother-in-law.
What are you saying right now?
You...
Gi Jeong.
You!
Run!
- Huh?
- Hey, hey!
Song U Yeon! Song U Yeon!
Hey, you punk!
Bro-in-law! Bye!
What did you say?
♫ I was searching for something precious ♫
♫ While losing what matters most ♫
♫ This misunderstood heart of mine ♫
♫ No one could embrace it ♫
♫ The excitement I feel ♫
♫ Everything about you ♫
♫ Even dreaming feels miraculous ♫
♫ You make me understand ♫
♫ Oh, she's flying ♫
Jonathan.
Bigfoot.
Cute.
What brings you here at this hour?
We're currently rebelling.
Rebelling?
Perfect timing.
Can you watch the shop for a bit?
- About 30 minutes.
- Okay.
Alright, let's go, Bigfoot.
Take care. Bye.
Bye.
This is where you wanted to come?
I thought I'd never see this place again.
And now?
Fight.
Fight!
I'm sorry.
Me too.
What did you do?
All the things that upset you.
I wasn't upset.
It's just me being petty.
Because you like me,
I felt like I'm actually a decent person.
And as time went on,
I think my greed grew bigger.
I'm sorry
for making it hard on you.
You are a good person,
and it's okay to want more.
In my whole life,
I've never really cared
deeply about anyone.
So, you can imagine how flustered
I was because of you at first.
I find myself caring anew,
feeling happy anew,
feeling uneasy anew.
Anyway,
everything with you is a first for me.
Again, again!
Is this your 'I like you' face?
Gi Jeong.
Get up.
Huh?
Gi Jeong, that's right.
I
I've fallen for you.
♫ It's always you, I think ♫
♫ My super color in my mind ♫
♫ My monochrome world ♫
♫ Brightens up whenever you pass by ♫
♫ On the empty canvas of my heart ♫
♫ Painting rainbow-colored dreams ♫
Oh, nice!
That was good.
♫ You're my super color ♫
Cool, good.
This is weird. Why is he working so hard?
He didn't lose his temper
with the boss today.
And he even got an offer from an agency.
So I guess he's not an
amateur anymore, huh?
Kinda feels like he's actually a celebrity.
I feel a bit off.
Why?
Seeing that guy I always
hang out with working so hard
makes me feel like I
should do something too.
Don't you feel that way?
Exactly.
It's so unfair that he's
the only one doing well.
Want to see?
Here.
♫ You're my super color ♫
Hey, there.
Yeah.
Heard you're going to Germany.
It's awkward.
We're not close enough
for a heartfelt goodbye,
but if I let you go without saying
anything, I'll regret it forever.
Regret?
Yeah.
I'll regret it for ages.
Like 'I should've said
something back then.'
If you speak up now,
you will really regret it.
Probably.
Either way, am I just
left as a pathetic guy?
[4 Weeks to Master Germany Listening]
I knew I'd end up like this if I hesitated.
Not exactly.
But come back.
I'll start over from that moment.
What? You're not coming back?
Take care.
Come back safely.
I've liked you for a long time.
It's been a long time for me.
Traitor.
What's going on at this hour?
I need to say something.
It's me.
It was me first.
Huh?
Actually...
Right, there's a new guy joining today.
Wow! They say he's handsome.
Hey, hey.
He's just a middle schooler.
How good-looking can he be?
Stop chatting and start drawing.
What's wrong?
Geu Rin, what's wrong?
Hey, hey!
Hey, Geu Rin.
Call 911!
One.
Two.
Three!
That's why I couldn't say it.
How am I supposed to tell you I've
had a crush on you since middle school?
Ugh, so embarrassing.
This is the most embarrassing
moment of my life.
Happy now? Feeling relieved?
Nam Geu Rin.
The plane's taking off.
Seriously?
Ma'am, we'll ensure you get there safely.
Forget everything we talked
about starting tomorrow.
I'll just think about it.
Hey!
[U Seok, I'm here. Where are you?]
Oh, U Seok.
I'm waiting. Where are you now?
So which school does he go to?
Not 'him, ' Gi Jeong. Nam Gi Jeong.
Got it, got it. So which school?
- He goes to Chiwon High.
- Chiwon High?
Are you insane?
What?
What's wrong with Chiwon High?
What do his parents do?
Right.
No sane parent would send
their kid to Chiwon High.
What's so great about our family?
Our family's the messed-up one.
What are you talking about...
Yeah.
I'm not fit to be your mother, am I?
I spoke out of line.
That's not what I meant. Why are you...
That's not what you meant?
You found my weakness.
You should use it now.
I wish I could do that too.
But I can't.
I keep wondering why you did it,
and what your story was.
The worry comes first.
It's unfair to me too.
I want to hate you with
all my heart, but I can't.
You treat me differently and push me away,
but I can't bring myself to hate you.
It's so unfair.
U Yeon.
I did it all for your own good.
Do you really think I did it out of hate?
What does 'doing well' even mean?
Everything's according to your standards.
Then what are your standards?
Let's hear how great they are.
Living happily
while painting what I love.
That's just naive talk.
You think doing what you love
makes everyone happy, huh?
Were you unhappy doing ballet?
Let's drop that topic.
No, I want to hear it.
You don't want U Dol to keep
misunderstanding either, huh?
I had talent for ballet,
so I enjoyed it at first.
Felt proud when others envied me.
Then one day,
a girl too poor to buy ballet shoes
joined our academy.
I gave her my old shoes
when I bought new ones.
Can I really take these?
Yeah, I got new ones.
Thank you so much.
But you won't last in ballet.
It costs too much money.
Even my mom nags about it daily.
Yeah, I know it too.
But I'll never give up.
It was fun seeing Seung Hee think that way.
Now, the next demo...
Hey, they're calling you.
Seung Hee, try it.
Me?
That day I tasted
humiliation for the first time.
'Living happily doing what you love'?
That's only for the talented ones.
So, you quit?
Couldn't even quit properly.
My grandparents vehemently opposed it,
so I kept following that girl's footsteps
until she joined a company.
So, you did join a ballet company.
Then, you quit after
you got injured, right?
No.
Seung Hee was the one who got hurt.
Huh?
The power went out during rehearsal,
and there was an accident.
Suddenly I, the second-best, got framed.
Coincidentally, my
father's business collapsed,
so I quit ballet without hesitation.
Why let people misunderstand?
Don't you feel wronged?
Better to be seen as a villain than pitied.
You enjoy hearing this pathetic story?
No one would believe the truth anyway.
A cool lie's better.
I believe you.
And I prefer the 'pathetic' version anyway.
You are really saying something dangerous.
What exactly did you hear?
I said it's tough.
Someone as soft as you couldn't handle it.
I'm not soft at all anymore.
If you and Dad object,
I'll just skip college and keep drawing.
Work part-time to become independent.
And keep dating Gi Jeong too.
See?
Now I even talk back to you properly.
Jeez, you really...
Let's just stop talking.
Who did you get your stubbornness from?
I got it from you.
Don't be like me!
But I want to.
I'm your daughter. I take after you.
And I'll live like you.
So,
from now on, live splendidly.
Okay, Mom?
Let's do that.
I get it, now let go.
I won't let go.
Let go now.
It's ticklish, U Yeon.
Ah, why?
I'm hungry.
Why did you leave in the middle of eating?
Byeon Soon.
When Gi Jeong smashed this,
he destroyed our glorious
childhood memories too.
Watching Gi Jeong grow up
is so painfully exhausting.
Don't grow up.
Dae O, think of it this way.
The more mature Gi Jeong gets,
the fatter our wallets become.
He'll introduce us to
pretty girlfriends too, right?
Since he's mature now.
- Girlfriends?
- Yeah.
So,
let's throw away this junk
and prepare for a new era.
- New era!
- Yeah, new era!
Ah, Gi Jeong.
Respect the new era.
Excuse me.
Over here.
This one here.
This one?
These are the repair experts.
I searched the whole country to find them.
- Look at this thing.
- Huh?
This is completely ruined.
This won't be easy.
Huh?
Can't fix it?
There's nothing we can't fix.
The only thing we can't fix
is someone's personality.
Bro?
- Let's go.
- Wait!
No, no.
I'm sorry.
I almost destroyed our childhood memories.
Don't worry.
I'll never change.
Never! Never! Never!
Snap out of it!
Sir! Don't fix that!
Just throw it away.
It's a new era now!
New era?
We returned to our daily lives.
This thought came later.
When Delulu returned,
she seemed more childish than me somehow.
Or had I outgrown Delulu in that time?
Delulu left again.
Oh, my.
Oh my, oh dear, such a
big one on Mom's back...
Feeling guilty about what he said to Mom,
U Dol didn't try to leave.
Eventually,
he became a pampered kid
memorizing 195 world capitals.
Mom let me keep attending SF meetings.
That wasn't all.
I'll be back.
U Yeon, wait.
Today's your academy
payment deadline, right?
Pay in three monthly installments.
Mom!
Register, change the
canvas, and get new brushes.
Thank you.
She kept saying I'd never
get into SNU with my art skills,
yet enrolled me in art academy.
- This?
- Yeah.
There.
What kind of safe is this?
- Dad!
- What?
You should untie it and throw it away.
Why tie it up if you're just gonna undo it?
You were the one who tied it up.
My hands got dirty.
Bye.
Se Ra left for Germany with her mom,
while Seon Ho prepared for enlistment.
Gi Jeong called himself
a 'promising rough diamond',
becoming more serious
about work than before.
Today would be
my last SF meeting.
While preparing for my senior year
and college entrance exams,
I decided to go all-in
on the exams as Mom advised.
[Spirit Fingers, Final Meeting]
The older members said
they would wait here
for me, as always.
Oh, my ball, my ball!
Strike!
Even with our sports theme,
indoor ball games are forbidden.
Sorry.
Everyone, look here.
Our Red got cast in a project.
Hey, you Green Pig!
Why? This is good news.
Every audition, he was
criticized for bad acting,
so he gritted his teeth
and practiced acting.
Seriously, why are you telling them?
What's the role?
A convenience store part-timer.
He gets two whole lines.
Two whole lines?
Song U Yeon.
Not you too...
- Wow, congrats.
- Congratulations.
A handsome convenience store worker
should trend online for sure.
Oh, I want your autograph first.
I should get it before anyone else.
Address all requests to me.
I'm Gi Jeong's manager now.
Huh? Khaki?
You styled your hair?
Ah, yes. For a blind date.
Blind date?
Yes - Since when?
I should do it too. Dating.
Today's main character is late.
He said he had to stop somewhere first.
He's not getting a buzzcut, is he?
- No way.
- What?
No way!
You can't stop him now.
Geu Rin, where are you going?
Seon Ho, your hair...
You haven't cut it yet?
What? Why are you crying?
Black said you're
getting a military haircut.
It makes enlistment feel real.
That you're actually enlisting.
Why the tears?
Don't cry, okay?
I'll wait for you this time.
I'm a loyal girlfriend.
What're you doing? What if someone sees?
What do I do if I miss you?
What's this? What? What!
What are you doing? No, no.
No, no.
This isn't right.
Ugh, ruined it.
Just redraw it, no big deal.
I don't know how to play golf.
The ball came to me!
Stay back.
Red's changed a lot too, huh?
Yeah - True.
Speaking of which,
the first time I saw
him, he was really scary.
He was scarier in middle school.
Seon Ho, I'm still scary now!
Stay away from our U Yeon.
Hey, stand properly.
I'm watching.
Ugh, that troublemaker.
Oh, but hasn't Brown changed the most?
What? Me?
Yes!
You wore the same outfit every day.
Thought it was a uniform.
Exactly.
Even now, look, he's the most serious
about the concept.
Come to think of it, that's true.
If I hadn't met Blue back then,
I'd probably still be stuck at home,
drowning in alcohol.
Honestly, it's not easy
to socialize at this age.
Thanks, everyone,
for hanging out with this old man.
I'm the oldest one here.
What are you talking about?
Who cares about age when you love painting?
True.
Saying things like that.
So cool, Baeblu.
That's our Baeblu.
We're so beautiful.
Wait a minute.
Hey, we're not done yet.
Yes, Mom.
I think I'll be home after dinner
because of Seon Ho's farewell party.
Got it, I'll be home on time.
Okay.
♫ The colors hidden in my diary ♫
♫ What new adventures await today ♫
Excuse me.
Yes?
I'm sorry, but do you have a moment?
Pardon?
Me?
♫ But trapped within time ♫
♫ I stay up all night
overthinking about you ♫
♫ I couldn't say anything at first ♫
♫ But now I'm gathering
courage to approach you ♫
Sometimes, I think about that.
What if I hadn't met SF that day?
How different would things be?
What if my friends had arrived earlier?
What if I had refused to be the model?
If that had happened,
no one would be here now.
Neither me nor my dreams.
♫ I'll never crumble ♫
♫ Take my hand and rise again ♫
♫ Together, we're enough ♫
♫ With you by my side,
let's fill our dreams together ♫
Honey.
I used to
only imagine things
that could happen in fantasies.
I was too scared
to dream in reality.
But
now I know.
That even someone like me can do something.
That when I change, my world changes too.
I'm still timid,
and anxious about what the future holds,
but I won't give up halfway.
Because...
♫ Though we used to
look in different directions ♫
♫ From now on, we'll
gaze at the same place ♫
♫ Stand up, I'll never fall down ♫
♫ Brush off my knees and rise again ♫
U Yeon.
What are you doing here?
Because I'm
the one and only.
Special Baeblu Finger in the world.
Now, who will be the next model?
Me!
Time for I'm Ground self-introductions!
[Would you like to join Spirit Fingers?]
Sign up now!
Let's hang out.
♫ You're shining brightly, like a star ♫
♫ You're lighting up my heart ♫
♫ With your own light, your own color ♫
♫ You make the whole world beautiful ♫
♫ You, who fill my dreams ♫
♫ I really want to reach you ♫
♫ Become a comet of miracles ♫
♫ And shine on me ♫
♫ There was a boy who loved stars ♫
♫ There was a young
comet that protected him ♫
♫ A heart that remains
unchanged through time ♫
♫ Our eternal story
that will last forever ♫
♫ The story of the star and me ♫
Spirit Fingers!
- Fighting! I love you!
- We love you!
- I hope for Season 2.
- Love.
- Goodbye.