Previously on
Seducing Drake Palma.
Get out of my house.
But I’ll buy you your own condo.
Open the door.
I have short-term memory loss.
I forgot it already.
Stand there until you remember.
1121.
My noob girlfriend!
Drake!
You’ve got this, Alys!
1131.
You’re so harsh with your words, Drake!
I’m okay with it,
but other people might
think you’re a terrible person.
They won’t hear my harsh words
because I won’t talk to them.
If something happens to her,
I’ll chase you to hell’s end.
Why are you such an introvert?
Because they can’t
catch my attention.
You’re the only person I talk to,
in case you haven’t noticed,
because you’re such a noob!
So that means…
I got your attention?
Catch is an understatement.
You got me whipped,
and smitten – hard.
Oh, high school.
St. Collete High will
always be a part of who I am.
A lot of things happened.
There were moments that will become
my core memories moving forward.
I fell in love with
my best friend Sheen.
Sheen, on the other hand...
I love you and I want you back.
Don’t you get it, Sheen?
We’re over!
He experienced his
first heartbreak.
Do you still love her?
Yes.
Of course,
I’ve learned to let go of Sheen
and my feelings for him.
Make Drake Palma your boyfriend!
And I fell in love with a weirdo.
Drake Palma!
You’re my boyfriend now!
Even my ever-jaded best
friend, Aya, fell in love.
I’ll treat you, Bee!
Can you believe it?
She said yes to Kent!
Who would’ve thought?
I like you, Bee!
But, I’m genuinely
happy for them.
And for me...
I’m his girlfriend!
I’m Alys.
Alys Zyril Perez, soon to be Palma!
What used to be a mission
impossible to seduce Drake Palma,
feels like a mission accomplished.
Bestie, time to go home.
I think.
I’m territorial.
High school gave me a
roller coaster of emotions.
Keep dreaming. You’re ugly.
Happiness and laughter,
Aja!
sadness and tears,
But I promise...
that I’ll try to fall
while you’re falling.
And a ton of heart palpitations.
But like all things,
there’s an ending.
My high school life ends here.
Because let’s be real,
high school isn’t forever.
New chapter unlocked!
I’ll miss my friends so much.
Even if Brenford is just
a walk away from SCA,
I feel like I will
still get FOMO.
Just when things seem to be
going well with Drakey baby,
now we’re in an LDR.
But whatever!
For now, vacation mode!
We’re heading to the
US to visit my little brother.
Whatever comes next in college life,
St. Collete, it’s up to you.
I love you, Drake Palma!
Tss.
What do you want?
You.
Can I have you now?
Tss.
Shut up!
Tripp Marco Palma!
Can you hear me?!
What is your problem?!
None of your business, Pa.
What?
You didn’t even get into SCA
and now you’re acting like this?
Why are you like this?!
If you don’t want me,
go switch with Uncle Steve.
Or better yet,
send me back to Mom.
You better not –
I wonder what Alys is
doing in the States right now.
Bird brain.
You’re rude!
Miss Blossom.
We’ll get there soon, Alys.
Why don’t I have her number?
I should have her number.
Silly me.
Hey, Palma.
Did you miss me?
What are you doing here?
Silly!
I waited for you.
Drake!
Stay right there,
I’ll text you later.
Drake, Drake, Drake,
it’s always Drake!
Drake this, Drake that!
“Why can’t you be like
your cousin Drake?”
Okay.
Your SCA exam is tomorrow.
You need to get in!
But I don’t want Business Ad, Dad.
You’re always so hard-headed.
Why can’t you be
more like Drake?
You didn’t even get into SCA,
and now you’re acting like this?!
Why are you like this?!
If you don’t want me,
go switch with Uncle Steve.
It’s a good thing
I didn’t get into SCA.
For once,
I can forge my way through life
without being compared
to my “amazing” cousin.
I can live my life here in
Brenford, outside of his shadow.
It’s a shame I wasn’t able to find a way
to take Fine Arts like I wanted.
But it’s okay,
I’ll just let Pa have his way
with this Business Ad course.
My plans can wait.
Wrong timing.
Maybe next time.
Uh, excuse me, Miss!
Excuse me, Miss!
Do you need help?
Where’s the Registrar’s Office?
I need my schedule for tomorrow.
The offices are closed.
What’s your course?
Culinary Arts.
I know someone in the office.
I can send you your schedule.
Really?
You’re so nice!
Anything for a pretty lady!
Can I get your full
name and email address?
Sure!
Alys…Perez…
Thank you.
What’s your name again?
Uhm...
Tripp!
Should I mention “Palma”?
Hmm.
Not yet.
Uh, Tripp. Tripp Marco.
Thanks, Tripp!
Bye.
I really approve of
your taste, Drake.
We are cousins, after all.
St. Collete,
I know I’m not part
of SCA anymore,
but I hope you guide me.
Please guide me.
I hope I’ll meet new
friends in Brenford,
and I hope college
life won’t be too hard.
Amen.
Oh, and P.S.
I hope my relationship
with Drakey Baby goes smoothly, too!
Please!
Amen again.
Let’s go, Alys.
Alys Zyril Perez!
Aja!
Get your hands off me!
I don’t want to!
Tss.
We’ll be late!
I don’t care!
It’s scary, I don’t
want to go in!
It’s true,
going in is scary.
I don’t know a single
person here in Brenford.
It seems I’m in an
alternate world.
They’re all at St.
Collete Academy,
and I’m the forsaken one!
Huhuhu!
You’re such a child!
Well, I am still a minor!
I’m only seventeen!
Time is running, hands off.
Drake, please!
Okay.
Lord, please let me
meet some friends.
Even just one!
Even if they’re ugly,
just please not stinky!
Noob!
Please!
My noob!
What?
Good luck.
Calm down, Alys!
It’s just a simple
“good luck”,
but my heart is
fluttering like crazy!
It’s my first day
at my new school.
You can do this, Alys.
Aja!
Good morning!
Thank you, everyone!
And welcome again to Brenford University.
You can start your
Freshman Walk now.
Why is everyone standing up?
I knew I’d be late.
Miss, why is
everyone standing?
Freshman walk!
What a snob!
She acts like she’s pretty. Tss.
Annoying.
I miss Aya and Sheen.
I don’t know anyone here.
Hey.
Do you have a partner yet?
- How about us instead?
- Huh?
I have a boyfriend!
No, I meant for the
Freshman Walk.
Do you have a partner yet?
Do you want to pair up?
Oh.
Okay, sure.
Gosh, that was embarrassing!
He might think
I’m assuming he likes me.
Was that my fault?
His question was misleading.
Shall we?
What’s your name again, Miss?
Alys Zyril Perez. You?
Tripp Marco.
Nice to meet you.
You don’t remember me?
Huh?
He looks cute.
That was just yesterday.
Sorry, my memory is weak.
So, where exactly
did we meet again?
Uh, nowhere.
Wait, are you mad?
I’m sorry.
This can’t be.
He’s going to be
my first friend here,
and he’s already mad at me?
This can’t be happening!
Hey, I’m sorry.
Please don’t be mad.
Sorry, I’m just kidding.
I’m not mad.
Ouch!
That hurts, Miss.
You’re mean!
I said I’m Alys.
- You’re so mean.
- Then that hurts, Alys.
You’re the one hitting
people with your bag.
Don’t hit me with your bag!
Hey!
What?
What was your name again?
Tss.
Tripp Marco.
Remember it.
Okay.
Hello, Tripp!
I hope we become friends.
Friends?
We’ll see.
What’s his problem?
Drake, wait!
Drake, wait for me!
You didn’t text me yesterday,
I was waiting for you!
I have class.
Huh?
Wait, Drake!
Ahhh!
Ouch!
Ouchy, Drake!
Drake, I sprained
my ankle. Help me!
Drake, help me! Ouch!
Ouch!
It hurts!
Ouchy!
It was frustrating earlier,
I couldn’t find any parking space.
What’s taking Aya so long?
My Aya babes is coming.
- “Aya babes”. Must be nice.
- Bee!
Just hold this!
My stomach hurts.
You’ll be fine. Just take
some medicine later, okay?
Ouch!
Drake!
Ouch, Drake!
Who’s that?
That’s Shaira.
Shaira who?
Shaira Silos.
Silos?
- Mmm.
- Silos, really?
Why do you even know her?
She was our schoolmate
back in elementary.
Last I heard, she was also
Drake’s classmate in Brenford.
Until Drake moved here to SCA.
So what if they
were schoolmates?
Does she really
need to be carried?
Do you want me to carry you?
Do you want me to smack you?
You’re so cute, Bee!
No, you’re cuter.
You’re dramatic.
Anyways...
Shaira’s first love was Drake.
How do you even know that, huh?
Yes, how?
I already knew that when
I was in elementary.
All our batchmates
knew about it.
It’s common knowledge
that Shaira was all about Drake.
And Drake, of course,
doesn’t care about anyone.
Tss.
- Hand me my phone!
- Sorry, Bee.
My phone.
Your boyfriend’s
flirting over here!
Just try cheating on Alys,
Uncle Andy and
I will castrate you!
Kent!
You should rest
your ankle, dear.
Good thing it’s just
the start of classes,
nothing major yet.
I advise you to take
a day off, okay?
- Okay. Thank you, Nurse!
- You’re welcome.
Ouch.
Drake, it really hurts.
Can you take me home?
Don’t you have a car?
Drake!
How do you expect
me to step on the gas
with this swollen ankle?
I’m really just a girl!
Tss.
Please?
Pretty please?
Keys.
I knew you wouldn’t let me down.
Carry me.
Carry me!
Poor me.
You’re so annoying.
You know, I really
missed you, my husband.
I haven’t seen you in so long.
Let’s go?
Ouch!
It really hurts!
Your fault.
Hey, wait.
Let’s catch up first.
So, how’s my husband?
You know, you look different.
More matured, more…
mysterious?
Tss.
Or maybe not.
You’re still the
same Drake I knew
back in elementary
and junior high.
And you still care about me.
What are you even talking about?
Well,
if you really didn’t
care anymore,
then you should’ve
just left me at the clinic.
But you stayed.
You even offered your
own car to take me home.
You carried me, too.
Ouch, it really hurts.
Hubby, can you take me up to my room?
Tss.
You’re so sweet, Drakey!
Thank you, my husband!
What will I ever do without you?
I’ll just get you home,
so you can rest.
Oopsies!
Thanks, hubby!
I’ll message you.
You take care!
Hey, Tripp!
How annoying!
That guy’s mood swings are wild!
A while ago he was
trying to be friendly,
and now he just keeps
on walking.
Obviously, Alys, it’s
the Freshman Walk.
He has to walk all around
the school grounds.
Are you giving up?
Well, we’ve been walking
without even talking!
It’s so boring!
If Aya were here,
I wouldn’t mind walking for two hours
at least I’d have someone to talk to.
Alys!
You’re alone here in Brenford,
so deal with it.
Why are you so grumpy, anyway?
We just met and you’re
already acting like this?
See, now we’re behind the group!
Hey, Tripp!
Where are you going?
I’m tired already.
Why are guys like that?
If they’re not saying
“Tss.” they just shrug!
Is it that hard to
form a sentence?
Oh, gosh.
I’m so tired.
Why couldn’t I have
a girl partner instead?
Life would’ve been
so much easier!
Excuse me, can I buy
one bottled water?
Did you order a drink already?
It’s taking so long.
OMG! Are you alright, Erica?
Does she look
alright to you, Kim?
My God, you’re too slow
for your own sake!
Don’t you know who I am?
Give me that.
Next time,
take extra care,
Alys Zyril Perez.
Everyone would
love to see you cry.
You freak.
Alys, there you are.
- Alys, what happened to you?
- I don’t even know them!
What happened?
They ganged up on me.
Alys, who did this to you?
Who?
I don’t know them.
What happened?
Go home first and
change clothes.
It’s still early, we’ll be
here until afternoon.
You might get sick.
My Mom will see me.
Alys.
If Mom finds out I’m being
bullied here in Brenford,
she might change her
mind and pull me out.
I don’t want to go to the States.
What do you want to do now?
I’ll just buy new clothes.
Okay.
Shhh, don’t cry.
It’s okay.
You’re going to leave like that?
Why? What’s wrong
with how I look?
You look like you
fell into a sewer.
And besides…
Not a single cab will pick
you up looking like that.
So, what am I supposed to do?
Isn’t that dangerous?
It’s actually fun.
- So, are you game?
- Uhh...
But I might fall...
You won’t, come on!
Are there any options?
Don’t you have a car?
Are you sure about this?
Yup!
Hey, are you sure that’s safe?
Is that where I’m getting on?
It’s safe!
Why? Is it your first time
riding a motorbike?
Don’t worry, I got you.
Tripp?
Hop on.
Sorry.
This is safe, right?
Are you sure about this?
It’s safe.
Hey.
Just go slow, okay?
You’re sure this is safe.
This is safe.
You’re really sure?
Hey!
What the heck?!
Are you ready?
Let’s go!
Tripp! Go slow, Tripp!
Tripp, don’t speed up!
Tripp, that’s enough!
Tripp!
Slow down!
What?
I said slow down!
Come on, slow down!
- What the heck, slow down!
- This is slow!
- I said slow down!
- Fine.
Alright.
Ouch!
- I said slow down!
- You hit hard, you know!
Thank You, Lord!
Ouch!
I thought I’m going
to die because of you!
Ouch!
What’s wrong with you?
Wait, I’ll just park.
Wait up!
Alys!
Hold on.
Alys, wait for me!
Alys!
Alys, come on.
- Alys your face.
- Hey.
What’s taking her so long?
You already look pretty.
Let’s go.
Really?
I look pretty?
You’ve always been beautiful.
Alright, I’ll pay now.
Miss Perez, hop in.
Whatever! I don’t want to!
What the...
Here, Alys. Hop on.
I said I don’t want to!
I’ll just take a cab!
I’m not riding that
motorbike again!
You drive like you own the road.
I won’t, promise.
- Promise!
- You said that earlier, too.
You’re so dramatic!
Sorry if I love my life.
You’re overreacting.
We made it here
because of my motorbike.
Whatever!
I’ll just take a cab,
at least I’ll be safe.
No, I won’t allow it.
- Go home.
- Come on, wear this.
- Speed off on your own!
- Here, take this.
I said I don’t want to!
Whatever!
Thanks, anyway.
Mister, to Brenford please.
Please take good care of her.
Okay, Sir.
This jerk seems to be a
gentleman, after all.
Your boyfriend…
was flirting?!
Drake, who are you flirting with?
Sir, to SCA please.
Where’s the College of
Business Administration again?
This school’s so massive,
they might as well
take over the whole city.
Why don’t I have
that guy’s number?
But I don’t want to
be the first one to ask.
I should be demure,
he should be the
one to ask first.
Yes!
Drake!
Why are they staring?
There are a lot of Drakes here.
Hi, Drakey Baby!
Why are you here?
Nothing, I just missed you.
Tss.
Do it again.
I missed that, too.
You’re acting weird again.
Have your classes started?
Can I sit in?
Why are you even here?
Don’t you have a class?
Oh no! You’re right!
Bye, Drake!
I’ll see you at your condo,
I’ll be there. Okay?
Bye!
Alys, what are you doing?
Focus!
You don’t want to be sent
back to the States, right?
Why did Aya even text
me something like that?
Why now?
It's just the first
day of school!
And then when I got there,
he wasn’t even
flirting with anyone.
I’ll text Aya.
No, I’ll call her instead!
Oh, sorry!
What the heck, Miss?
Watch where you’re going!
You don’t own the road!
Sorry.
Emotional runner,
first day struggles!
You got this.
College life, let’s go!
Okay, class, listen!
Welcome to Culinary Arts!
Mr. Palma,
can you share with us
what you know about
Business Administration?
Well, Sir, from what I know
Business Administration
is about managing
and organizing different
parts of a business.
Including marketing,
finance, and operations.
It also talks about how
they can grow their business.
Do you believe you
are ready to apply
business concepts
to real life situations?
Yes, Sir!
My expectation for this subject is
to learn how the economy works
from the basic concepts
of supply and demand,
to major economic policies.
And of course,
I also want to
understand how the
economy affects our daily lives.
Very good!
On the course of a few months,
we will cover the
fundamentals of business.
You’ll get a well-rounded overview of
how companies are structured,
and how they function.
Understand?
- Yes, Sir.
- Boring.
Mr. Palma?
Mr. Palma!
Yes, Sir?
Fashion Design is all about turning
ideas to a wearable piece of art.
In this class,
you’ll learn to design,
pick fabrics,
and find your own style.
Do you know how to sew?
Mmm, just a bit.
How about you?
Of course!
Do you want to see my portfolio?
Oh no!
Last ten minutes!
Guys, double time, okay?
This will serve as your test!
Make sure everything’s right!
And after this, you have
to clean all your areas!
Guys, please move faster!
Hi!
How’s your day?
Fine.
Your answer is too short.
We made dumplings,
but mine turned
out a bit bland.
Noob!
You’re harsh!
But honestly, I’m
okay with bland...
my seatmate
earlier was annoying!
He kept saying, “That’s wrong!”
“This is how you do it!”
He keeps on interfering.
He kept butting in
with instructions.
I didn’t even ask for his help.
Then guess what?
What he made was super salty!
You’ll get kidney stones!
Really?
What an adorable baby!
- Baby!
- Alys!
You’re too cute!
Stop it!
Alys!
Why are you laughing
at my husband?
“Husband”?
Tripp?
I should confront him.
Wait.
Why am I bothered?
Hop on.
Hey.
Just go slow, okay?
Are you sure this is safe?
This is safe.
Game?
On the next episode of
Seducing Drake Palma.
Okay, if you say so!
I’m easy to talk to!
Ouch!
Why are you hitting like that,
acting like you’re my girlfriend?
If I were your girlfriend,
you’d be in way more trouble!
What are you doing here?
Did I tell you to leave?
Well, you were with your “wife”.
Are you jealous?
Why would I be jealous?
What are you?
Drake’s groupie?
I’m his girlfriend.
What are you doing here, anyway?
I have a date with Drake.
Dates aren’t Drake’s thing.
Well now, it’s his thing.
Hi, Drake! Good morning!
Hi, Drakey baby!
Why are you here?
We have a date, right?
Stop!
I told you so.
“Dates” are our thing.
Ha-ha-ha.