[Fate Chooses You]
[Episode 30]
Go!
I can walk by myself.
Kneel down!
Behave yourself.
Look at where you are!
Where?
What a huge cesspit.
With so many of you here,
are you lining up to use the latrine?
Slap his face.
Let's see
if you still dare to behave insolently.
This man is Lin Muhan,
the Young Sect Master of Lingji Mountain.
A few days ago,
he and a group of immortal sect thugs
hunted down another group of human scum
who acted in the name of the false god
and committed evil deeds,
burning the ancient books
stored in the Sihe Library of our sect,
causing a thousand years of heritage
to be destroyed in a fire.
By all rights,
he should be executed.
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
Presumably,
some people have experienced
all the injustices in this world.
The goals we strive for
all our lives
are merely the starting point
for those immortals.
Just because they have noble bloodlines
and extraordinary backgrounds,
they are born with everything.
Without immortal perception,
one cannot cultivate.
That is an insurmountable gap
separating mortals and immortals.
Why are they born with everything,
while we are not?
Unfair!
You said the cultivators
were cruel and ruthless,
not treating you as human beings,
and taking whatever they wanted
from your Wang family.
Yes.
These damn cultivators
have made our Wang family suffer so much.
Whenever I think of the tragic deaths
of my father and brothers,
I wish I could eat them alive
or tear them apart.
If right now,
there is a chance
right in front of you,
granting you a kind
of immortal perception for cultivation
as well as immense power,
dare you fight the immortal sects?
It's what I seek,
and I will never regret it until death.
Good.
I will grant your wish today.
Lingji Mountain
Young Sect Master's immortal perception
will be yours,
paving a path for you
to change your fate and seek revenge.
Go
and use this knife
to dig out his immortal perception.
Young Sect Master Lin,
may you rest in peace.
I will make good use
of your immortal perception.
And by the way,
I will take care of your father.
It's a pity my father is a neat freak.
He never gets along with nasty beasts.
And he didn't
have an affair with your mother.
I'm afraid he won't like
a lowlife like you.
I will take care
of my father myself.
May you not rest in peace.
If there is a next life,
I will kill you again.
Surrender now,
and maybe you can survive.
He actually got it right.
What a jinx.
Who are you talking about?
I'll take my leave.
See you around.
Be careful.
You have very likely been discovered.
You disobeyed him time and again.
He couldn't have missed it.
Do you need help?
No need.
I can handle it myself.
The Master raised you single-handedly,
treating you as his own.
He not only gave you wealth and glory
but also allowed you to hold
the position of Vajra in the sect.
Yet you betrayed the Master
and the Holy Sect!
Never mind.
I have nothing to say to a fool like you.
You wouldn't understand
even if I told you.
Come on.
Let's do it directly.
A mere cultivator
at Foundation Establishment Stage like you
dares to fight me?
Who told you
that I am just
a Foundation Establishment cultivator?
You're
at Nascent Soul Stage?
How is it?
It's fine now.
I'm done, too.
Then let's go.
The carrier of heaven
creates something out of nothing;
movement and stillness without cause;
Yin and Yang without beginning.
Open!
I,
Lin Muhan,
am the 5th-generation direct disciple
of Lingji Mountain.
Who dares to challenge me?
Kill him!
Junior Jiang,
why are you here?
Where is Senior Bai being held?
Take this.
Where is Senior Bai locked up?
That man was caught, too?
I didn't see him.
I have sent a message to our sect.
Reinforcements will arrive soon.
If you want to survive,
let us go immediately.
Not to mention that they can't come,
even if they do,
they will end up dying with regrets.
One is at Foundation Establishment.
One is at Golden Core.
Both have top-grade immortal perception,
and both are Heavenly Talents
of their immortal sects.
I wonder
which lucky dog will benefit
from their immortal perception
we dig out today.
Lu Qianqiao,
if you still don't show yourself,
I'm going to make my move.
You knew I would come.
You are just a righteous, merciful,
and stubborn fool who can't make choices.
That girl
who made a blood pact with you
must be someone extremely important
to you.
Since she is here,
there's no way you're not coming.
You really know me well.
Fan,
long time no see.
Senior Bai?
Senior Bai!
Xin Mei.
Hurry.
Kill me.
What's wrong with you?
His immortal perception was dug out.
Senior Sister,
we have to go.
Leave me alone.
Just go.
I can't survive.
It's not only cultivators
who deserve to live.
Come with me.
You recalled it?
Yes,
I recalled everything.
Some things
can be avoided for a while,
but not for a lifetime.
Even if you don't want to face them,
there will always be a day
you have to face them.
Like birth, aging, illness, and death.
Like the impermanence of the world.
Like
you and me.
So pessimistic.
I still miss
our old days.
You miss them?
Of course.
At that time, my family was in poverty.
My father was
a terrible gambler.
When I was 7 or 8,
he sold me.
After being passed around several times,
I ended up
being brought by that woman.
She took me to Liubo Temple.
At first, I was very happy.
I thought
I had finally lucked out
and entered the immortal sect
to be a person of high status
and trample those
who used to look down on me
and bully me.
What a pity.
I was born without immortal perception
and couldn't cultivate.
I could only do some chores
in the Liubo Temple, like carrying water,
washing clothes, and cooking.
How old were you when you first came
to the Liubo Temple?
I remember
you were only this tall.
I was a little taller than you.
You were a warm-hearted person.
You taught me to read, write,
play chess,
and draw.
As for me,
I cooked for you.
You couldn't tell
whether it tasted good or not.
But I still felt
we were friends.
But today,
is this how
you treat me as a friend?
What?
Have I ever hurt your heart?
Did you kill the people
of the Bishui Branch or not?
Was the Sihe Library
destroyed because of you or not?
You were injured,
and I went to save you,
but you bit the hand that fed you
and killed my sect members!
I won't hold any of these against you.
I just want to ask you one question.
What are you up to
at the altar today?
It's been years since we last met.
You are more eloquent than before.
It's been so many years,
yet you are still so stupid.
I heard that the Qinghong Sect
was established during the war.
Some scholars
took it as their duty
to protect ancient books
and committed themselves to resisting
the immortal sects' erosion
and destruction
of human civilization.
Later,
more and more ordinary people
who hated the immortal sects joined,
gradually embarking on a path of faith
to resist the oppression
of the immortal sects
and maintain the heritage
of the Human Race.
The affairs of the Qinghong Sect
have nothing to do with you.
But you used the secret technique
of the Liubo Temple
to win over the sect members.
This has something to do with me.
Back then, Master failed to break through
for a long time
and could only raise her realm
by seizing
others' immortal perception.
At that time,
both you and I felt pity
for those killed cultivators.
But I didn't expect
that after so many years,
you'd have become someone just like her.
This is the only way
for us ordinary people
without immortal perception
to gain power.
So,
just like everyone else
in the Qinghong Sect,
you hate the immortal sects extremely,
right?
Cut the crap!
And don't think
just because you're
our master's old acquaintance,
you can spout nonsense here!
If you disrespect our master,
we'll still kill you!
Do you have any more Yangyuan Pills?
Yes, of course.
Tell everyone
what this is
and what effects it has.
Listen carefully, you all.
This is our immortal sects'
secret medicine, the Yangyuan Pill.
It can heal wounds, stop pain,
restore vitality,
and make spiritual power surge.
We usually use this medicine
to heal wounds, stop bleeding,
improve spiritual power,
aid cultivation, and break through realms.
In critical moments,
it can even save your life.
Do these effects
sound familiar?
Does this share
the same origin
as your Phoenix God's golden liquid
that changes your fate?
You...
Don't talk nonsense!
Am I talking nonsense?
Fan,
do you want to tell everyone
which immortal sect is
behind you?
I really underestimated you.
The Master used
the Secret Nine Breaths Technique
to seal your acupoints.
How did you escape?
Stop guessing.
You couldn't figure it out
with your thick skull.
You really want to die.
Kill them!
In the disguise
of rebelling against the immortal sects,
you use these commoners to work
and risk their lives for you.
You also utilized
the Sihe Library and Wushuang Society
to lure immortal sect disciples
to North Xiang,
snatch their immortal perception,
and turn it
into Phoenix God's golden liquid
for your own cultivation.
Then you dilute it into Yangyuan Pills
to give to the immortal sect members
behind you,
helping them amass wealth,
aiding their cultivation,
and acting as their lapdog.
Don't you plan
to tell your followers
these things?
Master,
he's talking nonsense, right?
This is impossible.
This is impossible!
I don't believe it.
How could the Master do such a thing?
We believe in the Master.
Lu,
do we really have to come
to this point?
Back at Liubo Temple,
there were only the three of us.
Even so,
she still drew
a class distinction.
You could focus on cultivation.
But I,
destined to be lowly
without immortal perception,
could only do some menial work.
Please spare me, Temple Master!
Please forgive me, Temple Master!
Get lost.
[Liubo Temple]
Later, that woman died.
I left Liubo Temple
and came to the Qinghong Sect.
Lu,
come with me.
Let's leave here together.
If we stick together,
we will surely have a great life.
No, thanks.
Where are you going then?
I don't know either.
Maybe to atone for Master's death,
or maybe to find my father.
Fan,
no matter what,
I hope you get what you wish for.
Lu,
just wait and see.
I will definitely live a decent life!
What's your name?
Fan.
You want to join the Qinghong Sect?
Yes.
Yes!
Only when I got here did I realize
that this was just a larger Liubo Temple.
What they say or do
doesn't matter.
Just to stay alive.
Living well is what's important.
Since then,
on every sleepless night,
I would think of that day.
If I had followed you,
or you had followed me,
would things turn out differently?
Unfortunately, just as you said,
there is no
magical artifact to turn back time
in this world,
nor is there a second chance in life.
Coward,
clean it up.
I secretly swore to myself
that I must not let
others look down on me again.
I would climb my way
step by step to the center of power.
I wanted to live a better life
than everyone else,
including you!
So I returned
to that place
and found the evil technique
that she had been practicing.
I used to despise her.
But now,
this is my way
of surviving.
Liars shout slogans,
madmen believe them,
and fools die.
Do you think there is
only one Qinghong Sect in this world?
No!
This world
is actually
a larger battlefield.
For profit,
power,
and fame,
people will do whatever it takes
to fight to the death.
If everyone else does this,
why can't I?
I just want to survive!
To survive is the most basic
and justified thing in this world!
There's nothing wrong
with wanting to survive.
But in order to survive,
you kill other people
to extend your own life.
That is wrong.
You're so righteous.
Even if you're right,
there is one thing
I am so curious about.
You're a War Demon.
Why are you fighting for their injustice?
He is a War Demon?
-He is a War Demon?
-A War Demon?
You War Demons are
truly useless.
Born with the body of a demigod,
a perfect War Demon has the power
comparable to that of gods.
Yet your race
ended up being wiped out.
Don't you wonder why?
Because of weakness!
You've got a body as tough as iron,
but a heart
that's way too soft and indecisive.
I am not like you.
I will work
with whoever is useful to me.
Relationships between people
are simply about mutual exchange
and exploitation.
You're so lofty.
Ask them
if they want to join you.
It is true that I am a War Demon.
Your business with the immortal sects
has nothing to do with me.
But since you used the Wushuang Society
to capture my friend,
I won't let you go.
Won't let me go?
What can you do about it?
Blood for blood!
It's you.
Are you surprised?
I knew
there was something wrong with you, bitch.
You usually hid yourself quite well.
You even suppressed
your cultivation level.
I didn't expect that
you had already reached
the Nascent Soul Stage.
If I didn't hide my true strength,
how could I kill you today?
Why are you standing there?
Waiting to die?
Senior Bai.
I'm fine.
Go ahead.
Gather.
Burn.
I can't hold on much longer.
Sheng!
No guards?
They died inside.
Where is Lu Qianqiao?
We agreed that
I would come to save you,
while he stayed in the hall
to stall the Master.
Just him alone?
Senior Bai,
you are seriously injured.
Find a place to hide first,
and we will go help him.
Okay.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Lu Qianqiao!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
And how are you?
I'm doing well.
Yingying,
I am very disappointed in you.
You've never had hope,
so how can you be disappointed?
I am just more clear-headed than they are.
I saw through
your dirty deeds long ago
and would no longer be deceived by you.
You would rather choose
a War Demon everyone hates
than your own master
who treats you as his own,
right?
Exactly.
You've all heard the truth.
Are you still willing to work for me?
We stand firmly with the Master
to the bitter end!
You've all already
known his true colors.
Why still follow him?
No matter how we fight
the Immortal Race,
that is, in the end,
an internal conflict of the Human Race.
But he is
a War Demon!
He is everyone's enemy!
All War Demons deserve to die!
You helped a War Demon,
so you deserve to die, too!
Yes!
The War Demons and we
can never coexist!
They just choose
to side with power.
They'd turn to whoever
gives them power.
Be it the hatred
towards the immortal sects
or the hatred towards the War Demons,
it's nothing
but your high-sounding excuse!
Your words
are quite insightful.
Lu,
since I knew you'd come today,
wouldn't I be prepared?
Lord Baori!
We should've done this earlier!
I must remind you
that Fu Tian is a Void Stage cultivator.
Besides, he has
2 Void Stage Guardians
and 3 Dharma Kings by his side,
not to mention the numerous
capable men in the sect.
How can you kill him?
Did you bring what I asked for?
This magical artifact
has the power
to rewind time for a short while.
By sacrificing your own essence blood,
you can restore your body
to a certain state in the past.
This is Gui's Sunblock Banner?
Exactly.
I modified it a bit.
How come I didn't know
that woman taught you formations?
There's a lot you don't know.
♪ With tear-filled eyes,
we face the desolate wilds ♪
Lu Qianqiao!
♪ A thousand piles of withered bones ♪
♪ The lowly, in mortal flesh,
march first ♪
♪ All offered up in sacrifice ♪
♪ To build the stairway to the heavens ♪
Though I am one of the War Demons,
♪ Forging an undying obsession ♪
I don't want to be a War Demon.
♪ The blade is stained with blood,
and with countless tears ♪
I just want to be human.
For my wish,
I shed my skin,
♪ Sparks boil over,
and demons run rampant ♪
renewed bones,
and replaced flesh.
Every time I succeeded,
♪ Heaven and earth
are destroyed together ♪
my cultivation
would decrease significantly.
♪ Deeply knowing that the common people ♪
But I'm still happy
♪ Are an untouchable weakness ♪
that I can see
this colorful world,
and that I can feel pain.
♪ Do not turn back
to the pain of the past ♪
And this feeling makes me
♪ Mindless killing must not be done ♪
feel truly alive.
♪ With a clear conscience, a grand spirit
overpowers the majesty of heaven ♪
♪ I ask the Nine Heavens:
what is the purpose of this life? ♪
♪ With my spine as my monument,
I shall never kneel ♪
Void Stage?
No,
his level is still rising!
♪ Though this life be wretched,
I will not sink so low ♪
♪ As to become a puppet of fate ♪
♪ What is the purpose of life?
To draw my blade and slay evil ♪
Great Completion Stage?
♪ Even if I am turned to dust,
I will not regret ♪
♪ By my will,
I shall bring back the sun and moon ♪
Oh, my god.
♪ And restore clear radiance
to the mortal realm ♪
♪ Rather than bowing my back
to apologize to the Heavens ♪
Lu succeeded in renewing blood.
♪ I would sooner rewrite
this fated calamity ♪
♪ I demand the story
follow my own desire ♪
♪ To serve as its final conclusion ♪
How is that possible?
That's because you
have no idea
what I've sacrificed
to be an ordinary person.
You used her spells
to collude with the immortal sects,
steal others' immortal perception,
and deceive your followers.
Fan,
do you admit your mistake?
Why should I admit it?
Why should I?
What mistake did I make?
People are born with distinctions
of noble and humble,
rich and poor,
immortal and mortal!
Some are high above,
while some are as lowly as ants.
Why must I be
the one crawling on the ground?
I am not resigned to this!
I will change my fate against God's will!
I will make you all know
what it feels like to have nothing!
Why did you end up
like this today?
Stop saying those disgusting words.
Survival of the fittest.
Lu.
I suggest you sober up.
In this world
where people prey on each other,
the foolish
can't live long.
[Guiyuan Hall]
It hasn't rained on the mountain, right?
Senior Brother,
it hasn't rained this month.
How is it down the mountain?
It rained once on the 5th.
It started at 7:30 a.m.
and stopped at 9 a.m.
Don't worry, Senior Brother.
The disciples have dug
another well down the mountain,
so there's no problem
with drinking or using water.
Here we are.
-Senior Brother Bai.
-Senior Lin.
-Senior Jiang.
-Senior Jiang
[Tianyuan Sect]
Senior Bai!
-Senior Brother Bai!
Senior Bai.
Senior Bai, wake up!
-Senior...
-Senior Bai.
-We're back in the sect.
-Senior Brother Bai.
-Senior Jiang.
-Senior.
What exactly happened
to Senior Brother Bai?
He was harmed by villains.
Hurry and help him inside.
Okay.
Sect Leader.
Sect Leader,
Senior Bai is back.
He fainted at the gate.
What happened to Senior Brother Bai?
Is he sick?
I heard he was seriously injured.
Will Senior Brother Bai
get through this?
-Don't jinx it.
-Yeah.
Make way.
Make way, everyone.
Greetings, Sect Leader.
Master Li.
Sir,
I guess we don't
need so many people inside, huh?
Master Li.
How is Bai?
He...
The physician said
he's in a very bad condition.
Where did Senior Bai get hurt?
How could he be so badly injured?
I heard from the physician
that his immortal perception was dug out,
and his Qihai was damaged.
His cultivation level
has dropped to the bottom.
No way...
He is now no different
from an ordinary mortal.
Nonsense!
It's what the physician said,
not me.
Why are you yelling at me?
What?
Are you afraid that without Senior Bai,
no one will protect you?
You...
Enough.
[Baosu Courtyard]
Master Li,
how is Senior Bai?
His immortal perception was snatched,
his spiritual veins were destroyed,
and his energy base is empty.
The spiritual energy accumulated
over decades of cultivation
vanished in an instant.
Surviving this is
already a miracle.
Let Bai have a good rest.
And I have some questions for you.
[Liubo Temple]
Whenever you do some work,
you are either drinking water
or using the toilet.
It didn't delay
my carving anyway.
See?
How many volumes?
Three volumes.
I'm not like you,
who eats as soon as your eyes open
and sleeps as soon as they close.
You don't do any work yourself,
but love to nag others.
You also did a good job.
Congratulations.
You carved quite fast.
You almost caught up to half of Sheng's
half speed.
How is that possible?
Which volume is she on?
I didn't pay attention to that.
It's just that
she seemed to be doing faster than you.