(Previously)
Have you figured it out now?
About our status.
To be honest, I still
can't give you an answer.
Rome!
You don't get to interfere.
Don't forget, we're nothing to each other.
Besides, doesn't Tua like Arnold?
How do you think he feels
watching you do that?
I talked to him.
He gave me the green light.
What did I tell you, Jack?
I'd get those followers for you.
So, this is me.
The new Dean.
(Episode 6: Building a Relationship)
Awww! #ArnoldDean
Love thisss #ArnoldDean
I'm screaming, they're perfect #ArnoldDean
Great chemistry #ArnoldDean
So cuteeee #ArnoldDean
Can't stop smiling #ArnoldDean
They're boyfies, don't tell me otherwise
#ArnoldDean
I get butterflies #ArnoldDean
Give me more #ArnoldDean
It's not a ship, it's real #ArnoldDean
Keep it coming pls #ArnoldDean
I smile so much my lips hurt #ArnoldDean
Argh!! Biting my pillow #ArnoldDean
They're lucky #ArnoldDean
Ship of the year #ArnoldDean
Loveee #ArnoldDean
Give us a fan meeting #ArnoldDean
Loving thisss #ArnoldDean
The captain himself is sailing #ArnoldDean
Arnold the microwave, only warm for Dean
#ArnoldDean
0.5 seconds eye contact equals
million unspoken words #ArnoldDean
"Only Friends : Dream On"
Aren't you afraid,
coming to see me like this?
If we're in love, what
is there to be afraid of?
Cut!
It's already a kiss scene,
but I'm still not feeling anything.
You're not?
I felt plenty just now.
Mhm. We felt it more than last rehearsal.
But it's not reaching the audience.
If the chemistry's
real, I should feel it too.
Is our chemistry off,
or are you just in a bad mood?
As the director,
tell us how to kiss so
the audience feels it.
Well?
How is it?
How should we kiss?
Like that.
Why don't you get it?
That's just how our director is.
Hard to get. All over the place.
Let's just call it a day.
Alright, everyone, that's a wrap.
You're free to go.
Nothing.
Their chemistry just wasn't there.
What's with you? Why so moody?
I'm fine.
This is "fine"? Hm?
Or are you unhappy about Arnold and me?
Why would I be?
Everything's normal.
If you're not okay with it,
you can tell everyone we're back together.
We're just on good terms now.
We're not back together.
Besides, what you're doing
is good for the play.
You've created buzz. Tickets are selling.
So, thanks for that.
What do you want exactly?
You say no to this, no to that.
Are you just going to
stay jealous of Arnold and me like this?
Fine.
I'll get used to it eventually.
Earlier, it just caught me off guard.
Okay.
Hey.
Arnold and I, it's just for content.
Got it?
Hey.
What are you doing?
People can see.
Now you're shy?
You just kissed me
in front of everyone in the room.
No one keeps up with Jack like I do.
Why isn't he picking up?
Hello.
Where are you?
(Not your concern.)
(I'm busy.)
(I'm hanging up.)
Hey, wait.
What's his problem?
I'll get back at you. Someone's calling.
Hello, Dean?
Yeah, sure.
Send me the details.
Okay.
What did Dean say?
We've got work tomorrow.
We need to film some sponsored content.
Mm.
Hey, what's up with Jack and Dean?
I heard they broke up.
But at rehearsal… oh, wow.
It looked like Jack was jealous.
It wasn't just that he looked like it.
I think he was really jealous.
Right? That's what I thought too.
I was shocked when
Jack pulled Dean in and kissed him.
I was shocked as well.
Exactly.
Is the director going to have me killed?
I still have to film
fan-service content with Dean.
Come on. No.
That's just how friends are.
You can't fully cut each other off.
That's why things stay unresolved.
I knew it.
Knew what?
Going from friends to lovers.
It'll never work out.
In the end, you break up.
You lose the relationship,
and the friendship goes with it.
Hey, that can't be true for everyone.
Some couples make it work.
Right?
Are you okay?
I am.
I'm thinking the same thing you are.
I said something that set him off again.
Guess I can never change his viewpoint.
I just have to accept it.
You're playing really good music today.
Thank you.
Actually, it's not just your music I like.
I'm glad you asked me out.
I'm glad you came.
So after this,
can I come over to your place
and listen to more music?
Rome.
Excuse me.
I need to discuss something urgent.
Be right back.
What is it?
I told you, I'm busy.
Come with me after work.
We're not together.
You don't get to drag me around.
You do realize that, right?
Are you jealous of Boston and me?
No.
Whether you want to go with
Boston or Jack, that's your choice.
Will you stop being sarcastic?
That's my choice.
I think I'll go back to my fun life.
This is what you want?
Mm.
I'm busy.
When I'm free and
there's no one else around,
I'll come back and play with you.
Let's go.
Someone like him
should see this side of me.
Actually, ignoring him is just an act.
It doesn't get me anything.
Timmy.
Where are Dean and Arnold?
They'll be here.
Have someone stand in for them for now.
A stand-in won't feel the same
as the actual actors. Right?
They're running half an hour late.
They're filming sponsored content.
They'll be here soon.
I've been waiting for an hour.
Is the whole production
supposed to wait for them?
I don't think it's acceptable.
Should I rehearse with a stagehand first?
No.
I'll call them right now.
Don't.
I'll go find them myself.
He double-cast me,
and I haven't even
had a proper rehearsal yet.
Cut.
Pass.
Change the angle.
Dean, Arnold, come take a look.
Thank you.
Wut, play that back.
How was it?
You both did great. I like it.
Especially you, Dean. You see?
Your emotions and your eyes.
Oh, I have a new series coming up.
Would you be interested in auditioning?
Of course.
I'd love to.
Good. I'll have my team contact you.
Thank you.
Hey, are you the next superstar or what?
I'm happy for you.
Hey, I really have to thank you
for filming content with me.
Damn. I never thought being shipped
with you would get me this far.
No problem, Dean. I'm getting paid too.
And I really enjoy working with you.
What are you two doing?
Why are you here?
No. Why are you still here?
Why aren't you at rehearsal?
I sent you a message. I said we'd be late.
You said half an hour. It's been two hours.
Jack, please calm down.
Dean, Arnold, if you're ready, head to set.
Everything's ready.
I'm sorry, sir.
We have to get back to rehearsal now.
Jack.
I understand my actors
need to film sponsored content.
But if it takes this
long, my play will fail.
Boy, if you don't have sponsors,
your play will fail anyway.
Hey, Jack.
That's enough.
I want to finish filming.
Please.
I'm sorry, sir.
Let's continue.
You're ready to film now?
Yes.
Alright, let's resume.
Hey, let's shoot.
Go get ready, you two.
Cheers!
Drink up, drink up.
Raffy, what's wrong?
You're not feeling it.
It's my birthday. Have fun.
Come on, man.
For the birthday boy.
That's right. And it's his treat.
No idea where he got the money.
We usually split the bill on his birthday.
I don't do this often.
This is a special occasion.
Order what you want.
Special, it is.
Go on.
You keep staring.
Do you like him?
Hey!
No. I'm just looking.
Just looking, huh?
Raffy, are you tight with Rome?
No.
We work in different areas.
Why do you ask?
Nothing.
I just see Pete staring.
Why don't you help him out?
Hey, no.
Are you crazy?
Come on, that's your birthday gift.
Don't you want it?
Say yes, my friend.
No way.
Be bold. Go on.
If Raffy won't help, go tell him yourself.
"Please be my birthday present."
Go on.
Get up.
Get your ass up.
Stand up. Stand up.
Just go.
Do it.
Are you guys serious?
Hurry up.
Go on.
- Really?
- Come on. Go already.
Chop-chop.
Here he comes.
Rome, have a seat.
Please.
Guys, say hi to Rome.
Cheers.
Hey. How's it going as a sound
engineer for the faculty play?
Having fun?
It's pretty fun.
I get to meet people from other majors too.
Usually, I only hang out with music people.
It's a shame I'm an accountant.
I don't get to see you much.
But I think Raffy sees you a lot.
I told you I don't. I'm not close to him.
We work in different areas.
We do see each other.
At the play and outside of it too.
I don't really pay attention.
Yeah? I think you do.
Pete.
Hm?
Happy birthday.
Hope you get what you want.
Lucky in game and lucky in love.
Thank you, Rome.
Would you excuse me?
I'm going to grab something from my car.
Rome.
Uh… I'll go with you.
Mm.
Nice!
Awesome.
Cheers.
Hey.
Why are you here so early?
I knew you'd be busy,
so I asked to leave early.
I also knew you'd be working so hard
you wouldn't eat,
so I got you the famous Pad Thai
near Pink's.
Thanks.
Don't thank me.
Stop working and eat first.
You need the energy.
I'm helping you tonight.
Tua.
I'm sorry. I've been really busy lately.
Between classes, rehearsals,
filming with Dean,
and my part-time job at Pink's,
I barely have time for you.
If you're that tired, you don't have to
go out of your way to see me.
Seeing you doesn't make me more tired.
It makes me happier.
If you're happy, then I'm okay.
Hey.
I told them not to add bean sprouts.
Here, let me eat them for you.
Give me the bean sprouts,
and you take the shrimp.
Here.
You haven't peeled it.
How am I supposed to eat it?
You're right.
Okay.
Here you go, sir.
Good?
It's good.
Special bite.
Special?
It's so good.
How come yours tastes better than mine?
Because I fed you.
Hey.
Rome, why don't you get in the car?
What is it, Pete?
I like you, Rome.
Thank you.
If…
If we do it in the car, would you mind?
Don't you want to think it through first?
I got you some premium matcha.
You can drink it when you're stressed.
You had time to go shopping?
I thought you only had time for content.
Come on.
Are you still mad at me?
I have every right to be.
You kept people waiting.
Alright.
I'm sorry.
But you shouldn't have done that on set.
You know that was my opportunity.
Is this really what you want?
All you do is create hype around your ship.
Are you actually happy with that?
Jack.
You know why I have to do this.
Honestly, I don't like it either.
But who would've thought
this would get me closer to my dream
of becoming an actor?
I promise it won't
affect your play again.
I know how important
this play is to you.
And I want to give my best performance,
to live up to being your number one actor.
Mm.
Just don't let it happen again.
So…
can I stay over?
So you can punish me however you want.
It was a serious offense.
Mm.
If it's that serious,
then I truly deserve to be punished.
Hey.
You can just sit and cheer me on.
You don't have to actually do it.
I want to help so you can finish it faster.
The way I see it, it
might take even longer.
Don't tease me.
Hey.
Since becoming your friend,
I've gotten to do so many fun things.
Shopped for fabric in Little India,
tried Indian food, and
even acted in a play.
Stick with me,
and you'll get to do even more.
Yeah.
I spend so much time with you
that my friends tease me.
"Arnold, acting major."
Ow.
Hey, are you okay?
I'm fine. Just a little cut.
Hold on.
Here.
Press on it.
I told you I'd do it.
You didn't listen.
Sit and rest.
I'll handle it.
Mm, I'll let you do it
so you can finish faster.
I'll just sit here and cheer you on.
What did you even do?
It's the effort that counts.
Just being with him like this
makes me happy.
Right now, Hype Wave FM is joined by
the cast of the play
everyone's talking about on social media.
They're right here with us.
Please welcome the team
from the play Romeo &amp; Romeo!
Hello.
Hi.
Hi, welcome.
You guys are so cute.
I can confirm that with my own eyes.
The whole team is here in this studio.
Before we get into the play,
can I be a shipper for a moment?
Because I just have to ship.
I'm talking about #ArnoldDean.
The buzz around them
is just as big as the play itself.
The chemistry is amazing.
Why don't we let the two of them
say something to the fans?
Let me give you a little spoiler.
Our chemistry in the play
is even better than this.
If you want the full experience,
don't forget to grab your tickets.
That's right. We'll be waiting for you.
Gosh, they'll be waiting for us.
I'm smiling without even realizing it.
I don't even know why, but I am.
Why?
Because they feel so real.
It doesn't feel like just a ship at all.
Let's do this.
We'll welcome the comments.
If you're watching live and
you ship #ArnoldDean, drop a comment.
WANNA HIT PINK'S CLUB TMR?
I'll read it out loud.
Let's go.
GOING FOR THE DRINKS OR FOR ROME?
Here's the first one with #ArnoldDean:
FOR ROME. JUST KIDDING.
OOH! THAT NIGHT IN THE CAR
MUST'VE BEEN REAL GOOD.
"They feel more real than just a ship."
STOP TEASING ME.
"I ship them so hard."
Here's another one.
Next: "I love Arnold so much,
but I love him even more with Dean."
Alright. I kind of agree.
Last one: "The MC should see a dentist.
(What's up?)
You can't stop smiling."
Okay, I'm sorry, guys.
I'm just getting too excited.
Our livestream is blowing up right now.
We've never had this many viewers before.
Alright, this one's interesting:
"I want to see Dean and Arnold
make a heart together."
Wow.
Go on, you two.
Look at this camera.
Okay.
And there's the heart.
Everyone, screenshot that right now.
Capture it.
Excuse me!
Should we talk about the play now?
Right, let's get into it.
Now that you've seen the
chemistry between our leads,
don't forget to grab your tickets
and come see us.
Everyone's been working so hard,
without pay.
Wait, what?
You're doing this for free?
That's right.
They're giving it their all.
Even if we're not getting paid,
we hope the happiness we share is worth it.
That's so sweet.
They're really working hard, you guys.
They have a passion for stage plays.
Holy shit.
Why is everyone else
not getting paid, but I am?
Hey, take it easy. Don't get upset.
It's really not a big deal.
Not a big deal?
Then explain it.
Where did the rehearsal pay come from?
Please don't hate me.
I meant well.
Actually…
I'm the one who hired you.
Why would you do that, Tua?
Do you think I have to work to survive?
Why? Do you feel sorry for me?
It's not like that.
I'm sorry.
Please don't worry.
I haven't told anyone.
I mean, if you're worried
people might judge you, they won't.
Tua, do you even hear yourself? Huh?
What you're doing
feels like you're buying me.
Do you think I'm that money-hungry?
Hey, I don't want you to feel that way.
I just didn't want you to struggle.
Just think of it as a job.
Once it's done, you get paid. It's over.
Do you really think
I want your money that badly?
I thought you knew me better than that.
I trusted you.
I didn't think you'd do this to me.
Hey.
What's wrong?
You've looked irritated since the studio.
I'm fine.
Where are you headed?
Want a ride?
No.
I don't want to get in your car.
I don't want to take someone else's place.
You mean Pete?
Yeah.
Did you bring someone else there too?
But it's none of my business who you bring.
I don't care.
Hey. You don't have to worry
about taking anyone's place.
Pete and I didn't do anything that night.
It was practically a lamb to the slaughter
and you didn't go for it?
I'd be stupid to believe that.
So you don't believe me?
You can listen to
the recording from my dash cam.
Here.
I don't think we should, Pete.
Why not?
I don't want to.
And I have to DJ later.
It'll be quick.
I'm sorry, Pete.
I don't think this is a good idea.
Let's get out of the car.
Do you believe me now?
Pete and I didn't do anything.
Then why did he say you did?
Don't know.
Maybe he just wants to brag
he hooked up with someone hot like me.
Everyone wants to claim me.
It's nice though.
Seeing you jealous.
What?
Who's jealous?
I just don't like sharing
stuff with my friend.
Rest assured now.
I'm clean food.
Ready for you to eat.
The more you have, the healthier you get.
You're not "clean."
Who knows what processes
you've been through?
Not healthy.
Still tastes good though, right?
You keep coming back for more.
Come on.
I'll give you a ride.
Come.
Damn you, Jack.
You really don't know
when to compromise, do you?
You killed the vibe the MC built up.
I wanted people to focus on the play.
Or what?
You want me to make an announcement?
"Our ship is just a ship."
"My real man is the director."
"And he's way spicier than his stage play."
Right here?
Mm.
When you act,
do you ever fall for your co-stars?
No.
I think I'm pretty good.
Acting is acting. Reality is reality.
Why do you ask?
I just wanted to know.
Do you think I'm into Arnold?
Well…
Sometimes it feels that way.
Then maybe you should compliment me.
It means I'm acting well enough
to make you believe it.
No. I'm not complimenting you.
You're always like this.
I don't get praise when I do something
right, but I get yelled at when I mess up.
Someone like you deserves to be yelled at.
Jack.
When I said I wanted to be a better person,
it was because of you.
I like it the most when I'm with you.
You don't have to do it for me.
Do it for yourself.
Well, if I become better,
that just means you get a better boyfriend.
Right?
Hey.
We're not back together yet.
How many times do I
have to tell you that?
Then I'll keep saying
it until you give in.
Stop talking and start
filming the casting video.
Then we can lie down and watch a movie.
Alright.
I'm ready.
Move a little to your left.
Good?
Okay. Stay like that.
Alright.
Five, four, three, two, action.
HOW DO YOU GET SOMEONE
TO STOP BEING MAD AT YOU?
THERE'S NO SINGLE WAY
THAT WORKS FOR EVERYONE.
BUT SOME THINGS HELP.
1. GIVE THEM TIME.
20,000฿ HAS BEEN
TRANSFERRED TO YOUR ACCOUNT.
CURRENT BALANCE: 230,050฿
Did you really bring me to a concert?
In a place like this?
I thought we'd be going to a concert hall.
This is the place.
It's an underground show.
It's cool because you only find out
which venue 36 hours before,
and you don't even know who's performing.
Surprising, right?
And how did you even find out about this?
My seniors are hosting it.
They love going to concerts, so they
started organizing shows themselves.
Extreme, huh?
But I think you know them.
Here they are.
Sand, Ray.
What's up?
Have you been well?
I have. Thank you.
I haven't seen you guys
since the seniors' farewell party.
But I've been following
you on social media.
We've been busy with shows
and this craft beer.
Give it a try.
This one's brewed from
all my years of drinking experience.
Tell me what you think.
It's good.
You're doing all this on your own?
Yeah.
Well, not exactly.
I'm doing it with my boyfriend.
Oh, wow.
Long time no see,
and you're still such a show-off.
So what's this?
Introducing your boyfriend at my event?
Hey, no.
We're just friends.
He likes to party, so I brought him along.
Sounds more like an excuse to flirt.
We're really just friends.
Okay.
Friends, it is.
Let's drink, bros.
Hi, everyone.
First of all, thank you all for coming.
I do believe concerts are for music
and music connects people.
Just like it did for me,
the day I met my boyfriend.
Tonight, I hope music
does the same for you.
Let's give it up for Something Sweet!
Whoo-hoo!
♪ Do you still feel lonely? ♪
♪ Open up, let in some company ♪
♪ Count the stars up high ♪
♪ Being alone doesn't feel so right ♪
♪ Look into my eyes, you'll see ♪
♪ Can you feel we're meant to be? ♪
♪ I counted thousands of stars ♪
♪ Lighting up the night sky afar ♪
♪ In my heart, you're my only love ♪
♪ Shining brighter than stars above ♪
♪ This true love belongs only to you ♪
♪ No need to wait so long like others do ♪
♪ This true love for you means no harm ♪
♪ Please accept it with open arms ♪
♪ True love is nothing like flowers ♪
♪ Blooming to prove their power ♪
♪ True love waits for no sign ♪
♪ Open your heart, just give it a try ♪
(Next Episode)
Hey, Arnold. What's up?
Which is your house?
Dean, can I switch places
with you? I want to talk to Jack.
I'm not sure if I still want to act or not.
I see, you're still not giving up on him.
But you don't have to worry about me.
Are you guys ready?
What are you hoping for?
I just want to have a date with you.
My bro and bro-in-law have to be this
strong.
Can I take a picture with you? I
'm going to make some content.