=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 35=
So, Yan Ke rebelled.
The Void is still in turmoil.
So, you'll be leaving again soon?
That's right.
How long will it be?
Will it be years
or even over a decade?
As for the Void, it depends.
Sometimes, it's a few years;
sometimes, it's over a decade.
How long will it take you?
Me?
About half a year.
Foxy?
Half a year?
You'll miss Luozhou's bloom.
Luozhou's peonies
are the most famous.
I planned to take you
to see peonies
once they bloom
next spring.
The breeze will be soft;
the flowers will be sweet.
If you like the wind,
we can ride horses
through the flower fields.
Foxy,
listen to yourself.
How many things did you name?
Sight, touch, and smell.
You want to give me all of them?
That's not impossible.
Duan Xu,
ever since Fengyi taught you
how to swap the five senses,
you've grown restrained.
If you have only one sensation,
you'd have no way
to feel all things in this world.
I don't want to go back.
I want to go to your Void tomorrow
and build you
another splendid palace.
A splendid palace?
Then,
should we also build
a peacock that fans its tail?
The other spirits can't see it anyway.
Only I
would have
such a palace in the Void.
Wouldn't that be delightful?
Besides, once I give you
my sense of color,
you'll be able to see colors.
Just thinking of it feels so striking.
It'll also help you know colors.
I still think it won't look good.
I'll make sure it's beautiful.
(Weizhou)
At last, we've taken Weizhou.
Where do we strike next?
Next,
we should throw all our strength
into taking Youzhou.
- Yes, Youzhou.
His Majesty's decree has arrived.
By His Majesty's decree,
Duan Xu has beaten greater odds
and won back Weizhou for Great Liang.
He is hereby appointed
Grand Marshal of All
to command the Three Armies.
Thus decreed.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Congrats, Marshal Duan.
Good.
Very good.
Truly excellent.
- You've been promoted.
- From now on,
we can't call you General Duan.
From now on, we should call you
Marshal Duan.
- Marshal Duan.
If Han
were still here,
that would be even better.
Even better.
Xu.
Xu,
are you going to see Xiaoxiao?
Lately, you've gathered
all the goodies
from the camp.
It must all be for Xiaoxiao.
You're a sharp one.
Xu, you're so unfair.
Why are you still following me?
Why aren't you drilling?
Xu,
it's been so long
since I last saw Xiaoxiao.
You can't keep her all to yourself.
I still recall the rich fragrance
of Nü'erhong.
Xiaoxiao.
Xu picked this on the way.
It's for you.
You can finally taste things,
but the camp has little to offer.
The ingredients are plain.
This camellia honey can be sipped.
It's sweet.
Give it a try.
It's light and sweet,
with a floral note.
Even better than a sugar figurine.
Now, try these as well.
The fresh sweetness of nectar lingered.
Even these dishes
taste much sweeter now.
Xiaoxiao,
try my favorite meat pie too.
It's so good.
No wonder you eat eight at a meal.
Xiaoxiao,
you can't eat anymore.
You've already had ten.
Then I'll stop.
It's all gone already.
Great Ancestor,
you're feasting in style,
and you did not invite me?
I was working hard
on blessing talismans
on the battlefield,
while you were relaxing here.
Prophet Hejia, thanks
for your hard work.
It's not hard at all.
He enjoyed himself.
Perfect timing.
I want iced fermented rice wine.
Great Ancestor knows how to enjoy life.
You boss me around once I arrive.
Who'd have thought
that one day,
I'd be sharing wine
with Great Ancestor?
Another joy
in the Mortal World.
Still,
Marshal Duan swapped
the five senses now.
Aren't you worried about the battle?
The war has eased for now.
I only changed my sense of taste.
It won't matter.
Prophet Hejia, rest easy.
With Xu's capability,
losing her sense of taste is nothing.
Even if he lost his five senses,
he could still crush the enemy.
Xiaoxiao,
you have no idea
how terrifying Xu is,
especially when he trained me.
I truly thought he was tormenting me.
Well done.
Only then will he learn.
Great Ancestor…
Move aside.
I must return to the Void.
If danger finds you,
be sure to call for me.
Keep yourself safe too.
Remember to miss me.
Don't worry.
Great Ancestor won't lose.
Xu.
Xu, what's wrong?
Chenying,
I'm fine for now.
Leave us.
Don't tell anyone about me
coughing up blood.
- But, Xu...
- Go.
I'm ordering you.
You traded your senses
with Great Ancestor,
so you suffer such agonizing backlash.
Now, your senses are fading,
and your body is failing fast.
If this continues,
you won't be granted
a peaceful old age.
It's all right.
It's enough already.
Prophet Hejia,
please don't tell Simu
about this.
There is still no way
to cure it for now,
but if you stop swapping
the five senses,
perhaps
the illness can be held for now.
I have long known of this harm.
This is why I remain
by her side.
There is little
I can do for her.
If I can't even do this,
what else can I do?
But you are doing this by spending
your health and your lifespan.
Would she be pleased?
The days I can stay by her side
have never been many.
Perhaps I will end up blurring
and fade away
just like
all her other lovers.
But exchanging the senses
was unique to her.
By my side,
she once possessed
a lively world.
I only hope that she can be happy,
and that this happiness
will make her remember me.
I have felt the world
she lives in every day.
It's too cold and lonely.
I don't want that for her.
You're a madman.
No wonder Great Ancestor
fell for you.
Enough.
I will find a way to save you.
There's no spiritual medicine here.
I'll return to Nandu at once.
In that case,
I'll leave it to you.
Xu, the Chong forces
strike the western front.
Their assault is fierce.
Qingsheng sent for aid.
Gather the troops.
Yes.
The Liang Army is advancing fast.
Weizhou has already fallen.
We can't let Duan Xu live on.
If he dies just like this,
it would be letting him off too easily.
Those Chong forces under poison again.
If not for them,
we'd never be surrounded.
Hold on a little longer.
Xia can break out with the host.
Xu!
Xu, are you alright?
What happened to you?
Xu!
Guards!
Take Marshal Duan back
as soon as possible!
- Yes!
Xu!
Xu, hang in there.
Marshal Duan!
Stay with us, Xu!
After you proved
Yan Ke's crimes to everyone,
all the Lords pledged loyalty at once.
You cleared
quite a few old cases.
You're always at Xuling Temple
or the Sovereign's Hall.
I'm so bored
by your side.
You insisted on following me.
What?
You want to read memorials too?
I can give you a few.
You can lend me a hand.
Why read
all that long-winded stuff?
When you were the Lord of Qiling Temple,
Yan Ke handled the reports
for you, didn't he?
No wonder you'd be fooled and not know.
I think you're doing this
to get back at me on purpose.
Bai Sanxing has quite a fierce temper,
but when facing you,
he just can't vent his anger.
He deserves it.
If the one controlling him
were someone else,
with his temper,
he'd choose annihilation over bowing.
Let's talk about your young lover.
I've heard that lately,
he's famed for battle
in the Mortal World.
Why not have him come to the Void?
Then you two needn't live apart.
He has his battles to fight,
and I have mine.
Lady Jiang Ai,
let's drag him into this.
What's wrong?
You miss him?
Simu,
what is it?
I can't quite put it into words.
Lately, I've found
something off.
Lady Jiang Ai,
I'll leave the memorials
to you for now.
The bleeding won't stop.
The blood is dark.
- Quick!
- The arrow is poisoned.
What are we to do now?
It won't stop.
Marshal Duan is still unconscious.
Quick!
Move!
Over here.
The water is here.
Bring more water.
Go fetch more water.
Yes.
Hurry!
The water is here.
Duan Xu.
The bleeding won't stop.
Everyone,
step outside first.
This...
Let's go.
Go.
What should we do now?
- Go.
- Let's go.
How do we cure this poison?
I've never seen this poison.
Duan Xu.
Duan Shunxi.
Foxy.
What happened to Duan Xu?
We were ambushed by Chong forces.
Xu and 5,000 riders
were trapped for three days.
Trapped for three days?
Yes.
Has he gone mute?
He was trapped
and never once called for me.
To help the army break free,
Xu led a squad to draw off the enemy.
But an assassin
of the All-Knowing
shot him.
The physician said
he could treat the wound.
But...
The arrow was poisoned.
The physician said
the poison is spreading too fast.
If there is no antidote by tomorrow,
it will seep into Xu's bones.
Then no cure will save him.
Who hurt him?
All I know is it was
the All-Knowing's assassin.
I don't know who it was.
I understand.
Take care of him.
By tomorrow,
I'll bring back the antidote.
You made the poison on the arrow
that struck Duan Xu.
Give me the antidote.
Your Grace, you came in person.
You truly care for Duan Xu.
I've heard that you act
in the Mortal World
with fairness.
You always trade.
What do you want?
The Spirits Lantern.
You know Yan Ke.
I didn't expect
the High Priest of North Chong
to end up like the father he despised
and turn to an evil spirit.
I only wish for North Chong's peace.
I will bear every sin
and every punishment alone.
Duan Xu borrowed
your unmatched power.
He must die.
Or,
you must lose your power.
Do you think Duan Xu has come this far
because I helped him?
Your Grace,
I made the poison.
Only I know the antidote.
You may do as you please.
You may report my dealings
with the evil spirit to the Royal Court.
I will take my life at once.
Without the Spirits Lantern,
I won't give you the antidote.
I may not be a match for you,
but you
can't cut open my mind.
Luda,
you know nothing of war,
so you should never be part of it.
Nor are you fit to be a Priest.
Trying to use Cangshen's ways
to control all under heaven
was foolish from the start.
In this life of yours,
you were never meant for the times
and will achieve nothing.
As for me,
I do share some bond with Duan Xu,
but why would I ever give you
the Spirits Lantern for him?
That thought of yours
is too naive.
You have only one day.
If there's no antidote by tomorrow,
he will die.
Everyone dies eventually.
Whether today or tomorrow,
what difference does it make?
Simu.
He's calling for me.
Now, he finally calls my name.
(Tomb of He Yicheng and Siwei)
It's been a long time since I came.
Father,
I'll soon avenge you.
I truly don't understand
why Yan Ke wants the Spirits Lantern
and to become the Sovereign.
What is a Sovereign?
Upon the throne,
there is only sacrifice.
But none of those evil spirits
vying for it understands.
♪Lingering for a fleeting moment♪
It's just a sacrifice.
So what if I lose Duan Xu too?
He is only one small part
of all the sacrifices.
Life and death go in cycles.
In this world,
there will be many people
like him.
It is just
that I may have to wait centuries
to meet the next spell bearer.
♪Wander to the other shore
with the lantern♪
Only a few hundred years.
I can wait that long.
♪Whether I stay or go, I'm all alone♪
The weather is turning cold.
Wake up.
The dream is already over.
I like how you worry about me.
But he is always warm.
♪Falling down like snow♪
♪Joys and sorrows of the mortal world♪
♪Swept along by the daylight♪
♪The forms and hues of the mortal realm♪
I set up a tomb
for you here.
♪Was once touched by laughing tears♪
♪If I could live a simple life♪
But in this world,
you are no longer here.
♪I'd be a guest in a sweet dream♪
I will never find you again.
♪Dawn and dusk rise and set♪
♪Longing to meet, yet parted by destiny♪
It's like no one can hear the words
I'm saying now.
This is what parting
truly means.
♪Accompanied by eternity♪
Duan Xu is no different.
If Duan Xu dies,
in this world,
there will be no more Duan Xu.
♪As stars shift and change places♪
♪A century is like a dream♪
When I had a sense of taste,
I drank this wine.
♪Let me journey across them all♪
It's fine wine.
♪A lone lamp shines on the other shore♪
♪Accompanied by the abyss♪
♪Moments may last♪
Even without the Spirits Lantern,
I can still win.
But you must be disappointed in me.
Simu.
You were trapped for three days.
I just...
A full three days.
Why didn't you ask me for help?
Victory and loss are common in war.
It was not my first time
in grave danger.
If I had to call you every time,
you'd be worn out.
Besides,
even if you came,
you could only save me alone,
at most with Chenying.
As the Marshal,
I could not leave my men behind.
Why?
What did I say wrong?
You said nothing wrong.
Think about it.
You never called for me
when you needed me most.
It hurts.
I'm still badly wounded.
I've pressed on your wound this long,
and only now you feel pain.
When did your senses begin to decay?
A little over five years ago.
Before Yan Ke's rebellion?
Because you gave me your five senses,
right?
Why didn't you tell me?
Mortals are so fragile.
My five senses were keener
than most.
Dulling a little changed nothing.
What sensation do you still desire?
I can exchange it with you now.
No need.
What is not truly mine
will never be mine.
♪I go alone in the night without end♪
♪I can't remember the seasons
or the passing years♪
Let us end things here,
Duan Xu.
What did you say?
Listen.
Let us end things here.
Simu!
Xu, you're awake.
Xu.
Xu, what's wrong?
- Xu.
- Simu!
Simu.
♪I hold a lantern to draw the moon♪
(Liang)
Xu, what's wrong?
♪I have simple wishes, but I fear♪
♪The world can't hold them♪
♪You always stay with me♪
Xu.
♪See the world I've never seen♪
Xu, where do you hurt?
Tell me, Xu.
♪I wish I could live in your heart♪
She's taken back the world
she gave me.
I'll never find her again.
Xu, what are you saying?
Xu, you...
Xu.
Xu, what's wrong?
Xu, wake up.
Xu.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪