[Disclaimer:
All depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
Do you remember that shop still?
We should choose new rings to wear.
Run! Now!
Make way! Make way!
Klao! Move!
Klao! This way!
We can go no further.
You must hide here.
I shall go and seize him myself.
No, please!
What if we should be parted again?
Countless times have we been parted,
yet ever do I find my way to you.
I promise you,
I shall return.
Nothing shall ever part us again.
[Love Upon a Time Series]
Happy birthday, Nakun!
[December 2023]
Oh...
We're so sorry.
Gosh, Pun.
I thought Nakun was already at the shop?
The surprise is ruined.
He really said he did,
but I have no idea why he's not here.
That's okay.
We'll try again.
Guys, do we still have any party poppers?
We're out.
- He told me to pop them all at once.
- Oh...
What do we do now?
Surprise.
Damn.
What the hell did you do?
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
I'm alright!
Damn!
The state you're in...
Why do you look so bad?
Thee!
What?
Stop making fun of Nakun.
I'm not.
He's really forsaken by the heavens.
Taxis refused to take him,
so he had to walk here.
Then his umbrella broke,
and a motorcycle
splashed him as it drove by.
When he finally got here,
he even stepped in some mud.
Mhm...
Bangkok...
A city of life...
It's okay, buddy.
Shake it off. Don't mind it.
It's your birthday after all.
Make a wish, buddy.
Mhm.
Uh, Nakun...
Why do things always get in my way?
Happy birthday, Nakun.
Thank you very much.
Wishing you a ton of happiness.
So have you...
made a wish again?
Yes, already.
What did you wish for?
Why do you want to know?
That way I'll know
if I should wish you well or not.
Do you really have to choose
what kind of wish to give?
I want him to find a great partner
so he's finally settled.
Better wish that for yourself.
I'm not officially taken,
but I've already found myself a good love.
Are you sure?
Of course I am.
Even though you don't choose me now,
my love for you
is surely a good thing for you.
I need to use the toilet for a bit, Nakun.
To relieve yourself?
To throw up!
Huh?
Pun, I'll help you rub your back.
[Mom]
- I'll help.
- I'm so sorry.
It's okay!
I'll help clean it up.
It's okay.
- It's fine.
- No, it's okay.
Ow...
Blood?!
Shit! My phone!
The screen's totally cracked!
Shit!!
So damn unlucky.
Can it be fixed, Nakun?
You'd be better off getting a new one.
I can't.
No modeling gigs are coming up.
I do think I'm handsome, though...
- Whoa!
- Bird poop!
- Nakun...
A bird pooped on your head!
Nakun!
- Oh, that's a lot.
- Give me a moment.
- Pun, wipe it off my head!
- Whoa...
Get it off my head!
- Pun, please wipe it off my head!
- Whoa!
- Get it off!
- I'm on it. Please wait.
How can someone be this unlucky?
Gosh, you're so unlucky!
At least it's gone.
- Not like this!
- Just as you requested.
[One month later]
♫Let's skinship♫
♫This is freaking drip♫
♫Moving closer♫
♫I'll whisper you with my feelings♫
♫Just skinship♫
♫My heart's in heat♫
♫Blowing you a kiss♫
♫With no rehearsal needed♫
♫Love is nothing you can touch♫
♫No measurement can hold this much♫
♫Let be clear, make it all clean-cut♫
♫It's the feeling,♫
Help me! Somebody!
Help! Someone just stole my handbag!
Help me!
Please help!
That guy over there!
Help me catch the thief, please!
- Help me, please!
- Sure.
Please! Catch that guy!
Stop!
- Stop!
- Somebody, please catch the thief!
Catch him, please!
Hey, stop!
Stop running away already!
Hey!
Let go.
You're a thief, yet you're so slow.
Give the handbag back to her.
If she takes this up,
you'll end up in jail
and get a criminal record!
Hey, man...
What do you want from me?
Please let me go.
My mom's sick.
This money's for her.
Listen to me.
To be human is to fight.
But don't fight others.
You're still young
with a bright future ahead.
It's not too late to change your mind.
It's that person.
- It's that guy!
- Stop!
- What the hell?
- Stop!!
- That's my handbag.
- Hey!
That's mine.
You're a thief, yet you're so slow.
If she takes this up,
you'll end up in jail
and get a criminal record.
Please listen to me.
So...
To be human is to fight.
But don't fight me.
Guys, listen to me.
I fucking... Sorry.
I didn't...
Just believe me.
I think it's getting worse and worse.
This isn't normal.
So what?
You're acting like I can change anything.
Of course you can.
That's why I brought you here.
[Fortune Teller Rattikarn's Pavilion]
Are you crazy?
No thanks.
I'm leaving.
Hold on!
The fortune teller here is really good.
Take my mom's word for it.
If it doesn't work out,
you can just go home,
okay?
Give it a try, Nakun.
If this is a scam, we'll leave.
Things like this are always a scam.
Do you believe me now?
This is the real deal.
No.
No matter how bad things get,
I'll never...
So cold!
How many times do I have to get soaked?
Come on, the water is warm.
I don't buy it.
You forced me here,
and now you're mocking me?
The water really is warm, Nakun.
It's hot, even.
One misfortune after another.
If holy water makes you shiver,
then it's no surprise.
Ow!
Once you get changed,
head inside.
We have a lot to talk about.
Hey.
How did you like the warm bath service?
- Come and try it yourself.
- Whoa, whoa!
Wait, wait.
- Out of the way!
- Whoa...
- Looking good, Nakun.
- That's enough, Thee.
Move.
Hey, what the hell?
Wait up, please!
Don't leave just yet.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Rahu transits the natal sign.
You are about to experience misfortune.
And?
An incident will occur...
No.
It has already occurred
since your birthday last month.
Whoa...
How did she know?
It's all written right here,
[4 December 2003]
his date of birth and everything.
We've already told her everything.
At any rate...
The reading I did was from his natal chart.
I truly mean well.
This misfortune is fatal.
Be extremely careful.
I'm heading home.
What promise did you make, and to whom?
Someone from the past
awaits its fulfillment.
Whoa, this is giving me chills.
Who did you make a promise to?
None. This is nonsense.
Nakun, this is a serious matter.
If it is, then why are you smiling?
Is there any way we can help him?
Hold him down!
- Let me go!
- Hey! Hey!
- Thee, let me go!
- Pun, help me out!
I don't want to!
- Pun, help me!
- Let me go!
Thee, don't!
Thee!
I told you to let me go!!
Quite a fighter, aren't you?!
Thanks.
As for you...
it might be wise
to lift the curse you made long ago.
Me?
Whoever you felt resentment toward,
release the grudges you hold.
This will break the cycle.
And you...
Visit your family if possible.
Pray for and take care of your mom and dad.
This will alleviate your misfortune.
I don't have a dad.
It's just a divorce.
He didn't pass away or anything.
He is still your father.
And...
you're going back to Ayutthaya anyway,
aren't you?
Did you tell her that?
No, I didn't.
I have no idea what you're thinking.
I don't need to be told that.
This Friday,
your mom is going to call you.
At night,
don't forget to bathe in the moonlight.
And wear this.
No, I'm not wearing it.
Hey, Thee!
You must not take it off.
It's no use trying.
Keep it on.
Time travel literature
is not just about traveling into the future
or back in time to change something.
It questions whether time itself
is a phenomenon of nature
[How is this important to me?]
or merely an illusion created by humans.
We may think time moves linearly,
but in the world of time travel literature,
it is often portrayed as fragmented.
It jumps back and forth,
moving in circles,
as if it were a dream
or a memory.
- It loops back,
- Why are you taking notes in English?
- becoming a cycle.
- I was just going to ask for it.
This suggests that
the concepts of past and future lives
might actually exist.
Thee, give it back to me.
Students over there...
Yes, you.
What's your name?
She's asking you...
Uh...
It's Kun,
short for Nakun.
"Kun, short for Nakun?"
That's a mouthful.
You can call me Kun for short, Professor.
Do you believe in multiple lifetimes?
Yeah, do you?
Answer her.
Do you?
Come on.
Answer the question.
I don't.
I think it's an idea created by humans
to cope with loss
or things they can't explain.
Interesting.
And?
Well...
Say, if we were born with hardships,
we might say it's the consequence
of actions from a past life.
We'd then tell ourselves to be content
with what we have
and to keep cultivating good deeds,
without recognizing
the underlying social issues.
Sheesh.
I believe in logic.
Every action
has its consequences.
But...
I don't think consequences
carry over to our next lives.
What an interesting answer.
Those who don't believe in
multiple lifetimes might think that
we have the power to shape our own destiny
and that nothing is predetermined,
correct?
Be careful, Nakun.
In the world of time travel literature,
we cannot always rely on logic.
It might reflect something
that lies deep within.
It might be fear,
hope,
or the unwillingness
to believe in something,
correct?
Well, I...
I have no fear, Professor.
You have no fear?
Be honest with yourself and ask
whether you truly have no fear.
Hey.
Come on.
Take it easy.
You better sit down.
Do you believe in multiple lifetimes?'
That's the topic of your assignment.
- Oh...
- Gosh!
The deadline is today.
No!
Class dismissed.
Nakun.
Go take care of your Mother,
as the fortune teller said.
Having ill luck is bad enough,
yet you have doomed us all.
That has nothing to do with me.
Professors here love giving
piles of assignments.
Why the hell
do I have to get into this faculty?
Can we go back in time and change this?
Going back in time?
See?
The professor has stuffed your head
with ideas about time travel.
Yeah, you're right.
But I'd rather not.
If I studied at a different faculty,
I wouldn't get to see Pun.
Has anyone ever told you that
when you talk about Pun,
you act like a Siberian Husky?
Who said that?
Was it Pun?
Me.
Pun is like a Persian cat, though.
Cats and dogs don't get along very well.
Wait, but I've seen videos on TikTok.
They can be together, alright?
Stop talking nonsense.
Yeah, what does this mean?
Nakun...
Nakun.
Nakun!
I'm here to return your notes.
Thanks to you,
I got the top score
in the Western History midterm exam.
Thank you.
Whoa, you're amazing, Pun.
Your fraternity brother
topped the class in English, you know?
But he's a goner
when it comes to Thai History.
Huh?
Thee.
What? The midterm exam was last week,
and you said
you couldn't remember a thing.
We're talking about Nakun here, you know?
He was just being humble, more like.
He'll get an A when the results come out.
Yeah, you're right.
Nakun always tells us he hasn't studied
and can't do the exam,
but he always
ends up at the top of the class.
Mhm.
[Mom]
Nakun, are you coming home
for the break?
I miss you.
We haven't celebrated your birthday.
Give me a call once your classes are over.
By the way, Pun,
we studied time travel literature today.
The topic was about multiple lifetimes.
- Do you believe in stuff like that?
- Multiple lifetimes.
Um...
I guess I do.
The concept sounds fun
if you think about it.
If you do, I will too.
Perhaps our paths
might have crossed in past lives.
Then, we'll meet again in the next one.
Okay.
Then, I don't believe in it.
This lifetime is more than enough.
What? Why?
There are only
so many lifetimes for souls to meet, Thee.
Can't I just meet you again
in the next life?
This lifetime is already killing me.
Why?
- No.
- Pun, wait up!
- Nope.
- What's the rush?
- Why are you always on my case?
- Come on, wait for me.
Be careful, Nakun.
In the world of time travel literature,
we cannot always rely on logic.
It might reflect something
that lies deep within.
Be careful, Nakun.
Hey! Nakun!
Nakun!
[D.E. 6613,
Phra Nakhon Si Ayutthaya]
Are you okay? All good?
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
It's okay.
That really scared me.
Whoa...
Hey, Nakun.
Nakun!
- Nakun! Look out!
- Hey!
Hey...
- Shit...
- Nakun!
Are you hurt?
Damn...
How did that fall over?
Are you okay?
Are you alright, Nakun?
You're...
going back to Ayutthaya anyway,
aren't you?
It just fell down randomly.
[D.E. 6613,
Phra Nakhon Si Ayutthaya]
Mom...
[Certificate of Excellence]
[Master Nakun Phattanatada]
I'm finally home.
Oh, Nakun?
You're home late.
Oh, Mom?
Whoa...
You look amazing, Ma'am.
Your son just got home,
and you're leaving already?
Oh no, I'm not.
I'm leaving for
the District Chief's child's wedding.
Do you want to come with me?
The party will last
the whole night, you know?
I'll call it a pass.
District Chief's child?
I don't even know the name.
I thought so.
But I've prepared dinner for you.
Eat a lot of rice, alright?
Don't just go for the main dishes.
Mhm...
Whoa!
This much?
Are you throwing a party or something?
You'll finish all of that.
Oh, if you're not full,
there are fruits and snacks in the fridge.
Go ahead and go to town on them, got it?
Sure...
Do I look beautiful now?
I guess.
I'll be going now.
Nakun!
Wait...
What happened to your face?!
Huh?
Oh, this?
No one would dare hurt me, Mom.
I fell over.
And I ended up slamming my head!
So my face got all swollen...
Oh, for goodness' sake...
So you were just being clumsy as usual.
I thought you got into a fight
or something.
Who would I even fight, Mom?
You, the deputy,
have taught me since I was little
that violence is off-limits.
And when I do something,
make sure no one can criticize me.
Isn't that right?
I'm so proud of you, honey.
That really warms my heart.
Gosh! What's gotten into you?
I'm overjoyed, okay?
I'm proud of you.
Raising you on my own
into the good boy you are today
makes me incredibly proud.
One more.
What is this?
Why don't you head out already?
Drinks don't pour themselves, you know.
I don't drink.
I'm off.
Good luck.
Thanks!
And you said you don't drink...
Well then...
If she doesn't drink,
this is all mine.
[Detective Conan]
[Do you believe in multiple lifetimes?]
[I freaking don't!]
"Thai History Test Results."
What?
Why did the results come out so early?
"Mr. Nakun Pattanatada"
I got...
14.5?
First time failing an exam.
Am I really suffering from misfortune?
Geese.
Geese, where are you guys?
Geese!
Come out, it's feeding time.
Where are they?
Oh, I missed the bucket.
Come and feed yourselves, then.
It's always me!
It always happens to me!
Why does a future honor English student
have to fail Thai History?!
If past lives do exist,
why aren't my past memories
carried over into this life
so I don't have to study Thai History?!
Gosh!
Might as well take a swig...
Gorgeous.
Look...
Even a star is falling on me.
Is it actually falling?
Ow...
Master Klao is over there!
Tread lightly!
There are king cobra dens.
Master Klao.
- Master.
- Master Klao.
Master Klao!
- What?!
- Master!
Master Klao.
- Whoa! What?!
- Master Klao!
- Master Klao.
- Master.
- Master Klao!
- Gosh! Who are you?
- Ow! That hurt!
- Master.
His Excellency and the Lord
have commanded us
to search for you these several days.
What circumstances led you to these woods?
Huh?!
Master?
What the hell?
- Bastard!
- You son of a rogue!
Father and son alike, wretched both!
- Scum!
- The likes of you shall never prosper, Klao!
The likes of you shall never prosper, Klao!
Does your head hurt, Master Klao?
Everyone! Escort him back
to His Excellency's estate.
Master Klao!
My Master!
Master!
- What a comfort!
- Whoa!
Master, you are still alive?
- How are you, Master?
- Hey!
Who are you guys?
And I'm...
I'm not dreaming, am I?
I beg your pardon?
You've got it all wrong.
I'm not Klao.
Oh, Master.
You still jest at a time such as this?
This suggests that you are well.
Is it not so?
You...
You guys are filming a period piece,
aren't you?
Since when has my mom
let people film a play in her orchard?
Film...
A play?
A play...
You...
What are you doing? Filming content?
Master Klao...
Wait...
This is different from last night.
What is this place?
Last night,
I was drinking.
After that, I left the house.
And then, the star fell!
Then I ended up here.
What's next?
God! I was too drunk to remember anything!
I too have been pondering
the circumstances that brought you here.
My Lord...
My Lord.
Who's that?
He looks so familiar.
A celebrity?
How is that?
Will you now tell me?
Uh...
I think you've got it all wrong.
I'm not an actor.
I'm Ms. Nahathai's son,
from the nearby mango orchard.
Last night, I must've gotten pretty drunk,
wandered around, and ended up here.
That said,
I won't trouble you any further.
Take care, guys.
Seize him!
- Do not let him stray from our sight.
- What the hell?
Hey, let go of me!
You...
This course of action...
I could sue you for this!
Master Klao! Master!
Master! Master Klao!
Master Klao!!
My Lord!
I beg you, my Lord,
please spare him the cane.
The fault is mine alone.
You entrusted Master Klao to me,
yet I have failed you
by permitting him to indulge in spirits.
Enough!
No one shall be punished.
Attend to your master at once,
and bring him back to the small manor.
Shall we not go to
His Excellency's estate?
Not at this moment.
Is it not evident
that your master is troubled in mind?
I wish to spare my parents from distress.
Yes, my Lord.
Waste no time.
Find Klao at once.
I shall follow shortly after.
Yes, my Lord.
Master Klao!
Master Klao! Master!
Master!
- Master!
- Master Klao!!
Let go of me!
- Master...
- Let me go!
Let go!!
Ow!
I told you to let go of me! Come on!
You've got the wrong person!
Please, Master.
Master, please.
I'll sue! I'll sue!!
My phone.
You even took my phone from me?!
- Master Klao.
- Gosh!!
Not going anywhere!
Let me go!!
Let go!
Help! Somebody, help!
This way, Master.
Gentle, please!
Where am I now?
Lord Phop has arranged
these quarters for your comfort.
Lord?
You mean the guy
with the scary-looking face?
Please cease this mockery, Master Klao.
My heart grows uneasy.
You guys need to stop playing games.
I'm not entertained by this.
It actually hurt.
And you dragged me
to a cabin in the middle of nowhere, too.
"Cabin in the middle of nowhere"?
This is kidnapping.
I'll take this matter all the way.
Also, tell the 'Lord,' or whoever he is,
to be ready to face me in court.
Master.
How may I, Chuay,
be of service to you?
Your name's Chuay?
Master...
Even I, you...
It's hot in here.
Can you turn on the air conditioner, Chuay?
Hm?
The A/C.
Turn on...
the A...
Don't tell me there's no A/C here.
Grant this humble servant
your pardon, Master.
Stop calling me Klao already.
My name is not Klao!
Master Klao...
What a waste of time.
No, Master!
It is at the Lord's request
that you seek repose here.
Should you leave,
I shall surely receive a harsh caning.
Can you stop playing
the character for a second?
Playing the character?
I fear I lack the talent.
I have not mastered the art.
You keep up your character so well.
Where did you learn to act?
You are well aware that
I am no master of Farangi speech.
What speech?
"Farangi," Master.
"Farangi"?
Like, French?
I was speaking English.
"Fa-ran-gi," Master.
Who cares.
Listen.
I don't know what you're trying to do,
maybe make a screenplay,
kidnap me for ransom,
or something,
but you've got the wrong guy.
My name is not Klao.
It's 'Nakun.'
Also, I'm useless to you.
My mom definitely doesn't have
money for a ransom.
Chuay.
You look like a good person.
Can you please...let me go?
I won't snitch.
Master! Wait!
Where do you wander to now, Klao?
I'm getting out of here.
Move.
You are attired somewhat oddly.
Hey, what are you doing?
Stop it.
The butterfly-shaped mark of birth.
There is no mistaking you, Klao.
Butterfly-shaped?
It's shaped like
the northern region of Thailand.
Have your wits forsaken you?
Is it overindulgence
that clouds your words?
I'm the one speaking coherently.
Sure, I had
a little too much to drink last night,
but I wasn't out cold or anything.
Have you guys lost your minds,
claiming that I'm Klao?
Why, then, did you claim you were not Klao?
Nobody here gets it.
I told you I'm not Klao!
Gosh, what the hell is going on?!
Master Klao!
Master!!
Master Klao.
Master Klao!
Where am I?
How the hell did I end up here?
What happened to me?!
Master Klao! Stop!
Master.
I beg you, Master.
Wait, Master!
Master Klao!
Gosh! Still following me?
I'm probably in a film shoot
for a period piece.
The extras are rehearsing
for their scenes, aren't they?
Master!
Please wait, Master.
Master Klao.
How is this even played?
Master Klao!
Hey, move!
Out of the way!
Move!
Master...
Awesome job on the props.
So realistic.
What company is behind this?!
Master Klao.
Be wary, Master!
Make way, if you please.
Make way, I beg you!
Please wait, Master.
Yes, this is it!
Many period pieces were filmed here!
Where are all the crew members?
Help me!
Master Klao!
Do wait, Master!
Do not go there!
My feet can go no further!
My poor feet can bear no more!
- Master Klao!
- This place is not to be entered, Master!
This quarter must not be entered!
Master.
I beg of you, Master! Stop!
Excuse me.
You guys are working on a series, correct?
Well...
I'm not here to interrupt you, but...
Can anyone tell me
how to get out of this filming location?
Dear Klao.
Where have you wandered off to?
Dearest Klao.
So you have returned.
Come, let us eat together.
No, thank you.
My Prayong.
Yes, my love?
Has dearest Klao lost his wits?
Oh, good heavens.
Indeed, a most unfortunate fate...
Klao.
Klao!
Klao!!
- Let us settle this matter.
- Gosh!
Stop chasing me!
Oh, heavens!
I nearly tumbled down the stairs.
I'm really sorry!
I nearly went down with him.
If this isn't a film set,
then where the hell am I?
Scratch traveling back in time
off the list.
It's impossible.
And who the hell is that Lord Paddle Phop?
It's not coming to me.
But he looked at me
like we'd known each other forever.
Master!
Master Klao!
Pray, stop running.
Master Klao!!
At last, you are within my grasp!
Remain still, Master.
Be still, I beg you.
Master Klao, cease this.
Pray, remain still!
Stop chasing me already!
Help me, please.
Somebody, help.
Klao!
Anyone but him!
Let us speak and be understood.
I refuse!
Oh, Master!
Are you well?
Sis, move!
I can do this all day.
Gosh! My intrusive thoughts!
Everyone's acting so well.
Artistic integrity is unreal.
I don't think this is a film set.
Shit!
What is the matter, Master Klao?
It hurts,
but I'm not waking up.
This isn't a dream.
I don't think scammers
pull off stuff this fancy, either.
Where am I even?
A mysterious village
and weird cultists?
Like the ones in the movies?
Master Klao!
Master!
Cease this, Master.
A rooster?!
- Master Klao!
- I am utterly weary, Master.
Master Klao!
Master, where are you going?!
- Master, I beg you!
- Ah!
Master Klao!!
I do fight back, alright?!
Master, compose yourself!
Be wary!
I beg you, Master!
- Don't come any closer!
- Master, do cease this.
Ah! What the hell are you?!
Do not go, I beg you!
- Master Klao?
- After him!
Help me!
- Master!
- Master Klao...
Hey, stop!
Hey!
Don't come any closer!
I'll curse you...
I'll curse you all!
What do I do now?
Espresso Petroleum!
A perfect name for a drink, isn't it?!
Have I really traveled back in time?
How did I even do it?
When we think of traveling through time,
we usually imagine it happening
with a time machine,
magic, some kind of sorcery,
or a portal.
But sometimes, drifting off to sleep,
passing out,
or being knocked out by an accident
can make someone travel back in time.
When it comes to traveling back in time,
death is considered the starting point.
It's about dying
and traveling to a different realm,
then being reincarnated as someone else.
A portal?
Ah!
It's like in video games.
If we die,
we'd start over from the beginning.
I must've blacked out
and ended up here.
If I die now,
do I go back to the present day?
My Lord...
It has been far too long.
At your word, shall we...
This way, Curer.
Thee?!
Klao.
Pun!
Yes. I'm safe now.
Klao.
Jom's words were true.
You have lost your wits.
You...
Regarding Klao's affairs, your heart
is more troubled than by your own.
That deadpan lord.
Is he taken?
The Lord usually takes no regard
for the welfare of others.
His concern is reserved solely for...
you, Master Klao.
♫Seeing you feels like destiny come true♫
♫All that I dream and long for leads to you♫
♫Fate isn't chance, but something meant to be♫
♫Thank you for giving love its meaning to me♫
♫Seeing you now is more than fantasy♫
♫Every second I give you faithfully♫
♫As time goes on, no matter where we are♫
♫My heart is yours, no matter near or far♫