I didn't know…
that was possible.
How…
Do-hee!
Do-hee.
The tattoo…
has come back to me.
EPISODE 11
A PARADISE OF THE OMINOUS
Now that's what I'm talking about.
The perfect life of a demon
who looks down at insignificant humans.
The leisure that only
an apex predator can enjoy.
It's nice to finally be back
to my perfect self!
I'm incredible as usual.
Yet humans are as insignificant as ever.
Seriously.
So you're back to your old self.
Do-hee! I told you not to move around.
You might injure yourself.
I can't be lying down all day.
I have to get to work.
Who cares about work?
Are you obsessed with work or something?
This is called a sense of responsibility.
I have a lot on my shoulders
as the CEO of my company.
What are you doing?
Car accidents are not to be taken lightly.
They may have lasting impacts
even after you think you've recovered.
I'm really fine.
You've healed me completely.
Don't you trust your powers?
That's not it.
It's just
that I almost lost you for good.
We almost lost each other.
I'll be late.
Be careful!
-Do Do-hee!
-I'm fine!
Dodo!
Let's see here.
What should I wear?
Thanks.
Which bag…
Hold on.
Take the black one.
Sure.
You should get ready too.
We don't have much time.
Only if my powers weren't back.
Jeong Gu-won!
This outfit symbolizes
my perfect rebirth as a flawless being.
-What do you think?
-It's perfect.
It's so flawlessly obnoxious.
You think so?
How about now?
Goodness, are you performing
at a nightclub later?
Looking good, maestro.
Here's a standing ovation for you.
You're amazing, Jeong Gu-won!
Then you pick out my outfit.
Okay. One second.
This looks good.
What do you think?
Got it.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Because…
I don't need to.
Let's wear matching outfits.
No way.
It's not my thing.
Turns out I love matching outfits.
Should we get going?
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Why are we walking?
You said you'd walk with me
if the world were to end tomorrow.
-We have to stop by somewhere too.
-We'll be late.
Don't worry about that.
We'll be at work
at the snap of my fingers.
I almost forgot.
This is the life of a demon.
Yes. And let me know if you need anything.
Everything is a piece of cake for me.
What?
Wait for me, Do-hee.
Hurry up.
Look. You didn't expect to see
the two of us together again, did you?
Are you bragging right now?
I'm rubbing it in.
I can hear you.
Just say it to my face.
How do you feel
about this unexpected anomaly?
I'm surprised.
Congratulations.
Hold on.
I don't think you have a knack for it.
Here's a billion won.
Quit gambling and start saving up.
Don't forget.
I won.
How exactly do you know her?
She's my boss.
What?
It's ten won, damn it.
Don't mind her.
Is she really?
MIRAE F&amp;B
-Good morn--
-Good morning indeed.
It'll be yet another insignificant day,
but have a good one.
He seems to be in a good mood today.
You're right.
He's glowing.
When is he not?
You're right.
He's always glowing.
Why are you two being so awkward?
What do you mean?
We're just being polite.
I'll be busy all day
finishing up the work from yesterday.
What's this? Is it for me?
Do you like it?
It's my birthday cake.
Right.
Make a wish.
I don't need to
because I can do anything now.
Maybe it's the 200-year-old in you.
This is a bit old-fashioned.
I didn't know
it'd feel this nice to have a birthday.
Congratulations, Demon 2.0.
Demon what?
You've been upgraded.
You don't flicker
or need to charge up anymore.
What am I, a robot vacuum?
Also,
I still need to charge up.
We can't eat the cake like this.
Like I said, I can do anything.
-It's good.
-Is it?
Try it.
Here, 2.0.
-Good, isn't it?
-Yes.
So they survived that fiery pit?
-The Perilla Seeds and Scallions!
Halt!
Hello, boss!
-Hello, boss!
I'm not your…
I have a task for you.
If you fail,
I forbid you to show up
in front of me ever again.
I am your boss.
Who knew you'd manage to find him?
We're quite capable.
Hold on, boss.
I almost forgot.
My trypophobia!
Boss.
It's perilla seeds and scallions.
I see.
It's beautiful.
Thank you, boss!
-Thank you, boss!
My ears are ringing.
He must be feeling shy.
-Boss!
"Transfer of ownership"?
Sunwol Foundation is mine now.
You've had your eye on my company
all this time, haven't you?
Now I know
why you've been hanging out in my office.
That's right.
I've been looking forward to
your spontaneous combustion.
What kind of demon plans to die?
My car payments aren't my only problem.
I even took out huge loans
to buy my apartment.
Don't you dare die
until I pay off all my debts.
You get your way out when you die,
but what about the performance?
It's not that simple
to transfer ownership either.
There's a ton of paperwork to go through.
Imagine how tiring that'll be
and how much it'll break my heart.
Stop crying.
Anyway, from now on,
you're a mere figurehead.
My Sunwol Foundation!
I applaud your sense of ownership.
So what on earth happened?
How did you get the tattoo back?
What are you talking about? I'm a demon.
There's nothing a demon can't do!
You're really back.
You're completely back
to your obnoxious self.
But how did you know my tattoo came back?
Star Jin told me.
-Where are you going?
-I have to make a deal.
Everything's back to normal now.
Director Jeong.
What's wrong, Star Jin?
Why is he so upset?
Let me introduce
Mirae F&amp;B's much anticipated new product.
This drink doubles as a hangover cure
and is scheduled to launch
just before Christmas.
We're working on a promotion strategy
targeting workers in their 20s and 30s.
Even though times have changed,
many workers are still forced
to go for drinks with their superiors
day in and day out.
That's right.
And when you get drunk
at an unwanted team dinner,
you always end up
chewing out your superior
and humiliating yourself.
Do you forget your manners
and black out whenever you drink?
Hey!
You better get your act together!
Get it together, will you?
Do Do-hee! Get your act together.
I'm on fire today.
Let's have a fourth round, everyone!
If that sounds familiar,
I present to you
our new anti-hangover drink,
-Ultra Santa X!
-X!
-Santa X!
-Ms. Shin.
-Yes?
What's…
on the schedule for today?
Today,
you're very busy.
-Should we get going?
-Yes.
I've never seen Ms. Do
at a loss for words like that.
I'm more surprised
to see Ms. Shin so flustered.
It must mean that we did a good…
No, an amazing job!
Amazing job?
This calls for a team dinner.
What are we having?
-What are you in the mood for?
-Homemade food.
Homemade food?
Let me see.
Where can we get some good homemade food?
-My place.
-Your place?
Then shall we have a team dinner
at her place today?
That's a good idea.
It's been so long.
Found you.
If only she could recognize me just once.
That's all I could ever wish for.
I'll grant your wish.
Who are you?
I'm a demon.
In other words, you just hit the jackpot.
Hold on a second.
I haven't said that line in forever.
A demon?
Yes, I can make your wish come true.
In return, make a deal with me.
The terms are that
you will go to hell in ten years.
Please bring me my husband.
Honey.
You're up.
Sir.
Where's my husband?
Please look for him.
I'd like to see him
one last time before I die.
Come on.
I'm right here.
Why can't you recognize me?
Alzheimer's?
She doesn't remember
the current version of me.
She only remembers me
from when I was young
and asks for him all day long.
I feel so sorry for her.
Can you really grant my wish?
Of course.
Let's do it right now.
But she doesn't have much time left.
Is a few minutes of reunion
really worth going to hell?
There's something
I must tell her when she recognizes me.
It was crazy enough to grant a wish
before signing a deal just one time.
Honey.
Where have you been all this time?
Where else?
I've been next to you the whole time.
Then why couldn't I see you?
Exactly.
Why couldn't you see me?
I've always been by your side.
I had no idea.
I thought you had abandoned me.
Of course not.
I can't live without you.
Don't say that.
You should go on with your life
even when I'm gone.
Even if you can't see me,
I'll always be by your side.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Let's meet again.
Please don't forget me.
I won't.
I'll always remember you,
even after you're gone.
Am I…
crying?
I wasn't crying.
I was just…
sweating.
I was sweating out of my eyes.
I've never once teared up for the
past 200 years, even when I yawned.
So there's no way I was crying.
Also,
trading a couple of minutes for ten years
is against business ethics.
Why do humans wear out so fast?
How insignificant.
Where are some evil humans
who deserve to go to hell?
You're here.
Did you make a deal?
No luck today.
All right.
Should we go catch them now?
Catch who?
The real culprit.
They should be punished
for breaking the peace treaty first.
Welcome back, Do Do-hee.
You're being haughty like your name.
Where should we begin?
Sokcho.
The culprit knew we were in Sokcho.
Someone leaked our information.
It's always the confidant that betrays
the main character for money.
We should start with our inner circle.
The people who knew we were in Sokcho
were Seok-hoon and Ms. Jin.
So did Mr. Park and…
I'm leaving.
Thank you for today.
And that woman.
She's the most suspicious of all.
She would never…
do such a thing.
What's with her?
Just look at the way she behaves.
Do you see that?
She's our prime suspect.
It doesn't get more suspicious than that.
Nothing's for sure.
Let's not jump to conclusions.
She would never…
Who's that?
What is he carrying?
An apple box hints at bribery.
I know humans weren't to be trusted,
but who knew she'd do that?
I still trust…
How could she…
No, that can't be. Right?
But still, this is obvious, isn't it?
The apple box and everything!
This isn't right!
Calm down, Do-hee.
Let's go get her.
Hold on.
We need proof.
I'll swoop down on the guy first.
Mr. Park?
What the…
I mean…
YOU'RE A STAR, MS. SHIN
A STAR IN MY HEART
I mean, why would you be
so secretive about a cake?
We weren't being secretive.
We were just shy.
What about the apple box?
I wanted a box that was big enough
for my feelings for her.
What on earth did we miss?
Remember when you asked me
to take Ms. Shin home when she got drunk?
Well, she wouldn't tell me her address.
So…
Tell me exactly where you live.
You're a kind man.
-I'm just following Director Jeong's…
-You're also responsible.
You've got to be kidding me.
You look cute when you smile.
Ms. Shin!
When did you…
Ms. Shin.
Your nose is bleeding.
You're the one for me.
Fork-gyu.
A bloody kiss.
Brought together by an irresistible fate,
we spent the night passionately…
That's enough. Spare me the details.
I don't want to know too much
about my family's private life.
Your family?
Ms. Shin.
You said you were lukewarm.
I happened to find that attractive.
I'm sorry for everything.
Why are you apologizing?
Falling in love isn't a crime, is it?
If you're so confident,
why were you being so suspicious?
I'm not confident.
All my past relationships
have left me ashamed.
Ms. Shin.
By the way,
have you been following me in a car?
Yes. Why?
Wouldn't it have been more convenient
to use your powers?
If I had used my powers,
we could've ended up in your back seat
or trunk… Hold on.
What?
That caught me off guard.
How do you know everything about me?
Did you tell her everything?
Did you?
Well, love has no secrets.
Ms. Do.
I'd appreciate it
if you could keep it a secret at work.
Ms. Shin.
We were totally wrong.
I knew Ms. Shin would never betray me.
"How can she do this to me?"
Guess who said that.
I have no idea.
The answer is
Do Do-hee
Should we get going?
What an unproductive day.
What are you doing?
We can't let them outdo us.
My goodness.
Are you crazy?
I am crazy about you.
Go away!
Hey!
Wolsim!
I would rather forget myself…
than forget you.
What?
What is this?
Why do I keep dreaming
about when I was human?
And why can't I see the face
of the woman called Wolsim?
Is this what they call
manipulative editing?
One question at a time. I can't follow.
Why am I still dreaming
of when I was human
when my powers have returned?
Let me guess.
Perhaps…
you want to remain a human.
You don't want to lose the human emotions
that you've been experiencing.
Then what's with the editing?
Do you think I'm responsible for that?
Didn't I tell you?
I may set the basic rules,
but humans create anomalies
by disobeying the rules,
just like you did.
You must have erased
the memories of that woman
because they tormented you.
It's the human instinct
of self-preservation.
A defense mechanism.
The memories tormented me?
Why?
How should I know when even you don't?
You're wrong.
I don't have human instincts,
nor do I want to remain human.
Two people entangled in fate
are meant to be reunited
in one way or another.
Because fate always repeats itself.
I'm here to see Do-hee.
An investment agreement?
I wish to fund Mirae F&amp;B's expansion
into the Americas.
I appreciate the gesture,
but I'd rather not owe you anything.
That's a shame.
I really wanted to help.
I found this in my mother's belongings.
Would you at least take this?
Do you already have a copy?
No.
My mother cared deeply about your parents.
She was devastated
when your father left the company.
We've had our moments of conflict
following the cruel turn of events,
but I stand by my words
that I consider you family.
Let's resolve our past conflicts
and work together from now on.
You have a guest.
I suppose an unwelcome guest
is a guest all the same.
You're part of the family now,
but I don't know how to address you.
In that case,
you can call me bro.
See you again.
Not up for it?
What was he doing here?
Who knows?
Don't mind him.
So it's back.
Mom…
Dad…
Mom!
Don't you know how to knock?
What were you looking at?
Nothing.
Why would you peep like a little rat?
I can't sleep.
Just so you know.
Me neither.
It's hot!
Wait for it to cool down.
You're an impatient one.
It's hot!
It's my family.
But you're not in it.
I'm…
here in my mom's tummy.
The day my parents passed away
was my 11th birthday.
I was especially
looking forward to that day
because my dad
had promised me a birthday party
that I'd never forget.
I was excited for days.
But on my birthday,
my dad suddenly had to go to work,
although he'd quit a long time ago.
I couldn't understand.
Being a little kid,
I cried and threw a tantrum.
If you go now, I'll never see you again!
Don't you take one step.
The accident was caused by speeding.
He rushed because of me.
If it hadn't been for my birthday,
they'd still be alive.
Humans tend to blame themselves
when misfortune strikes their loved ones.
I know it's absurd.
Yet,
I think to myself time and time again,
"If only I hadn't rushed him."
"If only I had gone with them."
You said I should let you know
if I needed anything, right?
There's something I need.
I want you…
to stay next to me.
So never say
you're going somewhere
far away alone again.
I know I wasn't dreaming
when you said that to me.
I'll grant your wish.
I'll never leave you
no matter what happens.
Promise me.
Do-hee.
That's really hard to believe.
On top of all the talk
about powers, deals, and whatnot,
a demon protects you like a guardian?
People would think you're crazy.
You saw it yourself, didn't you?
That's why I'm so confused.
But why did the culprit
come after you again?
You've given everything up,
including the inheritance.
Maybe the culprit isn't after money
or the chairperson position
but just wants me dead.
By the way,
Noh Suk-min came to see me.
He did?
What for?
He made an investment offer
out of nowhere.
Knowing him,
I'm sure he has an ulterior motive.
Should I go talk to him?
What?
I'll just casually sound him out.
You know I'm good at looking innocent.
I thought it was just a little sprain,
but here we are.
Tennis is dangerous, I tell you.
That's why you should work out regularly.
You're right.
Anyway, what's Do-gyeong up to?
I can't reach him.
He's on a business trip. Why?
Just because.
I haven't seen him in a while.
I'll be honest.
I'm here to join your side.
Is it too late?
I actually went to see Do-hee today.
You did?
What did you talk about?
That we should get along
since we're family.
It seems like
she's still holding a grudge.
Please put in a good word for me.
I will.
I hope we can all get along.
Seok-hoon.
This isn't the bathroom.
The door was open.
Come have some dessert.
Okay.
Do-hee.
I'm leaving Suk-min's house now.
Something's definitely off.
He said Do-gyeong was on a business trip,
but he seemed to be hiding something.
And I saw something suspicious.
Which is?
A green book
that says "Demon" on the cover.
JIU-JITSU 2 DAN, NOH DO-GYEONG
Get me
some painkillers.
Get me morphine or something!
You must be in a lot of pain.
I'm fine.
This isn't my first rodeo.
Is Do Do-hee dead?
You…
failed to prove yourself.
Turn yourself in
once the urgent care is done.
-Father.
-That'll reduce your sentence.
You understand
the gravity of your crimes, don't you?
You killed your grandmother for money
and attempted to kill Do-hee,
who's also like family.
But I won't give up on you.
Because you're my son
until the day you die.
This is where the book is supposed to be.
This will take forever.
It's Gi Kwang-chul's phone.
He saw my face. He'll come for me.
Let's find Noh Do-gyeong.
REQUESTED CCTV FOOTAGE NEAR THE SCENE
Who on earth could be behind all this?
From murder to arson…
A psycho, for sure.
How can I help you?
Mr. Noh Do-gyeong?
I'm the one…
who killed them.
Pardon?
Mr. Cha,
Gi Kwang-chul,
and my grandmother.
I killed all of them.
What is Noh Do-gyeong doing here?
It was me.
I'm the one who killed…
all of them.
Do Do-hee.
Noh Do-gyeong.
Let me ask you one last time.
Was it really you?
Did you order Gi Kwang-chul
to kill Madam Ju
and me?
Answer me.
Grandma…
didn't die at Gi Kwang-chul's hands.
Then who?
Are you saying you killed her?
It wasn't me.
I just followed orders.
Who gave you the orders?
The devil.
The devil lives within me.
I was just following the devil's orders.
Give it to me straight.
Did you kill Madam Ju or not?
Answer me!
Tell the truth!
There's no point, Do-hee.
Make a deal with me.
I have a wish.
I want to torch the world
so that everyone will burn to death.
Perhaps burning in hellfire
will finally make them repent their sins!
It's hot!
Help!
Please!
Stop!
Please make sure this doesn't get out.
I feel devastated as his parent,
but this is the right thing to do.
I'll never forget your kindness,
Commissioner General.
Yes.
Tell people
that he's on a long business trip.
When will you
get him out?
He's unwell.
He won't last long in there.
Since when do you care so much about him?
He killed people.
His own family at that.
Should I hold you responsible
for giving birth to and raising a monster?
I'm sorry, honey.
It's all my fault.
It all came to nothing.
It makes me even more upset.
He killed Madam Ju
because of his mental illness?
So what if he's crazy?
He's running away from his crimes.
If his condition is as claimed,
he'll be put into custody
for treatment soon.
Did he look like he was faking it
for a reduced sentence?
It wasn't fake.
It was real.
Let's wait for the results
of his psychiatric evaluation first.
Mr. Jeong.
Let's go grab a drink.
MIRAE F&amp;B
Your bones won't heal if you drink.
Humans frustrate me.
Mr. Jeong.
Do you love Do-hee?
Can you believe what the devil says?
I'm doing my best to believe you.
I've always disliked humans.
No, it'd be more correct to say
I've loathed them.
Do-hee is human too.
She is.
That's why
I'm starting
to adore humans.
Except for you.
What brings you here?
I'm not here to apologize.
I didn't think you were.
But I guess you are.
Now that you're here, let's celebrate.
No one died,
and Gu-won got his powers back.
Just say it.
Chew me out all you want.
I've been going after someone
a lot worse than you,
so I have no anger left for you.
I heard
the culprit got caught.
I didn't expect to feel this way.
I wonder if this is
how revenge is supposed to end.
Pull yourself together
and go back to your normal life.
So that Director Jeong can relax.
You never change, Ms. Jin.
The man Do-hee married
isn't just some regular bad guy
but the devil.
What's more ridiculous
is that I somehow feel reassured
by the fact that you're by her side.
Is that so?
Do you feel reassured?
Then please stop showing up.
I don't want to see you anymore.
I can't do that.
I'll keep showing up all the time
and make sure you're being good to her.
Don't forget I'm keeping an eye on you.
It's exactly the same as the last time.
You sound so threatening.
You scare me so much
that I can't even sleep--
Also,
show some respect.
I'm your senior
in the family tree.
You're not even her real cousin.
Cheers.
Before I met Director Jeong,
my life was a living hell.
When that hell crumbled down,
his face was the first thing I saw.
He's…
like a mother bird to me.
I know it sounds crazy,
but I was envious
that you could make a sacrifice for him.
I understand you.
He's like that for me as well.
Don't empathize with me.
I don't want you to be such a nice person.
It makes me feel…
It makes me look bad.
To be clear, that wasn't an apology.
For crying out loud!
Listen.
If you ever hurt Do-hee,
I'll become a priest…
and exorcise you, Jeong Gu-won.
How come everyone in this family
becomes a mess when they're drunk?
My Do-hee…
needs to be happy.
She…
has to be happy.
Don't worry.
I'm ready to risk all
for her happiness.
Keep your word.
If you don't,
I'll chase you…
to hell.
-You scared me.
-Sorry.
I was too tired to use the door.
It seems like Ju Seok-hoon
is actually jealous of you, not me.
He likes me way too much.
Did you drink?
No.
I smell alcohol.
Drink only when you're happy.
If you drink because you're sad…
it makes me even sadder.
I said I didn't drink.
Did you drink?
Do you want some tea?
Sure.
Do I smell like alcohol?
Here's a gift.
Open it up.
You must have erased
the memories of that woman
because they tormented you.
Two people entangled in fate
are meant to be reunited
in one way or another.
Because fate always repeats itself.
I killed…
you.
The company would take a huge blow.
So please keep a lid on this matter.
Did he really not know
what Noh Do-gyeong was up to?
You knew everything, didn't you?
You're the real evil one.
When I was human, I killed people.
A lot of people.
That must be why your tattoo transferred.
So that the misfortune could strike again.
Our encounter wasn't a coincidence.
What kind of person were you?
I was in love with someone.
Her name was Wolsim.
Subtitle translation by: Min-jin Kim