[Baek-jeong breathes deeply]
Give me four days
and I can arrange the flight.
[tense music playing]
So, where are we going?
I'm thinking maybe Thailand or Vietnam,
but it might be easier for you in Thailand
because you know people there.
Yeah.
I'll go through and make the arrangements.
I'd also recommend
some S-class bloodhounds.
If you have three,
then that should get the job done.
That is
if you're trying
to kidnap Kim Gun-woo's mother.
How much?
300 million each. So 900 million.
[chuckles softly]
[Man-bae] You're wanted
and we don't have much time.
We have to do this the right way.
It's a
necessary investment.
S-class is special,
I promise you with my life,
because they'll do the job right.
Get us two, would ya? You're number three.
I understand.
[music fades]
-[phone buzzing]
-Who's that?
It's just my mother.
Then take it.
-Hey.
-[mother] Where are you right now?
-Why?
-Min-a got hit by a car.
What? How bad is it?
-Where are you?
-The ER at Seonkuk University Medical.
-Hurry up and get here.
-Got it.
[tense music playing]
My daughter was hit by a car.
They're at the hospital.
Go then.
[breathes shakily]
[tires screeching]
Show me your ID, please.
[Tae-geom breathes shakily] Just a second.
-And the name of the patient?
-Yun Min-a.
Okay, come on in.
Room's around the corner and to the left.
[panting]
Min-a.
Oh, Dad!
I need you all in position.
Are you okay?
Huh?
Listen to me.
Please stop doing this.
[gasps]
Tae-geom. Tae-geom!
That's enough. Hey, stop!
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Put the guns down.
-Put the guns down.
-Min-a.
Close your eyes and hold on tight.
[Gang-yong] It's all right. Put them down.
Hey! Put them down. It's okay.
It's okay.
Tae-geom, hey.
We're not gonna hurt you.
Let's just talk.
I promise, I'm really just here
to talk to you.
[sighs]
I also have a young daughter.
From one dad to another,
let's just talk about it.
[water running]
[suspenseful music playing]
Sir, what brings you in?
A guest sent by your uncle
has arrived, sir.
[music fades]
I want to thank you for coming here.
Nice to meet you. I'm Choi Sin-hyeong.
[tense music playing]
Hmm. I know the name's a bit unusual.
It's a code name I go by.
[tense electronic music playing]
BLOODHOUNDS 2
[music fades]
If they were to bring you in, you'd get
a life sentence or the death penalty.
If you help us, I'll do my very best
to get you the life sentence.
-[uneasy music playing]
-And what would be the point of that?
If you're sentenced to death, you won't
be able to have visitors or seek parole.
But with a life sentence,
it could be possible to get parole,
assuming that you're good.
[sighs]
Yun Tae-geom, sir.
I mean, bro.
Didn't you start working under
Im Baek-jeong to provide for your family?
[chuckles] Well, then, you should do
whatever it takes
so you can live
to protect your mother and daughter.
Your family? They're never gonna give up
on you, no matter how much you screw up.
And your mother?
That woman would do almost anything
to save her child, even if it kills her.
You know that. And your daughter?
Hey, man, your daughter, I bet she'd wait
her whole fucking life just to see you.
But man, "the point?" [scoffs]
You can't see the point? Is that it, huh?
Is that the type of dad that they need?
Fine, then.
Be that guy.
Tae-geom, please.
It's not over until it's over.
We could still do more for each other.
I'm sure of it.
[tense music playing]
So, how about you join us?
[Tae-geom exhales]
Keep my family safe from Im Baek-jeong.
I promise you that.
[exhales]
What do you want me to say?
Well, first, where is Im Baek-jeong?
He's on the move,
aboard his yacht on the Han River.
If I contact him,
he'll tell me the pickup point.
The yacht could be docking
at one of three positions.
He's a smart guy.
How about we raid them tonight?
If by chance we fail to arrest him,
won't Tae-geom be in danger?
How about we maintain his cover
and wait for the right opportunity?
We could. You're right.
But, um, how did he know
we would be raiding the Entra Hotel?
I believe he was informed by an employee.
[exhales]
Lots of people in his circle, then?
Yes.
Who's organizing all this for him?
That's what I need from you.
Could it… could it be a cop?
There's a guy called Lee Dong-hyeon.
He was an NIS agent.
Lee Man-bae, right?
His actual name is Lee Dong-hyeon.
Is he the one
who gave the order to kill Gi-na?
Yes.
So, who in the police force
does he control?
I'm not sure yet.
I know for sure there was more than one.
I could hear that much
from his phone call.
He's a meticulous man.
Then it's possible he could have heard
about the wanted alert.
Lee Dong-hyeon's looking
for a private plane.
I'll bet you he's going to Thailand.
He couldn't do that with a warrant though.
He's the kind of man
that would make it happen.
[scoffs]
Our goal
is to capture Kim Gun-woo's mother
and take her to Thailand.
Im Baek-jeong wants
to fight Kim Gun-woo again.
So he plans to kidnap his mother
to lure him in.
For ransom money?
It seems that Baek-jeong
has a more personal reason.
I think he believes he lost to Kim Gun-woo
in that previous fight they had.
Because viewers all over the world
rooted for Kim Gun-woo to win.
So while everyone's watching,
Kim Gun-woo's going to be killed.
Gun-woo's gonna what?
There are a few ways to fight in the IKFC.
One of those is a death match.
They fight until one of them dies.
That's the fight
that makes the most money.
So kidnapping Gun-woo's mother.
How's he doing it?
Dong-hyeon is paying S-class bloodhounds.
What's that?
They're professional killers for hire.
The S-class means that Dong-hyeon's people
are as deadly as they could be.
So then, do you think he also knows
where Gun-woo's mother is staying?
I don't have a clue.
It wasn't ever mentioned?
No.
[Gang-yong sighs]
[phone buzzing]
PRESIDENT
Im Baek-jeong?
Let's tell him that Min-a hurt her head
and she's waiting for a scan right now.
[Tae-geom] Sir.
[Baek-jeong] How is she?
She hit her head pretty bad on the ground.
She's gonna get a CT scan.
-[Baek-jeong] Wrap it up and get back.
-Okay.
[sighs]
[Gang-yong] Tae-geom.
[tense music builds]
[music fades]
-[nurse] Kim Jin-su, please come in.
-[man] Okay.
The wound is healing well,
so you don't have anything to worry about.
I appreciate it.
How's your shoulder?
Um, it hurts a little.
Could I see it?
[Gun-woo winces]
Do you need painkillers?
I'll be okay.
[doctor] All right, then.
Min-beom.
How's it going?
This room is so small.
You want me to upgrade you?
Oh, no, this room's already
too much for me, but thanks anyway.
I'm going to the hospital
to visit Gang-yong.
-Could you let me come?
-No, you shouldn't.
I'll talk to him and call you.
Just rest up.
Okay.
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
[breathes deeply]
[mysterious music playing]
Seul-gi, have you thought
about your code name?
I haven't thought of anything yet.
You know, your look is delicate,
so it's important
that you pick a strong name.
Something like… Jung Hwa-gi.
Jung Hwa-gi?
-You don't like it?
-It'd be an honor.
I'm just joking.
-[exhales]
-[Sin-hyeong] What kind of name is Hwa-gi?
How about Kang Ryeok-han?
Ryeok-han?
Mm.
Incredible.
I'm good at making code names.
[phone chimes and buzzes]
Hello?
-The meeting's about to start.
-[Sin-hyeong] All right.
[tense music playing]
HONG MIN-BEOM
PRESIDENT OF IIL GROUP
We'll have two chances.
When they come to kidnap Gun-woo's mother.
And when they get off the yacht
to flee abroad.
Is this person trustworthy?
Yun Tae-geom?
-We'd say he's worthy of your trust.
-Hmm. I agree with that.
How about Gun-woo's mother? Is she safe?
[Gang-yong] Well, we did
talk about that too.
Where she's at now is the safest.
Woo-jin and Woo-jeong
will stay at the hotel
and they have guards to keep her safe.
[Min-beom] So if they're after his mother,
does Gun-woo know?
He doesn't know. Gun-woo wouldn't
think twice about leaving the hospital.
Probably, yeah.
I'd like it if he could just focus
on his recovery.
I believe we can ensure
his mother's safety.
It'll be more dangerous
if Gun-woo fights in his current state.
[poignant music playing]
So…
what do we do once we catch 'em?
Hmm?
[chuckles]
Punish them to the fullest legal extent.
That doesn't feel like enough.
I'm still anxious
with Kim Myeong-gil behind bars.
We need something… more.
So then how do you wanna deal with it?
[Min-beom] Could you excuse us?
No, Gwang-mu, it's okay.
It's okay. Just say it.
[music fades]
I want him dead.
[tense music playing]
My uncle
assigned some agents to me.
[Gang-yong] What kind of agents?
Black ops.
[exhales] This issue is ours. There's
no reason for the NIS to get involved.
-Well, can you kill these guys?
-[Gang-yong] Min-beom.
We have to… let them
spend the rest of their lives in jail,
reflecting on what they've done,
and return all that stolen wealth
back to society.
Do you understand?
I need to see these stupid fucks gone.
You know that isn't justice.
I have people.
Min-beom, we need to be
on the same page about this.
Then I'll do it my way.
[music fades]
You should know, my dad won bronze
at the Barcelona Olympics,
so I asked him if he happened
to know of a guy named Im Baek-jeong.
Apparently, Im Baek-jeong
was a student to his friend.
Whoa.
He remembered him because he said he was
ambidextrous and had a really good hook.
According to my father, everyone
expected him to become a world champion,
but he's a piece of shit, I guess,
and he totally ruined it for himself.
Mm.
So then, I asked him some more about it
to see if he might be in touch
with the coach who taught Im Baek-jeong.
I mean a coach is the person who would
know almost anything about his boxer.
Go-to moves, weaknesses, all his steps.
That's right. I bet that you'd know
all of my weaknesses.
I, um, watched the video of you fighting
Im Baek-jeong over and over again.
I was thinking about
what kind of advice I could give you
to help you beat him in a fight, and…
[sighs]
I don't think I'm a good enough coach.
I'm at a loss for answers.
I promise it's not your coaching.
I don't know if I've seen an ambidextrous
fighter that could change up his stance.
I just couldn't keep up with him.
Well, his left jab
looked super strong and heavy.
It was. Also, that right hand's fast.
Honestly, I can't really remember
how I fought.
[poignant music playing]
Yeah, so, Gun-woo, how about
we go and get you trained by that coach?
You know, the one
who taught Im Baek-jeong?
This coach could know
the method that might beat Im Baek-jeong.
-Good idea.
-Is it?
I want to win.
[music fades]
Argh. Ow.
-I'm okay, I'm okay.
-What are you doing?
Huh?
-There's food.
-Oh.
-[So-yeon] Eat slowly.
-[Gun-woo] Hmm.
Here.
[gentle music playing]
I don't want you guys to be
getting into something dangerous.
It just breaks my heart
when you guys get hurt.
Don't worry too much, Mom.
How can I not worry
when you're hurt like that?
I'll take better care of him, Mom.
Go ahead.
-Is there any kimchi?
-Just eat your food.
[Gun-woo] Mm.
Let's grab those kimchi noodles
from the convenience store afterwards.
-Pretty much the same thing.
-Let's do that.
[chuckles softly]
Damn, this egg tastes better cold.
[So-yeon] I used
the entire carton of eggs.
Don't eat too fast.
-[Gun-woo] Hmm.
-[So-yeon] Here.
[music stops]
We are currently divided into two teams
that are working in two shifts.
As of now, both Team A and Team B will be
staying on the 16th floor of the hotel.
If we encounter a situation,
both teams can respond together.
So then, how many people is that?
There are a total of 12 personnel.
Uh, you can vouch for their skills?
Yes, you don't have to worry.
Ah.
[tense music playing]
Uh, when…
When we take down Im Baek-jeong,
will the Major Crimes Unit be enough?
No, not at all.
Should I call the mobile unit?
Uh, that's not what I meant.
We still don't know who took the money
from Im Baek-jeong, and it's worrying.
[Gang-yong sighs]
Mr. Min, would you like me
to get some Marines?
It wouldn't work.
Oh, yeah. [exhales]
What about the Green Pine Tree Club?
Oh.
Yoon Han-gu, the sergeant?
Is Han-gu in Suwon currently?
Yeah. Baek-jeong's money
shouldn't have gone out that far so…
[snaps fingers]
Okay, I'll reach out to him.
[music stops]
[ominous music playing]
[Man-bae] Hey.
Hey, Diego.
You sure know how to pick a place to meet.
Happy birthday, Captain.
I asked for US dollars.
I'm sorry. I didn't have enough time.
I'm gonna need an extra 10%
when we get to Bangkok.
[tense music playing]
Yeah, fine.
Wednesday, 3 a.m.
[Diego] See you in Cheongju.
Yeah. Okay.
Understood.
Let's get the stitches removed
tomorrow at 10:00.
I'll handle it, sir.
Two nights from now,
Gun-woo's mother will go to the airport.
Say goodbye to your daughter.
It's gonna be a while.
[sighs]
Yes.
[music fades]
[suspenseful music playing]
Han-gu, thanks a lot.
Anything for family.
This is the Violent Crimes Unit.
-[Gang-yong] Hi.
-He's our head detective.
-[Gang-yong] Thank you for coming.
-Nice to meet you.
The owner of the veterinary clinic,
Moon Dong-jo,
has served three prison terms for
manufacturing and distributing narcotics.
He's been practicing illegally
since his license was revoked in 2022.
Here are photos from the site.
Now, let me explain the mission.
Team 1 will wait
at the back door of the clinic,
Team 2 at the restaurant,
and Team 3 at the salon.
Headquarters will give a signal to move in
once the suspect enters the clinic.
Suspects may try to escape
through the back door of the clinic.
Team 1, be as vigilant as possible.
Now, some key info.
Trust only the people in this room.
If you see any unexpected backup,
be on your guard.
It's possible there are cops
who've been bought.
Let's work together and show them all
what great cops are really made of.
[all] Yes, sir!
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
Oh shit. Motherfucker.
[sighs]
MOON DONG-JO VETERINARY CLINIC
[Gang-yong] Team 1,
you're in position, right?
Team 1, in position.
Team 2?
Team 2, copy.
[Gang-yong] Team 3?
[Han-gu] All clear.
[music subsides]
Vehicle approaching. Stand by, stand by.
[car approaches]
[suspenseful music playing]
-[device beeps]
-Action!
-[man 1] Let's go.
-[man 2] Go, go, go!
[tense music playing]
[grunts]
-[man 2] Freeze! Don't move!
-[man 1] Get him!
[man 3] Police!
-[man 2] Get his ass!
-[man 4] Come out!
Shit.
[men grunting]
[man 5] Im Baek-jeong.
Put your hands in the air.
-[music intensifies]
-[men grunting]
[man 6 grunts] Ugh! Ugh! Ugh! Ugh!
[groaning]
[man 1 groans]
[man 5] You fucking bastard!
-[knife slicing]
-[man 5 groans]
Son of a bitch!
Stay still!
[knife slices]
[screams]
[Taser rattles]
Shoot his ass!
[wheezes]
-[Baek-jeong groans]
-[man 3] Get him!
[Han-gu] You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything that you say
can and will be used against you.
Now, get up!
[music stops]
Don't fucking move.
Stay right there.
I'm Min Gang-yong.
I'm gonna make sure that you rot in jail.
[gentle music playing]
[Mr. Moon claps] Yes!
Yeah!
-[sighs deeply]
-[door slides closed]
[tense music playing]
[shuddering]
[man] What are you doing?
Tell me what're you doing!
Why should I go on doing this?
[exhales]
How much you want, huh?
Five Bitcoins. Got it?
-You want 500 million won for this?
-Yeah.
[scoffs]
[chuckles]
Shit!
-I sent it.
-[phone buzzes]
Thank you for the payment.
[sirens wailing]
BLOODHOUNDS : SEOUL
-[phone rings]
-[man] Son of a bitch.
Oh, just hit it.
STAREX FROM CLINIC TO POLICE
EXTRACTION, 200 MIL
Let's go make some money.
It's 200 million. Hurry up!
Let's fucking go!
[phone chimes]
[chuckles]
[phone beeps]
[phone buzzes]
FROM MOON DONG-JO VETERINARY CLINIC
STAREX VAN TO NATIONAL POLICE AGENCY
SAVE MY COLLEAGUES, 200 MIL
MOON DONG-JO VETERINARY CLINIC
[suspenseful music playing]
[detective] What's that?
What's going on?
-Ah, shit!
-[horn honking]
Fucking hell.
[engine revs]
-[horn honking]
-[detective groans]
[tires screech]
Hey, get out of the fucking way!
[passing car horn blaring]
Whoa, shit!
[grunts]
-What now?
-Let's just get out of here.
Requesting backup here at Jinho Bridge.
Car accident. Car accident.
[tense music playing]
[detective] Shit. Shit.
[men bellowing] Ah!
-[man 1] Come on! Come on!
-Open it! Get the fucking door! Come on!
-[man 2] Yeah!
-[man 1] Open the fucking door! Get out!
[man 3 yelps]
[man 4] Come on. Get in there. Let's go!
-[groans]
-[Taser rattles]
Oh shit.
Come here!
[engine revs]
[men scream] Agh!
[gasps]
[men grunting]
[groaning]
Stay out of it!
Son of a bitch!
[men straining]
[yells]
Let go, you little bitch!
[man 2] Motherfucker!
-[Taser rattling]
-[Baek-jeong yells] Agh!
[Baek-jeong groans] Agh! Agh!
Get me out of these. I can help you.
Han-gu, help him.
Get Baek-jeong.
-[detective] Round 'em up!
-[man 3] Get up!
[Baek-jeong] Shit.
Oh, fuck.
[detective] Don't move.
Stay still, you bitch.
[ominous music playing]
[all grunting]
-[stabbing]
-[groans]
[stabbing continues]
[both straining]
[Tae-geom grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
-[Taser rattles]
-[Baek-jeong yells]
[panting]
[gasping]
[knife slicing through air]
[knife slices]
[man 5] Shit.
-[man 5 yells]
-[Tae-geom grunts]
[both straining]
[Tae-geom grunts]
-[bones crack]
-[man 6 yells in pain]
[groans]
[both grunting]
[growls quietly]
[Gang-yong groans]
Fuck you, you little…
Who the fuck do you think you are?
[grunts] Dumb motherfucker!
Die, you dumb motherfucker!
[blood squelches]
[music fades]
Hey!
Come on.
Yes.
Open it.
[tense music playing]
[distant grunting, shouting]
[gagging] Agh!
[groans]
[grunts]
[Mr. Moon grunts weakly]
[man 5 screams]
[yells]
[Tae-geom yells]
[squelching blows]
[groans]
[somber music playing]
[Tae-geom groans]
[groans]
I… will make sure your daughter dies.
[growling]
[Baek-jeong spits]
[Tae-geom howling]
[bones crack]
[Baek-jeong breathes heavily]
SWAG S
[music stops]
Yes?
Grab Gun-woo's mother.
Yes.
[tense music playing]
[tires screeching]
Gun-woo's mother's room key.
[computer beeps]
[keyboard clacking]
[phone buzzing]
I sent it.
[chuckles softly]
Please go easy on Ji-uk.
Don't worry about him.
[engine starts]
[music fades]
[suspenseful music playing]
[device whirring]
-I'm all better now. I'm okay.
-[mouse clicking]
NO INTERNET ACCESS
[gasps]
Get ready.
Stay in formation.
Gyeong-nam.
[batons click]
[knocking on door]
Call the police.
And don't come out, no matter what.
-[men grunting]
-[dramatic music playing]
[guard 1 groans]
-[guard 2] Get up.
-Yeah!
Dumb shit.
Oh!
Oh, yeah, we're here
at the Yeongdeungpo Marriott Hotel.
[knife slices]
[yells]
[gasps]
Whoo!
[grunts]
[knife slices]
[men roar]
[groans]
[exhales]
[exhales] Don't do it, Woo-jin.
Mom.
[guard strains]
[whimpering]
[both straining]
[music fades]
[dramatic music playing]
[yells]
[roars]
[groans]
[music fades]
[suspenseful music playing]
-[snarls]
-Come on!
[huffing]
[In-beom yells]
[groans]
-[yells]
-[Woo-jin groans]
[In-beom yells]
[In-beom growls]
[In-beom snarls]
[choking]
[Woo-jin gagging]
[music fades]
[dramatic music playing]
[chokes]
[gagging]
[music fades]
Would you stop hitting him?
Please stop it.
I'll just go with you.
-I'm begging you. I'll go with you.
-[Woo-jin gags]
[laughs]
[Woo-jin chokes]
-[Woo-jin wheezes]
-[So-yeon gasps]
[Woo-jin gasping for air]
-[shuddering]
-[So-yeon] Woo-jin.
Not right now.
Please listen to me.
No, please.
[whimpering] You can't go.
Mom, I'll go instead.
Woo-jin…
[poignant music playing]
…I'm going to be okay.
Don't follow me.
[tearfully] No!
Mom!
Mom, wait!
Mom! I'll go. Mom!
No, Mom!
[echoing] No, Mom!
[dramatic music playing]
[music fades]
[tense electronic music playing]