=No Doubt In Us=
(Adapted from the Manman comic No Doubt in Us)
=Episode 4=
Xiao Jinyun has been
acting strangely lately.
So as the Empress.
Haven't you found this suspicious?
Xu Yu is simple-minded and not a threat.
As for Xiao Jinyun,
isn't your father investigating him?
Focusing solely on Xiao Jinyun
will only make you blind.
Xiao Jinyun matters most, not Xu Yu.
You don't understand her.
The messenger from the north
will arrive shortly.
It's best to ensure nothing goes wrong.
Then leave the task
of testing Xu Yu to me.
No matter how you test her,
please ensure she gets no harm.
The Empress
is of great use to us.
(Xiao Jinle)
No, this scent is completely wrong!
Get lost!
(Five years ago)
Sorry.
I just enjoy meddling in others' affairs
and despise people like you,
who could fight back
but just silently take a beating.
Whether you're courting death
or you just seek for punishment,
since I know it, I won't stand by.
Take it.
Not any good news?
Why come to report then?
Please calm your anger.
She was merely reporting
what she saw yesterday.
What matters now is His Majesty
staying in Fengyi Palace every night.
Even the Empress Dowager has become
much more lenient towards the Empress.
No wonder
Xu Yu gave me the Empress's Seal.
She wanted to use palace affairs
to tie me down,
allowing her to keep His Majesty!
Why couldn't you keep His Majesty?
You're the only one in the entire palace
carrying the imperial heir,
yet His Majesty doesn't go to see you?
His Majesty was never close to me.
Useless!
Consort,
if you wish to separate
His Majesty and the Empress,
I do have a plan.
General Chen resolved the grain
issue just like that?
General Chen and Chancellor Zhao
has been at odds in court,
but when it comes to wars,
they will do everything possible
to make the Ministry of Revenue
comply anyway.
Although that day you did not act
according to my instructions,
however,
you established my authority.
(Should I tell him about what I heard)
(in the Xunfang Pavilion?)
(Will he believe the Xu family?)
One more matter.
Greetings, Your Majesties.
Lady Tao, you are pregnant.
No need to bow.
Your Majesty,
why did you push me?
When did I ever push you?
Your Majesty.
My stomach hurts so much.
It hurts!
Your Majesty.
I did not push her.
Guards, summon the imperial physician!
Your Majesty!
Imperial Physician Feng.
How are Lady Tao and the unborn child?
Your Majesty,
Lady Tao's pulse is deep,
faint, and thready,
indicating lack of nourishment,
and unstable fetal signs.
She requires complete rest.
Don't worry too much.
She should be fine.
Mother.
You've wronged the Empress.
You've misunderstood her.
Xu Yu harmed the imperial heir.
How much longer will you shield her?
Mother.
Before you get the truth,
aren't you being too hasty?
If the imperial heir suffers any harm,
I will not let the culprit
go unpunished.
Now get back to your Fengyi Palace
and pray for Lady Tao
and the unborn child.
Mother!
I take my leave.
I'll go with you.
Your Majesty.
You should also spend some attention
on the other concubines.
The child Lady Tao carries
is my imperial grandson.
I will stay then.
Eunuch Qin.
Summon Xiao Jinming to the palace.
My Empress,
how can you spare the energy
to do it now?
News of Lady Tao's unstable pregnancy
has spread everywhere.
You'd better focus on
how to get yourself out of this.
What?
Do you also think it was my doing?
(It feels like Xu Yu is walking
on thin ice in the imperial harem.)
This matter definitely involves you.
Jinming.
You may leave.
Yes.
(Carefree)
If you weren't as beautiful as a fairy,
why would Jinyun
spend every night with you
and provoke jealousy among the consorts?
Otherwise, this heavy blame
wouldn't have landed on you.
Is that what you should say?
Sister-in-law,
why are you just like Jinyun?
Can't you use your brain?
Sister-in-law,
just poke me a few more times.
Jinming.
If you don't go handle something now,
Jinyun will face imminent disaster.
If this child had been born
to the Her Highness,
Your Majesty,
you would surely have been overjoyed.
I know I can't compare
to the Her Highness.
I only beg you
to spend more time with our child.
That way,
I will be fully content.
Rest well and don't overthink.
Did I accidentally press on your belly?
No, Your Majesty.
M-My belly...
It hurts!
Guards!
Get the imperial physician!
Your Majesty.
I am incompetent.
After the Empress collided with her,
the imperial heir couldn't be saved.
Your Majesty,
I bear you no grudge.
Why did you harm my child?
Your Majesty.
This concerns the imperial heir's life.
How should we handle this?
Mother.
I'd like to ask you a question.
Rumors say I caused Lady Tao's
miscarriage by bumping into her,
thus destabilizing her pregnancy.
Would I be foolish enough
to know the truth was exposed
and still keep harming her?
Isn't it like giving the evidence
of my crime to others?
Well...
Mother.
I believe the Empress.
This matter is indeed suspicious.
If it is suspicious,
Jiang Tang, Head of imperial physicians,
can uncover the truth with examination.
Jinyun, Mother.
Jiang Tang came back from his leave.
We've just examined the body.
Your Majesty. Empress Dowager.
(Jiang Tang,
Head of imperial physicians)
The child Lady Tao carried
died days ago.
What was delivered today
was inevitably stillborn.
Imperial Physician Feng
took Lady Tao's daily pulse,
yet failed to detect it.
You're lying!
Impossible!
How could I harm my own child?
Then tell me,
did I push you?
Or did you stage this to frame me?
The truth is, your child died long ago.
Imperial Physician Feng.
Do you have anything to explain?
Speak now!
Please spare me!
Have mercy!
Lady Tao discovered the fetus had died,
and tried to pin the blame
on the Empress.
She forced me to do so.
Lady Tao used the imperial heir
to frame the Empress,
doubly guilty, is banished
to the cold palace.
Imperial Physician Feng is imprisoned
to await trial.
Master.
Prince Xiaoyao has sent yarrow
from the Taihao Mausoleum.
The turmoil in the palace has subsided.
Prince Xiaoyao said he'll await
your comeback from seclusion tomorrow.
The Purple Star moves retrograde.
There's an omen
of the auspicious star and phoenix.
How interesting!
(Luo Hanying)
You love your child deeply,
but the person behind you
only sees him as a bargaining chip
and exploits him
merely to achieve his own goals.
I don't understand what you mean.
It was my own plan
to use the child to drag you down.
No one else is involved.
Is it worth it?
Yes.
You were born the daughter of a marshal,
and became the Empress
upon entering the palace.
While I must exhaust myself
trying to please everyone.
Usually, sincerity
can only come with sincerity.
Sincerity?
If His Majesty sincerely loves you,
how could he bear to let his Empress
be trampled by a mere consort?
Xu Yu.
How much sincerity
do you have for His Majesty?
Didn't you also marry him
for your family?
People like us
have never lived
a single day for ourselves.
Sincerity?
Sincerity is the least worthy thing
to be mentioned here.
What's wrong?
Don't cry! Don't cry!
Mother is here.
Don't cry!
(Xu Yu.)
(How much sincerity
do you have for His Majesty?)
(Didn't you also marry him)
(for your family?)
(Sincerity is the least worthy thing
to be mentioned here.)
(Lady Tao is wrong.)
(If there's only one who's sincere
toward me within the harem,)
(then it will only be Xu Yu.)
Your Majesty.
What's wrong?
Is something wrong with
the interrogation of Lady Tao?
No.
I just feel
it's good that you are with me.
Your Majesty.
Has something happened to Lady Tao?
You still care for her
despite her hatred toward you?
It's true that Lady Tao framed me.
But she genuinely cared for that child.
That was her own child.
How could she possibly harm him?
Moreover,
that is also your child.
Xu Yu.
My relationship with Lady Tao
isn't what you imagine.
I never have...
News!
Your Majesties.
The Grand Preceptor has come back.
Please go
to the Directorate of Astronomy.
♪Parting clouds
to pluck the waxing moon♪
♪Brewing a pot of bygone years♪
♪Chill flame, window shade,
console my grieving soul♪
♪Drunk through lifetimes
with no dreams returned♪
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
♪Returning to drift
through the mortal world♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪