(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
I slept with your friend behind your back. I lied to you over and over.
I love you, Dao, but back then it just—
Don’t say you love me. That’s disgusting.
Thanks for helping out.
Are you sure it’s okay for me to draw these?
I figured if someone finished them, my mom would be happy.
She’s not in pain anymore.
She’s just… not here anymore.
Direk.
What?
Are you immortal or something?
What the hell kind of question is that?
Are you going to die before me?
Can you wait until I die first?
Are you crazy?
Of course I’ll die first. I’m way older than you.
I’m not dying that easily.
You never know, Direk.
Damn it.
I really hate this, Direk.
Alright then.
I’ll let you die first.
If I end up dying, I’ll have someone take you out before me.
Okay?
Sure.
Let me ask you something.
Don’t you ever think about opening your heart to someone?
If I really die someday,
you’ll have no one left.
No.
I don’t want to get attached to anyone.
Honey,
our son doesn’t believe in love at all.
Do you think it’s because of us?
When you left,
I almost died too.
Is that why
he doesn’t want to fall in love?
Will I ever get to see him love someone before I die?
Hey.
Don’t tell anyone about what happened yesterday.
Especially that asshole North.
Why would I tell him?
Well…
In case he makes fun of me.
Why would he?
It’s not even funny.
Idiot.
Hey.
Maybe you should ask yourself what you find funny.
Anyway,
thanks.
For helping me.
Yeah.
You're really gone, Emma.
I used to think
that if you were really gone,
I’d be able to handle it.
But it’s not that easy.
If you believe I’m strong enough to move on,
then I’ll do it.
How did you know my mom was gone?
I don’t know.
Just a feeling.
That she’s in a better place now.
A better place?
Like where?
I don’t know.
I just know she’s somewhere better.
After that, I don’t know.
If you say she’s in a better place, does that mean she really is?
You’re wondering if she’s happy right now?
Yeah.
Do you think that’s true?
I don’t know.
What?
Damn.
You’re supposed to comfort me.
Like, “Your mom’s definitely happy,” or something.
I honestly don’t know if your mom is happy.
But what I do know is—
What?
Your mom
wants you to be very happy.
No matter what, she’s not here anymore.
The one who’s still alive
deserves to be the happiest.
If you keep being this sad,
how can your mom be happy?
So,
from now on, live as happily as you can.
You know what?
No one’s ever told me that before.
That’s because you’ve never shown anyone you’re hurting.
Who’s hurting?
Shut up, idiot.
Hey.
Hey, what’s wrong?
Wake up.
Hey.
Hey!
You okay?
Why did you suddenly pass out?
There were a lot of spirits at the cemetery.
And I’ve been using my powers a lot lately.
So?
Is there any guarantee
that you’ll be safe every time?
What if a ghost wants to hurt you?
What if one of those ghosts at the cemetery tried to hurt you? What would happen?
I could even die.
Shit.
Hey.
I’m sorry.
I shouldn’t have taken you to the cemetery.
It’s okay.
I wanted to go anyway.
And I don’t really want you to be alone lately.
I don’t get it.
Huh?
Why do you push yourself this hard?
It’s normal.
When I’m sick,
my spirit gets weaker.
I’ve had worse.
Besides,
Besides what?
I wanted to help as much as I could.
Well,
are you going back to sleep?
Let’s go home.
There are too many spirits here.
Yeah.
I saw it fall at the cemetery.
You’re seriously
so nice.
How are you feeling?
Better?
Yeah, a bit better.
You draw really well.
Just like my mom.
I saw your mom’s drawings.
So I tried copying them.
You’re good.
Is there anything you can’t do?
Why are you listening to this song?
No reason.
Huh?
I didn’t think about it.
It was at the top, so I played it.
Damn.
Should I be happy
that you listened to my song for that reason?
Your song?
Yeah.
I made it with friends in high school.
High school?
You made something like that back then?
Cool, right?
Why’d you stop?
We all went our separate ways.
As for me,
I just do it for fun sometimes.
But not much lately.
That’s a shame.
Why?
It’s a good song.
Are you hungry?
Yeah, I’m hungry.
Can you cook?
Give it a try.
There’s fresh food in the fridge.
The housekeeper stocked it.
Now I believe you can’t cook.
Is there any jam?
Yeah.
In the fridge.
I thought you could do everything.
Do you play music?
A little.
What do you play?
Guitar and keyboard.
Come play with me.
Hmm?
I’ve got a music room at my place.
Wanna play together?
What are you looking at?
That was cool.
Huh?
What you just played.
It was cool.
You’re really good.
You’re good at guitar too.
Teach me.
Drums, you mean?
Yeah.
What made you want to play?
It looks fun.
Come on.
How do I hold it?
Just try.
Wait, wait.
If you hold it like that, you’ll drop it.
I don’t know how.
Hold it like this.
Move your hand up.
Loosen your grip.
Lock it with your thumb.
Mm-hmm.
Then hit it slowly.
Okay.
Hey!
Sorry.
I zoned out.
Hello, Fah. What’s up?
Hey, go ahead and keep playing.
Yeah, what’s up, Fah?
What’s up?
That's my line.
You’re the one who called.
Uh...
Fah.
Can I ask you something?
What?
I mean...
When you liked your boyfriend,
how did you know?
Thit.
Yeah?
That’s a weird question.
Just answer me.
I just liked him.
He was cute.
I wanted to be with him.
Something like that.
That’s it?
You thought he was cute and wanted to be with him?
What does “cute” even mean?
I’ve never felt that before.
Wait.
Is this about you?
Huh?
Do you like someone?
Do I look that obvious?
Well...
You seem restless.
Or...
Do you like Dao?
No, Fah. You’re crazy.
I said no.
Shit, why would I like—
How long have you been standing there?
Just now.
You little—
Were you eavesdropping?
I was coming to the toilet.
Alright, I’ll call you later.
That reaction means I’m right, doesn’t it?
I don’t like him.
Are you crazy? I don’t like him.
Really?
Then why did you call?
Damn.
But...
Fah.
I just...
You what?
I...
Fuck.
You never thought
you’d be someone who could like another person, right?
You know me too well.
Are you living in my head or what?
Damn.
Honestly?
I don’t think it’s strange.
Love always seemed so far from you.
You know,
I never thought there’d be a day
you’d ask me about this.
Isn’t it weird, Fah?
I mean...
It doesn’t feel possible.
I’ve never cared about this stuff before.
Yeah.
But from what I see, he’s actually pretty interesting.
He suits you.
Not too much.
Not too little.
If you miss this one,
you won’t find another like him.
I don’t know, Fah.
I don’t even know how to act.
This is me, Fah.
Me. A guy like me.
Shit.
Alright.
I’ve got a simple question for you.
Between having him and not having,
which do you prefer?
You.
Why does it have to be you, huh?
What?
Hey.
Yea?
Your mom’s pictures.
Hey.
Did you draw all of these?
Some of them were almost finished by your mom.
I just added a few details.
Wait.
You’re with me all the time.
When did you even draw these?
Late at night. I couldn’t sleep.
So I found something to do.
I studied what your mom drew and tried to copy it.
It might not look the same.
Do you like it?
Yeah.
Uh...
Yeah, I like it.
It’s really nice.
Mm.
I’ll take a picture and show Direk.
Okay.
What’s wrong with you?
Is it pretty? Do you like it?
Direk, do you like it? It’s cute, right?
(Blocked)
What did you do to get blocked by your dad again?
I just texted him saying I missed him, that’s all.
That’s it?
Why the hell would he block you?
I don’t know.
Go tell him to unblock me.
You make it hard for me every time.
Alright.
That’s it. I’m heading back.
Why’d you rush back anyway?
Thailand’s doing better without you here.
I was afraid you’d miss me.
Pfft.
Yeah, that’s it.
Are you upset about something?
Hey.
That’s kind of a tough question.
I just saw you staring.
I was just looking.
You’re sitting right in front of me.
What else am I supposed to look at?
You’re pretty good to lean on, you know.
What do you mean?
I don’t know either.
Are you going to pick up Khun John?
Maew said he’d be back late.
So I thought I’d go back and sleep first.
Hey, are you sick or something?
You look tired.
Just tired from traveling.
Thit
No, man.
No way.
You think I’d like someone like that?
Oh.
Thit.
Hm?
- Yeah.
- You’re back?
Hey.
I was gone for a bit. What happened to you?
Hey, hey.
Damn.
Wait.
Shit.
Did Do really break up with you?
Yeah.
Why?
They say the more you contact spirits,
the easier it is for them to reach you.
What?
Lately, other spirits have been approaching me too.
One of them even hurt me.
And you know, I’m not that strong mentally.
The only solution is
I have to stop dealing with spirits altogether.
Oh.
So Do broke up with you.
Yeah.
Hey.
Hm?
I told him I was okay.
I was okay.
He just disappeared.
He won’t come even if I call.
Do you get it?
I miss him.
No matter what, she’s not here anymore.
It’s the ones who are still alive
who deserve to be happy the most.
If you keep being this sad,
how can your mom be happy?
I can’t do this, man.
Damn it, Meen.
Shit.
Why the hell did you come back so I can see you?
Yeah, I know.
Do would want you to be happy for sure.
Don’t cry.
He’d rather see you smile.
- What the hell is this?
- Who are you?
You jerk.
That hurts, asshole.
Get out of my friend’s body right now.
Meen.
I’ve never heard you talk like that before.
Who are you?
I just heard it from someone else.
It’s just a simple word that helped me.
I hope it can help you too, Meen.
I’ll smile.
I really will.
I’ll be happy for him too.
- Yeah.
- But give me some time, okay?
Yeah, I get it.
Stuff like this takes time.
Hey, Meen.
- Huh?
- Can I ask you something?
What?
When Do passed away,
you were really hurt, right?
Look at my face.
Of course I was. I cried like this.
And...
have you ever thought
that if it would end like this,
maybe it was better not to start?
Even if I knew he would die,
or if I had a time machine to go back,
I’d still choose him.
Why?
If it never started,
it wouldn’t hurt.
Doesn’t that mean one day it has to disappear anyway?
I don’t know.
All I know is,
without him,
I wouldn’t have made it through each day.
You know,
all these past years,
I never regretted being with him.
I’m even thankful to myself
for choosing him.
From now on,
even if he’s not here anymore,
those memories still make me happy.
Why...
are you asking me this?
A friend of mine
really likes someone.
He’s never liked anyone before,
but this one is different.
Once he fell for them,
he wanted to spend his whole life with them.
But he’s scared that one day, if that person disappears,
he won’t be able to handle it.
Your friend?
Yeah, my friend.
It’s not strange if he’s scared.
How much does he like that person?
Does he want them in his every day?
Or if he woke up tomorrow and they were gone,
would he be okay?
Try to imagine it.
If they suddenly disappeared,
would that be better?
I think
I’m not the only one who’s got it bad.
What are you talking about?
I told you, it’s about my friend.
Idiot, you’re so obvious.
Even a dog could tell.
Bottoms up.
Are you in love?
My friend is.
I don’t buy this love stuff. It’s nonsense.
Oh really?
Sorry.
Did I wake you up?
Are you leaving?
You already knew, didn’t you?
Thank you for everything, Daotok.
Yeah.
Please take care of Meen.
P’Fah and I will take John back to your room.
We don’t want you driving late at night.
Thanks, Maew.
No problem at all.
You’re back already?
Yeah, I’m back.
Dao’s back.
We missed you so much, Dao.
Heh, not me.
You’re the one who kept talking about him.
Oh?
You drink?
Whoa.
That’s strong.
Want some?
Nah, I’m driving.
You two, seriously.
The second you hear “bar,”
you come running.
Damn.
Hey, didn’t you say you came with a friend? Where are they?
I’m heading out first.
There.
- I’m leaving first.
- Meen, that’s enough, damn it.
How much are you gonna drink?
- Hi there!
- Go grab your own drink.
Cheers.
Hey.
You don’t even know each other and you’re already clinking glasses?
Nice one.
It’s more fun with a crowd like this.
Coming with just you
is boring as hell.
True. Want me to invite more people?
Sure.
- Go ahead.
- I’ll call Dao. Haven’t seen him in a while. Miss him like crazy.
Hey, no need to call him, North.
Why not?
Seriously, don’t call him.
I want to.
Damn it, I said don’t call him, North.
Why are you so pissed?
Did you two fight or something?
No.
Then why can’t I call him?
Come on, if he gets drunk I’ll take care of him.
I can carry him.
- I said don’t call him, North.
- Hey!
What the hell is your problem?
You must really hate my friend.
What did he ever do to you?
Yeah.
What did he do?
Someone like him wouldn’t hurt you.
He’s quiet,
and he’s a good guy.
Not a jerk like you.
He went to San Fran to help you.
Do you really hate him?
You don’t even know how to be grateful.
- You're not that great.
- Yeah, right.
Damn, he went all the way to San Fran for you.
Shit.
Wait.
Hey,
are you talking about Dao?
You know Dao too?
Well—
He’s my benefactor.
He helped me see my late boyfriend.
Hey—
Don’t tell me
your boyfriend is…
- The wall-scratching ghost.
- Yeah.
Holy shit.
Just talking about it makes me sad.
Didn’t you say you quit smoking?
It’s fine once in a while. North won’t mind.
Jo.
Yeah?
Have you ever felt like this?
Trying to get something out of your head
but you just can’t?
Yeah.
When?
When I tried to get over North.
So what did you do?
Nothing.
I just couldn’t.
But one day, you might lose him.
Will you be able to handle that?
No.
But if I didn’t have North,
I wouldn’t handle that either.
It might hurt even more.
Why, Jo?
Wouldn’t it be better if it never started?
You really think that?
Ask yourself.
Why should I?
So… who is it?
The one you came with?
Damn it.
Shit.
So it finally happened to you.
Yeah, damn.
I can’t believe this shit actually happened to me.
It’s so fucking messed up, you know?
Maybe it’s not that bad.
It is, damn it.
I still feel like shit right now.
Jo.
I never wanted to cross that line.
Arthit.
You already crossed it.
Otherwise you wouldn’t be overthinking like this.
You know what?
This shit’s so damn complicated.
These messed-up feelings.
I don’t even know how to act, Jo.
I’ve never felt anything like this before.
So what are you gonna do?
I don’t know.
Maybe I’ll try stepping back first.
I mean…
Maybe I just caught feelings ’cause we’re always together.
When I tried to move on from North, I thought the same as you.
That once I let go, everything would get easier.
When I really tried to move on,
I was just like you.
Drinking every day.
Talking nonsense all day.
Shit.
I don’t wanna end up stuck in a loop like you, asshole.
Maybe you won’t.
If you can really move on.
I can.
Yeah, I can, damn it.
I can handle it.
But if one day you realize you can’t step back,
then move forward right away.
Before it’s too late.
If someone like you falls for him,
maybe others stand a chance too.
Chug it. Come on, chug.
Arthit.
What the hell’s wrong with you?
I asked you to come cheer me up ’cause my boyfriend dumped me.
Why do you look worse than I do?
I need to get drunk.
So I can finally stop to think about this shit.
Hey.
What did you two go talk about?
Why’d he come back like this?
That guard dog.
Turned into a jealous dog.
Jealous of what the hell?
I’m not jealous of anything.
Good.
Then you’d better get over him fast before someone else claims him.
Because once that happens,
you might not even have the right to look at him.
I won’t even have the right to look?
Shit.
He’s my favorite view, damn it.
Yours?
Yeah.
Looking at him makes me feel good.
No one else enjoys the view like I do.
You sure about that?
North.
Yeah?
I heard your friend from Engineering
likes that kid a lot.
Which kid?
Daotok.
Shit.
What?
Why does it have to be my friend?
I’d like to know that too.
Why your friend?
What do you even like about him?
I’m telling you, don’t get your hopes up.
You’ve got no chance.
Yeah, I know, asshole. I’m trying, okay?
First love?
Yeah.
Honestly,
if you liked someone else,
I’d help you all the way.
But this is my friend.
I want my friend to meet someone good.
Damn it.
- Hey, North.
- Huh?
Which friend of yours?
The one who likes him.
A lot of them.
Daotok’s super popular.
- Guys ask for his Line every day.
- And what did you do?
- I just gave it to them.
- Just like that?
Why the hell would you give it out?
Engineering guys?
Besides their gear, what’s so great about them?
Hey, that’s not fair, P’Arthit.
I’m in Engineering too.
Oh come on, I’m in Engineering.
Don’t worry, Arthit.
Everyone in this world is better than you.
Damn it, Jo. Asshole.
You bastard, Arthit.
You’re freaking pathetic.
Look at me — I’m walking straight as hell.
Hey, are we at the room yet?
Thanks for walking me back, man.
- Are we there yet?
- Your keycard?
- Huh?
- Your keycard.
Your keycard.
It should be in my pants.
- Somewhere in your pants?
- Where exactly?
In my pants.
I don’t see it.
What about this?
That’s not it, idiot.
Shit. Damn it.
I lost my keycard again.
What should we do, P’Jo?
Daotok.
Can you help us out?
P’Arthit freaking lost his keycard.
Please?
Mm.
Fine.
Nice.
Ugh.
Can I take the bed?
Stop being picky.
Hey.
Dao.
What?
Engineering guys only have that gear thing going for them.
If you’re gonna choose,
pick a med student instead.
Trust me.
Hey, can you hear me?
Hey.
You’re sleeping so comfortably.
Leaving me freezing to death on the floor.
Hey.
Wow, sleeping in his room makes you that happy?
What are you talking about?
You’re not really over him, are you?
I’m serious, Jo.
Since when does someone serious go cuddle the person they’re trying to forget?
Huh?
How did you even know?
I guessed.
Are you serious?
You guessed right.
Oh?
You’ve done it before, haven’t you?
North and I were dating. What’s weird about that?
Then what are you to him?
His brother?
He wasn’t feeling well.
It was cold, so I hugged him.
Oh.
I see.
Jo, you asshole.
Damn it.
You never stop teasing me.
Seriously.
I’m not teasing you.
Hill once said
don’t approach someone with half-hearted feelings.
If you like him or not, be clear about it.
Right now your actions and your words
don’t match at all.
Honestly, Arthit,
you already know that.
Yeah.
Did you tell Tonfah yet?
About moving on?
Not yet.
Are you still going to tell him?
Maybe you don’t have to.
Jo.
But this time I’m serious.
I’m really going to move on.
Besides cuddling, what else did you do?
You tell me.
Did you sleep together?
What the hell, Jo?
Come on, it's possible if it were you.
- What kind of person do you think I am?
- A jerk.
Well...
He wasn’t feeling well.
I was scared he might die.
So I
took care of him a little.
I just didn’t want another ghost next door, that’s all.
I didn’t know this is how people “move on.”
See?
I tell you everything and you still tease me like this.
You’re contradicting yourself.
These things take time, don’t they?
Whatever. Take your whole life if you want.
Yeah, I know.
I'm not gonna use my whole life or anything.
I guess.
Hello, Khun Phuangthong.
I think a ghost is messing with me.
A ghost in your room?
Who did it?
What did it do to you?
I don’t know who did it.
It felt suffocating.
Like I was being hugged.
That’s really scary.
Did you do something to them?
No.
I haven’t even been in the room for days.
We’ve always been fine before.
Or maybe they’re upset we didn’t make merit for them.
Alright, I’ll make merit for them.
I’m going to the temple anyway.
Mm.
Please do it for me, Khun Phuangthong.
Tell me if anything happens.
Take care of yourself.
Yes, Khun Phuangthong.
Today is my first day of the semester.
Could you give me a blessing?
Good luck, dear.
I hope you encounter only good things.
May today be a good day for you.
Thank you.
That’s all for now, Khun Phuangthong.
Going to class?
Yeah.
Well,
Feeling better from cold?
Thanks for wiping me down.
Yeah.
How are you getting there?
By motorcycle?
Wait.
Uh—
I’ll take you.
You just recovered. You shouldn’t be riding.
It’s fine.
I’ll take you.
Hey, where do you study again?
Faculty of Science.
What did you say?
Science.
Say it louder.
Yeah.
You’re hugging me tight. Scared?
A little.
I don’t usually ride on the back of a motorcycle.
Oh?
Mm.
Thanks.
What time do you finish?
5 p.m.
Then you come to wait here.
You’re picking me up?
I brought you here. How else would you get back?
- I can walk.
- Are you kidding?
I’ll wait here.
Thanks for the ride.
Say it like you mean it.
I do mean it.
"Thank you," properly.
Say it.
Thank you.
Say my name too.
Thank you for the ride.
P’Arthit.
I like someone already.
- I’m trying to court him.
- It won’t be easy, P’.
If you’re trying to court him,
what’s so hard about it?
Just be myself. Be sincere. Be natural.
I’ll break down the door for real.
Maybe don’t be yourself.
Just be a little better, that’s enough.
Since I started courting you, how many points have I earned?
Zero.
Why do you like me?
That’s a question I don’t know either.
I just know it has to be you.
Well, zero—from having nothing at all.
From now on, I’m starting to count.