It's been two days
At least, I think it's been two days,
I now measure the day
I look at photos of us when we were happy,
Or the number of texts I've sent
Or my personal favorite,
by counting all the things
Maybe I should just go home,
No one hates me at home,
When the pendulum swings
I know it's gonna get me…
God, I can almost smell
Wait, I actually can smell
What?
Hello?
Hi, sister,
Oh!
I can't believe it, Thank you,
Tell me everything,
- After you take a shower,
I'm very fragile right now,
Good Lord! I am ripe!
- I'm so sorry,
- I'm gonna deal with it, Right now,
Ugh,
And then I fully accused Min Ho
- Okay, that's not great,
Um, but isn't this whole thing just,
Sure, One that proves
Someone unlike me,
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't know, I just… I've always thought
Like a K-pop star,
Okay, if that fool can't see how awesome
But I should have trusted him,
Hey, didn't he lie to you
And… and about the necklace?
Only because he was trying
the way our mom was
Then he should've trusted you,
Well, I don't even trust myself right now,
Like, I was wrong
and then I messed up my entire friendship
Okay, stop acting like your life is over,
Stop it,
You still have plenty of time left
And then you're coming
Speaking of which,
Not great,
Wait, what?
Ah, something like,
I'm at, like, 12 hours,
Kitty! We talked about applying early
I know,
"Who are you?"
Hello? I don't know
Okay, your pity party is over,
I had the entire summer
And you have, like, less than 24 hours
And I texted Jiwon,
Okay, fine, I can handle that,
I thought you were gonna
No, yeah, I'm totally gonna
But first, we have
You'd be giving up your dream,
Yeah, Honestly,
I was scared at first,
But when you told me
it was odd, but suddenly, I felt relieved,
I don't have any privacy,
it's too hard,
Once I tell my dad,
I know,
But fame isn't what I want,
Min Ho, I'm really sorry,
No, you should do what you want,
Thank you so much,
You were a great manager
Are you crazy?
You have to hold her to her contract,
I can't do that, Dad, Eunice is my friend,
This is just not right,
Then you're not right for this job,
I wanted to believe that you had
You're fired,
Sorry again for all the drama
Oh, no worries,
Did you figure out
Let's see,
Jin's ignoring me
and Marius, who normally
left me a really nice gift,
See my dilemma?
Kitty just got broken up with too,
She's done enough talking,
It's her big mouth
Yeah,
What do you think I should do?
You want to talk feelings with… me?
Yeah, um…
Were you happy with Jin?
I mean, I thought I was,
but part of me is wondering
because I was nervous
Mm,
Oh, it's my turn again? Well…
If Kitty had never come to KISS,
I'd have to spend the rest of my life
Right,
Can't know what's at the end of the road
Exactly,
Wait, Am I good at this?
Oh yes, Yes,
Truthfully, this reservation is
Hello?
Yisoo's craving Impossible again, huh?
- There's a reason that's the name,
I love this, Who designed it?
Um, that would be me, I thrifted the ties
You're submitting your designs
Me? No, I'm just an assistant,
So? Everyone who submits
- I wouldn't even know where to begin,
- Mm,
Do you want to make dinner reservations
- Ready to go?
Um, is this a date with Gigi noona?
No, First Kitty and now you,
Does everyone think
No, I don't think that,
I'm sorry about
I feel really bad,
You didn't make her accuse me of cheating,
- That was all her,
But for what it's worth,
It is what it is,
- Ready?
I can't believe how well you know Seoul,
It's such a great city, isn't it?
And the shopping?
I got tech for Dad, O'Sulloc tea
I also saw you got character socks,
And I know who those are for,
- Does that mean--
But Peter is coming to New York,
Because we are still 5,000 miles apart,
Well, I'm not gonna give up hope,
Mm, I don't know about that,
This is a pleasant surprise,
- How's the eye?
Thank you for the flowers,
Of course,
Look, I think we should talk
How you came back to KISS for me?
I know that was a lot,
And I definitely overstepped
Had,
I… Actually, I don't even know
Well…
I was just gonna go on a ride if…
What does it feel like
Not holding on to memories
'Cause everything's still
Not falling into place
Yuri, what's going on?
Are you okay?
Is this SpongeBob wearing a kilt?
No, it's supposed to be
I'm entering this fashion design contest,
I can draw, remember?
- I'm down to help,
- Yeah,
So, Yuri, are you excited for tonight?
Um, I've never been
- But it was sweet of you to set me up,
What now?
You remember Sophie?
I think her and Yuri
Yeah, totally,
I think I know what I'm wearing,
Absolutely,
- I'm thinking neutral shadow, Maybe pink,
So, you work for a book editor?
- I'm an editorial assistant,
She wants to be a writer, she's working on
I don't know about that,
Yeah, it's the upside of being single,
Are you gonna show it to your boss?
Oh no, God, no, I am too scared
- Hi,
Welcome!
- What would you like to eat?
One pajeon…
- Good with beef tartare?
And three yukhwae bibimbaps
Oh no, Can you take off
- So two yukhwae bibimbaps?
Okay,
- But you love yukhwae,
Oh, my boss is so afraid of salmonella,
She's pregnant,
Your Korean is getting
Um, so Kitty says that
I bet your halmoni is so, so proud,
Mm-hmm, Excuse me,
She and Imo-Halmoni
But she doesn't normally
Mm, I get it, My boss, she just,
- Your pregnant boss?
- Oh my God,
Part of why I thought Eunice was pregnant
was because Yuri and I found
And Eunice was never pregnant?
- No,
I can't tell
You know I aim to please,
Yeah, our old spot,
Unless you take
We've had lots of good hangs here,
but that doesn't all
I want another chance…
with you,
I'm sorry, was it your eye?
No,
Do you remember
Of course, Our sophomore year, Last day,
I remember asking you
You made me believe that we could,
And then you ghosted me,
But I came back,
And I came back for you, I've changed, Q,
Yeah, When you were finally ready,
Even though I had a boyfriend,
Not everything can be on your timeline,
Things are different now,
I've changed too,
And a lot of that is because of Jin,
So that's it, then?
You're not even gonna try?
We've been down this road before,
This is where it ends,
Pay attention
You seriously thought I'd enjoy this?
Ugh, Can we take a break? My hands are
Aww! If your nail breaks,
Forget the bill,
That's why I brought you here,
- I heard what happened with your dad,
It just felt nice to have him
He should, You are a good person, Min Ho,
- Tell that to Kitty,
I just can't get past it, The trust thing,
She says she was in her own head,
But I never made her feel like that,
It… doesn't mean she didn't feel that way,
Your whole world is intimidating,
- I mean, your own dad just fired you,
Look, I don't know what to do
that you don't need to take
Right, Then what?
I mean, you produced
Maybe your talents are bigger
Maybe, But without my dad's support,
You know, it's easy
But the riskier one
Wanna give it a go?
All right,
No, I cannot get involved, LJ,
I have overstepped
If I do it one more time,
No, okay, Kitty, I know you better
You are a good person
And Jiwon might
Help with what?
I found a positive pregnancy test
We think it might be yours,
And you don't have to say if it was,
What am I gonna do?
My halmoni and I fought so hard
and instead of proving
And now I've ruined my life and his too,
No, you have not ruined anything,
Have you told the father?
An unplanned pregnancy will be
Because he was unplanned himself,
It's Alex, isn't it?
Yeah, Uh…
We met at summer orientation,
He's so earnest, and that accent…
But I love him,
This is wonderful,
But his dad is my boss,
so we kept it secret
I'm so sorry, Kitty,
No, I… I've been such a hypocrite,
No,
I… I was so hard on you
when I was busy
No, It's okay,
I know this is scary right now,
but if I've learned
it's that you are brilliant and so strong,
And honestly, you're a total baddie,
And I'm sure that's why Alex fell for you,
And I know he's gonna be there for you,
And we're gonna be there too,
Thank you,
Thanks,
Hey, What's going on?
- You've seemed off all day,
Okay, um, I wanna be mature about this,
You setting my ex up
Because you still have feelings for her?
No, no, no, no, I just…
Yuri was my first love,
And I think
I'm sorry, I'm trying to be honest,
I know you are,
That's the healthiest way to break up,
What? No, I thought
- I didn't say I wanted to break up,
I deserve to be with someone
who's excited to see me
The way you are when you see Yuri,
Maybe I was setting Yuri up because,
deep down, I knew you felt this way,
But… if I'm feeling insecure
a little bit… jealous?
Maybe we're doing something wrong here?
Hey, what are you doing?
I just got an email from Seoul National,
I didn't get in,
Really? You're the first in our class,
Mm,
I was always worried I wouldn't be
I never even thought I wouldn't get in,
Yuri asked me the other day
Dream? You have one?
Mm,
I do,
Uh…
But it's a little crazy,
Is it music, by chance?
How did you know?
Last year you held yourself back
but you ended up doing really well,
I have an idea…
Wouldn't it be fun
It would be fun, of course,
It won't be easy,
What do you say?
Chalk, I'm sorry,
Okay, she's telling him,
Mm!
Wow,
To think Mom set up Jiwon's parents
and now you're bringing
I think if Mom could see
I know I am,
Do you really mean that?
Kitty, at 16, you flew across the world,
You learned a new language, and you built
How can you not see how amazing that is?
I mean, it's what you did
God, it was so hard for me to go,
I mean, I had never been on my own
I was so scared to put myself out there,
You're the brave one,
The leaps that you take
that's what makes you, you,
And your heart is
Thank you, sister,
Who am I?
For better or worse, I'm someone
When I'm lucky,
like my incredible family
But even when I've made mistakes
Stretched by an amazing city that
It's taught me things
Like how to show up for people
How to be open
Or how to pivot when relationships turn
It takes courage to leap,
but it also takes courage
and keep going, to grow,
But that's exactly what I intend to do,
'cause I know there's
I'm not done leaping yet,
I love it, Kitty,
If this doesn't get you in,
Thank you, For everything,
Okay,
Ah, okay, Here we go,
What's wrong?
Early decision feels so… binding,
Like, if I do get in…
I thought that's what you wanted,
Yeah, I love NYU, and I would be
and be closer to you and home, But…
Seoul has become such a big part of me,
And I can imagine myself staying here too,
I get that,
I mean, you built
And Min Ho's here,
I would be lying
if I didn't say a part of me…
Still hopes that we're… endgame,
The way I know you and Peter are,
I don't know what's gonna happen
But we can't just stop living our lives,
I think that we have to follow our hearts
and trust that it will lead us
Okay, here goes nothing,
- I love you,
Hi, sorry I'm late, I hope you weren't
Not too hard,
Not bad, yeah, She asked me out again,
You gonna go?
Yeah, she's nice,
And your girlfriend has good taste,
That's great, I'm happy for you,
Show me what you've been working on,
You remember this one?
Wait, no, You fixed SpongeBob,
- A little tweaking, but it's your vision,
Just hear me out, Please,
This summer, I was confused,
It was before you visited me,
I slipped,
But I'm not confused anymore, Jin,
You…
You are my person,
Can we please start over?
Maybe we can talk about
As long as there are
I promise,
I took the time
but the choice is clear, I choose you,
Down the road? What does that mean?
Nothing, That we…
We rode to our old spot, Let me finish,
That place, it made me realize
Q, I didn't need
or go on some romantic ride
- I know, and I'm sorry,
I used to be the guy
but I trusted you and I let you in,
I'll never make that mistake again,
I wish you could stay longer,
Me too, but I have to get back before
And you have to get to Korean Lit,
You know, you could distract your boss
I already did,
Wait, what? Are you serious?
Yeah,
I sent it last night,
I feel like I was just so scared,
like, everything would
Like the future,
New York, and I really do not know
But I can't not bet on myself,
And that is
I can't believe I'm going to be related
to a New York Times bestselling author,
I love you, Kitty,
I love you too, LJ,
Please don't make me fly
I'll try my best,
Okay, you're gonna be late, Go, go,
- Oh my God,
Yo, Min Ho!
Yeah, um…
Lara Jean,
Hi, Min Ho,
How's Kitty?
Honestly…
She's great,
I thought I was coming here to help her,
And as it turns out, at the end of this,
She's a really great person
Yeah,
She really is,
Just don't forget that,
Oh, Let me get that for you,
Thank you,
Only in silence and I fell for your
Waning sugar kindness
And I fell for your
But you needed to be touched
And I could tell your
Sickness had enough
Only in silence
And I fell for your
Waning sugar kindness
But you needed to be touched
And I could tell your
Sickness had enough