(All characters, places,
and organizations are fictional.)
(Children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 15)
(Missed Call)
(New Message)
(Messages)
(Director Shin, please text me
when you have a moment. Ba Ra.)
Director Shin, please text me
when you have a moment.
Ba Ra.
Hello, Director Shin.
- Where are you?
- I'm at the cafe by the hospital.
- You're at the cafe now?
- Yes. But...
I'd like to meet somewhere quiet.
It's a little noisy here.
Go on up to my place.
The door code is the same.
Did you forget? Want me to text it to you?
No.
You've been in Korea?
- Yes.
- But...
where?
I'll order something.
You haven't had dinner, have you?
I'm not hungry.
Should I make you something simple?
Did you get married?
No.
(Someone said they saw you...)
About the surgery you mentioned before...
I'll do it.
Please do it for me.
Do you want me to explain why?
- Change?
- Yes.
- Momo might not agree to it.
- Even if she doesn't.
I'll take full responsibility.
Are you not up for it?
All right.
(Nua General Hospital)
Have a seat.
I rushed over...
empty-handed.
Are you okay?
I just had a dizzy spell.
You still look good.
I do?
I saw Momo. She said she's happy.
Except that you're
a bit too obsessed with her.
That's why she's deliberately...
keeping her distance for a while.
We decided to get a divorce.
We're going to.
How could you just leave like that?
- Vertigo?
- I have a blood test tomorrow.
They think it might be anemia.
So you have to fast tonight?
I'm not really that hungry.
Why are you being so formal?
You're not even looking at me.
Did something happen?
No.
Someone...
said they saw you at a rest stop.
You were with an elderly woman.
That was probably me.
Did you meet someone?
I said I needed time back then.
Time to force feelings for you?
I wasn't forcing it.
Will you keep on staying at a distance?
My feelings haven't changed.
Nothing's changed.
We should have been honest...
and talked everything out sooner.
- What about a caregiver?
- I don't need one.
I can still get around on my own.
Then I'll stay with you.
As Momo's world-famous husband?
You're angry with me,
aren't you?
I lost sight of the young girl
you used to be.
I didn't even make an effort.
Please, stop being upset.
I'm here to check your blood pressure.
You can go now.
Your number.
I'll do anything to convince Ba Ra,
so please do the surgery again.
Just turn me into Ba Ra,
and then we can get married.
Ba Ra showed up today.
I met her.
What did she say?
I'll have ten kids
if that's what it takes.
As many as we can have.
I know Ba Ra,
and Yong Joong is the only one for her.
And after Geum Ba Ra disappeared,
Ha Yong Joong couldn't stop
thinking about her either.
We don't have to live as a couple
in name only anymore.
I want to do something good for once.
Ba Ra can become Momo
and marry Yong Joong,
and I'll become Ba Ra...
and live my life
admiring and devoted to you.
I'll study hard to become
more cultured and refined.
It's a win-win for everyone.
Discuss it with Ba Ra.
If she agrees to switch,
will you really do it?
I can put everything I just said
in writing as a pledge.
The truth is,
the news articles were right.
Things aren't good
between Yong Joong and me.
I just pretended
we were fine out of pride.
Think about becoming Momo
and marrying Yong Joong.
And I could become you
and live as Geum Ba Ra.
Director Shin said he'd do the surgery
if you agreed.
You'll get wealth, fame, and even love,
all from a surgery that takes a few hours.
Director Shin is an amazing surgeon.
I was completely blown away.
No matter how good Director Shin is to you
or how hard he tries,
you have no intention
of marrying him, right?
Honestly, don't you feel a little bad
for Director Shin?
He seems to have it all,
but when you really think about it,
does he have time to spend his money?
Or does he really have
any hobbies he enjoys?
He's in this hospital 24 hours a day,
either in the OR, his office,
or a patient's room.
If I became you
and married Director Shin...
and then dedicated my life
to taking proper care of him,
wouldn't that give you
more peace of mind, too?
Why did things go bad
between you and Yong Joong?
A little bit of everything, I guess.
We're completely incompatible,
right down to our tastes.
I think he was just Momo's fan.
You're sick and tired of your life, too,
aren't you?
Think of the discrimination and neglect
we grew up with.
Don't you have any intention
of apologizing to me?
Not even now?
For what?
I want an apology. A proper one.
I deserve one.
My life could have been so much better
if it weren't for you.
But you ruined everything.
By framing me for theft.
Even now, my chest gets tight
just thinking about it.
If you were in my shoes,
how would you have felt
if I'd done that to you?
I'm sorry.
I kept hoping
you would apologize eventually.
Since we were both left in the baby box
on the same day and grew up together,
I decided to just let it slide.
But you acted like nothing ever happened.
You weren't the Kim Jin Ju
I thought I knew.
I don't know how a person
could do something like that.
You act nice, then stab me in the back.
I didn't stab you in the back.
You didn't?
My circumstances made me that way.
- You don't get it?
- No.
We had the exact same circumstances.
That's because you're smart.
This isn't about being smart.
It's about having a conscience.
You ended up fine even though
Ye Jeong's family didn't adopt you.
But I was more heartbroken
than anyone else.
To be betrayed by you, of all people.
But I paid for it in the end.
I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
Deep down, I was always sorry.
But you were always so cold to me,
I could never bring myself to say it.
Living as Momo can't be that bad.
So what if you get divorced?
You can meet any rich, famous guy
you want.
Why do you want to become me?
My pride.
Everyone would love to see me fail,
wouldn't they?
The haters, the reporters...
You know how many reporters
can't stand Momo.
You'd do the surgery again just for that?
It's only the first step that's hard.
You're just asleep for a few hours,
and then you wake up.
It's no big deal.
Try living as Momo for a while.
Spending money is a lot of fun, too.
It's beyond your wildest dreams.
There's no reason
to cling to that face and body.
Think of all the tears you've shed
with those eyes.
Fate gives everyone a few chances in life.
Think of this as one of them.
Ever since you disappeared,
I've lived with a shell of Ha Yong Joong.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sick and tired of it.
Director Shin might seem cold
on the outside,
but he's better than the empty shell
Ha Yong Joong has become.
Even if he only wants Ba Ra's body.
It's about choosing the next-best thing.
That's what Director Shin is doing.
And Ha Yong Joong
has to pay the price, too.
He doesn't deserve to marry the real you.
Didn't he just end up hurting us both?
He should've chosen you from the start.
Do you need some time to think?
I should've listened to you.
There's no turning back now.
Everyone makes mistakes. We're human.
Just as long as you don't repeat them.
Chalk it up to a life lesson.
By the way,
Momo is a world-class liar.
Saying she was abused growing up?
Just what you'd expect from an actress.
Hyun Ran Hee.
After her first love,
Paul, the artist, came to Korea,
she found out
she had lost her own daughter.
So what's all this about abuse?
She thought her daughter was living well
in Japan with Paul.
I'm going to finalize the paperwork,
and then I'm going to marry Ba Ra.
You found Reporter Geum?
Please check the baby's diaper often.
The baby is very sensitive.
Is Grandmother still eating well?
She especially likes hairtail,
so make sure to debone it well for her.
Okay.
Her hemoglobin levels are a bit low,
but that can happen to women
because of their period.
But just in case,
I've scheduled an MRI this weekend.
Does she just need to eat well?
Things like meat?
Well, she's on an albumin drip for now.
Did she say anything else?
Like how she's been?
She'll talk when she's ready.
(Ready for surgery)
I have to go into surgery.
(No Visitors Permitted,
Please inquire at the nurses' station.)
It says no visitors.
Let's finalize everything in six months.
That's if you haven't changed
your mind by then.
I know I haven't been my best self.
I've been on edge
and took it out on you a lot.
I know I didn't live up to
your expectations.
I just want to stay your wife
for a few more months,
even if it's only on paper.
You don't have to give me alimony.
I didn't mean what I said.
I know money can't make up for it,
but you should take what you're owed.
If I hadn't had the miscarriage,
we probably would've just made it work.
I'll get the rest of my stuff tomorrow.
Ask Geum Ba Ra if she was really pregnant.
Someone saw her, and you can't even ask?
Are you sleeping?
(New Message)
Can we meet tomorrow?
I can't eat since I'm fasting.
Like Director Shin said,
it's true that
I used to have feelings for you.
When I was younger,
I just liked you because you doted on me.
I guess feelings are like the wind.
Over the past year,
those feelings have faded.
All that was left behind
were the memories.
The good ones.
You've given me so many.
We made them together.
Now, I'm the one...
who's going to like you much more.
I'm the one who messed everything up...
because I was so foolish.
I guess people need someone
to pour their heart into.
For me, that person was you.
But that's not the case anymore,
so don't feel burdened.
Are you going to keep pushing me away?
I understand if you're disappointed in me,
if you've lost all feelings for me.
I would be too.
I just didn't realize
how I felt soon enough.
Please understand.
Could you even accept...
my child?
I won't ask about the circumstances.
Of course.
If the baby is yours,
then they're precious and dear to me too.
I really mean it.
You're here in front of me right now.
And you're looking at me.
That's all that matters.
I never thought
I'd have this moment again.
That phrase, "aching with longing"...
I thought it was just
a line in a pop song.
But that's exactly how I felt.
It was torture.
I feel bad for Momo, but...
Thank you.
I was so pathetic...
and completely clueless.
It's not that you were clueless.
It's just that Momo completely occupied...
your heart.
You know that saying, "Blinded by greed."
It wasn't love.
I just got swept away for a moment...
by the actress, Momo.
I know I've sinned against both of you,
but please look kindly on me.
I'm asking just this once.
Now,
I think I'm starting to get
a faint idea of what love is...
and what it's supposed to be.
But people say love changes.
Love is different from a simple feeling.
Feelings are what come and go.
I finally get just how hard and painful
it must have been for you,
now that I'm experiencing it myself.
Let's just say we both messed up
because we were immature,
and let's start over.
The right way, for real this time.
Things with Momo will be over
in a few months.
I promised.
When did you have the baby?
Where is the baby now?
Who's taking care of it?
You can tell me when you want to.
When you're ready.
- What's important is...
- Remember what I say now.
I don't regret...
loving you.
I have never once regretted it.
The truth is,
I loved you more than words can say.
And now?
Thank you.
Remember what I'm about
to say to you now too.
Ha Yong Joong will never
leave Geum Ba Ra again.
And I'll make sure of it.
Let's watch our hair turn gray...
and see each other grow old.
Let's live a long, long life together.
Do you really think you can be happy,
Ha Yong Joong, after making me cry?
I'm going to make your life
a living torment.
I'm not the Kim Jin Ju who was impressed
by your 100-dollar taxi fare anymore.
Can I help you?
The card...
I'm just here for a delivery.
Which unit?
Unit 701, for Momo.
You can't just leave it here.
Take it up to her front door.
Her helper already went home for the day.
Then buzz me in.
Drive.
- You scream, and you'll regret it!
- Dad!
It's me, Jin Ju.
I'm Momo now! We swapped brains!
Don't give me that crap.
If you don't believe me,
the surgery scar is on my head.
Where is it?
Proof.
The surgery scar is the proof, Dad.
Front door code...
to your house.
Which one? Hyeonmi Villa?
What was the code again?
It's 3-5-4-4!
Kim Jin Ju's bank account balance.
It was probably 10,500 dollars.
Bank...
- account number.
- Shinjun Bank.
It's 222-812058-03014.
- Drive.
- Where to?
Home. Hyeonmi Villa.
Don't try anything funny.
I've got nothing to lose.
I won't, Dad.
The Han River Park.
Not home?
So only your brain is Jin Ju's?
Yes.
Then what about the body?
What happened to Jin Ju's body?
I don't know.
I can't drive, Dad.
It's a long story.
Can you put that away?
I'm shaking too much.
Is that even possible?
It is, that's why I'm here just fine...
How did you know, Dad?
The earring.
My earring?
The one with the pearl.
How could I forget?
Your mother bought it for you.
It was the first gift I ever gave a woman.
I saw it a few days ago
at Director Shin's hospital...
when you took photos with your fans.
Dad, you were there?
So...
your body...
is just gone?
How could...
That bastard Director Shin.
Director Shin isn't at fault here.
There are certain lines you don't cross.
Did you ask for this,
or were you offered it?
- You wretched girl!
- Dad!
Don't you call me Dad.
To cut ties with your own father,
you'd go as far as killing your own body.
I was scared.
Scared of your own father?
What did I ever do to you?
It's just...
I was sick and tired of everything.
It wasn't really because of you.
Then...
why didn't you tell me after the surgery?
If the world found out, I'd be finished.
I was going to come find you
once things blew over.
I swear.
And living as Momo hasn't been easy.
Why are you and Ha Yong Joong separated?
- We just drifted apart.
- Who did?
- Both of us.
- You sure he didn't figure it out?
It's more complicated than that.
It was just a lot of things piling up.
Wire me some money.
Send one big one for now.
A thousand dollars?
Ten thousand dollars?
Is a big one, only 10,000 dollars
for someone like Momo?
The daily limit is 50,000 dollars.
Then send
the other 50,000 dollars tomorrow.
Then wire 200,000 dollars by the weekend.
Go to the bank in person if you have to.
After severing family ties like that,
did you really think you could be happy?
The sky...
will punish you.
Woosung Bank.
Account 5-2-5...
I don't have any beer.
Will a Coke do?
Then...
Liquor.
Whiskey.
Give me the key card too.
Aren't you hot?
Why are you still wearing that?
I have a bit of a cold.
The code to Director Shin's penthouse.
- Why?
- So I know. Stop asking questions.
After you two break up,
should I ask Director Shin...
to turn me into Ha Yong Joong?
How much does it hurt?
You can't go through that twice, Dad.
Is that...
Sonbeni?
(Nua General Hospital)
Are you nervous?
Don't worry.
I might treat you coldly.
But you'll have Momo's face.
Just relax.
And try to get some sleep.
Oh my gosh!
- How did you get in here?
- What do you mean?
You gave me the key card.
Who did?
Playing dumb again?
It's just...
By any chance,
did you get it from Jin Ju?
You changed the passcode, didn't you?
Open up.
Should I just spill everything?
A strange man keeps ringing my doorbell.
Please come quickly.
Noir Hospital, 21st floor.
Yes.
What about Ba Ra?
Ma'am!
It's Mommy.
Remember me, okay?
I'll come back safe and sound...
and give my baby boy many hugs.
Eat well,
and sleep well.
I love you.
I love you, my sweet baby.
(New Message, Actress Momo)
Reporter Geum Ba Ra,
is this a good time to talk?
(Actress Momo)
Hello, Ms. Geum.
Momo.
I'm at my villa having some wine.
With friends?
No, I'm alone.
And I found myself thinking of you.
The look in your eyes, to be exact.
Was the look in my eyes...
bad?
I'll tell you when you get here.
Where is your villa?
If you text me your address,
I'll send my manager.
He'll give you a ride here.
The buses don't come out this far.
Goodness.
Go ahead, take it.
Director, if it's not urgent,
can I call you back?
Okay.
I'm sorry you have to see me like this.
Is something wrong?
No, I really was just thinking of you.
And I'm sorry to bother you
on your day off.
Are you kidding?
An invitation from you is an honor.
Since we met at that
Japanese restaurant by chance,
I think about the look in your eyes.
It was so indifferent, I guess?
You didn't see me as Momo the actress.
You saw me as a regular person.
I figured you'd be uncomfortable
if I made a big deal out of it.
Exactly.
To put it a bit dramatically,
unlike how people's eyes pounce on me,
you were a breath of fresh air.
You made me feel at ease, and I liked it.
That's a relief.
I'm glad you took it that way.
You were putting yourself in my shoes,
weren't you?
I know what it's like for actors.
You're constantly hounded by people.
I'm sure it's something
to be grateful for.
A lot of times, it can be overwhelming.
Could you be like a big sister to me?
Treat me like your little sister.
Do you have any younger siblings?
I'm an only child, too.
Weren't you ever jealous of friends
who had older siblings?
But at least you have your parents, Momo.
I grew up in an orphanage.
Goodness, I had no idea.
I'm used to people being taken aback
with that expression.
I'm not taken aback.
I assumed you grew up with a silver spoon.
You just give off that vibe.
I do?
That makes you even more amazing.
That sobered me right up.
I was going to vent,
but I'd rather hear your story instead.
I'm not just being nosy.
There's not much to tell.
Orphanages these days are a lot nicer
than you'd think.
Oh, you made gimbap?
I was in the middle of making some
when you called.
But we don't have any fruit.
I should've bought some.
That's okay. We don't need any.
I have plenty of snacks instead.
Gosh, this is amazing.
I've never had gimbap like this before.
It's aged kimchi gimbap.
I just threw it together with what I had.
Aged kimchi makes it taste so...
It's so clean, yet so flavorful.
You probably shouldn't gain weight.
I'll just starve myself tomorrow.
Fasting is just part of the job.
It must be stressful, right?
From what I see,
actors lose just as much as they gain.
That reporter, Lee Si Kyung,
is out for my blood.
Does he really hate me that much?
- You saw the articles, right?
- Think of him as your nemesis.
We all have one.
For me, the world itself was my nemesis.
I must sound pathetic,
whining in front of you.
I'm not judging.
If anything, I understand you better.
There's this very popular veteran actress.
We were in a show together.
She kept saying how unique and pretty
my bag was and asked me for it,
but I told her I couldn't
since a fan made it for me.
Since then, she's been bad-mouthing me.
You're kidding.
Saying I have the worst attitude
and that I don't even say hello.
But I've never even left her on read.
She's raising two daughters of her own.
How can she act like that?
What if her daughters go out in the world
and someone treats them the same way?
The world doesn't run on common sense.
And people aren't always what you expect.
I think...
the world has half and half.
Half are good, and half are bad.
Will evil people ever just disappear?
The world has no use for them.
They'll never go away.
The universe has day and night, right?
As long as the universe exists,
the human world, just like day and night,
will have good people and bad people.
You just have to accept it for what it is.
As long as we're not the evil ones
hurting others,
we can take comfort in that
and be at peace.
Is it that easy for you?
I've been slandered and had my share
of hard times, too.
But at some point, it just clicked.
They say humans mirror the universe...
I guess it’s the same principle,
the same phenomenon...
I realized I shouldn't get caught up in it
and just stick to my own path.
You're so right.
You really are something else.
Our bodies don't just have healthy cells.
They constantly create cancer cells, too,
every single day.
I really shouldn't let it get to me.
I feel so much better already.
Okay, from now on, you're my big sister.
We're even wearing similar outfits today.
Right. Only the colors are different.
Let's trade to celebrate being sisters.
Your shirt's silk, Momo.
I got mine for 25 dollars
at a discount store.
Why so formal? We can be casual now.
I won't call you "Reporter Geum" anymore.
I'll call you Ba Ra.
James, I've been thinking.
Looking at how confident Ba Ra is,
do you think she might've had my baby?
You think I haven't thought of that?
But no, the timeline doesn't add up.
Park Sun Woo said she looked like
she was 6 or 7 months along.
She probably just said that
to get you to give up.
Then why did she just disappear?
Because she couldn't bear to see
you and Momo together.
How is she acting toward you?
She's different than before.
She's a bit cold,
and she's keeping her distance.
It's all because I didn't listen to you...
Do you think it's easy
to get pregnant on the first try?
But if she really did have my baby...
She could have had a miscarriage.
Out of spite, couldn't she have gone...
to one of the guys
who were fawning over her?
Even I had a thing for Reporter Geum.
A Sungwoo Daily reporter meets top players
in politics, finance, and culture.
Among them...
If she still loved you...
or was pregnant with your baby,
she would've come to you.
Why would she go to Director Shin?
Don't jump to conclusions.
I'll meet with Reporter Geum and find out.
She'll be discharged
right after her MRI, won't she?
She's not going to disappear again,
is she?
If she meant to, she would've gone
to another hospital in the first place.
Mom.
Dad.
My little sister.
Our family of four was all together.
Mom.
Goodbye,
Geum Ba Ra.
I miss Oiji and Pickles.
(Artist Paul Kim)
Mr. Kim.
Hello. It must be late in Korea, right?
I've still got a while before I turn in.
Are you overseas again?
Yes.
I got curious and searched online,
and an article about
Momo's separation popped up.
I was just wondering if it's true.
I didn't feel comfortable
asking them myself.
Yes, it's true.
What's the issue?
It seems they just naturally drifted apart
after her last miscarriage.
I feel somewhat responsible.
Why would you feel responsible?
That goes for me, too.
They say only the couple truly knows
what goes on in a marriage.
Let me treat you to a meal
when I get back to Korea.
With Reporter Geum Ba Ra
from Sungwoo Daily.
You know Reporter Geum, don't you?
Are you close? With Reporter Geum Ba Ra?
Yes.
I asked her to check in on my place
every now and then before I left,
but it turns out
she took a leave of absence.
When was the last time you saw her?
I have no choice.
My little sister, Momo,
was a truly good soul who despised evil.
But into her angelic body...
went the brain of Kim Jin Ju.
Can you imagine how horrifying
and agonizing it must be for her soul?
I will give up my own body.
To me...
my sister is more important.
Reporter Geum wasn't pregnant.
Either that, or Park Sun Woo was wrong.
I just got off the phone with Paul Kim,
and he said Ba Ra was house-sitting
for him in Yangpyeong.
She also looked
after a colleague's grandmother...
who was stationed overseas.
Paul Kim could've been mistaken, you know.
If you were talking to her face-to-face,
couldn't you tell if she's pregnant?
Maybe not in the early stages, sure.
She was probably upset and said that
just to get under your skin.
If her MRI comes back clear,
she'll probably go straight to Yangpyeong.
You have to stop her, get on your knees,
do whatever it takes.
It's also possible she showed up
since your separation article gave hope.
My imagination was running wild too.
Anyway, what a relief.
(Nua General Hospital)
Has Geum Ba Ra been discharged?
She's one of the Director's patients,
so we wouldn't know.
He isn't seeing patients today.
He might be at a conference.
The Director said Geum Ba Ra had an MRI.
Did she have it done?
We have no way of knowing.
Why not?
There's no record of it.
The phone you are calling is turned off.
Please leave a message...
(Ju Shin)
(Ba Ra)
The phone you are calling is turned off.
Please leave a message after the tone.
(Ba Ra)
What's with both of them?
Welcome, sir.
Is this the one? The new model?
Yes, it is.
Can I get you something to drink?
- An iced Americano.
- An iced Americano?
Yes.
- If I order one, how long is the wait?
- It's a three-month wait.
Really? That long?
Is there any way to get it sooner?
I need Paul Kim's Yangpyeong address.
You're going there?
- Yes.
- It's no use. We were...
You're a step too late.
Has Director Shin ever
turned his phone off and gone MIA?
The whole MRI thing
could've just been a ploy.
Just to keep her at the hospital.
Looks like the two of them
left the country.
I really don't think
you two are meant to be.
Just let her go.
(Momo)
The phone you are calling is turned off.
Please leave your message after the tone.
That brat. Her father has stomach cancer.
- Samhap.
- You brought takeout?
Yes, from the manager's favorite spot
in Mokpo.
- I can't eat this.
- Me neither.
Then why did you get it?
I can barely breathe just from the smell.
It's a miracle cure for constipation.
My mom swears by it.
- But still...
- I'm serious.
This is to help with your constipation.
And I'll eat it with you.
- What about your mom?
- My mom has plans most nights.
Just pinch your nose.
Go on, eat up.
Together.
How can this even be considered food?
We probably need to eat seven pieces
for it to work, right?
Even I'm eating it,
and I'm not even constipated.
You're not just doing this to be nice.
I haven't done anything to deserve this,
have I, Momo?
My mom says it also clears up your skin.
My skin is clear.
Just close your eyes and do it.
I'm going to eat seven pieces
right along with you.
Alright, fine.
Since you went to all this trouble.
Exactly.
I, too,
can do anything for my little sister.
You did great.
Jin Ju...
Not yet.
She really needs to be taught a lesson.
She really does.
She must have seen my missed calls.
What?
Was Ba Ra discharged?
- No.
- Then what?
She had a brain hemorrhage.
A brain hemorrhage?
And?
- We did emergency surgery.
- You did it yourself?
- When?
- The day before yesterday.
Then why didn't you tell me?
How is she?
- How is she?
- It's only been a day.
She's in the recovery room now.
Then why don't the nurses know anything?
It's what Ba Ra wanted.
She doesn't want people to know.
You even had your phone off.
How was I...
supposed to know
I'd be operating on Ba Ra?
(Ready for surgery)
I have to go into surgery.
Let me see her, just for a second.
Ba Ra.
Were you in so much pain that
a vessel in your brain burst?
Please recover without any complications.
I'm going to stay by your side forever.
Kim...
Jin Ju.
Is there anyone at all we can call?
I'll try.
Wait, you can't do the surgery
without a guardian's consent?
The phone you are calling is turned off.
Please leave a message after the tone.
It's off.
You know...
The director here should know her.
Her name's Geum Ba Ra.
She's a reporter for the Sungwoo Daily.
He says he'll ask Geum Ba Ra
to sign the surgical consent form.
And it hasn't metastasized?
That's right.
- His registration number.
- It's 6663256.
The phone you are calling is turned off...
That brat...
Her father has stomach cancer.
Don't tell me she ran off again.
Even if she did, her face is famous.
How hard can it be to find her?
What kind of patients
do you usually look after?
Post-op patients, mostly.
For stage one,
you have nothing to worry about.
When can I eat after the surgery?
(Move her tomorrow morning.)
Watch this when you're ready.
Momo.
Will this work now?
Will it?
(Patient transport only)
(Counseling for epilepsy patients
and their families)
When can we see her? She must be awake.
It was brain surgery,
so not until she's moved
to a general ward.
This is unbelievable.
I mean, at her age, how could this...
It's not like she drank or smoked.
Could her vessels be weak from poor eating
when she was at the orphanage?
Mr. Kim Gwang Cheol.
Try to open your eyes.
Just you try running off again.
I'll find you if you do.
Mr. Kim Gwang Cheol?
Your surgery went well.
Did she...
go on a trip or something?
(Cashier's check)
To be honest,
you're the one I find most intimidating.
Well, don't be.
You can be comfortable with me.
It's not that I don't trust you,
Director Shin.
Move her to the 12th floor.
Yes, sir.
- Nua General Hospital.
- Yes, sir.
(Neurosurgery Director's Office)
How's Ba Ra?
Brain-dead?
How could this...
You're the one who operated.
What now?
- There's nothing I can do.
- What do you mean, nothing?
You have to find a way, whatever it takes.
Shin Ju Shin.
You have to make her wake up.
You think I haven't tried everything?
Then, operate again.
You crazy bastard.
After everything, you did this to Ba Ra...
This is it?
Go see her for yourself.
Ba Ra.
This can't be happening.
Do something. Don't just stand there.
Ba Ra. Can you hear me?
It's me, Ha Yong Joong.
Geum Ba Ra.
If you can hear me, squeeze my hand.
Come on.
It's me.
Geum Ba Ra, you're stronger than anyone.
Please.
Hey. Are you just going to stand there?
I'm moving her to Seoltap Hospital.
It's no use.
No use? After what you've done to her?
You should've had Dr. Kim Jun Oh
do the surgery.
Get Seoltap Hospital on the line.
It's an emergency.
You want to drag her between hospitals
just to open up her skull again?
One more surgery
and she'll die on the table.
Then take responsibility.
If you're human,
take responsibility for this, you bastard!
Hey!
I've made some beef porridge for you.
I think I'm ready for a proper meal now.
- Oh, yes...
- I'm Geum Ba Ra.
That's right. You have a unique name.
Why did you give up on me?
I'm your daughter.
Shouldn't a mother recognize
her own child?
After all the pain
of giving birth to me...
(Director Shin)
Yes, Director Shin.
(Nua General Hospital)
I never thought it would come to this.
(Doctor Shin)
You're supposed to wear a swimsuit
at the pool.
Jin Ju's father came to see me.
That looked like Geum Ba Ra, the reporter.
Was she in a car accident or something?
Is the owner of this house...
still not out of the hospital yet?
She's friends with my daughter.
But you haven't heard?
She passed away a little while ago.
There won't be a funeral
before the burial.
She was in the prime of her life.
Your Daddy...
cried so much today.
Sounds just like Kim Jin Ju.
It's true what they say,
people don't change.
I'm not sure I'm supposed to address you.
Let me get straight to the point.
(Nua General Hospital)
There's a dead body here!
I think it's a patient
we operated on recently.
- And the Director isn't here?
- No, sir.
You are not going to believe this.
I'm on my way to your house,
so run there...
at the speed of light.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)