♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 12=
You're awake.
How do you feel? Feeling better?
Thank you for your concern.
I feel better now.
By the way,
what's your name?
My name is Hu Yuanzhong.
All these years,
I've made my living by hunting.
Thank you for saving me.
Stay still.
Your wound might reopen otherwise.
Well,
let me apply the medicine.
The oral medication isn't ready yet.
Cheng Lisu is always so slow.
No need.
I can do it myself.
Miss Song.
You're a lady. This isn't proper.
I'm a man. Let me do this.
Well,
I'll go hurry Cheng Lisu.
Okay.
Thank you, sir.
No problem.
Judging by your attire,
you don't seem to be from Wei.
I'm from Liehe.
However,
I left the Liehe tribe
many years ago.
You're an experienced hunter.
Why did you
go out in such harsh winds?
My wife
just passed away.
I miss her terribly,
so I visited her grave,
braving the winds.
I notice many red rashes
on your hands.
I'll ask Taotao
to prepare medicine?
No need.
Poisonous weeds hurt my hands
when I climbed up the hill.
They'll heal soon.
Alright then.
Medicine's ready.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Give it to me.
Liehe's characters.
My late wife wrote it.
It's a love poem in the Liehe tribe.
My apologies.
I don't know it's your wife's stuff.
I was just curious.
You're not mad, are you?
What's wrong?
He.
When his injuries heal,
he'll leave naturally.
Stop being jealous.
He.
Miss Song.
My apologies.
I was practicing archery
and accidentally missed.
Are you okay?
He.
I know you dislike Hu Yuanzhong.
But he's just a patient.
Your repeated targeting of him
has gone too far.
It's fine.
I guess
he was joking with me.
I'm fine
and uninjured.
If this happens again,
I'll get angry with you.
Got it.
Excuse me,
I'll take my leave now.
Stop!
Oh, no.
It's a trap.
I didn't kill him!
A man in black
acted strange.
I wounded him,
but I didn't
kill Instructor Ma.
Instructor Ma
must've been killed earlier.
The killer
intended to frame me.
Fine.
I'll give you a chance to explain.
I suspect the killer
is Hu Yuanzhong.
He's from Liehe.
The Liehe tribe
is forested,
dark, and damp
all year round.
The Liehe tribe uses
distinctively designed scimitars.
(Their soldiers)
(used that kind of weapon,)
(making them develop rashes)
(on their hands.)
Hu Yuanzhong
claims to be a hunter.
Typically,
hunters
don't use scimitars often.
So, why
are there the same rashes on his hands?
Moreover,
he said he missed his deceased wife,
yet he secretly
lusts after Miss Song's beauty.
Do you have solid evidence?
He carries a note on him,
claiming it's a poem
in Liehe's language from his wife.
But I believe
it's not that simple.
Let's find someone
fluent in Liehe's language
to decipher it.
Also,
during the earlier fight,
I struck his chest
with a bamboo pole.
You can have someone check
if he went out tonight
and if he
has fresh injuries.
Sir.
From Hai hour to Zi hour,
I was on patrol duty.
The light in Hu Yuanzhong's room
is out at Hai hour,
and he didn't go out.
Go.
Bring Hu Yuanzhong here.
Yes.
Sir. Hu Yuanzhong is here.
Sir.
Strip his clothes.
You...
Stop it!
Stop this!
Stop!
Sir.
May I know why?
By your account,
you beat him with a stick.
His body should get the bruise.
Yet as you saw,
no bruise on his right shoulder.
Mr. Shen.
He must have an accomplice here.
Maybe the accomplice
is in Yezhou Garrison.
Enough.
Mr. Shen,
you distrust me?
I can't trust your side
of the story.
We caught you red-handed.
Guards!
Take He Yan to the dungeon
and await judgment.
Imprison me if you must,
but you must
investigate this thoroughly,
or Yezhou Garrison
faces grave peril.
Take him away.
- Yes.
(Now that I'm imprisoned,)
(Yezhou Garrison has only recruits)
(who never go to war,)
(with Liehe infiltrators among them.)
(Enemies lurk in shadows.)
(I guess they tried so hard)
(to frame me)
(for something big.)
(Well,)
(if the news from Litai)
(is fabricated)
(to lure Xiao Jue away,)
(then the Yezhou Garrison)
(will be controlled)
(by the enemies.)
He.
Miss Song.
Stay out of this.
Go back now.
I have medicine.
If I have to,
Cheng Lisu and I will drug them all.
We'll rescue you first.
Wait for Commander Xiao's return.
By the time he returns,
it'll probably be too late.
Can you give me the knockout drug?
May I
have your belt too?
In the coming days,
Mr. Cheng and you
must stay close
to Mr. Shen at all times.
He can protect you.
Help me deliver this to Mr. Shen.
Alright.
Hurry back now.
He asked me to give you this.
Why aren't you saying anything?
He is so kind.
How could he possibly kill?
Release him immediately.
Mr. Shen,
killing a comrade is a grave crime.
Moreover, He Yan has no motive
to kill Ma Damei.
So, we should
carefully examine the corpse
to verify if there's
only one fatal wound
before making judgments.
Mr. Cheng makes a valid point.
It's late.
You two
should go back.
Guards!
Escort Mr. Cheng
and Miss Song back.
If anything happens to them,
I'll hold you accountable!
Understood.
Please.
Issue orders.
Tighten security and increase patrols.
Sentries in pairs,
rotating
in five watches
until dawn.
Yes.
He is still in prison.
We must figure out something.
The weather is getting cold.
The dungeon has nothing.
The cold might
make him sick.
Cut it out!
Go to find Mr. Shen
and plead for mercy.
Go!
Come on.
(Yezhou Garrison)
Who's there?
How dare you barge in!
I am General Rida Muzi
of the Liehe tribe!
I came today
to annihilate the Yezhou Garrison.
Rida Muzi?
Surrender obediently,
and I might consider
sparing your lives.
(He Yan didn't lie.)
Commander Xiao and his men are away.
He remains imprisoned.
What should we do?
Mai, shut up!
Don't let them hear.
I've waited long for you,
Lei Hou.
You used the same move
during the flag contest.
I remember it well.
You killed Instructor Ma and framed me.
You feigned illness
to stay for something.
Now,
you rush to assassinate me.
Is it because you know
you can't beat me?
Now, you finally realize
who's the number one
in the Yezhou Garrison?
Years ago,
General Feihong
defeated the Liehe tribe.
I thought
the Liehe tribe had
been thoroughly subdued.
When my army
crushes the Xiao Army,
it will be too late for you
to beg for your life.
The Yezhou Garrison
is defended by General Fengyun.
How dare you act so recklessly!
General Fengyun?
Commander.
Something's off.
General Fengyun
can't even protect himself now.
Don't expect him to save you.
Commander might be in danger.
These bandits
planned this all along.
People die on the battlefield.
How can we be shackled by fear of death?
Soldiers of the Yezhou Garrison
would rather die in battle
than live in cowardice.
Xiao Army!
Go into formation!
- Yes!
Fine.
Since you all seek death,
we'll slaughter every one of you
and drown Yezhou Garrison in blood!
How dare you!
Who are you?
(Commander won't return soon.)
(Our troops)
(can't match Liehe's soldiers.)
(Fighting recklessly)
(would make us die.)
(Capturing their leader)
(will make things easier.)
I am He Yan,
the top warrior of Yezhou Garrison.
I hear Rida Muji, your brother,
is the former general.
He loved
to behead
captives
and tie them to his horse's tail.
Everywhere he went,
Wei people trembled in fear.
Guess what?
Before long,
General Feihong
effortlessly
chopped off his head.
Exactly!
General.
Why don't we
hold a duel here
today?
Who do you think you are
to challenge me?
You're so arrogant!
I just want
to see if I can chop off your head
and tie it
to my horse's tail too.
Very well.
Teach him a lesson.
In that case,
I'll give you a quick death.
By the way,
what's your wager
for this duel?
Well,
let me propose first.
If I lose,
do with me as you will.
But if you lose,
you must call me Father.
Very funny.
It's surprising
to meet an interesting
and brave man like you.
You deserve to be the top one.
Very good.
I like to play
with a tough guy.
It will be enjoyable
to crush you.
Let's see
who will
be crushed first.
You're impressive.
Same to you.
Let's see how much longer you can last.
Your blood
is nearly drained dry.
In his condition,
he won't last long.
He's wounded.
We can
fight together.
Anyway, we can't watch him die.
True.
Mr. Shen.
Should we attack?
- Charge!
Mr. Shen.
Are all people in the Central Plains
as pretentious as you?
Not exactly.
However,
I'm exceptionally good at pretense.
You remind me of someone.
Who?
My unfortunate brother once said
that when He Rufei, the General Feihong,
took an arrow in battle,
he could take out the shaft
and keep fighting.
You
resemble him greatly.
You're wrong.
I'm not He Rufei,
nor do I resemble him.
But every warrior of Wei
shares my resolve.
As long as we're alive,
we'll fight to the end!
- Fight to the end!
The Central Plains
breed countless generals
like General Feihong.
How many generals
can the Liehe tribe produce?
Is this all you've got?
You're quite weak.
(Xiao Jue will not)
(fall for a diversionary trap.)
(I have to buy more time.)
He!
Taotao!
Watch out, He!
Look out!
He Yan!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
But He...
All soldiers!
- Yes!
Capture those men!
- Attack!
Nine Banners Battalion.
He Yan.
Xiao Jue.
You're back.
(The messenger is suspicious.)
(That is)
(a path for Wutuo's invasion.)
(They must be remnants from battle)
(in Que City, ambushing there.)
(They tried to divert us.)
(Yezhou Garrison is in danger.)
Commander,
what should we do?
You'll impersonate me.
We'll go with it.
(Feinu will lead the troop)
(to ambush Wutuo's main force.)
(Coordinate with him)
(and annihilate enemies.)
(I'll take a squad
to reinforce Yezhou Garrison.)
Why is it that every time we meet,
you end up
in such a pitiful state?
Maybe because,
well,
I always know
you'll help me out.
He Yan.
What?
Check her pulse.
No need.
I can tell what's wrong.
Dress the wounds first.
Listen,
check her pulse.
Fine.
She's...
A girl.
Xiao Jue.
So, you've been
keeping a beauty.
No wonder you've been
so attentive and accommodating
to her.
You always took her with you
and even let her
stay next door to you.
Turns out you are
in love.
Are you done?
Keep blabbering, and she'll die.
How could you curse
a lady like that?
It's pretty embarrassing.
I kept calling her Mr. He
all this time.
Now,
should I switch to calling her Miss He
or Mrs. Xiao?
Stop nagging, or I'll punish you.
She's severely injured.
Even most men can't bear it.
I wonder how she
endures this?
Remove her garment.
Expose her back.
Clean the blood with warm water.
Then apply the medicine.
You were wounded too,
so you know the routine well.
Uncle.
And you?
I'll decoct herbal medicine for her.
♪Walking through the crowd,
without asking about the future♪
♪Wandering half a lifetime,
solitary as the moon♪
♪I failed to let it go and kept looking♪
Commander.
Does it hurt?
No.
In front of me,
no need to lie.
♪Just to tread the snow you described♪
Commander.
Did I
do well?
♪It's hard to sever love or hatred♪
♪Before fate is confirmed♪
♪My love for you burns fiercely♪
♪Lifelong devotion turns into a vow♪
♪That's my last wish♪
♪Awaiting the spread of moonlight♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪