(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
STILL SHINING
DECEMBER 2015
Your internship's over,
but can you even make it home
in this weather?
Nothing will be running.
But I have to go.
I heard you got
the only internship for Hawaii.
I bet you'll be there before Christmas.
Lucky you.
I'm not going to go.
I don't think I'm cut out
for this line of work.
I'm going back to school.
That's…
It's a miniature Sea Train.
They're local souvenirs.
Can I ask something?
Breaking up over the phone
doesn't count as a breakup, right?
Breaking up over the phone?
That's a bit…
So…
we're not broken up.
It's okay for me to see him.
I have to make it back today.
Can I pay for this with a card?
Give me five minutes.
Please text me.
I'll transfer the money to you.
I have to go.
-Thanks.
-Get home safe.
Tae-seo, I miss you so much.
The thought of seeing you makes me wonder
how I even managed without you.
I have so much to tell you
and so much to explain.
I have to go see you right now.
Rescue,
are you able to respond
to Yeonwoo right now?
I'm going to Yeonwoo too.
Can you take me there with you?
Able to respond.
The caller from Yeonwoo is stranded.
We've sent the caller's number.
Contact them directly.
Copy that.
Hello? This is the rescue unit.
Please go ahead.
We're on the road
leading to the Yeonwoo village hall.
We live here in Yeonwoo.
I know where that is.
I'm also from Yeonwoo.
I'll help.
Ma'am, I'm with someone
who knows the area.
Just leave your car
and go back inside your house.
The roads are pretty bad,
so it'll take me a while.
Gosh, my grandson
left for the army this morning,
but he went alone.
All because our truck
got stuck in the snow.
Please come get our truck out.
Even if we were late, we wanted to go
after getting our truck out,
but it got stuck in the snow again.
We should've at least been there
to see Tae-seo get his hair cut.
Goodness, that poor boy
went to that scary place all by himself.
He's endured so much by himself.
My goodness, we should at least be there
to see him enter the training center.
But Tae-seo went alone.
He shouldn't have gone alone.
FIRE RESCUE
COMMUNITY SAFETY UNIT
Gosh, thank you so much.
The wheels are just spinning.
-It's cold, so please wait in our car.
-Right.
Come on out.
All right.
Okay, be careful.
There you go.
Watch out. Slowly.
Will I be able to explain to him?
STILL SHINING
Rule Tongyeong out as well.
Don't go there.
Tae-seo.
Right now…
isn't a good time to talk.
I'll call you back soon.
YEON NAMSAN
If you're home, let's meet.
I'm not in Seoul.
I'll call you back tomorrow.
Hi, Grandpa. I'm about to leave now.
Yes, you need to use the truck.
You must be tired
after running the trains all day.
There's no need to hurry.
I'm going to leave now.
Okay, bye.
I'M NOT IN SEOUL
I'LL CALL YOU BACK TOMORROW
What time do you finish work today?
Did you finish your shift?
I'm at the hospital.
In Gangneung.
Where are you?
Seoul.
And yesterday?
I asked you to rule out Tongyeong,
but you haven't given me an answer yet.
I'll explain everything in person.
So there's something
you've needed to explain since yesterday?
What is it?
All right. Let's meet up.
I can be in Seoul before midnight.
Where should I go to see you?
Well…
I…
only have time right now.
You were going to see me briefly
to explain what had changed so suddenly
in that short amount of time
and then go back?
We were talking about our future
just the other day.
So when can I see you?
In three days.
Fine.
Tae-seo.
-It's not visiting hours yet, is it?
-No.
My goodness.
Gosh.
Hey, is the truck comfortable?
If you take the bus,
you can at least get some shut-eye.
It's fine. You need to use it.
Come sit.
You must be tired after driving all day.
Grandpa, I'll just be a minute.
-Hello?
-Close the window for me.
I already…
We just missed each other.
Missing each other,
being drained emotionally,
yet still trying our best
to make time to meet…
That's what you struggled with.
You want to do this again?
Even if you're mad at me,
I want to hear it in person.
I'm going to keep coming here
until I see you.
I don't care how many times
we miss each other.
Did anything happen
that I should be worried about?
No, it's nothing like that.
I just…
I really want to talk to you in person.
Please.
I'll tidy up a bit before I go
since I'm already here.
The floor's quite messy.
You must be tired from the trip.
You shouldn't be cleaning up.
Eun-a.
I don't want you to have a hard time.
But…
I don't want that for me either.
At least…
At least for us,
let's not make things hard for each other.
It's not working.
The portable gas stove…
Is it here?
Seong-chan, replacing just one breaker
in the guesthouse won't do it.
They all need replacing.
Eun-a asked me to change just one,
but that won't fix anything.
Please replace all of them.
Mr. Bae, we have a complaint that the room
is different from the booking.
I see. Okay.
-Mom, I'm going to head in first.
-Okay.
-Hi, Ga-on.
-Hello.
Hi, you made it.
Let me get that for you.
You've had it rough.
You're back now. That's what matters.
Thank you.
Let me know when the guesthouse is empty.
I'll replace everything real quick.
Seong-chan asked me to do it.
MO EUN-A
If she's back, that's good enough.
Eun-a, I'm in front
of your guesthouse in Tongyeong.
I'm not here as a surprise.
I meant to message you on my way here.
But I ended up driving without stopping.
Yeon Tae-seo.
Is this the place?
No, that one.
-You said we should meet.
-Not here.
Here.
I come here first thing in the morning.
I take a deep breath
and think as much as I want
about the people I miss.
I came here this morning as well
and thought about you a lot.
All right.
I'll explain.
When I heard this place would close down,
my mind went blank.
I heard it would be cleared out
if I didn't come back,
so I came.
-Cleared out?
-They were going to tear it down.
A truck had been camped out
here in front every day.
Even now?
No, that's been resolved.
But when I heard it would close down,
that truck came to mind right away.
I kept picturing that truck
knocking my guesthouse down.
You know me.
When I picture something bad,
I can't get it out of my head.
I wanted to finish things properly myself.
That's why I came.
There was no other reason.
What about your job in Seoul?
You found a room too.
The previous manager
will be working there again.
The room was hers, so she'd agreed
to pass it onto me when she moved out.
But the job she had lined up
was left up in the air,
and I was left hanging too.
Is that everything?
That's the reason I came.
What matters is
what will happen going forward.
I'll only come down here when I need to.
I'll go to Seoul
when I don't have bookings.
The lease is until next March.
As for what happens after,
I'm going to figure it out with you.
I'll be the only one going back and forth,
so you don't have to worry.
We're a couple.
Why let only you do all the work?
I'm the one who pushed for this,
so I should take responsibility.
I'll explain more.
About how I'll go
back and forth on my own…
You've explained enough.
This is where you lived and worked,
and you want to wrap things up.
I get it.
I'll fit however I can into your schedule.
I'm going to make all the effort.
It'll be different from when we were 20.
Okay.
Let's give it a go.
When I'm running a train,
I sometimes have an open view like this.
It's from an angle you can't see
anywhere else in Seoul.
But it's like that
in every direction here.
It's refreshing to look at.
I'm not going to rule out Yeonwoo.
I could maybe get a job
at the hotel there.
I wonder what will it feel like
to commute from home.
Except for when I was on my internship,
I've only lived in the residence hall.
Stay here for a second.
What?
Put these in your grandma's room
so she can see them when she wakes up.
She likes flowers.
She's still a young girl at heart.
They're not allowed in the ICU.
You've never gotten flowers
from a woman before, right?
No.
So I'm your first.
Thank you for coming
all this way to see me.
Hello?
You haven't sent your list
of credit card transactions
and the receipts for your expenses.
I requested them via email.
Please send them in an Excel file.
Your father never asked for any receipts.
All you need is my credit card statement.
He did request them.
What do you mean he never did?
I already checked.
Please send them by the end of this week.
Okay.
Okay, bye.
YEON HUI-SEO
I'm being discharged today.
Thank you for the other day.
If you're ever in this area,
please let me know.
I'll give you the red carpet treatment.
How cute.
I don't even have the strength to type.
I've been sitting down all day.
My muscles are wasting away.
I wonder when he'll come by to do it.
-Tae-seo.
-Hello.
Why do you seem so tired?
The tunnel section
felt unusually long today.
Gosh, I was concentrating too hard.
There's nothing like this
when you're tired.
Thank you. I needed this.
It's great.
Can I take this?
Sure.
Thank you.
Are you working right now?
Or running?
Or riding a public rental bike home?
I don't have any bookings
after this guest.
I'll come to Seoul.
I'm definitely going to follow
your routine this time.
I always wondered what you look at
on your way home every day.
Ga-on said he was the dinosaur king.
-Right, he did!
-He went all the way down there.
-What are you talking about?
-To calm him…
When he was playing with Da-gyeong…
If I went a little past Gwanghwamun,
I used to be able
to at least briefly see her.
Grandpa?
Yes, go ahead.
Right, so…
The doctor told me something,
but I can't understand a word he said.
Maybe I'm going deaf.
I can hear one moment
and can't hear the next.
Gosh, I know you're busy with work.
I'm sorry about this.
Well,
I can make the afternoon visiting hours.
I have today and tomorrow off.
Grandpa, I'll be right there.
Her intracranial pressure
and blood pressure are unstable.
She hasn't regained consciousness,
so we can't move her
to a regular room as planned.
Why did the numbers
suddenly change like that?
They're still changing,
so we'll have to keep monitoring her.
Can her condition worsen
as she regains consciousness?
What are her chances of getting better?
It's hard to say at this point.
No, the numbers.
-You can just tell me in terms of numbers.
-Tae-seo.
Grandma, I'm here.
You can hear me, right?
I thought you'd be bored,
so I'm here in place of the TV.
I'm going to be here
instead of Tae-seo starting tomorrow.
Hyang-gi is coming too.
I know you're really close with her.
Isn't that great?
Okay. Get out gently.
Hey, lean on here.
Careful.
Wait, hold on.
Tae-seo.
Tae-seo!
Over here.
-I'll do it.
-Okay.
-Lower one leg first.
Slowly.
Goodness.
Here.
Pour that out and add fresh water.
After your parents passed away
and when your grandma was bedridden,
I cooked rice
for the first time in my life.
You should learn how to do it.
Your grandma was worried
about you always eating out.
Later on,
when the person beside you gets sick,
you should at least
cook them proper meals.
Okay.
Hui-seo.
Hui-seo!
The healthy ones should do what they can.
Get out of there. It's too dangerous.
-Yeon Hui-seo.
-There they are.
Get out right now!
Let go!
Don't follow me. Go find some yourself.
Tae-seo.
I've never seen anything like this.
How can it be this dark?
The whole world is pitch black.
It's just endless darkness.
Is this what despair looks like?
What happened before won't happen again.
You were there alone
outside Mom's ICU room.
Grandma told me.
She said she felt sorry
towards you the most.
After she collapsed,
Grandpa couldn't go right away.
And you were left all by yourself.
Seven hours for Dad.
Two days for Mom.
She said you stayed outside the ICU
all by yourself.
You must've felt so…
helpless
and scared.
You were younger than I am now.
Tae-seo.
Grandma will be right back on her feet
for your sake, if nothing else.
This is nice.
Watching the fire reminds me of that time.
Eun-a, was it last year
or the year before that?
That day the power went out.
-It was last year.
-Last year?
-The day we lit candles?
-Yeah, when we lit candles.
Eun-a looked like she was about to cry.
But Ga-on was so excited,
saying it felt like we were camping.
-He was running around.
-Hello.
-Ga-on.
-Uncle Seong-chan!
Hey, Ga-on.
-What's going on?
-Seong-chan.
Hey, I thought you couldn't make it.
I should at least see you before you go.
What's all this?
-You bought something for us?
-Want a beer?
-Thank you.
-Come sit down.
-Thanks for coming when you're busy.
-It's nothing.
What were you talking about?
That time last year when the power
went out and Eun-a had a hard time.
I still get chills
when I think about that day.
I'll just sober up a bit.
I drove my car here.
Dong-sik came by, right?
It's hard to book him
for house calls, you know.
Man, that guy is good at his job.
We have to return this
to its original state,
so it's better to just repair it now.
This is all I'll say
as your business partner.
I know you'll manage the rest on your own.
Why are you drinking?
I can't even drive anyway.
Even if it's late,
call Dong-sik if anything happens.
He's the most reliable one around here.
Since I'll be moving somewhere else,
I came to say goodbye.
Where are you going?
Jeju Island.
I got the offer a while ago,
but I think I can go now.
Still…
if you're ever in trouble,
you can call me.
As your former colleague,
I can take care of that much.
What I can't stand the most
about Park So-hyeon is
she never lets go of any relationships.
She's friends with all her exes.
She'll come up with any excuse.
It's a talent.
She makes friends
without offending anyone.
Here.
It's the one you've been saving.
I brought this on the day
we opened the guesthouse.
I was going to open it that day,
but it was so hectic.
Keep it here.
You said it's really expensive. Take it.
Your dad gave that to me.
He got rid of all his alcohol.
He was serious about quitting.
He gave it to me,
saying it was his most prized bottle.
I was planning on drinking it with you
when we had something to celebrate.
You can have it.
Don't drink it
when you're feeling down, okay?
It's only for celebrating.
I'd never seen my dad
give anyone a gift before.
He wasn't very good
at connecting with people.
He must've really wanted you to have it.
It's yours.
Let's drink it today.
It's a day worth celebrating.
The relationship you're sick and tired of
is finally over,
so you can celebrate.
You're not good with wine,
so I can drink it by myself.
Just have a taste.
You acted like you wouldn't return.
You said you'd clean it out.
It reminded me of that truck.
Those damn scumbags.
You don't regret coming back, right?
I need to do well from now on
so I don't end up regretting it.
I'm glad I faced those scumbags.
You have that effect.
When I look at you,
it all feels worthwhile.
You said you depended on me a lot,
but I might have depended on you more.
You were always good to me.
The times we spent as colleagues together
were good times.
We'd finish the day's work,
wind down while having a beer here,
and make new plans.
It was our routine,
but I guess this is the last time.
What are you doing?
No, I just…
What, you think I'll try something?
No, that's not it.
I'll leave quietly at dawn
once I've sobered up,
so let's just say goodbye now.
Take care.
Also,
that truck won't be coming here again.
But if it does, don't confront them
and just call the police.
Or at least call Dong-sik.
You'll end up in trouble.
Okay, I got it. I'll stay away from them.
Now, I feel relieved.
She said it wasn't that house.
HUI-SEO
MISSED CALL
What brings you here at this hour?
Tell me.
Who are you?
Hey.
Hey, get out.
I said get out!
HUI-SEO
What is he doing here?
Eun-a.
Is that why Seoul…
You're worse than Park So-hyeon.
Tae-seo.
This is how the world looks again.
SEOUL (GANGNAM) EXPRESS
TICKET OFFICE
YEON NAMSAN
Grandma isn't waking up.
I'm afraid, and I'm exhausted.
Let's meet.
DAEJEON SERVICE AREA
They said Grandma
isn't responding to any stimuli.
The pressure in her head keeps rising.
And she's now in a coma.
Where are you, Tae-seo?
Did you…
see the doctor?
What did he say?
What do we do?
It's not yet…
Mom…
Mom.
CALLS
YEON NAMSAN
The back house is basically
the management office.
We come and go,
and we each have a separate room…
GRANDMA ISN'T WAKING UP
I'M AFRAID, AND I'M EXHAUSTED
LET'S MEET
MISSED CALL
EUN-A
Tae-seo.
Earlier…
Eun-a.
Let me explain.
-Earlier…
-You don't need to explain.
Right now…
it's all too much for me.
You're right,
and I'm right too.
That place is right for you,
and this place is right for me.
We should both…
forget the past month.
All right.
Let's do that.
I understand.
That's what we'll do.
I'm sorry.
STILL SHINING
Goodbyes are terrifying to me.
Trying to make things work,
intruding into your peaceful life…
Enough.
Let's go out for real.
We missed each other.
A few days ago…
She came to your house.
Is it okay
to go back to you like this?
Mo Eun-a.
Subtitle translation by: Hyesoo Lee