(Previously) Why did you bring Boston in
to work with you?
He nailed and bailed on Tua.
I want to start over.
It'd be nice to do it with you.
Next time you see him, give me a signal.
I'll be your human shield.
Poor thing.
You decided to audition,
and all you got was a supporting role.
Just don't fall.
Or I will step right on you.
You're the one
who leaked the news about Dean?
Anyone could've done it.
It's not just me who knows about it.
Seeing you hurt… hurts me too.
(Episode 4: Have fun, no drama)
Whoo-hoo!
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I'm bored. Let's go have fun.
I'm working. Just leave for now.
Hey!
What the hell?
What are you doing?
We're in the middle of the club.
So?
I don't care.
You like doing it out in the open, right?
You should care sometimes.
You can't do this.
Didn't you say you'd be ready
whenever I wanted?
I want you now.
Gosh.
What are you doing?!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Watch the booth for me.
You. Step outside with me.
Come here.
Ow! Where are you taking me?
- Ow! Where are you taking me?
- Here!
Ouch! That hurts!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Are you here to fish for info from me?
I'm not fishing for anything.
You tricked me.
You don't want it now, right?
Fine. I'm okay.
Didn't you already do it with Jack?
How was it? You happy now?
Jack's an idiot!
He's back with that asshole Dean, damn it!
See?
Damn!
What did I tell you?
Huh?
No matter how hard you try,
he'll never want you.
Yeah, no one ever wants me.
Hey, boy. Why don't you come with me?
Are you drunk, bro?
No, I'm not.
You can come with me.
I'm fine. It's okay.
I'm not drunk.
You can go home with me, seriously.
I think I'm fine.
I can do anything.
No, thank you.
Sorry. My friend's wasted.
Friend, my ass.
Let go of me!
Hell no.
Why are you grabbing me?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Didn't you say you only wanted Jack?
Let me go!
No.
Tonight, I'm going fucking wild!
Fine. You want it wild?
Then be wild with me.
Ow. Let go of me.
Let go!
Hello.
(Open the door for me.)
(I'm outside your studio.)
Make yourself comfortable.
I'll grab you a beer.
No need.
I'll say it quick.
Then I'll leave.
Alright then.
What's up?
Drop out as
the behind-the-scenes photographer.
Done. I'll drop out.
But you'll have to tell Jack yourself
why you want me out.
Um…
What should be the reason?
Ah!
You and I hooked up.
You got attached. And what else?
What exactly do you want, Boston?
I want to go after you.
The day I wanted you,
you chose someone else.
Now that you want me,
you just walk in and demand it?
Well, if you're really single,
I truly want to pursue you.
Back then, I didn't want commitment.
But now…
I do.
No.
Why not?
Are you waiting to get with Arnold first?
That's my business.
Why do you have to get involved?
Suit yourself.
But I mean it.
I can wait.
I miss the old days.
We were together almost twenty-four.
We'd rehearse until the theater closed
and the security guard kicked us out.
Then we'd keep rehearsing
on the rooftop of your apartment.
Do you think we could
ever go back to how we were?
Are you serious?
I just want to know
if we'll ever get back together.
I don't know, Dean.
I think a lot has changed.
This new me isn't the same as the old me.
Is it really that hard to
just answer yes or no?
Dean, you and I are both headstrong.
Maybe it's better for us to
stay friends like this than be boyfriends.
No. I liked it better
when we were boyfriends.
Better than being friends.
That's not true.
When we were dating, I was unreasonable.
I got possessive and jealous.
We ended up fighting all the time.
How about this?
Of all the things you asked me,
I can grant you one.
UNBLOCK DEAN_DECHAKORN?
Right now, this is all I can do for you.
Fair enough.
At least right now, I'm one step closer.
Hey, Jack.
I'll be the new Dean for you.
Dean.
That's not right. That's the old Dean.
Just wait and see.
I'm going to be the new Dean for you.
I'm going to be the new Dean!
I'll show you.
This time, it's for real.
I'll wait and see.
Watch it.
Thank you.
We almost caused a scene.
You were right to ask me to come help.
Here.
The orange one?
Mm.
I'm the one who knows you best.
Hey, Arnold.
Irene?
Hi.
Surprised to see you here.
Mm. I'm helping my friend
pick up some things.
He's making costumes for the play.
Ah, the one you're acting in, right?
You're really leveling up these days.
You can do so many things now.
I'm rooting for you. I'll
come watch your play.
Okay. I'll see you around.
Bye-bye.
Was that your friend?
Uh… friend?
Not exactly.
I'm not sure how to put it.
Care to explain?
We were very close back in high school.
But before graduation,
she confessed she liked me.
I didn't respond.
That's why it's kind of awkward.
Shit. That's exactly why
I never bring friends to the talking stage.
Not a single case ends well.
Hey, but that doesn't happen to everyone.
Really? From what I've seen,
everyone has this problem.
Like her and me. Or Jack and Dean.
In this lifetime, I'm
never dating a friend.
Breaking up with a partner is one thing.
Breaking up with a friend… hurts even worse.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Can you please grab that?
Sure.
It's like I just got indirectly rejected.
You're up?
How did I end up here?
You were such a troublemaker last night,
you know that?
And you're heavy as hell.
So how did I end up coming home with you?
Because I didn't want you waking up
regretting you slept with
someone less hot than me.
Gosh.
That's my tee.
We didn't do anything last night, though.
I don't sleep with drunk people,
especially the troublemaking kind.
Come on.
Don't yell at me first thing in
the morning. I'm not ready for that.
Here.
Have some coffee first.
My head is killing me.
You're really passionate about music.
I told you.
I'm soon to be a world-class DJ.
Someone's confident.
How about you hit 100K subscribers first?
For stuff like this,
you must take one step at a time.
On days you miss me,
you can play my playlists.
No need.
Because I won't miss you.
Hm. Smart mouth.
Here.
Your breakfast.
Sleep with me, free breakfast.
Hey, here comes the host.
Hi, James Dean.
Jeez!
I heard that he got paid 10K
just to eat and drink.
That's a lot.
- Should I do it too?
- Yes, you should.
Hold this.
So?
Yeah, I'm James Dean.
The VIP host you've been gossiping about.
Hey, you dare to hire me?
If you do, I'll entertain you too.
And my rate is 15K, not just 10K.
No need to ask why I had to do this job.
Because I'm not rich like you are.
I had to work an honest job
to support my family and myself
so I could study at the same place as you.
If you have more
questions, feel free to ask.
I'm right here to answer.
Stop spreading nonsense behind my back.
As for the one who tried to step on me,
congratulations on leaking the news.
But sorry, this crap can't hurt me.
Stop staring and keep your noses
out of other people's business.
Worry about your own lives.
No more drama.
You finally got over it.
I thought you'd hide
it for the rest of your.
Come.
Let's go rehearse the play.
He's cool.
If it were me getting criticized like
that, I wouldn't dare show up at uni.
Well, he had to face it.
It's the truth.
In the play, you're supposed to
look like you're in love.
So you need to convey that feeling
to the audience. Okay?
Mm.
So today we're going to do a workshop.
Face each other slowly.
Relax and get comfortable.
Slowly close your eyes.
Imagine the person in front of you
is your loved one.
Then slowly open your eyes.
Take a good look at his face.
See if there's anything you like.
Then slowly send your feeling…
to the person in front of you
as much as you can.
Once you feel it, slowly step forward
and hug each other.
Right.
Did you feel it, Arnold?
Hey. Yeah, I felt a lot.
That's great.
Dean?
Yeah, I felt it too.
Okay, that worked.
Try to hold on to that feeling.
Guys, let's rehearse the first scene.
Turn to page one.
Dean, Arnold, sit over here.
Arnold and Dean have amazing chemistry.
Aren't you scared?
They're lovers in the play.
Of course, they need good chemistry.
Want to grab something to eat after this?
I don't have time.
I have to work on the costumes.
We can go to the same place we first met.
I'll take care of you.
But if you don't like crowded
places, my house is free.
Yes, Mom.
I'm on my way.
The traffic shouldn't be too bad.
I should be there in half an hour.
Of course.
See you later, Mom.
Your engine doesn't sound right.
Is it broken?
I think so.
Where are you going? Want a ride?
No.
I'll call my driver.
Hi, Uncle Pong.
My car broke down.
Can you pick me up at the uni?
Ah…
You're at the car wash with my mom's car?
Alright then.
Goodbye.
Well, young master?
Coming with me or taking a motorbike taxi?
So, where are you going?
Hey!
Well, I usually sit in the back
when there's a driver.
Oh, wow.
Are you seriously
treating me like your chauffeur?
Drive safe, Mr. Chauffeur.
I've already sent you the location.
Give you an inch and you take a mile.
Mm.
Okay.
Then this chauffeur will do his best,
young master.
Just sit tight.
Don't go crying to mommy
if you hit your head.
You asshole.
Are you really not coming with me?
You said you wanted to
talk to me about the script.
I have an audition.
Don't you want to come cheer me on?
You should ask Tua and Timmy.
They're not available.
So now it's down to you.
It's fine if you don't come. If I
don't get the part, I'll just cry alone.
You don't care anyway.
Even though you know I'd feel
more confident if someone came with me.
Hey.
What?
Why are you so dramatic?
Don't come.
Just wait here and comfort me after.
Alright!
I'll come.
But I'll come as your
friend, not boyfriend.
Sure thing.
I'll show you different
versions on the way,
and you can tell me which one's best.
Sound good?
So we're taking my car?
Just like old times.
You drive and I'll navigate.
Yeah?
Hi, Mom.
(I haven't heard from you lately.)
(Was the money I sent you enough?)
It was, Mom.
I've got classes and part-time jobs.
Kind of swamped.
Oh, hey. I'm in the faculty play.
I even got paid.
I'll send you some photos
so you can see them in LA.
(Mm. Don't forget to
take some time to rest, son.)
(Whatever it is,
you can always give me a call.)
(If you have some problems,
you can call me anytime.)
(Okay?)
Yes, Mom.
I miss you.
Say hi to Uncle Steve for me, okay?
Okay. Love you, Mom.
Arnold.
Hey.
You're still here?
Yeah. Just finished a call with my mom
and was about to record a TikTok.
What about you?
Can you do the move I taught you?
I practiced a little.
I think I can manage a bit.
Hey, that's great. That's my friend.
Let's try it now.
Action.
Tasty! One bite, and the crunch
stays with you forever.
A new PIZZA flavor is out now.
Tasty! One bite, and the crunch
stays with you forever.
A new PIZZA flavor is out now.
One more time, please.
Make it more fun.
Okay.
Tasty! One bite, and the crunch
stays with you forever.
A new PIZZA flavor is out now.
So so good, I'm not even lying.
Cut!
That's good. I like it.
If it works out, you'll get a call.
Sure.
Good luck.
Thank you.
I like it a lot.
Get home safe.
Thank you.
Come on. It's done.
How was it?
I might get it. They said I did well.
Should we go now? I have to edit my script.
Let me run to the restroom for a second.
You can wait for me in the parking lot.
I like Dean so much, but we can't pick him.
Why not? He was so good.
He hasn't hit 50k followers yet.
The client won't say yes,
no matter how hard we push him.
Gosh, what a shame.
Come on.
But he was so good just now.
Chef's kiss.
Right. His delivery was perfect.
Did you see when he took a bite?
Yum.
Hi, Mom.
Gosh. I thought you
weren't going to make it.
You took forever.
Once you're in the industry,
you can't be like this.
My car broke down. That's why I'm late.
Yeah?
So how did you get here?
I booked a ride.
Hello, ma'am.
I'm Rome, Raffy's friend.
Hello, there.
Thanks for bringing our Little Raf here.
I've been asking him to come.
I thought he was going to bail on me.
Little Raf, huh?
Are you going to shoot the show
with this outfit and hair?
I had class earlier and
didn't have any other clothes with me.
I don't think this will do.
Good thing I told the staff
to prepare a costume for you.
Please take Little Raf to get makeup done
and change into the new outfit.
Of course.
Little Raffy, this way, please.
Thank you.
This is amazing.
I didn't know you liked Indian food.
I've never tried it before.
This is my first time.
I never paid attention to it either.
But after coming to Little India often
to buy fabrics, I gave it a try.
And I realized I'd been
missing out all my life.
That good, huh?
Guess I should try it too.
- Can I go now?
- Go ahead.
And take a bite.
Come on, you barely dipped it.
Mm.
Good?
Mhm.
Wow, it's really good.
Come on. You eat like a kid.
Here.
Thank you.
Why do you like making clothes, Tua?
When I was a kid, I loved watching parades
at my family's amusement park.
I thought the costumes were
cute, and I loved dressing up.
What about you?
Actually, I don't really know.
I just do whatever makes me money.
At first, I didn't feel anything special
about my jobs.
But after a while, I started to enjoy them.
Good.
That's different from me.
I'm lucky I don't have
to worry about money.
I get to do what I like.
Yeah, that's really different.
Ever since my mom remarried
and moved to LA with her new husband,
I've had to take on more jobs
to support myself.
She sends me money,
but I don't want to burden her.
Anyway, working is fun.
I really admire you.
Sometimes I can't help wondering
if I'd have come this far
without my family's support.
You're really amazing, Arnold.
Thank you.
Pass me a tissue.
ARNOLD, WANNA MODEL
FOR A SHOOT FOR ME?
UH… CAN I THINK ABOUT IT FIRST?
YOU'LL GET PAID TOO.
Tua, Boston just DMed me.
He wants me to model
for a shoot at his studio.
He'll pay me too.
If you're not okay
with it, I can just not go.
I'm okay.
I don't think he's after anything with you.
And whatever we had
ended a long time ago.
Mm.
Are you sure?
I am.
Okay.
What exactly does Boston want from me?
Now, let's talk about Miss Ran's son.
I heard he showed potential as an actor
since he was young. Is that true, Miss Ran?
Little Raf has always
been confident in front of people.
I had him take acting, singing,
and music classes when he was little.
Wow, he's very skillful.
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
What about you, Little Raf?
Are you planning to
follow in your mom's footsteps
and enter the entertainment industry?
Uh, I am.
If any producers are watching this,
feel free to contact me directly.
Wow. You're his manager too, yes?
He's a handsome young man, and
the son of Miss Ran, a top-tier actress.
I'm sure we can look forward to
a new rising star in the industry.
Lastly, Miss Ran, could you tell the audience
what projects they'll be seeing you in?
I have a TV drama coming out
at the end of the year.
But I'd also like to share that Little Raf
will be starring in his faculty play.
He plays the lead role,
so please stay tuned for that.
Wow, like mother, like son.
Thank you so much today, Miss Ranchalee
and Little Raffy, for speaking with us.
Until next time. Goodbye.
Cut.
Miss Ran, thank you so much again.
It's truly my pleasure. Thank you so much.
Can we get a photo, please?
Of course.
I've always been your fan.
Thank you so much.
And thank you for interviewing us.
Looking good.
Do you want a picture too?
Come on, step in.
She's your fan too.
I dressed up for this.
One, two, three.
One, two.
Okay.
Raffy.
Next time, if you don't
want to come, just tell her.
I have to.
It's a family show.
Are you trying to dig something up?
I'm not digging up anything.
But…
You do like to brag.
You told your mom
you got the lead role in the play.
I didn't tell her.
She just filled in the blanks herself.
I never told my mom I had the lead.
I know I'm just a supporting character.
Hey, I didn't mean it like that.
And I'm not blaming you for anything.
I'm just telling the truth.
I only got a supporting role.
And no matter what I do,
my mom will never be proud of me.
That's why I didn't want to come.
Then next time, just tell her
you don't want to come.
What's she gonna do?
Hey, trust me.
I've pulled every kind of
stubborn stunt with my family.
If you insist on saying no,
what can anyone do to you?
Come on. Clean off
your makeup and change.
I'll take you back.
Come on, guys. Let's cheers!
- Come on, guys. Let's cheers!
- Cheers!
Listen.
Our backdrop isn't empty anymore
because we've got a sponsor!
Nice work, Timmy.
But the money you got
only covers the stage set.
It doesn't include the costumes yet.
What?
It's just the first step, dude.
We should be happy
with the small wins first.
I'll pitch more sponsors later.
I'm not letting our
actors go on stage naked.
As for you, Jack. Don't be stubborn.
We have to show the sponsor's logo.
The size is exactly
what they asked for. Okay?
Okay.
Ooh! Put it here.
Bring us another bottle of whiskey.
Tell Pink to put it on Jack's tab.
Tonight, it's Jack's treat.
Cheers!
Look how happy you are.
I think the 50K we got today
is going straight into tonight's drinks.
Tua won't get a share.
Of course, he will.
Right, Tua?
Tua.
Hey.
Is something wrong?
Nothing.
Then let's cheers.
Just let me know if something's up.
I'm gonana use the bathroom.
Don't take too long.
Yeah.
Here.
Do you model often?
This is my first time.
I've always wondered what it's like.
If you're ready, take off your shirt.
I'll set up the camera.
How should I pose?
However you like.
Any pose you feel comfortable with.
We'll start now.
If I grab your ass once,
how much will that cost, James Dean?
If you're so desperate to grab an ass,
why don't you try your dad's?
Whoa, you prick.
Aren't you a hooker?
I'm not.
I'm just a host.
And if I were selling myself, I wouldn't
sell it to some ugly asshole like you.
Mouthy, aren't you?
Ugly face and an ugly personality too,
you motherfucker!
Let go of me!
What the hell are you guys doing?
Son of a bitch!
I was negotiating with a host.
Why the fuck did you butt in?
So you're not gonna stop?
Got a problem?
Just go.
Let's leave.
Hey.
Aren't Jack and Dean
coming back to the table?
I gotta go. There's an emergency.
What?!
You're leaving too?
Tua!
Fine, I'll drink alone.
Ouch. Jack, that hurts.
I see you don't like
being the lead in a romantic play.
You'd rather be the lead in an action one.
Thanks a lot anyway.
Without you, I'd have been
outnumbered and beaten up.
I won't let anything happen to you.
Besides, those guys were real assholes.
True.
If someone like me is going to get groped,
I should at least get paid for it.
You've still got the nerve
to joke about it, huh?
Ouch, Jack. It hurts.
What can I do?
I can't change my past.
All I can do is decide how to deal with it.
From now on, I'm not going to be afraid.
If someone tries to pick a fight,
I'll freaking fight back.
When I said I wanted to change,
I meant it.
I want to be the new Dean for you.
Do you still love me?
I don't want to throw that word around.
But I really want to hear…
if you still love me or not.
You got your answer?
Mm.
How long have you and Tua been close?
Quite long.
Since our first year.
You two don't look like you're friends.
Looks like something else.
Actually, I came to see you today
because I wanted to talk about that.
Stop making Tua uncomfortable.
Tua doesn't like you.
Why?
Do you like him?
I'm not sure.
That's not a good enough answer.
If you're not sure, you'd better back off.
I feel good about him,
and I care about him a lot.
Even if I'm not sure about my feelings yet,
I'm sure someone like Tua
is too good for you.
And how are you so sure
Tua doesn't have feelings for me?
And if I leave him alone,
what do I get out of it?
If you've got something better to offer me…
I might change my mind.
What are you two doing?
Whoa. You really came all this way?
Are you afraid I might
do something to your close friend?
And what are you doing?
I'm not doing anything. We're just talking.
Right?
Arnold's worried about you.
He wants me to stay away from you.
What did you say just now, Arnold?
How do you feel about Tua again?
I…
What exactly were you two talking about?
About me?
Well, you've had my attention lately.
Who else would I be talking about?
Leave Tua alone.
(Next Episode)
Timmy and I spoke with the sponsor.
They wanted leads with a large following.
So they suggested Raffy
take the lead role too.
Even though we
had a fair casting…
Why are you stealing
the lead role from me?
What the hell are you talking about?
Are you playing dumb?
Why were you drinking alone?
I was bored…
needed something to kill time.
I can accompany you.
I don't really have an answer.
I don't even know
what this feeling is…
But I like you, Arnold.