Again, bro.
Again.
Here, give it to me.
Here.
Come on, give it to me.
Get ready.
One,
two,
three!
♪ The stars twinkle, the moon curves ♪
Pull.
♪ A gentle breeze
sways the willow branches ♪
♪ The two of us, working late into the night,
sneak up to the base of the wall ♪
♪ Sneaking around, peeking through ♪
Again.
Again, bro.
Come on.
Here.
Hold on, bro.
Come on.
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 16]
Mr. Zhou has something important today.
You all, stay sharp.
Not a single mistake is allowed,
understand?
Understood!
Chief Zhang.
Zhou Rong didn't go to his company today.
He's moved all his people to his villa.
Looks like something's happening today.
Song Xing,
notify everyone to be ready to act
at any moment.
Alright, in a minute.
Song Xing!
You see,
I just called Li Qian,
but she suddenly hung up on me.
I wanted to ask what was going on,
but now I can't get through to her.
Is this really the time to be doing that?
Got it.
[Baoku Fresh Produce Delivery Center]
Delivery.
There are guests inside.
Boss instructed to turn off
the surveillance cameras today.
Rest assured, Gai.
Go get the suitcase.
Okay.
[Baoku Fresh Produce Delivery Center]
Gai.
You punk.
Come here.
Do you think this is the right place
to park?
Well, I...
Go park in the backyard.
Got it, got it. Right away.
Hurry up.
Why didn't you say anything
when I was parking?
I've already parked here, and now
you start bringing up all this nonsense.
These are all things
you need to watch out for.
Hurry.
Got it.
Alright, let's go.
Let's go inside.
Who are you?
The estate is too big.
I got lost.
You are...
One of Mr. Zhou's guests?
This way please.
I'll take you to Mr. Zhou.
If he's busy, forget it.
Please.
I wouldn't dare neglect
Mr. Zhou's guest.
Please.
Mr. Zhou,
your guest has arrived.
It's about that matter Du Cong mentioned.
Mr. Zhou.
Take her to the room next to the study
and wait there for a bit.
Yes.
Please wait for me for a moment.
Please.
Everything is normal.
I heard.
Mr. Zhou.
Mr. Zhu.
First time in Sanjiangkou, right?
Hello, Mr. Zhou.
I'm Zhu Yifei.
Mr. Zhu.
Mr. Zhou, even you didn't think
I was the driver—
so how could the police?
Yes, exactly.
True concealment is
blending into the crowd.
Mr. Zhu, your way of doing things
really is
different.
-Uncle Yifei.
Dear Mr. Zhou, sorry
to have kept you waiting.
My apologies.
I'm Zhu Yifei,
and these are all my buddies.
Zheng!
Here!
Chubby!
Scrawny!
Here!
We are all family.
Mr. Zhu, you act with such caution.
It's truly admirable.
Well, actually, I get motion sickness
in small cars,
so I arrived earlier in a larger vehicle.
Understood, understood.
What larger vehicle?
Shall we go inside first?
Sure, sure.
Isn't he insane?
Chubby.
Here.
Take someone
and bring the suitcase over.
Got it.
Let's go, bro.
Please go inside.
Don't stand on ceremony.
Please, please.
He really doesn't stand on ceremony,
does he?
Please, have a seat.
Mr. Zhou.
Keep watch.
Mr. Zhou,
let's not beat around the bush.
I usually
keep a low profile.
This time I came in person,
first because
this deal involves
a significant amount of money,
and second because
I wanted to meet you myself, Mr. Zhou.
You're young and promising, Mr. Zhou.
We've made the right decision to come.
Alright.
I plan to stay in Sanjiangkou
for 2 to 3 days.
I hope that during this time,
we can close the deal.
No problem, right?
No problem.
I've got the money ready.
Good.
Mr. Zhu,
this is just the deposit.
Can I take a look at the goods now?
It's just a minor trick,
so that we can
pass the security check
without showing the shape of the money.
Just an extra mechanism.
-High-tech.
Can't you just pour it all in?
What now?
Now,
I'll take my leave first.
In half an hour,
someone will deliver the goods here
in person.
Leave?
You want to leave?
But I haven't even seen the goods yet.
That's right.
In half an hour,
you will see the goods.
Then please, Mr. Zhu,
stay for another half hour with me.
So you still don't trust me.
Well, I haven't seen the goods.
♪ Doubt ♪
Here's the thing, Mr. Zhou.
I never do transactions with the goods
right in front of me.
That's my rule.
Please understand.
I also have my rule:
cash on delivery.
One million is not a small amount.
If I don't see the goods today,
you, you,
and all the vehicles—
none of you are leaving.
And if I refuse?
It wasn't me.
It wasn't me, either.
Then it must've been Mr. Zhu.
It must've been you.
Bro.
Is your last name Huo?
Your mentor's cousin
and my second aunt's nephew
are brothers-in-law.
In that case,
we are also relatives.
There's a place for entertainment
in the basement of Fenglinwan Hotel.
If you guys are interested,
you can go find
a manager surnamed Zhou.
She'll make the arrangements for you.
Try the services in Sanjiangkou, alright?
If this deal goes through,
it'll be good for both of us,
right?
My mentor does have a cousin.
I made it up.
Since there's a family connection here,
we can talk things through.
I'm willing to make an exception.
Thank you then, Mr. Zhu.
Please sit.
Okay.
[Protect Forest Resources,
Strictly Prevent Forest Fires]
[Depart in 15 minutes.]
Depart in 15 minutes.
[Go to Zhou Rong's villa.
Sturdy will meet you there.]
Go to Zhou Rong's villa.
Sturdy will meet you there.
Got it.
[Got it.]
[Photographs of Cultural Relics]
[Purchase Receipt]
Why are you driving so slow?
Drive faster.
Boss.
I-I need to take this call.
You'd better not use your phone
while driving.
But it's my boss calling.
He must need something from me.
[Gai]
Gai, I'll be there in a few minutes.
The owner of Jinxin Repair Shop
in Qilihe
just called me.
He said there's a Xiali taxi
with its rear bumper dented.
That must be them, Gai.
Can you ask the owner
to stall them for a bit?
I'll head over once I'm done here.
No need.
I know those two bastards.
As soon as I'm done here,
I'll take you to their house
to corner them.
[Protect Forest Resources,
Strictly Prevent Forest Fires]
Thanks, Gai.
Got it.
[Gai]
Alright.
Did we crash?
[Loyalty]
Okay.
Okay, got it.
The fresh produce truck
that delivered food
to Zhou Rong yesterday
went there again today.
How can they possibly eat that much?
Even if they can eat a lot,
they can't go through
an entire truckload in a day.
Maybe they just have a lot of people?
Go ask our cafeteria
how often they restock.
How can Zhou Rong's men
possibly outnumber us?
The bianzhong has arrived.
Let's go!
Buddy,
you can't blame this all on me.
How could you just
park on the side of the road like that?
Did you rear-end me or not?
Yes.
I should take full responsibility.
What are you doing?
Calling the police.
Let's not trouble the police.
It's such a small matter.
We can settle it ourselves.
Let's just leave it at that.
Leave it at that?
I'm easy to talk to.
If it were someone else,
you wouldn't be able to leave today.
Buddy.
This is a Mercedes.
What can
100 yuan even cover?
How much do you want?
Since this guy is willing to pay,
I should ask for at least 500.
Look at this—
the bumper is smashed.
At the very least,
it's going to cost this much.
Where am I supposed to steal
5,000 yuan for you?
If you can't steal
5,000 yuan for me,
t-then I'll call the police.
What do you want?
What are you doing?
Your car crashed mine!
A gentleman uses his tongue,
not his fists!
We can talk this over.
A gentleman uses his tongue,
not his fists!
A gentleman uses his tongue...
A gentleman uses his tongue,
not his fists.
Isn't this just about 5,000 yuan?
I'll pay.
Alright?
Boss,
what does this have to do with you?
He's paying me 5,000.
What kind of situation is this?
You think I don't know traffic rules?
This is rear-ending.
You're supposed to
take full responsibility.
Keep quiet.
Sir,
it's our fault.
I'll give you 5,000 yuan,
but don't call the police.
Okay.
Only 5,000?
10,000?
I'll give you 10,000,
but promise you won't call the police.
Wait,
why should you give him money?
Boss.
50,000.
One penny less and I'll call the cops.
You little runt.
How can you be so shameless?
Why are you talking so...
See if I dare to call the police!
50,000!
50,000 it is!
I agree.
Okay.
But I don't have that much cash
on me right now.
Go and
give Mr. Zhou a call.
Tell him to bring the money right away.
Hurry up!
Just ignore him.
He wouldn't dare.
Watch me!
Make the call!
Why do you have so much to say?
You're really...
It's no big deal. You...
Just let him call the police.
Pay to avoid trouble, okay?
[Photographs of Cultural Relics]
Pay to avoid trouble.
He wouldn't dare at all.
What if he does?
Look at his runty face.
[Purchase Receipt]
2.5 million.
[2.5 million yuan]
I'll give you 800,000.
[800,000 yuan]
For such a big deal,
you say you'll give me 800,000.
Then what do you make?
You think I'm doing this for money?
[Purchase Receipt]
[Its estimated value is 43 million yuan.]
That Mr. Zhou you just mentioned—
is he Zhou Rong from Rongcheng Group?
Who?
Is he?
I don't know him.
How dare he lie to me?
Mr. Zhu.
How much longer
do we have to wait?
That bastard Liu Bei ran off.
Have the goods arrived?
We ran into a bit of trouble
during the transportation
of the goods.
How about this?
Mr. Zhou,
you keep the money for now.
Once I've dealt with it,
I'll contact you right away.
So what kind of problem is it?
Just a minor issue—
easy to fix.
Mr. Zhu, I...
You two.
Stay.
They just left like that?
Wait, those two were here
to pull a fast one, weren't they?
Trying to scam me, weren't they?
That shouldn't be.
Is Zhu Yifei not planning
to stay in this business anymore?
L-L-Let Fang Yong go back first.
Are we getting back on the road or not?
Yes, yes, we are.
Let me take this call.
Ren.
I'm on my way.
It went well.
Very well.
Got it.
What now?
The deal's been called off.
My boss told me
to take you straight home.
No need to meet the boss anymore.
Rong.
What are you looking for? Let me help you.
Do you have a charging cable
for this phone?
Pull.
This is about it.
This could work.
It worked.
It worked. It worked.
♪ The sun is setting ♪
Let's try again, bro.
Again.
What the hell.
Lang Bowen's phone?
Wasn't this phone smashed
and burned?
Exactly. D-Didn't I smash it?
You did.
I saw it with my own eyes
that you smashed it.
How is it back again?
The right side is too high. Move it down.
Let me see.
A bit more. A bit more.
Still too high. Move it down a bit.
All of you, get out.
We're almost done here, Rong.
Get out!
Leave. Go on.
Hurry up!
That guy Lu has been causing trouble
for you again and again.
He even went after Ye Jian.
You said it yourself to kill him,
to let him know who's in charge
in Sanjiangkou.
I was just saying it offhand!
Come on, give it to me.
Rong!
Huo Zheng
picked it up from the ground just now.
Amazing.
It's been there for 6 months
and we never noticed it,
but he saw it a-as soon as he came in?
This is...
Unreasonable,
isn't it?
It's way too unreasonable.
Before they came,
I had someone clean the room.
I'll go ask them
if anyone has seen this phone.
How did it go?
No one saw it.
Right?
It's obvious that this phone
was brought by Zhu Yifei himself.
But how did they even get
this phone?
How would I know?
That guy Huo just came in
and gave me the phone!
Rong, did you take your medication today?
What medication!
Things are getting
more and more confusing now!
That Zhu Yifei came in
acting all mysterious, right?
One moment this guy is Mr. Zhu,
the next moment that guy is Mr. Zhu.
Is he crazy or something?
I can't figure out
Zhu Yifei's
game,
but that guy he brought,
Huo Zheng, is a badass.
His nickname is "Huoxiang Zhengqi Water."
He used to be a professional hitman
and has several lives on his hands.
He's been out of sight
for the past few years,
and who knows
why he ended up working for
that Zhu guy.
Zhu Yifei
wants to kill me?
But I have no beef with him!
Rong,
maybe we should put
the matter of the bianzhong
on hold for a bit.
I feel like it's too complicated.
The deal can be put on hold for now,
but we can't just stay here
like sitting ducks.
Have Li Penggai
stay here with a few people to keep watch.
You take everyone else out
and go find Zhu Yifei.
And after we find him?
After you find him,
don't alert him.
Figure out what he's up to.
If he dares to move against me...
Understood.
It worked, bro.
Put me down.
Here.
Alright.
Bro,
I'll go first.
No.
I'm worried the rope might not be
strong enough.
I'll go up first.
Come on, bro. Come up.
Come up. Come on.
A bit higher.
Bro,
let's go down the mountain
and find some food.
Why go down the mountain?
We're going in during the day?
What's wrong?
It's such a big estate—
there are definitely people
guarding it.
People?
I'm so hungry I'd eat anything.
Eat people?
I couldn't bring myself to do that.
You're still bound by morals and ethics.
Open a history book—
every page is filled with stories of
people eating people.
Bro, let me.
My turn.
Let's go.
Bro.
They've all left.
Our chance has come.
It's God's will.
These past few days, God has been
testing our patience.
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
♪ Oh Gimme ♪
♪ Dance me in the richness ♪
♪ Raining make it rain ♪
♪ Oh cash is my revolution ♪
♪ Get your head in the game,
we're all smart people here ♪
♪ Don't drag your feet,
even gold slips through slow hands ♪
♪ I beat it, I beat it ♪
♪ Aye aye aye aye yo ♪
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
♪ Tore down the kang in my old home,
dug up a pixiu ♪
♪ Ancestors bless me—
your boy's on the rise now ♪
♪ Hit the streets to buy New Year goods ♪
♪ Hit the streets to buy New Year goods,
haggling prices down ♪
♪ Whatever's expensive, I'll buy it—
today it's all about splurging ♪
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
I haven't tried Bowen's birthday.
Or maybe it's Yangyang's birthday.
Are you leaving?
Mr. Zhou.
Who sent you?
Du Cong introduced me.
You didn't come earlier or later—
had to be today, huh?
Who exactly are you?
We've met before.
Don't you remember?
The day of the rear-end collision, right?
That wasn't a coincidence, was it?
It indeed wasn't a coincidence,
but fate's arrangement.
You've got a sense of humor, huh?
I like you.
Let's go inside and talk more—
about fate's arrangement.
Hurry up and eat.
We've still got work to do.
Who are you?
W-What's that noise?
Gai.
A chick came
looking for Mr. Zhou today.
Can't you pay a bit more attention
to your image?
You know, Chao,
it's been 5 years.
The elastic in my pants
has pretty much worn out.
If people see this,
they'll get the wrong idea
that we're just perverts.
Chao.
This scene right now
really does make it hard
not to get any wrong ideas.
Looks like we can only go like this.
Why are you going to such lengths
to get close to me?
Which girl in Sanjiangkou
wouldn't want to get close to you?
I know what they're after.
But what about you?
I'm not like them.
They're just after money.
And what are you after?
You're kind of scaring me.
Let's have a drink first and talk.
I'm also used to talking after a drink.
What are you looking for?
I-I'm checking the time.
You're
here looking for this phone, right?
The car crash that day was arranged
by you guys.
You are with Du Cong.
I'm not with him.
Du Cong went to pick someone up
and isn't in the villa today.
You're with Zhu Yifei then.
You guys came for this phone, right?
What are you talking about?
Still pretending!
Zhu Yifei's deal with me
was just a cover!
You guys are just here
to get the password to this phone,
aren't you?
What are you doing?
Trying to hit me now?
What are you thinking?
Trying to escape?
This place is full of my people.
Don't even think about escaping!