There's a perfectly good staircase,
and no one ever uses it.
It's been a while
since you've set foot on this seabed.
The troublemaker of the Great Hall.
That was a long time ago, Alaira.
Was it though?
I hear you've stirred up trouble again.
Word is, you've taken on a new apprentice.
You know already?
Word travels fast.
I mean, they might be tied, right?
To the "Brimmed Caps"?
It's been four years
since forbidden magic was used.
She's an important lead.
That's not why.
She hasn't taken the exam yet,
so she isn't officially my apprentice.
What? Not yet?
It's too soon.
And the timing's bad.
Oh, that's right.
This time of year, the Dadah Range
where exams are held…
Is at its highest elevation.
I can't send her out there now.
Her life would be at risk.
Hey, Agott?
Are we really doing this?
The master isn't even here.
THE TRIAL AT DADAH RANGE
You test alone no matter when you do it.
But I just got here.
I passed when I was ten.
Everyone takes it to become an apprentice.
The conditions never change.
I see.
The first test is the
"Consent of the Crown."
You can only bring
three magical contraptions and materials.
You have to reach the peak
of Dadah Range without anyone's help
and bring back the diadem herb
that grows there.
The guidance orb that shows the way
to any destination,
and the vapor bubble for drinking water.
That's probably all you can manage.
Now go.
Oh, and, um…
Do you have any shoes?
- Shoes?
- Those shoes are contraptions too, right?
I saw the soles glowing
when you and Master Qifrey
were flying around.
So, if you don't mind, those shoes,
maybe you can lend them to me?
That's too much to ask! I'm sorry!
Forget I asked!
I'll lend them to you.
- Just hurry up.
- Thanks…
And go!
I forgot to tell you,
but you can only take the test once.
If you fail,
you can't be approved as
Master Qifrey's apprentice.
You'll have to leave the atelier.
I suddenly feel so alone,
but I've got to do my best!
There's no turning back.
I wonder how you use the guidance orb.
It must be telling me to go this way.
Okay!
It's just hiking. No big deal.
I can do it!
Agott said she passed
when she was ten!
If she did it at ten…
I'm sure it's a piece of cake!
No way.
Don't tell me…
That's Dadah Range?
The guidance orb is pointing up.
So it must be there.
I never thought it'd be floating
in the sky.
Ta-da!
The shoes I borrowed from Agott!
Hup!
The seal is split with half on each foot.
Make sure they don't shift.
Align them perfectly…
Wow! I'm really floating!
It's like Master Qifrey said.
I'm like a newborn foal.
But…
I flew.
If I can fly,
I'll be at the top in no time.
All right!
I'll give it my best!
You'll get used to it soon
and be running around in no time.
I'll get used to it soon…
- Here's the application form. Thanks.
- Of course.
- Totorei, number 12.
- Yes.
If you lived in the Hall,
you wouldn't have to travel for this.
You can bring your apprentice.
The Great Hall is the witches' stronghold.
It has everything you need.
Then I'll just come when I need to.
I've brought it here.
Thanks.
Your disdain for the Great Hall runs deep.
Keep a close eye on your apprentices.
Kids of that age,
you never know what they'll get up to
with no adults around.
Whoa, easy!
My balance has gotten much better.
I think I can go a little higher.
A brushbuddy!
I've never seen one before!
The shoes are all muddy.
Oh no! The seal's rubbed off!
No! Is it because I wiped it?!
Oh no, no, no!
I know! I'll draw over it!
The ink all spilled.
What should I do?
Maybe it's over for me.
Huh? Hey, Agott, have you seen Coco?
It's almost time for dinner.
Coco's not here.
She's at Dadah Range for the test.
What?! Alone?
But she just got here!
You didn't stop her?
Hey, Agott!
You normally take the test
before you come.
That's true, but…
If she can't even pass such a simple test,
she shouldn't be an apprentice.
You know,
I hate people who can't do what I can do.
I gain nothing being with them.
And an outsider at that.
Don't worry.
She'll be back without even trying.
This time of year, the Dadah Range
floats higher than ever.
Not even my sylph shoes can fly that high.
She doesn't even know the rules,
has no sense of danger.
I don't want an outsider like that
in our world.
You're not going to eat, Tetia?
I will,
but I don't know,
I just have this heavy feeling.
Seconds for me.
Am I the only one worried? Sheesh!
Either way,
we can only wait for Master Qifrey.
Up! Go!
Whoa…
Nope!
I tried using the little ink I had left,
but I can't even lift off anymore.
They're so soaked, it just smears.
What if I draw
directly on the soles of my feet?
No, I can't! Drawing magic
directly on the body is forbidden.
I don't know what kind of magic
to use right now.
Agott was right.
Wow!
Anyone can draw magic,
but not everyone can draw it well.
Maybe only people with special talent
can become witches after all.
Everyone has been drawing magic
since they were little.
What could I possibly do?
Here.
That's right. Straight.
Whoops!
Up we go.
Hey! Come here!
Wow.
I had no idea this village
had such a wonderful artisan.
This is magic.
I do.
I have it! My own magic!
If I moisten it a bit in the water…
My cloak that was wet
is now stiff from the dried mud.
I think I can draw with this.
It's normal to be a little unsteady
with a new tool.
Then I'll just change it
to a tool I'm used to.
My fingertips will be able to move freely.
Freely…
Okay.
Good morning, Brushbuddy.
You're not very cautious, are you?
It's not the prettiest seal.
A properly drawn one would have
a sigil in the center
evenly surrounded by signs.
But I also learned that uneven signs
can create too much force.
So I tried making
just one really long one.
I don't know if it'll work though.
You're coming with me?
Okay, then be sure to hang on tight!
I'm going to close the seal!
What? Why?!
Did I get the direction of the sign wrong?
It worked!
I'm flying with my very own magic!
A real flying coat!
It's a dream come true.
The things I learned helping Mom
helped me with my magic.
I never would've imagined.
The diadem herb is up higher.
The diadem herb!
Mom…
Wait for me, Mom!
I'll take responsibility for what I did.
I promise!
What?! So Coco went to Dadah Range
alone to take the test?
Yes! Yes, yes!
It's too dangerous!
We have to stop her now!
But if we stop her, won't she fail?
It's too soon for her
to take the test in any case.
She's not like us who grew up with magic.
If something were to happen to Coco…
It's not only the girl that'll be lost.
All right.
Huh?
- Coco!
Thank goodness!
Coco! You're okay!
We were so worried about you!
Agott!
I got the "Consent of the Crown."
Have I proved myself?
Coco.
Using magic recklessly
without preparation
or basic knowledge is extremely dangerous.
You should already know that.
A single misstep could have been fatal.
Don't ever do this again.
I'm sorry, Master Qifrey.
And besides, there's no need
to brave danger to prove yourself.
You're already my apprentice.
This is…
It's proof you're a witch.
A source of pride,
and a restraint you wear on your head
to keep you from abusing magic.
As long as you wear it,
don't forget its weight.
The witch hat will always
be watching over your magic.
Take good care of it.
I will!
Good. Then shall we head back up?
Yes.
First, dinner!
You should also take a bath.
Subtitle translation by: Emily Noguchi
The seed has sprouted.
EPISODE 4: AN ENCOUNTER IN KALHN