[woman] You had an accident.
We cleaned you up.
-Cancer, it's a godless disease, Mom.
-[patient grunts]
It's not your fault.
Should we give her some space?
That was really intense.
Morgan, I know that your generation
is terrified of anything
that doesn't make you feel good,
but this is one
of those full-circle life moments
that you need to be present for.
The woman changed my diapers.
Now it's my turn to change hers.
These are acts of love.
It just felt like she didn't want us
all standing around
watching her while it happ--
-[raised voice] It was an act of love.
-Okay.
[woman] Do any of you know
how much I'm carrying on my back
trying to scrape together an early
birthday party for my dying mother
while launching a mayoral campaign?
What are you two bringing to the table?
Have you even bought her a gift yet?
She just took a turn.
Well, that didn't stop Natalie.
Speaking of,
I need one of you to pop by the store.
-I had Leanne set aside some decorations.
-Oh, Mom, Mom, I can grab them.
Yeah, and it's looking like they are able
to push the candidates' town hall a week.
Good news. Tell your brother and sister
about the gift you got your nonna.
Uh, pasta bowls from the Amalfi trip
Kevin and I took last summer.
[whispers] She's on a feeding tube.
What does she need bowls for?
[Natalie] What did you say?
-Mom?
-What did you say?
-What? I didn't say…
-[woman] Mom?
[shouting] What do you want
for your birthday from the kids?
I don't want a birthday!
What do you want for your birthday
from Nicholas and Morgan?
-Who are they?
-[Nicky] Oh my God.
That's a good question, Nonna.
Your father gave me a necklace…
In Acapulco that you lost
on your honeymoon.
-We know. Get your nonna a necklace.
-[Nonna grunts]
It was a diamond necklace!
Nonna, I'm a public school teacher.
Okay, Morgan,
the woman doesn't know who we are.
I don't think she cares
if it's real diamonds.
Yeah, I know--
Just something cheap and nostalgic
she can cherish during her final days.
Is that so much to ask? Nicky,
help your sister with this, for once.
-For once?
-All right, do a good deed, for me.
I'm stepping out.
Okay, fine. Thank you.
-[Morgan] Are you going?
-[Natalie] Yeah.
[woman] Nobody expects
you to be like Natalie.
She is an anomaly in this family.
Confident, ambitious.
She doesn't have to work for that body.
But could the two of you for once
set your differences aside
and make my mother's death easy on me?
-Stop screaming!
-All right.
[Nonna grunts]
[shouts] She needs a nap!
[opening theme music playing]
[music ends]
Because while you might reach that island
and finally see those gardenias,
will it have been worth it in the end…
[coughing]
…if their sweet smell
is corrupted by the smoke
billowing in from the bridge
you burned to get there?
On that uplifting note, everybody,
I would like to remind you
that this is a fire-free zone, okay?
-[laughter]
-Okay? We have a lot of hardwood flooring.
If you wanted to contribute
to the food drive,
Rose would be happy to take your name.
[techno music playing]
[music continues]
Hi, Helen.
[exhales]
[man] You organize your drawers
like a serial killer.
Yeah, that's the intention. Hi.
[door opens]
-Fuck!
-[Rose] Reverend Nicholas!
[Nicky] Yeah. Rose?
Oh, we're just letting
ourselves in now, huh?
We might need to chat
about boundaries a little bit, Rose.
-The door wasn't locked.
-Well, okay.
-Did I hear something, though?
-No, I was just on the phone.
-Oh. The sponsorship team can do Friday.
-Uh-huh.
Okay, great.
Well, that could have been an email,
but thank you for letting me know,
and I'll see you tomorrow, okay?
-[Rose] Okay.
-[Nicky] Okay.
[door opens]
[Nicky] Bye-bye.
-[door lock clicks]
-Bye.
[Morgan] Imagine you get invited
to a game night,
and someone hides your crutches.
They're, like, throwing stuff,
they're fighting.
It's amazing.
[inhales deeply]
[exhales] Okay.
Can you unlock the door, please?
Oh.
Okay.
Uh… You always, like, pull away
from my touch.
-I pull away from your touch?
-Yeah, you…
-I'm at work.
-You pull away.
I know, but, like, you know
physical intimacy is my love language.
-I express my inside thoughts to you.
-Yeah, I know.
I think you're seeing
your therapist too much.
He told me you'd say that.
Okay, I'm sorry I don't want
to have sex with you
in a school parking lot.
I'm not trying-- You… you do this.
You ruin these moments.
[mocking] You, like, make it so… Whatever.
You… wreck things.
It's whatever. It's stupid.
-Okay, can you just unlock the door?
-Yes.
[door unlocks]
Thank you.
[kids speaking indistinctly]
What is that? What is this?
What does it look like?
Yeah, Morgan, I wanted to do a nice thing
for the woman I love more
than, like, my beating heart in my chest.
Are you proposing
by throwing a ring at my back?
-What am I supposed to do with this?
-I don't know, that's up to you.
It's up to you.
Whoa.
[man sighs]
Okay.
It's very nice.
I know.
I don't need, like,
a fucking flash mob, you know?
But I think I at least deserve something
that resembles a proper proposal.
-You know?
-Of course. Yeah. Heard.
-Um, I'll see you later?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-All right, I love you.
I love you too.
Okay.
All right.
Bye, have fun at work.
-Thanks, bye.
-Bye.
[gasps]
[whispers] Don't be so reactive.
[school bell rings]
[horn blaring]
Did I tell you I'm being honored
by Out and Loud next month
for the work that I do for them?
Raising money for queer people
so that they can be "out and loud"?
Mm-hmm. You've mentioned that a few times.
And yet, I can't surprise my boyfriend
at work because according to his church,
he can be gay but can't have a boyfriend.
They expect me to be nonpracticing, yeah.
I wanna practice
with my nonpracticing boyfriend,
not be in my mid-thirties
keeping our relationship a secret
from our friends and family.
You had one job last summer,
and that was to fix my roof.
Okay.
And you got greedy, okay?
And now look at us.
I couldn't help myself.
[inhales] I got a thing
for The Book of Mormon.
-Do ya?
-Yeah.
-Well, I'm not Mormon, so…
-I know, but you kinda dress like one.
-[Nicky] Mm-hmm.
-[boyfriend chuckles]
I told you,
as soon as my mom's campaign is done,
I'm gonna find a new congregation.
And we can, you know…
-Shh.
-…practice outwardly and loudly.
-I believe you, okay?
-For as long as we'd like.
Okay, I'm gonna book that cruise
this year, with or without you.
And I… I can't wait to go
on that cruise with you.
-Yup.
-I can't…
-I can't wait to get norovirus together.
-That's the best part!
You didn't need to come with me.
Yeah, well, Mom thought
you needed a babysitter at 30, so…
Yeah, well, she thought
I needed one growing up too.
Where were you then, Reverend?
Probably praying for God's protection
from your bad attitude
and all of those cigarettes.
[Morgan] I love cigarettes.
No, go ahead.
-Excuse me.
-Sorry, sorry.
[bell chimes]
I'm gonna get a card.
Okay, I don't think
she's gonna read a card, right?
It's a gesture. We're getting her a gift.
-I'm gonna get her a card.
-Get her a card. Go crazy.
["Firework" by Katy Perry playing faintly]
[sniffs]
[exhales]
♪ 'Cause there's a spark in you ♪
♪ You just gotta ignite the light
And let it shine ♪
[jewelry jingles softly]
♪ Just own the night
Like the 4th of July ♪
♪ 'Cause, baby, you're a firework… ♪
-Hey, excuse me, I'm--
-[clerk] That's display only.
Okay, yeah, I just wanted to try it on.
It's not for sale.
I know, you've made that really clear.
Um… Could you grab me one from the back?
No, because that's actually the last one.
Okay, good, then I wanna buy that one.
Can you fucking leave it alone?
It's not for you, okay?
Seriously? It's a cheap fucking necklace
in a cheap fucking store.
-[clerk] Yeah?
-Who's it for if it's not for me?
-Then get the fuck out of here.
-Okay.
Whoa, Morgan.
Can you just accept the fact that
this isn't some hot New York boutique?
"A hot New York boutique"? What are you,
addicted to humiliating yourself?
By the way, he wishes
this was a hot New York boutique.
Get your wife under control, man.
-Ew.
-She's not my wife.
I'm the pastor
of Glenview Community Church.
And even if she was,
we don't need to get hostile.
-"Even if I was"?
-Oh, Morgan, please.
-You're a very rude woman.
Morgan, wait outside.
Thank you, I'm gonna get this card
and two of those angel figurines.
[cell phone buzzing]
[Nicky sighs]
-Which, this?
-The… the blue ones.
And if you have a gift bag
and some tissue paper--
-Do you have any ribbon or anything to…
-[phone buzzing]
Just gonna put it inside of this.
Well, they're just gonna jinglejangle
around in that bag.
Carry carefully then, man.
-[figurines clinking]
-Oh.
-Okay?
-Well, all right, they're gonna break.
[Nicky] I'm just saying,
you're a slippery person--
I'm slippery
because I'm going to a dinner?
-I don't think so.
-[woman] She's gone.
-[Natalie sobs]
-Body's cold. You missed her last words.
Nicky, you weren't even here
to say a prayer.
Some teenybopper
from the hospital had to do it.
Read something right off of her phone.
Kept getting interrupted by text messages.
What were they?
What were what?
What were her last words?
I don't know. I couldn't hear.
She was mumbling.
I kept telling her to enunciate.
Something about her gloves are new.
Poor thing,
she was so out of it by the end.
-She was saying, "I love you."
-I do not think it was that.
Nevertheless,
your sister's been here since
ten this morning documenting the day.
She thought that it was important content
for the social platforms.
That feels exploitative.
Nevertheless, she died
before her birthday party.
Okay. Well, then what are
we supposed to do with this?
What the fuck did you do?
-[whispers] I took care of it.
-Oh, Morgan! [gasps]
-[Morgan] I… It's not wrapped.
-[woman gasps] Oh my God.
It's a little something from me and Nicky.
-Oh, from the two of you.
-Yeah.
Natalie, look at this.
It's gorg-- It's stunning.
-Nicholas…
-Mm-hmm.
I think that it makes sense
that you be the one to put it on her.
-Put it on her?
-And maybe say a few words.
She wants you to put the necklace
on Nonna and say a few words.
Put the necklace on.
-It's done. Say something.
-Okay. I don't… I don't know why.
Morgan? All right.
Please put the necklace on.
Natalie, just take this from me.
-And move.
-Nicholas, put the necklace on.
-[Nicky] Sorry, I'm just…
-No worries.
Morgan, help your brother.
It's your gift too.
Yeah, Morgan, come on.
Okay.
-Help me.
-[Morgan clears throat] Yeah.
Morgan, her head.
-Just lift her head.
-What else would I lift?
-[Nicky] Just lift it… lift it up.
-I've got it. I've got it.
-Morgan.
-I got it. I got it.
-[Nicky] Are you lifting?
-Oh, honey, honey. Just wait.
It's fine.
There we go. There we go. Okay.
-Okay.
-[Morgan] Oh my God. Okay. I feel like…
-I need you to lift more.
-Sorry, I'm losing it.
-Oh my God.
-[Morgan] It's really heavy.
-Can you lift it up?
-More?
Move forward a bit
'cause I can't get the clasp.
[whispers] Why is it taking so long?
-[softly] Eternal rest grant unto her…
-[woman] I can't hear you.
[raises voice] …perpetual light
shine upon her.
[Natalie exhales]
[softly] May she rest in peace, amen.
-[Natalie sniffles]
-[Nicky] Okay.
Oh, Natalie, did you want
to get a pic for socials?
-Oh, Morgan!
-Ha, ha.
-Morgan, fuck. You crazy?
-Please, have some respect for the dead.
Nicky, you really sped through that.
-[thunder rumbling]
-[rain pattering]
[loud pounding on the door]
[pounding continues]
Coming.
-Hey.
-Hi. Uh, can I help you with something?
I'm here for a pickup.
I… I think you might have
the wrong address.
No.
You said you were at the Glenview Church?
Uh… Yeah. Mm-hmm.
You came with your sister,
bought a card, two Elsa dolls from me?
I bought two angel figurines.
They didn't look anything like Elsa.
And a tennis necklace?
I…
No, I… I don't… don't…
I don't think I bought a tennis necklace.
I know you didn't buy the necklace.
I'm here to take it back.
[speaks Turkish]
I don't… I don't… I don't have it.
[clerk scoffs]
[suspenseful music playing]
-Very nice house, huh?
-Mm-hmm.
You must have a very…
supportive congregation.
Wouldn't want to lose their trust,
would you, Father?
Well, I'm not Catholic,
so I… I go by "Pastor."
I don't give a fuck what name you go by,
you dumb-looking piece of shit.
You don't know what you've taken, okay?
-Okay.
-You have no idea who you're dealing with.
Return it, or I'll make sure
your God gets very upset with you, okay?
-Okay.
-[speaks Turkish]
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
-Yep.
-Good.
[footsteps fading]
[frenetic music playing]
[keys jangling]
[exhales]
[Nicky screams]
[yells]
[whimpering]
[yells] Get in the--
Get in the… fucking car!
[exclaims]
[engine starts]
[music ends]
No, 'cause his is Gosling with a G.
He's not related to the eight kids.
-[Morgan yells] Fuck!
-Oh, shit.
Honey, what is wrong?
I am asking you, what is wrong?
I'm fine, I'm fine, I just got my finger.
I told you we should have ordered food.
God forbid I honor my mother
by making her cutlets on the day she died.
They're the best cutlets
I've ever had, Mrs. M.
Where's your brother?
I told him eight o'clock.
-I don't know.
-Uh, Mrs. M.
-I know that today's been really hard…
-[scoffs]
…but if it's okay with you,
I would… love to grab you privately
at some point.
I have something
I would really love to ask you.
Let's play it by ear, Max.
-Okay? Hmm?
-Okay.
Let's play that one by ear.
[knocking on door]
Coming!
Come on.
Since when are we locking the door?
Since Susan Gopnik's garage
got broken into a couple of weeks ago,
and all of her kids' bikes got taken.
-Where's your umbrella in this rain?
-I don't have one.
I can't lose my son and my mother
on the same day.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, today has not brought out
the best in me.
I could admit that.
-How are you dealing with everything?
-I'm not good. I'm not--
No, I just want a minute alone
with my firstborn.
Technically, that would be Morgan.
We do not talk about adoption
in this home.
I birthed you emotionally,
which is just as painful.
You're freezing.
-Why are we standing out here?
-You tell me.
[frenetic music playing]
We're making Nonna's veal cutlets.
[Morgan] They lived in Long Island.
Morgan, can I talk to you for a second?
No, no, there are no secrets
in this house.
Anything you have to say,
you can say in front of me and Max.
And half the women in this town. Ma--
Can I talk to Morgan, please?
[shouts] It is an inclusive
neighborhood Facebook group!
Okay. Morgan! I need five minutes.
I can't help who signs up
or what they send.
-Okay, okay.
-It's out of my control!
Just five minutes.
-[woman] How would I even begin to?
-That's all I need. Morgan…
[woman] I mean, seriously.
[whispers] Okay, first of all,
what the fuck is wrong with you?
Excuse me?
I need you to get
that necklace back right now.
What necklace?
The necklace you stole
after I told you to just leave it alone.
Oh… You mean the necklace that's around
our dead grandmother's neck at a morgue?
-Oh, Morgan.
-Come on.
You didn't seem freaked out
when you were taking credit for it
at the hospital.
Look out the window!
-Do you see that truck out there?
-Yes. Yes!
Don't look like that.
Hide yourself a little bit.
Okay, that man out there
followed me here from my house.
-What?
-The guy you pissed off in the store.
He knocked on my door
and threatened my reputation
if I didn't get that necklace back, okay?
I… I don't know what to do.
So you thought it'd be a good idea
to lead him here to Mom's house
where your entire family's having dinner?
-Well, I wasn't really thinking about--
-About the rest of your family?
-Oh, Morgan.
-Did you just eat falafel?
You are such a bitch.
I'm sorry that your sexy life
as an actress in Manhattan
didn't work out the way you want,
but I am not getting my life ruined
because you have given up on yours.
-Fix this, Morgan.
-It was a $79 necklace.
It felt really fucking heavy
for a $79 necklace.
I held it in my hand,
and it felt expensive.
I don't have time for this.
The Quick Post guy
isn't gang-stalking you.
-Then go outside and talk to him then.
-Seriously?
Yes!
[pans clattering in kitchen]
Okay, fine. Fine!
-I will go talk to him, fine.
-Go!
And you know what? If he wants $79,
I will Venmo him 79 fucking dollars.
-Great.
-If that's what he needs.
-[door slams]
-[exhales]
[sniffs]
[frenetic music playing]
[Morgan] Hello?
Can I help you with something?
What the fuck?
[muffled] You're creeping out my family.
I don't know what you're doing here,
but this is some kind of misunderstanding.
You deaf?
You need to go.
I know you can hear me. Hi.
Hey, great.
[music fades]
[softly mimics gunshot]
[music resumes]
[door slams]
[Nicky] And?
Um…
And yeah. Yeah.
So we just have to… get…
get the… get the necklace back.
-I know. I know we do.
-But we have… But we have to.
-[inhales deeply] We have to.
-Okay. Yeah, I know.
That's it? That's all… that's all he said?
[inhales deeply]
No-- Um, no, he didn't… he didn't…
-Morgan, spit it out.
-He didn't say much of anything.
But you could've warned me
about the fucking gun.
-[whispers] What gun?
-The gun! The gun!
The fucking gun
I got pointed at my fucking face.
-Did you--
-What gun, Morgan?
Did you not get a gun?
No.
But I had a man come to my house
in the middle of the night
and verbally threaten me.
-Oh, really?!
-Which was also very scary.
Did he scare you? He came to your house,
and he didn't point a gun at you?
-That's not the same thing.
-You have to calm down.
-That was so fucked-up!
-Shh! Shh!
-[whispers] You'll have to calm down.
-Oh, I have to calm down?
-You have to calm down.
-I have to calm down?
How the fuck are we gonna get
that necklace back?
I'm seeing Nonna tomorrow.
I'm gonna have to take it off her neck.
-I'm gonna have to take it off…
-Okay.
…a dead woman's neck.
-Okay?
-Yeah, right.
-Is there any other plan?
-No. I don't--
-Okay, so then…
-Okay.
-[sighs]
-Anything you wanna say?
-What?
-"Thanks, Nick"?
-Maybe "thank you for the offer"?
-Really? That's where your head goes?
-It is.
-Are you out of your mind?
-Are you? Are you out of your--
-Oh shit. That's next-level.
-[knocking on door]
-[Max] Am I interrupting something?
-[Nicky] I don't… Yeah, I mean…
-Um…
-No. It's… What's… What's up? What's up?
-[Max] Okay. Okay.
Well, I was just wondering if there was
something that you wanted to say to me.
-[Nicky exhales] I don't…
-Mmm, I don't think… No.
-Morgan, what's happening?
-Sure there's nothing you wanna say to me?
-Babe, I don't know what--
-Well, how about now?
Okay, yeah. Um…
Anything that you might wanna say to me?
-[Morgan laughs nervously]
-Oh my fucking God.
-Anything you might wanna say? [laughs]
-[Morgan laughs nervously] Um…
-Morgan…
-Yeah, yes.
-[Nicky] Oh my fucking God.
-…Janice Dardano…
…will you make my life by saying yes?
Um… Mom, what about… what about Nonna?
-The timing is not, um…
-[Nicky] Okay.
Oh no, hon, she would be relieved.
-Nicky, get the prosecco from the garage.
-What?
From the garage, okay.
-[Morgan laughs nervously]
-So it's a yes?
[Morgan whimpers]
[Morgan and Max scream]
[Max] Yes. Oh my God.
-Okay.
-[Max] Oh my God, it's happening.
[Max laughs]
[laughs]
-We're getting engaged!
-[Morgan laughing nervously]
Why are you so wet?
[bell tolling]
[softly] Oh, forgive me.
[clicks tongue]
[sighs]
[grunts]
-[door opens]
-Yeah?
Sorry to interrupt. Can I use
the office printer for the programs?
-Sure.
-The basement's out of ink.
Absolutely.
Thank you. And do you want those programs
in black-and-white or color?
I… I don't know, Rose. Are the programs
-Color.
-Then we print in color.
Then we print in color.
-Thank you, Rose.
-[phone buzzing]
[funky music playing]
[girl] Miss Morgan?
You look like a bad witch.
Thanks, Mackenzie.
-[loud thud]
-[children scream]
[music continues]
-[woman] Nicholas.
-[Nicky screams]
-Honey. Calm down.
-What?! [sighs]
I just got word your nonna's best friend,
Dina, slipped at a Five Guys last night.
-What?
-Broke her neck.
She'll be in the hospital
for the rest of her life.
So you're gonna have to read
her poem, okay?
And your father's here,
speaking of somebody
who should've slipped at a Five Guys.
-Ma.
-What?
If we don't have laughter
in these moments, what do we have?
-He left Denise at home, which was decent.
-Ah.
[Max] Okay.
-Good to roll, Mrs. M?
-Yep.
[Nicky] Uh…
-[Max] Let's do it.
-Can we stop?
Can we just, um…
Can we stop it for a second?
Can we just stop? Can we stop?
[yelling] Can we stop?! Just stop! Stop!
[Nicky exclaims]
I haven't said a prayer.
I need to say a prayer for the woman.
Okay? Can I--
I just need to be alone with…
-Honey.
-With her for a moment, please.
She's late to her own funeral.
You can bless her later.
Okay? Move.
[funky music playing]
[woman] What in the world?
[whispers] Fuck!
Fuck!
[breathes deeply]
[Nicky] Good afternoon, everyone,
and welcome.
[fly buzzing]
Uh… I wish we were gathering here
under happier circumstances.
But, um…
but it often is in these times
that the Lord, um,
shows us the true cap-- capacity
that we as human beings have
to… to process and to live through pain.
-Both emotional and, um…
-Mmm.
…and physical.
Sometimes it's easy to forget that death…
[fly buzzing]
…could be just around the… co-- corner
for any of us.
Um… Just look at Dina Caputo,
who just last night slipped in a Five Guys
and is now in a coma,
no longer able to read
her poem here today.
Thoughts and prayers
are with Dina and her family
at this time.
You know, Nonna was, uh, a special woman.
I use the word "special" because
I know she pissed a lot of you off.
[mourners laugh]
But she never lied
or forced any of her family members
to lie for her.
[percussive music playing]
How did you not get the--
Don't you fucking dare.
[music ends]
I'm gonna head home and let the dogs out.
Denise is in Tampa.
I'll see you back at the house.
-Your grandmother was a great woman.
-Yes, she was.
-[Natalie] Oh, yeah.
-She was so proud of your mom.
All right, we're good, Michael.
Thank you for that. Go home.
Let her poodles out.
Don't want them shitting on your carpet.
Yep. All right. I'll see you in an hour.
Hey, congrats again on the ring, honey.
Thanks, Dad.
[woman] Did you congratulate your sister?
On Max proposing to her
the day Nonna died? Um…
No, not yet.
Congrats, Morgan.
I'm… I'm just-- It's beyond words.
-I'm thrilled.
-[woman] Max is helping me out.
I've got him picking up Baileys
for your Aunt Joanie.
But we really should get back
to the house. People will be arriving.
I don't trust what those caterers
consider hot food.
Sorry for your loss.
[woman] Oh, thank you so much.
Have we met?
-[gasps]
-My condolences.
[woman] Oh.
It's a friend of Morgan's.
-Uh-huh. It's my friend.
-[woman] Ah.
That tracks.
All right. Honey, we should really go.
Kids, we'll see you back at the house.
[Morgan] Okay.
Okay, see you.
[engine starts]
-Let's take a walk.
-[Morgan] Oh…
I have some papers to sign, so--
-Walk.
-Oh, okay.
[Morgan] Okay.
-[Nicky] We don't need to push.
-[Morgan] I know how to walk.
Come on. Okay, give me the necklace.
Where is it?
Huh?
We don't have it.
-What do you mean, you don't have it?
-I-- We don't have it.
What the fuck you mean? Where is it?!
I don't know how else we can say it.
We don't have it.
What the fuck you mean you don't have it?
-Where the fuck is it?
-I--
-[speaks Turkish]
-Okay, okay.
Can you calm down? Because I don't think
talking to us like this is helping.
What are you,
some kind of crisis manager now?
-Whose side are you on?
-Not yours.
-[loud bang]
-What am I gonna do now?
[tense music playing]
[inhales sharply]
[mumbling] Fucking fuck.
You have no idea
what the fuck you've done. Huh?
-Get in the fucking truck.
-[Nicky] There has to be some…
What if I said
I wasn't comfortable doing that?
-Get in the truck. Get in the truck.
-No. [sighs]
-He has a gun. Get in the fucking truck.
-This is fully giving kidnap homicide.
It's "giving"? Those are your last words?
Is it giving kidnap homicide?
-Get in the fucking truck!
-[Morgan] Oh my God!
[Nicky] Ow!
[techno music playing]
[music ends]