I figured it out!
You switch between being yourself and Sun
every time you wake up!
Teacher Solar!
I've said it hundreds of times.
My name is Sun!
- Sponge bath.
- Huh?
My magic word.
I mean... can you help me?
You're the best!
You let others help you now, right?
Our teacher Solar has to take on
the character of Little Sun on some days.
Okay!
But don't worry.
I'm going to help you get better
no matter what.
[Today Is A Good Day]
Uncle!
Wake up!
It's 7 AM. Don't you have to go to work?
Wake up. Come on!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Hey.
It's only 6 AM.
Why wake me up so early?
If I hadn't, you'd be late for work again.
And this is the little troublemaker
I have to deal with every other day.
I'm trying to figure out
how to adjust and live with Sun,
even though I don't understand
what being a kid is like at all.
Luckily, Solar came up with a brilliant way
for me to handle it.
Have you ever wondered
why sometimes you sleep for days,
not knowing what day or time it is?
And have you ever wondered
why people keep calling you...
Solar?
Solar!
The truth is I'm...
a cop from the future!
[Future Police Department]
My job is to take down
the devils attacking our world.
Unfortunately, I got hit by a curse...
that makes me from the future,
and you from the past,
switch every other day.
But don't worry.
I'm trying to find a way to break the curse.
I've gotten help from
these kind adults from the future!
You have an important mission too.
That is, blend in at school
as smoothly as possible,
and learn to live with others.
Most importantly,
you have to listen to
these three kind adults from the future.
This is a top secret mission.
Do not tell anyone.
Sun, you think you've got this?
If you do, let's fist bump!
[Sukhum Udom Rak School]
Alright.
First word.
H is for Happy.
Clap your hands.
Good job.
- Looks like the kids have now opened up,
- Next one.
And really believe that Solar is Sun.
Just like Solar predicted,
everything is going well,
and we're ready for the next step.
Uncle.
Yes?
What are we doing here?
We're here to see a doctor.
She's a kind adult from the future,
and she knows how to break the devil's curse.
No! No!
I don't want to see the doctor! Let me go!
Sun! We have an important mission to do.
No! I don't want to do the mission anymore!
I don't want to see the doctor!
I don't want to get a shot. No!
I don't want this anymore!
- Sun, we have a mission...
- There'll be no shots.
Little Sun, right?
Don't worry.
We're just going to have
a fun little chat today, okay?
How old are you?
S... S... Seven.
Oh, your voice is shaking.
Are you scared?
No.
I just want to pee.
Oh, why didn't you tell me?
I'll have the nurse
take you to the bathroom now.
[Toilet]
Is Sun in here?
He's been gone for a while.
- Yes, well...
- Ouch!
Sun! What are you doing?
I don't want to see the doctor, Uncle!
Help pull me down!
Help pull me down, Uncle!
How much longer are you going to sulk?
I told you we need to see the doctor.
Uncle.
Am I sick?
You're not sick.
You're just cursed,
and the doctor knows how to break it.
So you won't have to keep switching
with Solar all the time.
So...
if the curse is lifted,
does that mean I can come out
and play like this all the time?
Yeah.
Really?
Fine, I'll believe you.
Good job.
Uncle has something for you.
Here.
- Wow!
- All these toys are just for you, Sun.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I can play with any of these?
Any of them.
Yay!
Wow! Yay!
- Hi, Aunt.
- Pobmek, how are you?
You've taken Solar
to see a psychotherapist, right?
Yes.
Well, Solar...
It sounds very fantasy-like,
but it could be a case of age regression.
As children,
if we experience something deeply traumatic,
our bodies create defense mechanisms
to protect our minds from breaking down.
Do you have any idea
if he experienced something like that
as a child?
I've talked to Solar
about his childhood before,
but he said he doesn't remember anything
from when he was a child.
The car accident
is probably the most traumatic for him.
So, I want to know what Solar went through
when he was a kid, Aunt.
I have to go. I'll call you back.
Sun! What are you doing?
Uncle! Look!
I made a flying robot!
You can play with any toy, but not that one!
Ouch!
Damn...
Ow!
Ouch!
[To Do List]
[Sun - Solar]
Did you just wake up,
or have you not slept at all?
I haven't slept. Look!
Jeez!
I can't take this anymore.
If you don't get back to your old self soon,
our room's going to turn
into a toy graveyard.
What did the psychotherapist say?
There might be a way to help you...
if we know what you went through
in your childhood.
Really?
As I said,
I really don't remember anything.
Yeah, I already told her that.
Then I called your mom last night.
What did my mom say?
I didn't get to hear anything.
Sun wrecked the room first.
And my phone's broken.
If you talk to your mom,
can you ask if she knows anything?
Please!
Please make Solar
go back to normal next month,
and never let Sun come back again!
Amen!
Maybe having Sun around...
is a good thing.
At least you found something
you thought you lost a long time ago.
Yeah.
It's good.
Not!
Look! Sun glued the robot.
And I don't even know if the umbrella
is breaking or not.
I'm tired of Sun!
[Sukhum Udom Rak School]
Alright, everyone.
[Rainy]
Read this together.
Rainy!
Let's spell it together.
R... A... I... N...
Wow, man.
I know teaching doesn't pay that well,
but you don't have to be this frugal.
Sun did that, didn't he?
Come on. Don't be upset.
The kid needed to use his imagination.
You can just get a new umbrella
like this one, right?
It's not hard to get a new one,
but there is no other umbrella like it
in the world.
Hello, Mom.
It's not this box.
My book box has a sticker on it.
This is the box of old stuff
I'm throwing away.
Really? They all look the same.
[Sung by me!]
Let me bring it to your dorm tonight.
It's okay, Mom.
I don't need it now.
Alright then. Have you eaten...
I need to study. I have to go.
Why is it raining so hard?
What's going on? It's raining every day!
Here.
It's the rainy season in Thailand.
Why didn't you carry an umbrella?
I forgot.
I was going to cut through the building,
but that didn't work.
Is that your umbrella?
Yeah.
It's my old one.
Let me see.
Hey!
Hey.
I'm on this too.
What do you mean?
Here, this is the sun.
It gives solar energy.
Unbelievable.
Hey!
There's another one.
You can take it.
No, I'll pass.
You should keep it for yourself.
Since that day,
I'd been using this umbrella
as an excuse to get close to Solar.
Wow.
What a romantic prop, man.
Oh, now I get why you're so mad at Sun.
I get that Sun didn't mean it,
but I can't just not feel anything.
So, I want to help Solar recover
as soon as possible.
That's so fetch!
Elsa, what are you writing down, sweetie?
Burn book?
Is that for writing down
your friends' secrets?
That's evil.
To be the queen bee,
you obviously need a weapon.
We don't go around using force anymore.
We use psychology.
Is this really a student in my school?
Sun is new,
so I have to take some notes on him.
If I know what issues my friend has,
I can handle them better.
Elsa.
We're going pee-pee. Wanna come with us?
Of course.
Please excuse me, teachers.
Let's go, girls.
[Sun: Naughty but handsome.
But cuter than handsome. Wanna adopt him]
Elsa,
I thought you were taking notes
on your friends' issues,
but there's nothing here.
If you want there to be something,
there can be.
When you spend a long time with something,
you tend to change along with it.
That's all I'll say.
Wait, what?
I think I've found a solution.
That solution is...
[Plan To Get Solar Back]
We need to keep him as Solar
as long as possible.
And get Sun to bed as early as possible.
If we keep doing that,
[Sun: 50%, Solar: 50%]
Solar will be with us longer.
And Sun might just disappear for good.
[Solar: 100%]
Genius!
You were a first-class honors student
with a gold medal, after all!
But will it really work?
If we don't try, we'll never know.
We don't know Solar's past trauma anyway,
so I think it's worth a try.
Solar.
Solar!
Huh?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Deal!
[Sun's Day]
Uncle, what are you doing?
Getting ready to do something fun, of course.
Here are your new shoes. You like them?
These are so cool, Uncle.
They're mine?
Let's go release some energy!
- Go!
- Faster! Faster!
Go!
[Day 1 Without Sleep]
[Solar's Day]
[6 Hours Without Sleep]
Since you're not going to sleep,
can you help me summarize the curriculum?
Sure.
Just for Grade 2, right?
Grade 1 all the way to Grade 6.
I'll leave it to you.
[12 Hours Without Sleep]
Here.
[Sun's Day]
Move!
[Solar's Day Again!]
We broke the record.
[Sun: 30%, Solar: 70%]
Solar hasn't slept for 48 hours.
[38, 40, 42, 44 Hours]
Soon, Solar will get his body back.
[45, 46, 47, 48 Hours]
Oh!
But until then,
won't he have to stay awake all week?
Pobmek.
We're leaving.
Let me walk you out.
If it's too much,
don't force yourself, Solar.
You don't want to collapse.
Okay.
Thanks a lot, guys.
Bye. I'm exhausted.
[Solar]
[Mom, are you free this Sunday?]
[Mom]
[For my son, I'm always free]
Come on.
Just push through for another 12 hours,
then nap tomorrow afternoon.
So that means on Sunday,
I'll probably wake up as Little Sun.
Yeah.
Okay. I'm going to wash my face.
I'll be right back.
[To Do List]
[Saturday - Sun, Sunday - Sun]
[P.S.]
[Allergy Medicine]
[May cause drowsiness]
What are you doing?
Solar, are you going to take medicine
to sleep?
Why are you doing this?
You're almost getting your body back.
Don't you want to recover?
Why wouldn't I want to?
But am I gonna die
if I have to keep doing this over and over?
I'm glad everyone's trying to help me.
But I feel like this is forcing it.
Everything just feels wrong.
You know what?
Every day I wake up,
I don't feel happy at all.
Are we being too harsh on Little Sun?
Clap your hands!
- Really?
- Yeah.
I can play with any of these?
I might not be able to communicate with him,
but I can feel that
he's not okay with this at all.
Do we really need to rush
and push him out of our lives like this?
Pobmek.
Do you know why I love you?
Solar!
I knew you'd be here.
Come on. Let's go back to our room.
Let's go.
Oh, when's that going to dry?
Turn around.
I'll dry your hair.
So...
you already got a new umbrella?
Yeah... for a while now.
So that means...
Yeah.
I just wanted to know...
how long you'll keep picking me up.
Well, do you know now?
Yeah.
Thank you for being consistent.
Why are you laughing?
Turn your face the other way.
I'm going to dry your hair.
Turn around!
I love you because you're consistent.
You never rush.
But if we keep rushing
to speed up my recovery,
and all end up exhausted like this,
I don't think that's the right way.
Besides,
we might forget
what's important along the way.
Sunday...
is our anniversary.
Exactly.
That's why I want to sleep now,
so I can wake up as myself on Sunday.
So I can be with you.
I hope we get to be together this Sunday.
[Sun]
Oh, Uncle.
Aren't you going to work?
You're going to be late.
I'm not going to be late.
It's Sunday at noon.
You slept for almost two full days.
Really?
That's good.
I had a good, deep sleep.
What should we do today, Uncle?
Do we have to go running again?
No. We'll just stay here.
You can play with the toys.
Consider it a reward
for obeying me the whole week.
Really, Uncle?
Do you mean it?
- Yes.
- Oh!
Yay! Yes!
Yay! Yes! Yay!
Here I go!
Yay!
[Chop it!]
Chop it!
Chop it up!
Go!
Teacher Jee, Teacher Sodchuen,
I can't hear you!
[Plan To Get Solar Back]
[Delete this file?]
- I'm tired! You go on!
- I can't hear you!
I'm tired!
I'm sorry.
I made you miss celebrating your anniversary
with your boyfriend.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I think it's all our fault.
Who would've thought Solar would sleep
for two days straight?
- Oh, hi, Aunt.
- Surprise!
Let me help you with that.
Thanks. Be careful.
Guys, this is Aunt Pranee.
She's Solar's mom.
Hello.
- Hello, Aunt.
- Hi.
Hey, Aunt. What's this box?
Solar told me that if he didn't call me
before noon on Sunday,
I should come see you here.
This box has Solar's childhood toys.
He said they might help him recover.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
My son looks so happy.
Do you want me to call him?
No need.
I have something more important.
Solar asked me to make this
for your anniversary.
And... there's this too.
Here.
Hello!
If you're watching this clip,
that means things didn't go as planned.
I probably didn't wake up on our anniversary.
But it's okay.
I've asked Mom to prepare everything.
Get ready.
Pobmek.
Before we know it,
we've already been together for 7 years.
I remember you love
my mom's coconut cake, right?
So I asked her to make a big one for you.
She's going to feed it to you.
Open your mouth.
Mom!
Are you moving your mouth too?
He knows.
Oh, don't forget to read the notebook
out loud,
so it'll be extra special.
Oh, okay.
[Being in the clouds]
"Even though I regret
not being able to
feed you the cake myself this year,
on the bright side,
it makes me realize how much I miss you...
when we're not together.
And how much I want to see you.
I don't know if I'll get better next year,
but I promise I'll make it up to you
by making every day I wake up
more special than this anniversary."
Hey, I know you're crying.
You're always such a crybaby.
There, there.
Tomorrow, I'll wake up to hug you.
Thank you so much, Aunt,
for coming all the way here.
Are you sure you don't want to stay over?
It's okay.
I'm meeting my SY gang tomorrow.
Huh? Senators of the Year?
You're retired, but still in politics?
SY, as in Senior Years, dear.
If you hadn't clarified,
I would've thought
you meant Sao Y, as in BL girls.
That I already am.
He's my bias.
Aunt, I'm sorry for prying.
What did Solar go through as a kid?
As far as I know,
he doesn't have a father, right?
That's right.
Sun's father...
I mean Solar's father...
He left Solar when he was a kid.
Aunt, was his name Sun when he was a kid?
Yes.
But why did he have to change it?
He must've heard the name Solar somewhere
and liked it,
so he changed it himself.
That's my ride.
I should go.
- Goodbye.
- Bye, Aunt.
Pobmek, I believe that someday,
Solar will recover.
Don't give up.
I won't.
- Bye now.
- Bye.
Safe trip home.
Thanks.
Uncle.
Can I take a look?
I promise I won't break anything this time.
I haven't said anything yet.
Let's see what you loved playing with
when you were a kid.
There are no toys here.
Oh.
What's this, Uncle?
[Sung by me!]
How did it get here?
Is that a music CD?
Play it for me, please.
No.
- No.
- Please!
Let me listen.
- Check out something else.
No. I want to listen.
Please!
- Pretty, please!
- Fine.
I'll play it.
"Sung by me!"
Why are you throwing it away?
It's just a normal recording of me singing.
I don't see why I should keep it.
Hey.
Solar. It's your voice.
It'd be a shame to throw it away.
- Let's listen to it.
- No.
Please.
I promise I won't tease you.
At all.
People who tease always say that.
- No, I'm throwing it away!
- No!
- Solar.
- Come on.
- No teasing.
- Hey, I already promised!
♫ Every second ♫
♫ I will spend on you ♫
♫ However much time passes through ♫
♫ And when the rain falls,
know I'm here next to you ♫
♫ We'll make it together ♫
♫ And that alone will do ♫
Solar.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
My tears just started falling out of nowhere.
♫ Let our story be written in our hearts ♫
♫ 'Cause this love is meant just for us ♫
♫ I will never let your hand go ♫
♫ I will paint and fill the storyline
with you ♫
♫ No matter if the sky turns dark and blue ♫
♫ I will remain right here
beside you, always ♫
What's wrong, Sun?
Sun?
Hey, Sun!
Sun! What's wrong, Sun?
Sun!
Sun, what's wrong? You scared me!
Hey.
It's me.
It's Solar.
Huh?
Damn!
This is straight out of a Doraemon episode,
The Snoozy CD!
Who knows?
Your song might just be the thing
that helps Sun turn into Solar faster.
Yay!
Finally, I've found a way to survive!
But what's that song?
Why does it have a sleeping-pill effect?
It's his voice from high school.
He sounded amazing.
Pobmek will play it for you.
Wait.
Are we going to hear it today?
Calm down.
The player is old. It's a bit tricky to open.
Shit!
What have you done?
Pobmek!
I'm going to have to run with Sun again,
aren't I?
Sorry about my boyfriend.
But it's fine.
At least we found out that
the song is our solution, right?
Right.
Let's call it a night. I'm sleepy.
Okay.
Damn!
Comfort me.
You always want me to comfort you.
It's alright.
Let's take it slow, okay?
Since the day isn't over yet,
can we keep celebrating our anniversary
a little longer?
As we promised,
let's not do it until I'm fully recovered.
Alright.
But can I cuddle you all night tonight?
Of course.
Even though we still don't know
when Solar will recover,
if we keep holding hands,
I believe time will heal everything.
It's that time of year again.
The class play day
from the English department.
As long as the kids don't choose Sun
as the director,
it should be easy.
Sun for director!
Squirm harder!
Jeez!
I can't deal with Sun anymore!
Do you remember this?
Am I really going to do okay?
You'll be fine.
As long as you're having fun,
the audience will enjoy it too.