Mom, don't go.
Be good.
I'll come back
as long as you behave.
Back then,
I believed what my mom said.
I thought my wishes
would come true that way.
What shall we play today?
Anything.
I'm fine with whatever you want.
I came here
because I wanted to play with Tuo.
Today I'll do what Tuo says.
Do what I say?
Today we follow Tuo's lead.
You can do whatever you want.
Can I read books then?
Sure,
we'll read today,
at my place.
Meeting Junxi,
he was the one who told me
I didn't have to be good
to do what I wanted.
And he made me realize
there was someone in this world
who would listen to me carefully,
and made my wishes come true.
[Episode 6: Wishes Come true]
[Secret Lover]
Throw it to me!
Come play with us!
Come on, let's play together.
Come on, join us!
Join us, come on!
No need,
you guys have fun.
You guys go play first.
Okay.
Why don't you go play with them?
I'll stay with you.
Junxi
had no idea how dazzling he was.
He's coming. He's coming.
Can you give this to him?
[To Junxi]
I know I'm despicable.
But these people...
I'm surprised that Lu Junxi is your type.
He's the cutest boy in the whole school.
I just love that Japanese-style boy vibe.
What should I do?
Excuse me.
Were you talking about Lu Junxi?
He's so handsome.
I knew they didn't really like Junxi.
Liking someone...
isn't that simple.
Don't tell me
all of Tuo's ex-girlfriends
liked Junxi first.
Tuo.
Is that true?
I had zero experience with relationships.
Unlike you, Casanova.
I worked so hard
to stand out for you.
I thought if I could become better,
more outstanding,
you'd always keep your eyes on me.
How many times have I reminded you
not to let girls get too close to you?
Get lost!
That's why I want to
make our relationship public,
so no one else will
set their sights on you.
It's better if people find out.
If everyone knows we're dating,
then no one would try to hit on you.
Tuo!
[Matsutaka]
Han Tuo!
Wait for me!
If you keep running, I'm not chasing you!
Why are you running away?
Tell me you're not mad.
I am mad...
I'm surprised too.
I never thought you liked me that much.
You said you dated girls to distract
yourself from your feelings for me,
but it was actually to distract them
from liking me.
I'm sorry.
I just can't...
stand the thought
of you with someone else,
and me not being by your side,
so I just...
Happy birthday.
You're not angry anymore?
Birthday boy gets to call the shots today.
If you want me not mad,
then I'm not.
I forgive you.
Junxi is so nice.
I'm willing to give everything
to protect his smile.
Coming.
-Hi, Mr. Lu. We're looking for Junxi.
-Welcome, welcome.
He's still sleeping.
Tuo.
What are you doing?
We got accepted!
What do you mean?
Stellaris!
Really?
-Did we get in?
-Yes, we did.
Tuo also received an interview notice
from Zhan Wensen.
He'll be reporting on the same day.
Everyone got in!
Congratulations!
We all made it.
[Stellaris]
We got this!
[Stellaris Games]
[Z. W. S Architecture]
Please wait a moment.
Thank you.
Your model...
is technically rough,
but...
your design concept is very creative.
Looking forward to you joining us.
Like I said,
in Unity,
if a character's movement feels off,
you need to go back
and check the raw motion-capture data
to see if there are any tagging errors.
Now let's start the hands-on practice.
[Basic Structure - Character Archetype]
[Xingwu University
of Science and Technology]
The teacher is coming.
[Xingwu University
of Science and Technology]
Morning.
Sir.
You don't actually think
an internship at Stellaris
means you've already got a job?
You've finished all your credits,
surely you don't need these two from me?
Actually, we do need them.
Sorry, sir.
Previous page.
Go back to the last page!
You guys must have been...
working really hard at your internship.
Physically exhausted,
mentally even worse.
What do you mean?
Stellaris's a high-output company
with rapid updates.
Nobody's got time to teach us anything,
so we have
to figure everything out ourselves.
And by the time you actually get to work,
you realize how lacking your skills were.
We even have to work overtime
always catching the last bus home.
Plus, Stellaris
is an hour away from school,
and even further from my place,
an hour and a half!
And making games
is nothing like playing games.
I've typed so much that
I got wrist tendinitis.
I got yelled at for trying to fix code.
Glad I didn't get accepted.
What are you talking about?
Keep applying!
Having internship experience
makes it easier to find a job.
Don't you dare give up,
or I'll punch you.
What's with that look?
I'm touched.
You said that for me, right?
I'm sticking with you, big sis!
Hold on,
you're younger than me.
I will be loyal to you.
I don't need you though.
Stop clinging to me, it's hot.
Alright,
just let us know if you need any help.
Okay, I know you're the best.
Heart sign?
No.
-Make a heart sign.
-Nope.
Just make a heart sign.
No.
Junxi...
No way!
What are you looking for?
Your loyal puppy, Tuo.
Doesn't he always
come find you after class?
What happened? Has he gone MIA again?
He's interning at Zhan Wensen's agency.
He's busier than both of us at Stellaris,
and hasn't been to school lately.
We haven't seen each other
for over a week.
Won't he fail
if he skips too many classes?
He's finished all his credits
except internship.
That's impressive!
Of course,
he's the guy
who gets scholarships every semester.
His job must be so interesting,
because he hasn't
even thought about you lately.
Not funny.
Zhan Wensen is an architect Tuo admires.
He's happy to be working for him.
But I heard that
architects deal with lots of details.
They work long hours,
and have to visit construction sites.
It's a high-risk, high-pressure job.
It's really dangerous, you know.
Han Tuo.
You changed my drawings?
The damping wall material
in this structural plan
is different from what I gave you.
Last Friday, we had a meeting
with the structural engineers,
and the last point
in the meeting minutes said
we need to change it
to the latest
Japanese rubber damping wall.
I'm sorry,
I just went ahead and fixed it myself.
Thank you for fixing that,
it could've been
a fatal mistake otherwise.
I'm just doing my job.
Let me take you to dinner tonight.
Sure.
Get back to work.
Thank you, boss.
It's 8:30 PM, why isn't he back yet?
I'll give him a call.
Tuo.
Why are you home so late?
I've been waiting for you for ages.
Was work tough today?
It was okay.
Han Tuo.
And this is?
Lu Junxi.
My...
good friend.
Hello.
See you at the office tomorrow.
Sure.
What did you buy?
Dinner.
Let me help you carry it.
I'll make you a copy of my key,
so you won't have to wait for me anymore.
Okay.
How's your internship with Zhan Wensen?
It's great.
He even accepted
my revision suggestions today,
said I had done a great job.
That's going so smoothly.
It sounds great.
You haven't eaten yet?
Nope.
I thought we'd eat together
when you got back.
Zhan Wensen just treated me to dinner.
I'm sorry.
It's fine,
I'll eat by myself.
I'm the one who suddenly showed up,
thinking we haven't
seen each other in a while.
I'll eat with you.
I bought a lot.
If we can't finish it,
we'll have it for breakfast tomorrow.
And it'll be your turn to eat with me.
Go sit down and rest.
I'll heat up...
your special dinner.
You're up early.
Han Tuo,
no greeting?
Morning.
Why are you talking
to me with that attitude?
Why did Mr. Han come back so suddenly?
Since you're making breakfast,
make me one too.
I saw a pair of shoes at the entrance
which I have never seen before.
Did you have a friend staying over?
They're Junxi's.
He's still sleeping.
We stayed up
playing video games until 3 AM.
You're about to graduate soon.
You should plan ahead,
and prepare for your future.
Don't stay up all night
playing video games!
Is that responsible?
Don't act like you know me so well.
You haven't been home
for over a month,
and the moment you're back
you start lecturing me.
I know I've been busy with work
and I've neglected you.
It won't happen again.
What do you mean?
Do I need to greet his father?
This is so awkward.
Han Tuo,
watch your attitude right now.
I've been running around
on business trips for whom?
It's all for
giving you a stable life.
Don't say it's for me.
If you really cared,
you wouldn't have driven my mom away,
leaving me to live alone since I was 10.
When I was sick, it was Junxi's parents
who took me to the hospital
and looked after me.
Fine.
If I didn't work so hard every day,
do you think
you'd be living the life you have now?
So you get to arrange my life for me?
Han Tuo,
you used to listen to me.
How did you turn out...
I've had enough.
Good morning, Mr. Han.
Your dad rarely comes home.
Don't fight with him.
Be like Junxi.
Look how polite Junxi is.
That's because
his parents raised him well.
Go wash your face and brush your teeth.
Breakfast is ready.
But...
Go now.
Please.
Mr. Han...
Then I'll...
go wash up.
Let me tell you,
once the house in Kaohsiung is ready,
you're moving there with me.
I've already handed this place over
to a real estate agent,
so whether you like it or not,
you're moving.
I haven't graduated yet.
Don't think I don't know.
You've taken extra credits,
so you could have graduated early.
Tuo can graduate now.
Why didn't he tell me?
Mr. Han is so bossy.
The first thing he says when he's back
is to take Tuo to Kaohsiung,
ignoring what he wants.
If Tuo moves away,
won't we have
to keep a long-distance relationship?
Your dad cares about you.
Growing up,
I've had dinner at your place
more often than with him.
Tuo, do you know all the words
for that upcoming dictation test?
Yeah, I know them all.
But I don't know any of them.
You're so silly.
Don't say things like that.
Mom!
Wait for me!
You're back.
I made fruit sandwiches
and put them in the fridge,
go wash your hands before eating.
Okay.
Delicious.
You've got something on your lips.
One of my parents lied to me,
saying if I behave like a good kid,
she would come back for me.
The other one was never around,
and when he showed up,
he just gave me orders,
expecting me to obey without question.
When I chose architecture,
he didn't speak to me for three months.
Now he talks about
father and son working together,
forcing me to move to Kaohsiung.
Why are they so different
from your parents?
You can go find an accountant.
Dad.
I can't handle all this work by myself,
please help me out.
Why did they have me...
if they don't care about me?
I won't go to Kaohsiung with him.
I'll stay here...
with you.
Okay.
Try find a chance
to talk with your dad again,
and be polite.
I'll help you too.
If that doesn't work, we'll ask Xiaoyang.
And if Xiaoyang can't help anything,
we'll ask my parents.
They’re the same age, they might
communicate better with each other.
Would you like to live with me?
What do you mean?
Let's move in together.
Move in together?
[In the Next Episode]
We've got the Yunlong Group's
three business hotel design project.
Han Tuo,
I need your help with this.
I'll be on a work trip lately,
test-staying at the hotels.
I miss you so much these days,
because you're not around.
When it comes to relationships,
you're still a rookie.
What's wrong?
You must tell me
if something's bothering you.
I'm feeling a bit confused right now.