What's going on? You can tell me frankly.
I don't like your father.
You think I'm a big fan of my Dad?
If you don't think of me that way,
you see me as an object like this?
Sure, I do.
What do you think of me?
Models with no thoughts are no better
than clothes hangers, don't you think?
Oh my…
Hello, Ms.Duangtawan.
This is 78 Questions with Taste Magazine.
78 questions? I That's right.
May I come in? I Sure, welcome.
Mr.Thara and your kids are not home?
I'm not sure if my husband is
at the ministry or the meeting.
Dana is a fashion student at CSM in the UK.
She's the youngest of her class there.
Education is significant
in this family, isn't it?
Education is significant in every family.
I see so many art pieces in this house.
Can you tell me a story of this piece?
This one?
I got it from a gallery
by the beach in Bali.
They showcased this piece
and it truly touched a
mother's heart like mine.
What about Diesel? How is he?
He's in Thailand, he
will be in college soon.
Actually, I'm more close to my daughter.
My son is close to his
father, you know... men.
Your birthday is next week, isn't it?
What is the theme of
your upcoming birthday?
When I was a kid,
my Dad built an aviary
in our home's backyard.
There were so many kinds of birds inside.
I wanted to reminisce
my childhood memories so
the theme of this year's birthday will be.
Conference of the Birds.
I wrote this article,
can you share it for me?
Hey!
I wrote an article, can
you share it for me?
It's gonna be my portfolio for college.
Glamorous climate criminals.
1% of the rich flying private jets
causing more pollutions than
normal people do for their entire lives.
I can't.
It's fine.
Wow! You're growing
up to be a pretty girl now.
Hello. I You haven't come to
our place for such a long time.
Hello / Hello.
You're doing well, aren't you? I I am.
How are you parents?
Mom! Stop asking about her business.
What? I was just asking.
She's like a family. I I gotta go, Mom.
Yeah? Take care, honey.
Look at your face. You're hungry?
I got this for you.
Since you two had a fight,
you still haven't talked
to her? It's been years.
Don't you regret it?
You two practically attached at
the hip when you were younger.
Find a way to forgive her, will you?
You don't know anything, you
don't get to share your opinion.
Let's go, I don't want
to be stuck in traffic.
Put on your seat belt, please.
You whine a lot. I
Well, you talk back a lot.
You're not playing?
Bambi,
What article are you sharing?
About billionaires flying their
private jets, causing pollution.
What the f... k!
You wanted them to fly commercial flights?
I mean like they require
some privacy, you know?
Look Diesel!
What?
What are you mad about?
I posted it because my friend asked me to.
It didn't mean anything to me.
Well, look who's talking?
You keep on sharing news
about that Name BOY MARX. See?
He's all over my feed now, look.
Well, I need to share my work.
Such a liar. I saw you chat with him.
And you asked me to
hang out with you tonight.
Yeah see? You're making it too obvious?
Okay, fine.
He texted me about his concert
tonight, and he invited me.
He could just be nice, whatever.
Now everyone knows, you want to join me?
What about our dinner?
Dinner?
I totally forgot.
Next time, okay? Please?
I want to see Name perform.
Pathetic. F... king groupie thoughts.
Hey! Don't you think it's too harsh?
You need to understand me.
He will perform tonight only.
We can have dinner anytime.
You told me that you
didn't care about Name.
SERIOUSLY! WHAT THE F... K!!!
It's not Name. It's you! I You
don't try to understand me.
This is the one and only
performance from him.
Take a look at yourself
before saying anything.
No, you don't get it. Here, take it.
Ow!
Well, we can all go tonight, okay?
Okay? It should be fun.
What about my game?
F... k!!!
For a kid who was born
in a top-tier 1% of the most
wealthiest families in society
it should be normal for anyone to see that.
Diesel should gain a lot of inheritance.
He didn't only receive
properties as his inheritance
but he also receive some other things.
Some traits are passed on
from generation to generation
from father to son.
I'm not the only one in my
class to use it, actually everyone…
Don't make me go to your school again.
Do you understand me, son?
Did I raise you to not answer me back?
I got it.
You're a man
and men don't cry.
This inheritance is pain on his face
which happens repeatedly.
It has become his life lesson growing up.
He started to question
if this is a way of your
father to show his love
or this is a way of lovers
to show their affections.
If a pain on his face indicates love,
then he's ready to
spread it / One more time.
To someone that he thinks would love him
and to someone that
he thinks he loves them.
This is the kind of love
that he understands.
What're you doing?
This is the kind of love
that he understands.
Let's play game. Get in here, Nainoi.
I'm ready to help you out.
Why're you calling?
What is it? You keep asking
me to play, I'm so not in the mood.
How the hell could I know that you're
not in the mood? Why did you call?
I don't f... king know! I'm just upset.
Stop with your bulls... t. I'm
not in a happy mood either.
Go on, what is it?
F... k, I don't really know.
What?! How could I know?!
If there's nothing, I'll hang up.
Go ahead and do it.
What do you do when you're upset?
You called me for this?
Are you gonna help me or not?
Hold up your two hands like this.
I'm holding my phone in one hand.
Right, then use one hand
and then close your eyes.
How could I watch it if
my eyes're closed? Think!
Well, you're funny.
Fine. Start again, then inhale.
And exhale. You need to close your eyes.
See? Now do it.
Slowly and focus.
What are you laughing at?
Feeling better?
When you're stressed out, you can do this.
Nope. More stressing out.
Well, suit yourself!
See you guys next week.
Don't have too much fun partying tonight.
See you.
I gotta go. I What the fuck?!
See you tonight.
See ya.
I think you should apologize to Lukjan.
I just wanted to tell you that
you should be nice to her if you like her.
Don't focus on yourself only.
Think about it, will you still be
happy if someone talks s... t to you?
I don't think so…
Just to be clear, I don't like Lukjan.
And I don't need to apologize
to her. I did nothing wrong.
She was the one who ditched me.
I can help you with that.
Help me with what? Now
you want to help me out?
Come on.
Let's start with something simple.
Like caring.
You can order her
favorite cocktail for her.
Do you know what it is?
What? It's Long Island iced tea.
Such a pro!
You need to come with me tonight, pro.
I didn't bring anything to wear.
No big deal.
Come to my house. I'll find you something
from my sister's closet. Let's go.
Hurry up, what're you waiting for?
I won't do anything to
you, don't be scared of me.
Let's go.
You look so horny, of course I'm scared.
What did you say?
Damn! I can take these?
When will your little sister come back?
Take them, she won't be home soon.
Diesel? I Yeah?
Can I ask you something?
How is your Mom like?
Why did you ask me?
You wanted to know the dirts about her?
Nothing like that.
I admire her talent.
And I'm a big fan of DEVI.
I just wanted to know what she's like.
Can I ask you another question?
What is it like to live
in a wealthy world?
Such a weird question.
I don't know. I'm just being me like this.
Actually, I just discovered that
my life is unlike others
when I started to grow up.
I just realized that
something that I got easily
could cause someone's
hardest work to get it.
Like..
Rambutans.
I just found out later that
rambutans
are fruits with red and hairy round shape.
Rambutans that I've
been eaten my whole life
are in white translucent
flesh with no pits.
You know what I mean, right? That's it.
Right.
Oh come on,
I don't think I will truly
understand someone like you.
Bambi / What?
If you need anything, just say it.
Well,
can I go to your mom's birthday party?
Can you help me with that?
So you planned it already, huh?
You know what the party is gonna be like?
I have no idea.
I just thought that if I could get in,
and be surrounded by someone like you
then people could see me differently.
And I could understand you.
Hello, Jib?
Can you add my friend's
name to the guest list?
It's Bambi.
Okay, thank you.
Honestly, you can just make
them recognize you from the party.
A theme for my birthday
is Conference of the Birds.
Diesel? Can I borrow your book too?
Fine, just take whatever you want.
Want a drink?
Oh my gosh!
I have no idea what's going on.
Lukjan.
Woah! Long Island iced tea, thanks.
So impressive.
Let's cheers.
Cheers! Come on.
Me too.
That looks so good.
Make some noise for us.
Lukjan?
Lukjan? I Yeah?
Name won't perform tonight?
Those rappers started the
show first. I still don't get them.
Are they the ones who
confessed love to you?
A... hole!
(Singing)
You get it? I don't get it.
You didn't get it at first too.
Can I go now?
Don't worry, if he starts
something, I'll take care of it.
Stay.
Good job, guys. Nice moves.
Hello.
Sorry I was rehearsing a play, I
didn't have time to use my phone.
It's fine.
Is everything okay?
I saw Mhong.
He kept looking at me.
I told Diesel about it and
he didn't let me go home.
Can't you tell him that
you got a problem with it?
He knows it so well.
Can you come and see me?
It's fine if you can't.
I get it.
Okay, well.
I'll rush out to see you,
okay? Just stay with Diesel.
Okay, sure.
Yo! What's up! Hi.
Hello.
Are you Name? I Yes.
Break a leg up there.
Someone's here to cheer you
from a side of a bed. I Are you crazy?
I mean a side of a stage. I Sorry.
Drink, let's drink. I You're funny.
Are you out of your mind?
Why're you here so early? The
other rappers are still up there.
I'm worried that if I came here
and went straight to the stage,
someone would be so sad.
You mean me, right?
Maybe / Aww..
Come on, let's have some fun.
Can I take this one? I Sure.
Sure, go ahead. I Whose is it?
Don't forget about us. I Fine.
Cheers!
Let's do a love shot.
Yeah, why not?
Love shot! I Yeah?
Okay. I Love shot!
Love shot!
How is it? I Good.
Lukjan?
Ouch! I What is it?
How are you?
What've you been up to?
Your life has been completely different.
Why's that?
You care about me?
Of course I do, Mhong. I Mhong?
You remember my name?
That's super great.
I thought that you forgot about
me when I'm useless to you.
Can you stop? I What?
Can you stop it?
Now I know how you wanted me to feel.
So can you please stop?
What're you trying to
say, Diesel? I don't get it.
You're wasting my time, okay? I Lukjan.
What?
I know that.
I know how you wanted
me to feel about Name.
So please stop, will you?
What the fuck! I've never
thought of it that way.
Are you drunk? You should go.
I'm not talking to you. I Lukjan!
Don't f... king touch me.
So annoying. I What's
happening over here? Calm down.
What? It's none of your
business. I Calm down, young man.
I talked to you nicely.
I felt really bad about it.
But
if I can help you with anything,
you can tell me. I Help?
How can you fucking help me?
Fucking help me?
Who do you think got me
kicked out from my label?
It's because of you.
I was a complete fool
to those stupid netizens
who knew nothing about
anything because of you.
I'm not the help of Gunner.
You saw me working on wires?
When you sat there and had the
time of your life with your friends?
Are you happy now?
You must be so thrilled, right?
You wanted to help me or look down on me.
Tell me?
I think you're drunk.
Let's talk later.
So what if I'm drunk?
You kept talking nonsense things.
In the end, you used me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that
caused you this way. I Why sorry?
You're also a bitch.
I admit that I'm an asshole, too.
Why is your life going great? Only you.
And why am I the only
one who lost everything?
Damn it!
I should have did what
they encouraged me to do.
I should have just fucked you.
You don't know anything so shut up.
Hey!
She tells me every day that she
doesn't like you, what more do you want?
You really want a piece of me? I So what?
What? Why? I This is none of
your fucking business, back off.
Stop it already. I What
the fuck is wrong with you?
You're just jealous. I Jealous, my ass.
Stop it already. I You punched me?
You think you're cool because
your Dad is a politician?
What if I punched you?
I'm drunk and so what?
Please stop! We're nothing okay?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
We are nothing.
We're just fucking fuck buddies, okay?
You and I are fucking nothing. I
have no feeling for you, you hear me?
Move out of the way.
Are you okay? I Are you hurt?
Diesel?
Stop it!
Are you okay?
Are you alright?
Name, you fucking asshole!
Stop the car, don't use your phone.
What the fuck is this?
Fine I stop the car. I I don't believe you.
Send me some photos.
You happy now?
You know that it's not
safe to drive like that.
If you're not worried about hitting
something, think about innocent people.
And you broke the law, you
used your phone while driving.
Be responsible to society.
What the fucking are you talking about?
Stop preaching me already.
You got nothing to do?
Go take care of your
business and buzz off my life.
You don't have to be so vulgar…
Okay, you're here.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Easy there.
Is everything okay?
I ruined everything.
Mhong.
Diesel.
It's alright.
It will get better.
You think it will get better?
Just go to sleep.
Shooting at 7 A.M.
Are you okay?
You can tell me anything.
Squeeze it.
More!
We're just fucking fuck buddies, okay?
You and I are fucking nothing. I
have no feeling for you, you hear me?
What're you doing here?
- If I'm surrounded by someone like you, people could see me differently.
- Bambi.
Hot News! Someone reported that they saw.
Diesel abused a girl.
Who the hell is he?
You said that you're nothing like your Dad.
I think you know
what your problem is.
Why do you need to
quit starring in the play?
I don't think your
name is in the guest list.
Who the hell is Anyone?
Bambi? WHO!?!?