Hi!
Are we a couple now?
Are we, like, a boyfriend-
girlfriend thing now?
Yes, we’re officially together.
You even have a lip tint on.
He doesn’t even
know it’s my birthday.
What if he has a birthday
suprise for you later?
You should be mad.
It’s totally valid
to feel a little upset.
- Hey!
- Happy Birthday!
Lewis!
Wait. There’s a—
There’s something in your—
An eyelash.
I waited the whole day,
but nothing--
Is it okay to do it here?
It’s tinted.
Take it off.
So this is what it feels like.
Do you know what you’re doing?
Turn around.
There’s someone outside, Cy.
There’s someone outside.
Aren’t you thrilled?
Aren’t you? It’s your
first time, right?
Yes.
But my goal is not to make you
feel like it’s my first time.
Wow.
Hey…
We need to go
back to your party.
Yeah.
So…
how was it?
It felt good.
But I’m tired.
I want to go home.
What?
Your party hasn’t
even started yet,
and you already want to go home?
Come on,
clean yourself up first,
and then let’s go back in there.
I’m tired.
Maui, come on. Let’s go back.
Fine.
Love?
Yes?
Happy Birthday.
What’s this?
Why are you getting shy now?
What is this—
What?
Yeah, the ring that you’re
wearing right now,
our parents chose it for us.
So, I think it’s just right that
I give you a ring
that I picked myself.
But if you don’t want
to wear it,
that’s completely fine.
Oh my gosh. This is beautiful.
Put it on me.
-Please.
- Okay.
I’m going to marry you.
Don’t be so sure, Cy.
Don’t give me false hopes.
What if something big happens
that forces us apart?
Even if the world
forces me to leave you,
I wouldn’t.
No matter what happens,
I’ll stay right by your side.
So, do the same for me.
Okay?
I want to stay with you, too.
You’ll always be
there for me, right?
Of course, love.
Yeah.
Thank you.
- Ke! Don’t leave me!
- Wait!
- Hey.
- Sorry, Sam. I’m leaving.
- Huh? Why?
- Wait!
- Hey—
- Sorry.
Ke! Don’t leave me! Ke!
What’s happening?
- Via?
- Larkin, what are you doing?
What the—
Wow.
I’m so confused right now.
Anyway,
let’s just get drinks.
Wait, but those were
your friends, right?
How chaotic.
Let’s go.
Wait ‘til you meet
my best friend.
Hey, it’s okay.
You don’t have to drink
if you don’t want to.
No, I want to drink.
Okay.
Those were strong.
It’s strong because it’s mine.
- Huh?
- Drink this instead.
I ordered it for you.
Try it.
Oh, yeah. This is better.
Don’t get drunk, okay?
You used to preach about
drinking alcohol back then.
Take it easy.
It’s just for tonight.
I’m still a little embarrassed.
Embarrassed? About what?
About what happened earlier.
Hey, it’s okay.
You don’t need to feel shy
about giving me a ring.
The sex, Maui.
It’s—
It’s okay.
You don’t have to feel shy.
That was
unforgettable.
Wait, are you sure
that was your car?
Oh my god. Don’t tell me
it was Ridge’s!
No, it’s not Ridge’s car.
That was an old Benz
I used to own.
That was my dad’s
graduation gift to me,
but I don’t use it
that much anymore.
- Cheers.
- Sam!
Girls.
Is this the lucky guy?
More like the lucky girl.
Sam, your man’s hot.
Cy, my blockmates.
Girls, this is Clyden,
my boyfriend.
- Hi, nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you, guys.
- Boyfriend?
- Yeah.
But you’re wearing
a diamond ring?
You’re fucking engaged?
Yes.
Okay.
You really are
the luckiest girl.
Okay. So, we are
celebrating your birthday
and your engagement tonight.
Yeah?
So, what are we going to do?
Let’s dance!
Girls, let’s celebrate.
- Okay.
- Go ahead, girls!
Okay. Let’s go!
I’ll be right there.
Hey, you don’t wanna dance?
- What?
- Let’s dance.
No. I’m not dancing.
But sure, I’ll go with you.
Okay.
You’re the only one dancing, okay?
You.
You have brought
so much joy to my life.
You’ve made my heart flutter.
You’ve made me feel things
I’ve only known
in songs and stories.
From the moment I met you,
it felt like things
in my life
were finally starting
to fall into place.
Every moment with you
feels like a reminder
that life has a way
of surprising you.
The way you look at me,
it’s as if you always see
the best parts of me.
It doesn’t matter
where we are,
as long as we’re together,
I’m the happiest.
We don’t need big gestures.
Just being there
for each other,
and doing the things we love,
are enough.
And you became my family
just when I needed one.
Remember when you asked me,
how I’d know if
I was already falling in love?
I knew I was falling in love
when I felt a love
I’d never known before,
when my fears
faded into ease,
when being with you
felt like home.
Easy love. That’s us.
Every time
I look at our photos,
I find more reasons to smile.
More reasons to love you.
And the best part?
We’re just getting started.
You've been staring
at that for a while now.
You really miss him, huh?
Of course.
He's just busy with school,
but we still make time.
That’s good.
Hey, thanks by the way,
for letting me stay here.
Come on, you're my best friend!
You can stay here
as long as you want.
Are you sure you're okay
living with two Yanna's here?
Of course!
I'd love to wake up
with my godchild around!
Wait,
have you thought of a name yet?
I'm still thinking about it.
How about Avi?
Since you like aviation.
That could work!
Avrielle.
Kinda close to April too,
since we made her in April.
Yanna—
Thanks for that TMI.
But, yeah. Avrielle.
I love that name.
Her second name could be
related to the sky.
What do you think?
Haven?
Yanna, that’s so beautiful.
She has her parents’ initials.
Avrielle Haven.
Hey, she kicked!
Really?
- Baby!
- She likes the name too.
All right, I’ve decided.
At least through her name,
Hiro can still be
a part of our child.
Avrielle Haven,
your auntie is
going to spoil you!
Auntie?
Yeah, why not?
Okay, fine!
What’s with all this stuff?
Do you have a business
or something?
No. They're for the kids,
for the charity event
this weekend.
You’re too kind!
- Avrielle.
- Avrielle. Avi!
Sam!
Hey!
You’re finally here.
Of course, this is my event.
Guys, this is Naomi,
my sister.
- Hello.
- Hello!
- They’re my highschool friends.
- I’m Sevi.
Sevi, Via, and Luna.
They’re all nice.
Are you okay?
And who’s this?
This is Clyden.
My boyfriend.
Huh?
Hello! I'm Via.
Clyden.
You two are so cute,
I hope you never break up.
Via, I've heard that before.
You told us not to break up,
and then we did.
That’s bad luck.
What do you mean,
Via's bad luck?
- You're the bad luck, Luna.
- Huh?
The name’s Sevi, bro.
Clyden.
It’s him. He’s the one
dancing with—
Why bring it up?
He doesn’t
remember it anymore…
Luna, by the way.
I’m Clyden.
Nice to meet you all.
You’re too formal, bro.
Aren’t you pretty?
Hey!
Sorry, I’m just a little late.
Hi!
This is my boyfriend.
Hi, bro!
You probably know me already,
so I won’t bother
introducing myself.
Wow.
I don’t know you.
That's Arkin.
One of my high school friends.
Arkin Sanchez, bro.
Clyden.
Aren’t you familiar with my song?
No?
Or maybe you’re
familiar with this line.
Am I not enough?
Am I still not enough for you?
That’s one of my famous
lines from my movie.
You didn’t get to watch it?
You didn’t?
Or maybe you know this one.
Refreshing!
That’s a commercial.
You haven’t even seen it on—
- On TV?
- I don’t watch TV.
Sorry.
Well, that explains it.
You should try watching.
TV’s fun, bro.
Sometimes there’s news
and a lot of—
Let me help you.
This looks heavy.
You should help out!
You’re just laughing there,
not doing anything useful,
no help at all.
- Take this!
- Moron,
you just embarrassed
yourself, dude.
Okay! Guys, we’re all here now.
Too bad Yanna
and Ke can’t make it.
All right, let’s go.
- The kids are almost here.
- Let me help you.
Let’s go.
- Thank you.
- Where should this be?
[background chattering]
Just over there.
Before, I used to think
Christmas was
all about food and gifts.
But now, I realize it actually
means something deeper.
What really makes
Christmas special are
the people you spend it with.
I’m proud of you.
So I’m really happy
to be with all of you
this Christmas.
I hope
this day becomes a happy
memory for all of you.
And whenever
you look back on this,
remember that you
deserve all the joy,
happiness,
and love in the world.
And to make things
even more fun,
Arkin and Sevi prepared a
special dance just for you all!
Let’s clap!
Let’s go, Sevi!
Cheer for them, kids!
Yes! Arkin and Sevi!
Hello.
Hi.
Bring Clyden here.
Hi!
- Clap!
- What?
I don’t dance. I don’t know how!
We have an actor with us.
Just follow his lead.
Clap!
Just follow my lead.
Hey!
This is for you.
Smile at the cam.
- Let’s smile at the camera.
- Smile!
Okay, thank you.
- For you.
- Thank you, Sam!
You’re welcome.
Wait a minute.
I’ll be right back.
For you.
Don’t forget to
smile at the cam.
Hi!
Come on, let’s join the others.
I’m shy.
What? You're shy?
For you, smile at the camera.
I’ll get you something,
wait a bit.
Okay. Here you go.
Here, this is for you.
- Excuse me.
- Smile at Naomi.
For you.
Here. This is my gift for you.
Thank you.
You’re welcome. Open it.
Wow! Let’s play later, okay?
Sure. Do you know
how to play that?
Yes, I do.
What’s your name?
Samantha.
You’re Samantha, too?
How old are you?
Nine years old.
Nine years old, huh…
He’s going to be an amazing
pediatrician one day.
Are you happy?
Did you enjoy the event?
Yes. Your friends are so fun.
Good.
I’m happy that you’re happy.
Sam,
thanks for letting me
stay at your house
this holiday break.
Naomi, you’re always welcome
to stay anytime you want.
And you can celebrate
every Christmas with me
until you get tired of it.
I want you to be happy.
Always.
Thanks, Sam.
But I don’t think
it's possible for someone
to be happy all the time.
Naomi—
I know a therapist.
Do you wanna meet her?
I’m fine.
I’m happy now.
You’re happy right now,
but what about tomorrow?
And the following days?
Naomi,
I wanna help you.
I’m your sister.
Okay. I’ll do it because
I don't want to see you cry
because of me.
I don’t wanna see you sad
because of me, okay?
Thank you for trying.
You good?
I’ll just take
a picture of the kids.
Yeah. Sure, enjoy.
Hey.
I’m so proud of
everything that you do.
Thank you for pushing me.
Of course.
So,
how did your talk with Naomi go?
She
agreed to see a therapist.
- That’s nice.
- Yeah.
Okay.
Mom set up a dinner
with both of our families.
I wonder what it’s for.
Huh? Really? I have no idea.
I don’t know.
Sam’s graduation and
Clyden’s clerkship are coming up.
After that,
we can finally set the wedding
for these two, right?
And during their wedding,
I will announce
Clyden’s inheritance
for our family business.
Dad, there's really
no need to rush.
You're still healthy.
It's better to be prepared.
And besides,
you don’t need to prove
anything to me anymore.
I gave you so many chances,
and you blew every single one.
But I’m better than him!
I deserve the inheritance!
I’m the eldest!
Son, please sit down.
In which aspect?
What?
In which aspect are you
better than me?
- Huh?
- Love—
I just want to know.
Do I really have
to spell it all out?
Go.
You took everything that
was supposed to be mine.
- The hospital,
- Stop—
the house—
Your fiancée.
What?
Does it feel good
to have my leftovers?
Fucker, don’t you dare
talk about Samantha like that!
You’re the one who
fucked up your own life.
And now you're
blaming it on others?
Manners please.
- Enough.
- I’m really sorry about this.
I’m really sorry.
You shouldn’t have been born.
Harsh.
Excuse me.
That’s enough.
I’m sorry.
Will you excuse us?
- Excuse us.
Hey.
Naomi, please go to your room.
Are you okay, sweetheart?
Oh my god,
that family is so chaotic.
If we just didn’t need them,
right now, right then—
I would have pulled you out
of that engagement.
What?
Why do we need them?
Maui,
just in case
anything happens to us,
you need Clyden.
With Clyden, your future’s
gonna be secure.
So just lean on him, okay?
That wasn’t the first time
he said that.
I’m sorry.
The hell with that
fucking inheritance!
If he wants it that badly,
then fine,
let him have
the damn inheritance.
Love, I’m tired.
I’m tired of always
receiving shit
for putting hard work
in everything that I did.
Do I deserve nothing?
Should I always be
considerate to those fuckers
who did nothing but to
make my life a living hell?
You deserve everything good
in this world, love.
You’re the only
good thing in this world.
No, Cy.
Despite everything,
there are still a lot
of good things in this world.
And we’ll experience
them together.
Today was just a bad day.
You know what?
Christmas is coming soon.
I just want to
celebrate and enjoy it
peacefully with you and Naomi.
Just us being together.
Okay.
Let’s make the most out of it,
together.
Merry Christmas!
Okay, what is this?
Open it.
Oh my gosh!
My dream heels!
Love…
I hope someday, you could
wear those on the runway.
- That really suits you, Sam.
- Right?
Thank you, love.
You're welcome.
So, here’s my gift.
Wow!
To always remind you that
I’m always here for you
throughout your whole journey.
You’ve still got
a long way to go,
but you’ve come so far already.
Thank you, love.
- All right.
- Okay.
That looks good on you, Clyden.
- Thank you.
- I know, right?
Yeah.
I like it.
Of course,
we have a gift
for my favorite sister.
Open it.
Really?
Yeah.
A photography book? No way!
I’ll read this everyday, Sam.
And when I get better,
I’ll take your
modeling portfolio.
Merry Christmas!
- Merry Christmas!
Thank you, Sam.
Thank you, Clyden.
Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas!
- Merry Christmas, let’s eat.
- Okay.
Cheers!
- Cheers!
Wow! You really look
like a model, Sam!
You know,
I’ve been learning a lot from
the book that you gave me.
I hope I can do justice
in this shoot.
Okay, let’s do it.
You know what, you’re getting
better at this.
Okay, what else?
This one?
Yeah. Try a different pose.
You know what, you’re getting
good at this.
This one?
See!
You can really be
a professional model one day.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I’ve been watching videos online
and it seems like
they're working.
Wow.
You know, if I didn’t know you,
I’d totally mistake you
for a supermodel.
Yeah. Look at these, Clyden.
Let me see.
Gorgeous.
Which one?
The shots or the model?
Both.
Oh, come on.
Okay. Your turn, Clyden.
- Your turn.
- Oh, yeah.
- Me?
- Pose for us.
- Go.
- I wanna see your poses.
Okay, go.
- I don’t know how!
- Go, love!
Go, go.
Go.
Wow, not bad.
That could work too.
Could even be a dog model.
Dog what? You're cracking up.
You’re just making fun of me.
- Okay, your turn!
- What?
- No way.
- Yeah.
It's your turn,
- It’s your turn.
- No, I’m the photographer.
No.
I’ll take the photo.
Let’s just do a selfie instead.
– All right.
– Okay.
Let me see.
Wait, I’ll just get something.
So, you’re going home tomorrow?
I don’t even know if I could
call that house my home.
I’m sorry, I know the feeling.
Well, our house is always here
if you ever need a safe space.
Did you move out of that house
to get away from me?
What? No.
I moved out ‘cause my condo’s
closer to school—
and I thought maybe
you’d be more comfortable
if I weren’t at home.
The truth is,
when you moved out,
it felt harder to breathe
in that house.
I don’t understand
myself either.
When you were still around,
I felt envy and anger,
but when you went away—
I felt fear. I felt scared.
That night on my birthday,
I didn’t know why I texted you.
My hands moved
before I could even think.
But you made the right choice.
It was actually one
of the few things I did
that led me to good things.
I wanna go there.
Where?
To the moon.
Or just beside it.
I wanna be one of the stars.
You shine bright
in my eyes, Naomi.
Like a star.
Do you think there’s
pain there, Sam?
I’m not sure,
but I hope there’s none.
Thank you for making me happy,
even for a short period of time.
Of course.
I’ll be here with you as you go
through your healing process.
May this year be
a wonderful year for both of us.
I hope so, Sam.
I really do.
Naomi, why do you want that?
What do you mean?
To be one of the stars.
I’m jealous.
I want to shine bright
like a star.
Look at that star.
It gives you hope, right?
The light it emits amidst
the darkness gives you hope.
I wonder how that feels,
to look as pretty as that star.
That when people look at you,
it gives them hope.
You look as pretty as that star.
No, you look prettier.
You have this radiance that
no star could ever give.
And when I look at you,
I don’t only think about hope.
I think about how blessed I am
to have a sister
like you in my life.
You keep me going, too, Naomi.
I do?
Yeah.
So I wish
you could see hope in me, too.
I’ll be your star.
A star doesn't necessarily
have to be in the sky
to shine, right?
You’re here on the ground,
but I’ll be here with you.
You don’t have
to look up anymore.
Just look for me
and I’ll be here.
I’ll always be here.
It’s almost twelve.
- Where’s mine?
- Here.
Ten, nine—
eight, seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one!
- Happy new year!
- Happy new year, love.
- Happy new year.
You guys are too sweet.
Happy new year, Sam and Clyden.
I’m so thankful to start
this year with you.
More years to spend together.
I’m claiming it.
This will be a good year
for all of us!
Wait, let’s take a picture.
Okay.
- Okay.
Hold this.
I’ll help you with this one.
Okay, wait.
Say, cheese.
- Cheese!
That’s nice!
- Cheers!
You’re graduating soon.
Congrats, Sam!
Thank you. You know what,
I’m so excited,
but I’m definitely
going to miss my friends.
Well, I might have some news
that might make leaving
school a little easier.
What is it?
Zenaida Models.
They loved your portfolio!
They’re gonna sign you.
Wait. What?
Are you serious?
Oh my god. Giselle!
I know, they're gonna
call you up.
Oh my gosh.
I don’t know.
Is this really happening?
Oh my gosh.
I can’t believe it.
Yes.
They wanna fly you
to Singapore,
so you can sign the contract
and then they’ll launch you
on their website.
Girl, you’re in!
It’s really happening!
Oh my gosh!
You know what, I’m so happy.
Wait, I need to call someone.
Go ahead.
I need to share this big news.
Cy! Hi, you won’t believe it.
I got the offer, the agency
is going to sign me.
What? Really?
That’s great news, love.
I’m so proud of you!
I really can’t believe this.
I’ll call you later, okay?
Yeah, bye.
- Cheers?
- Cheers!
Cheers!
Congratulations, Sam!
Thank you, enjoy the party.
Sam.
This is my daughter, Sam.
And this is Clyden Ramirez,
the heir to Ramirez Medical.
They’re engaged.
What a young lovely couple.
When’s the wedding?
Mid next year.
Don’t worry,
I’ll send you the invites.
Next year? We haven’t
even set the date yet.
Wow. I’m sure it will be
a grand wedding.
Of course, you know me.
It will be the wedding
of the year
or maybe the wedding
of the century.
- I agree.
- Wow, that’s so exciting.
Mom, can I talk to you?
Excuse me. My daughter
has to talk to me.
I’ll just go to the bathroom.
- Sure.
- Excuse me, Auntie.
Mom, what do you mean
the wedding’s mid next year?
You already picked a date
without asking us first?
Yes!
Clyden is graduating
next year, remember?
It’s so hard to
prepare for a wedding.
Let me handle everything, okay?
Just please,
let me handle it.
Just cooperate with me, okay?
We need to rush
your wedding, Maureen.
Why?
I don’t wanna rush my wedding.
Mom, I want to do
other things, too.
Well, you can do that.
After your wedding.
We talked about this
already, honey, right?
I’m going to Singapore
this weekend.
I got hired by Zenaida Models.
I’m going to Singapore
to pursue modeling.
Did I hear that right,
Maui?
Why?
Because it’s what I want.
I’ve been working hard
for this in the past year.
No…
No! Of course not.
You are not going to Singapore.
You are going to call the agency
and you're gonna tell them
that you’re not signing.
I am not going
to allow it. No way.
Mom, this is what I want to do.
You can’t keep
controlling my life,
I’ve already graduated.
I can decide for myself.
And I cannot be your mother?
Who is just worried
for you, Maureen?
Do you even know the kind
of industry you’re entering?
It’s a ruthless world
out there, Maui.
They will chew you up
and they will spit you out!
Then what do you want me to do?
Should I just follow
everything you say, then?
How will I ever grow
and be my own person
if I just follow you
my whole life?
My life is my own, too, Mom.
Let me live it.
Maureen, can you please
just be useful
to us just this once?
Be useful?
Was I only born just
to be useful to you?
You wanna be a model?
Fine.
You can be a model.
That’s what you want?
But make sure, Maureen,
you become a famous,
a very famous model.
So we can use that
for your dad’s campaign.
Right.
That’s right, sweetheart.
You can pursue your dream
and still help
with your dad’s campaign
at the same time.
You just have to be
very famous, Maureen.
Very famous.
You’re unbelievable.
Mau—
Hey.
Don’t listen to her.
You are worth more
than what she said.
So, just focus on doing
things for yourself, okay?
Can you just come live with me?
I can’t stand thinking about you
being stuck in this house,
dealing with them all alone.
I can still handle it.
Besides,
I’ve been taking your advice.
I’m doing regular
therapy sessions.
So, I’ll be fine.
Don’t worry about me.
Here. Keep it.
You’ll be okay, right?
Of course.
I need to be strong.
I have to set
an example for you,
and I know you look up to me,
and I can’t let you down.
You’re already
a great role model.
You’re the perfect
sister for me.
So, go after your dreams
in Singapore, okay?
I’ll always be cheering for you.
Hey,
I’m so proud of you.
I know that wasn’t easy.
It’s because of you.
You made me realize
that I have a voice.
I was always the obedient child
with no opinions for herself.
So, I never thought I had
the courage to do that.
You’ve always
had it in you, Maui.
I still have a lot to prove,
to them, to myself,
that I can stand on my own.
So, I need to make it
in modeling.
I never wanna ask them
for money, ever again.
And I believe in you, Maui.
And I’ll be here cheering you on
every step of the way.
But it’s hard.
I don’t want you to leave.
Cy, it’s just four days.
I know,
but no matter how close it is,
even if it’s just four days,
I’m still gonna miss you.
So much.
But it has to be done.
We’ll reach our
dreams together, right?
Let’s reach our dreams together,
for each other.
Yeah.
Take care, okay?
- Okay?
- Okay.
Hey, is everything okay?
Yeah.
I’m just feeling scared.
What if I get lost?
What if I miss my meetings?
What if they don’t like me?
What if they change their minds?
Hey, listen to me. Okay?
First of all, stop overthinking.
They’re going to love you,
and you're going to be amazing.
You’ve got this!
Yeah, I got this.
I was born for this.
That’s the spirit.
Thanks for seeing me off.
Why are you sad?
Because I’m gonna miss you.
Maui, it’s just four days.
But it’s the longest
four days of my life.
Come here.
Go now, you’re gonna
miss your flight.
Take care.
Okay.
- Be careful there.
- Bye. Yeah.
Okay.
Hello.
- Here you go, Miss.
- Thank you.
Cy?
What are you doing here?
You really think I’d let you go
to Singapore alone?
Of course I'll come with you.
But how?
Aren’t you busy
with your clerkship?
I have five days
before clerkship starts.
And I wanna spend
every single day with you.
You really love me
that much, huh?
Is it that obvious?
Wait, how about your
luggage and stuff,
didn't you bring anything?
Don't worry about that.
Let's just go shopping.
Thank you for
coming with me, Cy.
You know how much
this means to me.
First out of the country
trip together,
we're gonna have so much fun!
Yes! Singapore, baby!
Avi’s so pretty!
- Of course.
- Baby Avi.
But did you guys know
Avi isn’t the only blessing
in the group right now?
You’re pregnant?
Yes, Sam?
Huh?
- You’re pregnant?
- You’re pregnant, Sam?
No. I got signed to a modeling
agency in Singapore.
Wow!
- Wait, SG? Like, Singapore?
- Yes!
Congratulations!
Wow, international, huh?
Thank you guys,
I’ll be flying there soon.
So, are you gonna be
based there now?
I’m not sure yet,
but I’ll probably spend
a lot of time there.
But have you and
Clyden talked about this?
I mean, being in
a long distance relationship?
Yeah, especially with how busy
Clyden is with med school.
Yeah, that’s true. But well,
it’s still the same
time zone, right?
But then again, Clyden’s
usually awake at dawn.
I just realized,
it’s really hard dating
med and law students.
We haven’t talked about
the details yet,
but we’ll figure it out.
You know, we have
a strong foundation,
and we can work this out.
- We can make it work.
- Strong—
Wow!
- Confident!
- Seriously though—
Well, you guys already
managed dating
with different
schedules before, so—
You’ve got this!
You both got this.
Be careful there.
Bye. Yeah.
Okay.
I think this is the
start of our busy era.
We promise to have our regular
date every Sunday, right?
I know you’re a Ramirez.
But lives are on the line here.
It’s our date night.
Do you still want to go?
Should we skip?
'Cause I’m sleepy.
How are you?
The sched’s been hectic, but…
Isn’t Clyden gonna look for you?
Don’t you guys
have a celebration today?
What more do
you want from me?
I agreed to let you model,
didn’t I?
Is it true?
The accusations against you?
You benefited
from my money, too!
You disgust me!
Stop it!
You don’t have it rough
with your parents!
Me?