WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
EPISODE 7
Okay, let's go one more time.
In-a.
Yu-jin.
I'm here too.
Speak up.
Help.
Louder!
Help!
Shut your mouth!
Your sister's gone deaf,
and your brother is dead.
You can't sacrifice your voice?
Not every life holds
the same value, Hee-joo.
No.
We…
We can only stay
if the chairman feels sorry for us.
Do you understand?
No, tell her you don't want to.
No.
Hong Hee-joo!
Paik Sa-eon?
Right.
There was you.
When no one else cared about me,
you noticed me.
Whenever I was scared,
you ran over to save me.
Hong Hee-joo!
Even when I said nothing,
even when I didn't cry out for help,
you were the only one who listened to me.
Hong Hee-joo.
I like you.
But…
why couldn't I bring myself to say it?
That I feel the same…
Hee-joo.
Are you okay?
Can you see me?
Wait, I'll get the doctor.
Don't go.
Okay.
I won't go.
I won't go anywhere.
Okay.
It's okay.
It's okay now.
An accidental fall?
Yes, sir. During their company retreat,
someone fell on a hike.
Who was it?
A new presidential
sign language interpreter.
But security was tight,
so I couldn't find out.
Why did they fall?
Were they drunk?
Were they drunk hiking?
God… They're going to have
a field day with this.
I don't think that was the case.
This punk makes things worse
instead of helping me out.
This is a sensitive time.
How could he let that happen?
Excuse me, sir?
Maybe it wasn't an accident.
Keep going.
Instead of the presidential spokesperson,
how about focusing on him being your son
and making it look like
political…
Prepare the script.
Right.
Will I look good on camera?
I ended up speaking.
He knows everything anyway.
406! Listen to me carefully.
I've put a first-aid kit
inside of Hee-joo's backpack.
I hope Hee-joo finds it and uses it.
What do you think, 406?
He said 406,
but it felt like he was saying it to me.
He's not an idiot,
so there's no way he doesn't know.
But why hasn't he said anything?
Stand here, place your hands
on the sides, and put your chin here.
Is it because I'm still a patient?
Then the moment I get discharged…
Let's divorce, Hong Hee-joo. No…
I mean, 406.
Since you breached the contract,
cough up the two billion won.
All this time,
you sure fooled me.
How dare you?
Get out now.
I can't stand the sight of you.
I said I liked you.
I take it back.
Miss, don't move.
I'm taking the X-ray now.
Wait, where's the phone?
I said not to move.
There's no footage?
Yes, I checked the entire trail,
from the entrance to the summit,
but there was no one
who could be identified as a suspect.
And there were no cameras
where the accident occurred.
Any witnesses?
We're gathering statements,
but the scene was so chaotic
and crowded that day.
How's Ms. Hong Hee-joo now?
She's being examined.
For now, there are no major issues.
What a relief.
- The police are waiting for a statement…
- Don't tell them she's awake yet.
I'll get her statement.
Her identity
is being fully protected, right?
Yes, sir.
But why do you think
he went after Interpreter Hong Hee-joo?
I'm sure they were after me
and missed their shot.
What about the thing
I asked you to look into?
I've checked it.
Did you find anything?
The malicious code we found on the phone
during the voice modulation analysis
was actually planted
to facilitate hacking.
- Hacking?
- Yes.
The program is called RCS,
and it can control PCs or smartphones
to monitor users remotely
and track their location.
Is that how he followed us to the summit?
With the tracking device?
But if we hack the code
and collect the data on the other side--
Then we can track his location.
How long will it take?
At most, two to three days. I'll hurry.
Great work.
It's only a matter of time
before we find him.
You can go now.
Why are you being so tight-lipped now?
You had no trouble speaking earlier.
You'll stop talking again?
I like it.
I like feeling your heartbeat.
It's okay.
I already knew
that you could talk.
I know far more about you…
than you think.
406.
He told me your location.
He might've been the one who pushed you,
but he helped me find you too.
So, I'm torn.
406…
Should I catch
and hand him over to the cops
or just forgive him?
- The truth is--
- Do you see that?
ABSOLUTE REST
What you need right now is rest.
Absolute rest.
I have many things I want to ask you,
things I'm curious about, but…
I won't ask right now.
So, for now,
just rest.
What about my work?
You'll be on sick leave.
So, just…
think about getting better.
I'll be away for a few hours.
Your old phone was smashed,
so use this now.
Call me if anything happens.
Got it?
- Answer me.
- Okay.
I'll be back.
Did he not see it?
I was…
going to use this phone to escape you.
You wanted Hong In-a from the start.
Hong Hee-joo is just a stand-in puppet.
It's not like you married her for love.
You don't even love her now.
But this phone was
the only thing that connected you and me.
Hee-joo isn't supplementary pages.
She's a brand-new language.
Does Hee-joo want sincerity,
attention,
understanding,
and affection?
Is that what she wants?
You don't have any neck wrinkles at all.
I can see them, though.
Try your best.
I almost forgot. Your daughter's here.
Did you see her?
What? Is she really here?
What's gotten into you?
You never listened to me
when I told you to come.
Right.
There's something
I've been meaning to ask you.
Sa-eon seems to care about you a lot.
What's your secret?
Was it that work outfit?
Did that do the trick?
Get up, you brat.
You should be thanking me.
Do you get it now?
A man needs a woman's touch--
What? You!
- What are you doing here?
- It's been a while.
How have you been?
PARK DO-JAE
Yeah, I'm on my way.
It's not that.
There's something
you have to check right now.
What is it?
UNCOVER THE TRUTH
WITH UNBIASED INVESTIGATION
PRESS CONFERENCE
PRESIDENTIAL OFFICE RETREAT ATTACK
I am truly devastated
and at a loss for words.
I am not only a presidential candidate
of this country
but also a father to my beloved only son.
Yes?
So, you're saying
that you believe the fall
at the spokesperson's office retreat
could be a "political terror"
rather than just an accidental stumble?
Is that it?
I want to believe it's not true,
but how could this possibly
be just a random accident?
But according to what's been reported,
nothing happened to the spokesperson…
How fortunate is that?
Well, of course,
I know it's a great tragedy
for the presidential office staff
and their family
who were affected by the accident,
and I sincerely wish
for their swift recovery.
However,
to determine whether it was an attack
aimed at the spokesperson
or an accident involving a staff member,
I urge a thorough investigation
to get to the bottom of it.
We are still investigating
whether it was an accident…
This is the spokesperson's office.
- As of now…
- We're verifying the facts.
- Refrain from speculative reporting.
- Well…
We're still investigating
whether it was an accidental fall or not.
No, that's the position
of the presidential candidate.
It has nothing to do with us…
Someone got hurt. Does that really matter?
It's a matter of life and death, you know?
No, I'm not saying they died.
Hello?
Hello--
Sir?
From now on, our office will only say
these three things.
Repeat them like a parrot.
One, we're verifying the facts.
Two, we're finalizing our stance.
Three, the press release is tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
It's not today? It's not right now?
Rash responses will only fuel
misunderstandings and speculation.
We'll act with confirmed information,
which we will secure by the end of today.
Then…
what shall we do?
Mr. Kang, ensure that
the victim's personal information
is protected and not leaked.
Send a confidentiality notice
to other departments.
Sir.
I don't believe this.
We haven't worked with her for long,
but Hong Hee-joo is our colleague.
You don't explain anything.
You just want us to hide it,
cover it up, and conceal it.
We're worried about her too. That's right.
Is she okay? Did she wake up?
Is she eating well?
She's safe.
Fortunately, she wasn't hurt much.
I'm sure you were all worried.
I'm sorry for causing concern.
In the midst of it all,
what's with
Candidate Paik Ui-yong's statement?
Darn it.
I'll address that soon as well.
When did you get back?
When and how did you get the surgery,
and when did you start talking?
What's the rush?
Don't you care to know how I've been?
Your father's probably curious about that.
What are you up to?
Don't worry. I'm not here to be
the future president's daughter-in-law.
You can't have it anyway.
Hee-joo takes after me, after all.
You heard what I said earlier.
She has Sa-eon wrapped around her finger
in three years of marriage.
Do you really think so?
Even after she finds out
the truth about him?
What?
I know you know.
You're the one who kindly gave the hint
the day before the wedding.
CHUNGWOON ART CENTER
TO CEO HONG IN-A
CHUNGWOON ART CENTER CEO HONG IN-A
You sent that to me.
To scare me into running away.
What are you talking about?
What did you get before the wedding?
It wasn't you?
Whatever it is, I don't care.
It's in the past. Let's not bring it up.
If you're not here to cause trouble,
keep a low profile.
Don't provoke your father
right before the election.
I'm not here
to cause trouble but to help Hee-joo.
It wouldn't matter if this was just
a business agreement to her, but…
I don't think that's the case.
So?
Then she needs to know.
What she decides after that is up to her.
Help, my foot.
What do you know about Paik Sa-eon?
Tell me.
What more do I need to know?
Is there more?
The public is showing sympathy
and support as we speak.
As expected,
the supporters are rallying together.
However, the spokesperson's stance
hasn't been clarified yet.
Why don't you
align your positions with him?
You're right.
I thought I'd hear from him right away,
so why has it been so quiet?
You finally came, Mr. Spokesperson.
How are you? Were you hurt?
No.
Thanks to my father's heartfelt tears
and concern.
The mood's set, so just go with the flow,
and don't go off track.
You're the one who's going off track,
not me.
Unless you want to be countered,
you should stop here.
Countered?
By who?
You?
This is my sincere advice.
Don't stir this matter up any further.
Hey, you ungrateful bastard!
Hey, Paik Sa-eon.
Who gave you that name?
"Paik Jang-ho's grandson,
Paik Ui-yong's son."
Who gave you that title?
My son doesn't eat that kind of food.
Eat this.
My son doesn't wear clothes like that.
Wear this.
My son doesn't like those types of books.
Read these.
PAIK SA-EON
Did I ask for it?
What?
That name.
That title!
I didn't get it because I wanted it.
Stop shoving it down my throat.
I'm on the verge of throwing it all up.
Who's the staff member that fell?
Are they legit?
Are you sure they're not a mole
planted by those who--
- It was family.
- What?
Who are you talking about?
A new presidential
sign language interpreter.
A sign language interpreter…
That can't be.
Unless you've lost your mind,
you wouldn't hire her, right?
What?
Does it displease you that Hee-joo entered
the presidential office
before you could?
PAIK UI-YONG, A FATHER'S HEARTFELT TEARS
My goodness.
So what's the spokesperson's stance?
It hasn't been announced yet.
I hear no one knows yet
who had the accident.
No.
By any chance, have you contacted Hee-joo?
I texted her,
but she hasn't texted me back yet.
Goodness.
Be careful. You'll get hurt.
Coming?
The owner of the villa
listed in the land register
is a person named Jeong Jin-seok.
That's right.
I looked into that too in the past.
- Did you meet him?
- No.
He wasn't living at the listed address.
I wouldn't hire a private investigator
just to find him.
From our investigation,
Jeong Jin-seok has overdue
property and real estate taxes.
But the National Tax Service
wouldn't tolerate it.
That's right. They're tracking him too.
I told the tax authorities
we were preparing a program related
to a unsolved child abduction case
and that we needed
to find someone named Jeong Jin-seok,
and they said they'd share
the information when they find him.
Really? That's great.
I think we'll make progress.
Mr. Han?
Are you finally showing interest?
Didn't you want to pull the plug?
No, that's before I knew about the twins.
Have you tried to ask around
about the orphanage friends?
Does anyone know the twin?
Yeah, I'm looking.
Was it him?
How did he know to come there?
I'm on my way. Do you need anything?
No.
Anything you want to eat?
Tteokbokki?
Nothing spicy.
Then, fried chicken?
Nothing greasy.
Then anything sweet.
No, it'll raise your blood sugar.
Why ask if you were going
to say no to everything?
Is he teasing me?
HONG HEE-JOO
WHEN WILL YOU GET HERE?
If you want something sweet,
eat some fruits.
But these…
haven't been washed.
Are you saying that to me?
By the way, when did you go home?
On my way here.
I had to get some of my stuff too.
Why would you bring this?
Family members need certain items
for hospital stays too.
- Why are you only thinking about yourself?
- You'll sleep here?
We've already slept together.
Last night.
Where did we sleep together?
And where's he going to sleep tonight?
Here?
There?
Wait, there?
Is he taking a shower?
Why?
No, no, no. He can shower.
What am I thinking about?
- Let's wash up.
- Excuse me?
How's the water temperature?
They always ask you that at the salon
when they wash your hair.
Is it hot?
It's okay.
Sorry.
Hold on.
What? Hold on.
What is it? Are you uncomfortable?
No.
It's awkward.
What is?
Why are you being so good to me?
Am I being good to you?
Don't most husbands
do this for their wives?
I felt regretful.
I don't think I've done enough for you.
All done.
Now go to sleep.
What's wrong with me?
All my tests came back normal.
Wait, I'm not ready yet…
You weren't sleeping?
Go to sleep.
Will I…
be able to sleep?
That's it, everyone.
I concentrated as best as I could
to recall the details,
and it looked something like this.
Paradisers, please,
can I have your attention?
We're receiving reports from anyone
who has information about
this dragon ring.
Where did he go?
CALLS
PAIK SA-EON
Go to sleep. I'm waiting for a call.
Waiting for a call?
Who knew the day would come
when I'd be happy to get your call, 406?
Were you waiting for my call?
Why are you happy to get it?
I don't know.
Thanks to you,
I could find Hee-joo.
Aren't you curious as to how I knew
to tell you?
To tell the truth…
To tell the truth,
I know a lot about you, 406.
What do you know?
You're in your mid to late-twenties.
A woman.
How did you know?
Are you pretty?
Why does it matter if the person
threatening you is pretty or not?
I just have a feeling you might be.
Men.
Did you just laugh?
Yes, this is nice.
What's nice about it?
Talking to you
on the phone like this,
just like we always do,
makes it feel like nothing ever happened.
It's peaceful and nice.
It's peaceful?
Hong Hee-joo was on the brink of death.
What are you wearing right now?
I can't see you for myself,
so I want to imagine it.
Why would you imagine me, you lunatic?
From what I imagine,
you have a delicate frame
to match your voice
and a fiery personality to go with it.
Fiery? To go with what?
Wait, my body?
I won't go that far.
Well, anyway, it's fun just imagining it.
What are you doing right now?
Are you…
Are you flirting with me or something?
You're a married man!
Hee-joo…
is probably asleep by now.
You jerk.
It seems like you're not fully ready yet,
so let's try to get closer later.
I'd like to propose an offer.
An offer?
What offer?
Join me.
Let's catch the culprit together.
I know you're not in on it with him.
He's the one who pushed Hee-joo.
And you're the one
who told me where Hee-joo was.
After Hee-joo fell
from the mountain that day…
Hong Hee-joo!
While I desperately searched everywhere
looking for her…
Hong Hee-joo!
I made a resolution.
That I will…
make him feel the pain I felt, no,
the pain Hee-joo felt,
a hundred times over.
So starting now,
tell me everything you know about him.
Don't leave anything out.
- Hey.
- Wait, is this real?
Is this press release
really from the spokesperson?
Yeah, that's right.
Now, everyone, stand by!
- We're going live right away, okay?
- Okay.
What…
What's going on?
This is unbelievable.
Good grief. It's like a soap opera. Right?
I want to rip that rotten bastard's mouth!
I want to stab him
in the back with a knife.
Bastards who fool around
should be castrated with scissors!
People like him don't deserve
to be treated as humans.
How about that?
Is he about to get caught?
Goodness!
What did she do wrong?
They need to be taught a lesson.
- Honey!
- What are you…
doing right now?
You're a married man!
Hee-joo…
is probably asleep by now.
Honey!
Good grief!
Goodness.
Miss, this is mine.
Hello, viewers.
- What?
- We have breaking news
- that just came in.
- What is it?
I'm sure you have heard the news
about the fall accident that occurred
during the retreat
of the spokesperson's office.
The presidential office just issued
an official statement,
confirming that it was not an accident
but a criminal incident.
- Criminal?
- It's been revealed
that the victim
was Spokesperson Paik Sa-eon.
Spokesperson Paik revealed to the police
that he had been receiving threats
for two weeks, starting from June 1.
He also reported that he believes
the recent fall incident
was an attempt to cause him harm.
But the spokesperson drew a clear line,
stating that he does not view the incident
as a political attack against himself
or Paik Ui-yong,
the presidential candidate
of the Liberty and Justice Party,
and urged everyone to refrain
from unnecessary speculation.
But due to the ongoing death threats
and his concern for his personal safety,
he requested police protection,
an investigation,
and for the suspect's composite sketch
to be made public.
Cue the sketch.
Viewers, please take a careful look
at the screen we're showing you.
This is the composite sketch
of the suspect identified
in connection with the threats and bombing
targeting Spokesperson Paik.
406, starting now,
I want you to answer my questions.
The most important question.
Did you see his face?
I didn't see his face,
but he had a distinct feature.
The suspect is a man in his early
to mid-thirties, around 185 cm tall
with a solid build.
He is odd-eyed, and one eye
appears light brown in different lighting.
Good. Anything else?
There was a strange, fishy odor
coming from him,
and he stuttered when he got excited.
It seemed like he had
anger management issues.
The suspect has a stutter,
displays signs of anger management issues,
and appears to possess skills in threats,
hacking, homemade bomb-making, and arson.
I'll ask one last question.
- Yes.
- Why didn't you…
report this sooner?
I wanted to handle it quietly.
In the end, I failed to.
Do you have any suspect in mind?
Someone with a grudge, perhaps?
I don't know.
I'm sure about one thing.
Whoever it is, they know a lot about me.
Like what?
Where my personal office was
and even the schedule
of the company retreat.
They knew personal details
that only family would know.
I'm guessing that
someone is providing the information.
He said "Us."
- "Us"?
- Yeah.
Sis, I like you.
Because you have the same goal as us.
He can't stand being ignored,
gets agitated easily,
and can't control his anger.
Isn't it strange that someone like him
could carefully plan things
like hacking a car
and setting up a phone for threats?
Are you saying there's an accomplice?
Yes.
I'm sure there's one.
We need to catch him
along with the other guy.
DEPARTMENT OF PSYCHIATRY
DIRECTOR JI SANG-WOO
ODD-EYED WITH ONE EYE
APPEARING LIGHT BROWN
ODD-EYED
The suspect is a man in his early
to mid-thirties, around 185 cm tall
with a solid build.
He is odd-eyed, and one eye
appears light brown in different lighting.
FISHING SUPPLIES
Hey!
Is this what you meant by going off track?
You're trying to screw me over,
aren't you?
So you should've just stayed quiet.
If you hadn't tried to use the accident
for your own gain,
I wouldn't have had to go up
against what you said, would I?
How dare you talk back--
Enough!
Why didn't you tell us?
I wasn't the first person he attacked.
It was Hee-joo.
He knew she was my wife.
No one but family knows that.
So what?
Are you saying you suspected us?
What do we gain from threatening you?
Everyone in the family who knows
about your marriage wouldn't benefit
from the truth being exposed,
that includes us.
Besides that, why would you bring her
to work with you at the office?
I decided…
it was safest to keep Hee-joo
by my side, right in front of me.
I guess you really care about her.
Was that the only thing he knew?
The marriage?
For now.
I don't know how much he knows.
Our family has…
more than a few secrets.
Chairman Hong.
Do you think it's him?
That skeptical old man could
have decided to support another candidate.
Do you think he's plotting behind my back?
Speak of the devil. He's calling.
Want me to go ask?
If he's plotting something?
Spokesperson Paik
of the presidential office
revealed that the recent fall accident
during the company retreat
was a targeted crime against him.
And the police have launched
a public investigation.
Based on Paik's testimony,
the police created
and released a composite sketch
of the suspect.
Let's go live to our reporter
for more details.
You're the one who pushed her,
but my face is exposed.
Why did you try to kill Hong Hee-joo, huh?
Isn't our goal Paik Sa-eon?
The police have released
a composite sketch.
The suspect is a man in his early
to mid-thirties, around 185 cm tall
with a solid build.
He is odd-eyed, and one eye
appears light brown in different lighting.
Police said the suspect made
threatening calls to Spokesperson Paik.
HONG HEE-JOO DOESN'T SEEM TO
WANT TO GET DIVORCED.
So?
I WANTED PAIK SA-EON TO FEEL
WHAT IT'S LIKE TO LOSE
SOMETHING PRECIOUS TOO.
But Hong Hee-joo didn't die.
What now?
We're about to get screwed.
No, I mean just me!
FIRST, GET THE PHONE BACK.
Why didn't you tell me?
How could you not consult with me?
At first,
I suspected you too.
What? Why would I do something like that?
I couldn't be controlled,
and you disapproved.
Strangling me wouldn't be off the table
if it meant you could control me.
If you know so much,
why did you act like an amateur today?
Why would someone as skilled at media play
as you step into the spotlight?
This issue concerns
both of our families anyway,
so you had either me
or your father to hide behind.
You should rest.
I'll get going.
No.
You wouldn't act like
an amateur overnight.
The most common
yet the most reliable method.
Cover an issue with another issue.
You've got the world's attention
focused on you.
What are you hiding behind you?
PAIK SA-EON CASE,
POLICE INVESTIGATION NOW A PUBLIC INQUIRY
EVERYONE'S GOT DIRT ON THEM.
HIS IMAGE IS RUINED!
WHAT WAS HE BLACKMAILED FOR?
WHY'S THE ARTICLE UNFINISHED?
CALLS
PAIK SA-EON
UNKNOWN CALLER
Sis, did you see the news?
Was it you?
Did you tell him what I looked like?
But it wasn't me.
I didn't push you.
Liar.
You probably don't believe me.
Since you backed out,
you should return my phone.
I'm on my way. Open the door.
Hong Hee-joo!
Hee-joo!
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Are you okay?
HBC JANG HYEOK-JIN
What is it?
Are you okay?
The voice phishing call
you asked about before,
is that him too?
- Yeah.
- Hey!
You should've told me sooner.
I know you're nuts,
but this is the first time
I've seen you act this crazy since then.
"Since then"?
In the conflict zone,
bullets were pouring,
and you ran with a mic and camera.
Sa-eon, stop being so reckless. Okay?
If I stop,
there won't be a place to hide.
What?
There's nowhere to hide
except behind me.
How are you feeling?
I'm okay.
What happened earlier?
Did someone come?
You look tired.
Yeah, I am.
So go to sleep now.
So I can sleep too.
Are you not scared?
Why? Are you scared?
Do you want the light on?
Everyone's talking about you,
and they're gossiping about you.
Aren't you scared?
What about you?
Are you scared?
I'm…
not scared.
And I don't regret it.
So you just…
have good dreams.
CALLS
PAIK SA-EON
Hello?
I saw the news.
But…
I'm curious about something.
What is it?
When are you going to catch me?
I ended up helping him, after all.
Whether it's punishment
or an investigation, it has to be done.
Also, when will you take this phone?
It's important evidence.
Don't you need it?
If I need it,
will you give it to me?
I guess so,
to catch him.
How will you give it to me?
Will you…
show yourself to me?
Yeah.
Let's meet.
I'll come to you now.
With this phone.
What expression will you make
when you see me?
I was torn because it might
torture you even more, but…
But that was an excuse.
I was scared, and it was just an excuse
to avoid the moment
I'd have to face you as 406.
However,
I won't run away anymore.
I won't let you struggle alone any longer.
Where…
are you right now?
I have a place where I want to meet you.
Come there.
Are you here?
Yeah.
Why here, though?
Have you been here before?
On the day this park first opened…
After that, the word "amusement park"
became forbidden in our house.
Come to the carousel.
Let's meet there.
Would you like to enter?
In-a, there are so many horses.
Look there!
I don't see you.
Where are you?
I'm by the ice cream stand.
Are you coming?
I'm waiting for you.
What do you see in front of you?
In front of me?
I came up.
But there's no one here.
Just wait.
What are you doing?
I'm getting you to relax.
I've been waiting for the moment
to meet you too.
I don't want to see you looking all stiff.
Don't get your hopes up.
You'll probably wish
you never saw me at all.
I guess you're not confident.
Are you confident
you won't be surprised to see me?
I don't think so.
You'll be shocked…
and disappointed.
So you might
end up feeling lonely.
Are you
worried about me right now?
No.
I'm worried about myself.
I'm worried about seeing…
you like that.
I swear,
you don't listen.
I'm sure I told you.
Underestimating yourself is a bad habit.
How should I…
fix that for you, Hong Hee-joo?
Thank you…
for all your hard work, 406.
You…
knew everything?
Since when? No…
If you knew, why didn't you…
Why didn't I what?
Why didn't you hate me?
Tell me…
Hong Hee-joo.
Tell me how to hate you.
Tell me how to not love you.
WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
It's just hard to believe.
Us being completely ordinary
just like everyone else.
Could you do the same
when you know everything about me?
I'm going to take it all.
What grudge does he have against you?
What are you doing?
Do you already know who the culprit is?
What bothers me isn't the case, it's you.
Don't hide anything from me.
Show me everything.
This kind of happiness
would never happen to me.
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce