Subtitle Provide by Kisskh.Asia Translator [ Admin Qari ]
Where are you guys heading to, anyway?
We’re heading south.
Kinda hoped it was going to be a romantic road trip date.
Just do it.
Just knock me out and leave.
I can’t do that.
I love you, Bison.
With all my being.
You’re not fooling me again, are you?
As long as I’m alive,
I’ll make you kiss me again.
I think I know now where Bison is.
You like The Beatles?
My father did.
He had a big collection of them.
You know,
when we used to come here,
my dad loved playing frisbee.
He would throw it in the ocean,
and made me fetch it.
I felt like a puppy.
You really are like a puppy.
My parents loved traveling.
I went abroad with them a lot when I was a kid.
When the plane went down,
we were on our way back from Europe.
Babe was very young at the time,
so we didn’t take him with us.
I honestly can’t say
that I was lucky to have survived.
God must have wanted you to live.
For Babe.
For you, too.
You know
what’s another thing
that I really miss?
What?
My childhood.
I remember, after my parents died,
I was so depressed and lonely.
It stayed that way for a long time.
I barely got to go out and play like the other children.
It’s fine now, isn’t it?
I was like that, too.
I forced myself to be mature
just to take care of Babe.
You know, I’m only 29,
but I keep being told I dress like I’m in my 40’s.
Do I look old?
Not at all.
It’s pretty cool.
What’s wrong with being 40 anyway?
Kinda hot, really.
You can be my daddy.
Okay, then, baby.
We have a lot in common, don’t we?
I guess we’re just perfect for each other.
Can’t argue with that.
Oh, hey.
If the cops want to reopen your cases,
what are you gonna do?
I don’t know.
All I know is I gotta have everything in order.
If I ever get go to jail one day,
I want Babe to be able to take care of himself.
Why don’t we just get locked up together?
I don’t want to go anywhere without you anymore.
You’re my home, Kant.
Hey.
Alright.
You’re home now.
Oh?
Ow, come on!
Does he have any CDs?
We–Well?
How do I drive?
You seem to sleep pretty well.
Are we there yet?
Almost.
I’m keeping up the speed.
Are you sure they’re there, though?
Yes.
Bison told me his parents had a house on an island.
That was before they got murdered.
If you’re sure, then alright.
I just hope Kant is still alive.
I can’t guarantee that.
You’ll have to find out for yourself.
Oh, jerk.
Can’t you at least lie to make me feel better?
Hey.
Can I ask you something?
Can we get me some new clothes?
I’ve been wearing yours this whole time,
and it’s getting disgusting.
We can just stop by around here somewhere.
You sure make a lot of requests.
You think we’re on a road trip or something?
No.
We are not stopping anywhere.
Oh, come on.
If you’re gonna kill me,
can I at least die in something that’s actually my style?
I want my corpse to look good.
Gotta look presentable on the news.
“Gorgeous man with clear skin found dead in a crop top.”
My dad will recognize me right away.
Whoa.
These look pretty good.
Oh, this is nice.
Hey, what do you think of this?
Think I can match it with something.
Hurry up and grab what you want.
We need to keep going.
I hardly feel like a hostage right now.
I feel like a boyfriend.
This feels like going shopping with my boyfriend.
Listen to me.
You are not a hostage.
And I’m not using you as leverage for anything.
You don’t matter enough for that.
I’m just letting you find a little joy before I kill you.
Well…
Can I ask for one more thing?
You think I’m a wish granter or something?
You’re going to die soon,
what else do you want?
When you dispose of my body,
can you choose somewhere nice?
The beach or the mountain, for example.
At least my ghost will haunt beautiful places,
like the ocean or the mountain.
I don’t want my ghost to haunt some dumpster.
If you don’t choose something right now,
the only place you’re haunting is this damn secondhand store.
Well?
How about this?
What a beauty.
I’m going with this one.
I’m gonna try it on.
Well?
What do you think?
Now this is more like me.
I never saw you in stripes before.
Oh?
Been observing me, haven’t you?
You can’t kill me.
You love me.
Style, duck!
Who the hell is that?
How would I know?
Is he here to kill you or me?
Should I go and ask him?
Go, go.
Go, go, go!
I’m out of bullets.
Shit, that’s in the car.
This is all because of you.
I forgot everything.
Why are you blaming me?
How should we fight him?
I’ll run over there.
I’ll distract him.
Are you out of your mind?
How the hell will you outrun bullets?
Trust me.
I’m fast.
Style.
Style, Style!
Shit.
Who the hell are you?
Who sent you?
Style?
Style!
Crap!
Style.
I’m alright.
It’s just a graze.
Shut your trap.
Look at how much you’re bleeding.
This is nothing.
Keep putting pressure on it.
This is gonna hurt a little.
Put pressure on it.
Crap…
Flip it before you burn it.
I am flipping.
It just won’t flip.
Let me help.
That’s it.
I told you I’d do it.
You nearly burned our food, you see?
But I just wanted to help.
Just do it yourself next time, then.
You’re stubborn, huh?
I’ll just root for you quietly, then.
Hey.
I’m handling hot oil, for God’s sake.
If we burn this, we don’t get to eat, you know?
Hey, stop it.
Young master.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t mean to interrupt.
It’s quite alright, Mr. Maew.
Is something the matter?
Someone just landed on our shore, sir.
You okay?
Why don’t you get in the house and lock the door?
I’ll be right back.
No.
I’m going with you.
It’s too dangerous.
That’s exactly why I won’t let you do it alone.
Okay.
That’s Style.
Fadel!
Style!
What’s going on?
What happened to you?
Why are you bleeding so much?
Kant…
You’re alive.
I’m happy to see that.
You’re the one who’s barely alive, dude!
How did you get here?
Save your questions.
Help him first.
I’ll help.
Stay back!
Let go.
You alright?
Just put your weight on me.
Get him up here.
Bison, help me.
Gentle.
Careful.
Hey, what are you doing?
You’re not a doctor.
If I don’t do something,
he’s dead.
Have you done this before?
I stitched Fadel up before.
Hold on.
This is going to hurt a little.
But Bison’s here to help you.
If you’re not doing anything, just leave.
I got this.
Kant.
Grab some clean cloth for me.
I’m taking the bandage off.
Crap.
Alright.
Hold on.
You got it?
Hang on, alright?
Bite on this.
Hold my hand.
Hold it.
It’ll sting a little.
That hurts!
Fadel.
Style’s taken care of.
He’s out cold right now, though.
Good thing it was just a graze.
He’ll be fine.
He’ll be up in no time.
You never listen to me at all, do you?
How could you just run away like that?
I’m sorry.
I was enraged.
Really wanted him dead at the time.
Dead, my ass.
Am I looking at a damn ghost, then?
It’s not easy for me.
You know I love him.
And he told me everything.
He only did it because he was promised a clean slate.
He’s on our side now.
And you’re stupid enough to believe him.
Fine.
I’ll kill him myself.
No one will find out who dies on this remote island anyway.
Go on!
Go ahead.
Do it.
Why don’t you just kill Style as well?
He fooled you, didn’t he?
Do it for me
since I don’t have the guts to do it.
Don’t try me.
I’m not.
I just know you can’t do it.
The way you were holding his hands,
and the look in your eyes as you stared at him.
I’ve never seen you worry about someone like that before.
If you can do it, go on.
Be my guest.
He’s just over there.
Can we forget about those two for now?
Just tell me
who followed us here.
Probably one of Ruerat’s hires.
We messed up our last mission.
They’re probably after us as payback.
For real?
Should we tell Mother?
I don’t think so.
I got this.
But we gotta make sure it’s them.
Okay.
How’s your wound?
Now that you mention it, it still hurts.
Want another stab wound?
Careful when you get up.
The stitches are still fresh.
It was amazing I didn’t die from shock on that table.
Take some painkillers.
Bison told me to give them to you.
Thanks.
I honestly thought I’d come here to see your dead body.
Almost.
I told him the whole truth.
So he knows everything?
Then how are you still alive?
He loves me.
The power of love, alright.
I love him, too.
I’ll do anything to keep him alive.
And how are you going to do that?
This mess is getting out of hand.
It’s not just the cops who are after them,
but someone else clearly wants them dead.
I don’t know,
but my heart is already in this.
So you’re safe now, huh?
Meanwhile, my chances are 50-50.
He’s hot and then cold.
He loves me and then he doesn’t.
I honestly can’t keep up with him.
You think?
But from what I saw,
he had your hands clasped in his so tightly.
And the way he looked at you
was exactly how I looked at Bison at the hospital.
Thanks, though,
for risking your life looking for me.
I don’t need your gratitude.
I’m here mostly because Fadel dragged my ass here.
Fine, fine.
You can’t just say you love me like a normal person, huh?
I love you soooo—
Ow! It still hurts!
My bad, dude.
Hey.
When he had my hand in his,
how did he look at me?
Let me show you.
He clasped your hands like this,
and looked at you with worries…
Then he said, “Hold on, Style.”
“I won’t lose you.”
He did?
He moved in closer…
Eww!
Gives me the creeps.
Yeah, that was it.
He was clearly worried about you.
What are we making today?
Oh, hey.
I’m blanching some vegetables.
What’s the matter?
The hell did you do that for?
Fadel!
Fadel, stop it.
Stop!
You brought all this on us!
Fadel!
I’ve talked things out with him!
But I don’t!
Fadel.
No.
Fadel!
You’re turning a gun on your own brother for him?
But it’s my life.
You don’t get to decide for me.
Fadel!
Don’t hurt Kant!
He’s sorry for what he did.
It’s okay.
Fadel’s right.
I brought all this on us.
If this is how it ends,
let it end with me.
If you’re going to kill me,
go right ahead.
But Style has nothing to do with this.
I lied to get him roped into this.
Don’t you dare take all the credits.
If you’re going to kill him,
kill me, too.
Nobody forced me into this.
I agreed to it willingly.
Don’t you have a little sympathy?
We’ve been through all these things together.
Why did you bother stitching me up
if you’re going to end up killing me anyway?
Why didn’t you just let me die?
I’m happy to have called you a friend.
Thank you
for making my life such an adventure.
It’s been so goddamn fun, you know that?
How can we be sure you’re not just fooling us again?
You think I’d risk my life for all this
if I didn’t really have feelings for you?
People make mistakes.
Won’t you give me a chance?
I really love your brother,
and my friend really loves you.
The two of us will do anything
to make sure the two of you get the life you want.
You alright?
Are you?
I’m fine.
Are you hurt?
Any of you allergic to seafood?
Let me help.
You’re a hitman, a doctor,
and a househusband all in one, huh?
I’m literally just hanging up laundry.
This is for Fadel and Style in the guest bedroom.
Will your brother agree to that?
I don’t know.
I gotta admit he’s got his ego.
Can’t blame him, though.
His trust was betrayed.
It’s gonna take a little time to heal.
Well…
How is the trust
between you and me?
You gotta admit
the cut was deep.
It’s going to be difficult to completely heal.
I’m still arguing with myself
if I made the right decision.
You did.
I won’t let you down again.
Okay, then.
Our trust is alright now.
But those two…
What should we do?
I have a plan.
I know you have been through something painful
and you lost your parents at such a young age.
But don’t worry.
You’re going to have a new family,
and we’re going to build it ourselves.
I… will be your everything.
Call me Mother.
Mother.
Why do we have to learn how to use a gun?
The world is full of people who want to hurt us.
I want you to know how to defend yourselves.
It’s a skill.
You will get to use it one day.
This is the guy
you want us to kill?
Yes.
He’s a bad person.
He needs to be eliminated.
He kills people and abuses women.
He leaves behind widows and orphans everywhere he goes.
Why not let the law or the police deal with him?
Oh, Bison.
You’re naive, baby.
We can’t trust the law.
I have to deal with this myself.
But I can’t do it alone.
I need all of you.
Remember.
The world is made up of good people
and bad people.
Our job
is to kill the bad guys.
Come in.
Where are we on that matter I asked you to take care of?
I…
What is it?
Stop mumbling and just tell me.
I messed up.
Of course you did!
I knew it.
This is why I never trusted you to take care of these things.
I knew I was only going to be disappointed.
Now that you’ve alerted them,
I bet they’re out of reach now.
They have been dying to quit this job.
No.
I…
I think they still want to get even with Ruerat.
They will come back.
You’re right.
We should hire someone else to do this.
They will take care of it.
Yes.
Hire someone.
Maybe the one we hired two years ago.
As for you,
get back to the job you’re more well equipped for.
Don’t try to do something you’re no good at.
Now go.
Hey, Dad.
I’m at the beach with some friends.
Yeah, I’ll be back soon.
Don’t worry.
My phone’s dead.
I’m calling from my friend’s number.
Right.
Eat properly, you.
See you.
Thanks, Bison.
I didn’t want my dad to worry.
No problem.
But wouldn’t he be mad
if you showed up at home like this?
It’s alright.
Don’t worry.
I’ll just come up with some badass stories.
Maybe some superhero stories, even.
I promise not to let loose on you and Fadel.
I didn’t mean that.
I know you’re good at making up stories.
Kinda sounds like an insult.
It’s not.
Oh.
Yeah?
Fadel wants to talk to you.
About what?
I don’t know.
He just said you should meet him at the beach.
Crap.
Maybe he changes his mind
and wants me on my knees
with a gun to my head
before shooting me dead into the ocean.
What?
No way.
The worst he’d do would be trying to drown you.
Kidding.
He won’t do that.
I bet your brother would actually do that.
Can I ask you something?
Do you really like Fadel?
Whatever Kant feels about you,
that’s how I feel about your brother.
If you understand him,
you should be able to understand me.
If you really like him,
you need to prove it to him.
He acts all tough and rough on the outside,
but on the inside, he’s just a softie.
Really!
He never hesitates when he kills.
So if you’re still alive,
that means he’s got a soft spot for you.
You think…
I have a chance?
Go for it.
After all you’ve risked your life for,
what else do you even have to be scared of now?
Am I right?
What the hell are you doing here?
Bison asked me to give you the toiletry bag.
Put it there.
What?
Thank you for giving me a chance.
I won’t let you down.
I don’t need your promises.
If you don’t live up to what you said,
I’ll just kill you.
Okay.
Don’t take it out on Style.
I asked him to take you out in exchange for my car.
What did you just say?
Take me out?
For your car?
Yeah.
I gotta dangle some reward to lure him in.
But you know,
he’s long forgotten about my car.
I think he loves you.
I don’t need to know what you think.
Well, I don’t know.
He and I have been friends for a long time.
He’s got a lot to look forward to in life.
If he’s not serious about you,
he wouldn't have left any of that to be here with you.
Also…
Bison said he needs to talk to you.
He’s waiting at the beach.
Why isn’t he here, then?
Why did he send you?
I don’t know.
Maybe it’s about something he doesn’t want me to know.
Bye.
What are you doing here?
Where’s Bison?
Why would Bison be here?
He told me you had something to talk to me about.
Hey.
Don’t go.
I’m here, so talk to me.
What the hell?
I can’t sleep unless I talk to you.
Say what you want.
Here.
Take it.
What is it?
A list of all my relatives.
I want you to be sure that I’m not lying to you again.
If I ever do that,
you can kill me and my entire extended family.
Are you insane?
You’re selling your whole family out for this?
And you said you’re a family man.
Because I know for a fact
that I won’t ever lie to you again.
Words are cheap.
I’m only worth as much as one car to you.
From what you did to me,
I just hope that car’s a real beauty.
Did… Did Kant tell you that?
Yeah.
Your best friend sold you out.
How are you gonna defend yourself now?
Well…
That was in the past.
I admit I started off with the wrong intention.
But after spending time with you,
I’ve changed.
I never let anyone get the better of me.
But for you, I’d do it again and again.
I think we get along well.
The only thing I can do right now
is promise you that I’ll be by your side.
But if you give me a chance,
I can show you I mean every word.
You don’t believe me?
Fine.
A guy like me
is a man of my word.
What are you doing?
Style!
What the hell are you doing?
I’m going to keep walking until you give me a chance.
You’re only going to get an infection!
And I will die of that, too!
Style!
I’m gone.
Bye-bye.
Oh, it’s pretty deep around here.
No, wait, I just stepped on some seashells!
Ow!
Fine!
I’ll give you a chance.
You will?
Nah, I’m gone.
There’s no way you mean it.
Style!
What the hell are you doing?
What are you doing?
I promise you that, from now on,
you’ll only see the 100% real me.
Besides work,
I’ve been real to you from day one.
If you don’t stay true to me after this,
you’ll find out how I deal with liars.
Now come on
before you infect your wound.
Even when you’re threatening me,
you’re worried about me.
How adorable.
I can be worse.
You want that?
No.
From now on, I just want to see you being lovey-dovey.
How so?
Well…
In a situation like this,
if we weren’t fighting,
what would you like to do to me?
They’re cute, aren’t they?
Took them long enough.
I always knew Fadel needed to find someone stubborn like that.
I did my part, didn’t I?
I tried so hard he punched me square in the face.
Oh, poor you.
Hey.
Won’t you just let Ruerat go?
It will only add fuel to the flames.
Someone is hunting you guys down.
If you kill him,
he will just come back and kill you.
He destroyed my family.
But it will just keep going in a loop.
All you’ll get is satisfaction.
That’s exactly what I want.
I’ve lived my whole life with this grudge.
Now that I have it within my grasp,
you want me to let it pass me by?
I told you
this would be the last mission.
It won’t be.
If you do it now, you’ll do it again.
I understand how you feel.
I’m just worried about you.
You see?
I told you hitmen aren’t made for love.
You’re giving me false hopes.
I’m not.
The future we picture together is more than possible.
Then tell me what this future looks like.
We’d be living on an island.
I’d have a tattoo parlor.
When we have a lot of customers,
you have to take care of them.
Sounds boring.
I want to do something else.
What do you want to do, then?
Designing?
Do you want to be a doctor?
You seemed pretty adept when you stitched my buddy up.
Sounds interesting.
Anything is possible
as long as we’re together.
Careful.
Sorry.
Be gentle.
Don’t do something like this again.
But I gotta pull some dramatic stunt for someone like you.
Hey.
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
There’s a photo of a man in the glove compartment of your car.
Who is he?
I’m sorry for prying.
If you don’t want to tell me, I understand.
He’s my ex.
How long were you together?
Two-ish years, I guess.
Why did you break up?
He and I were going to start a life together.
Hey.
I’ve asked Mother about quitting my job
and moving to the South with you.
Well, did she give you the greenlight?
Of course.
I’ve worked for her for a long time.
She’s fine with it.
She told me she wanted me to find love
and live a normal life.
What exactly do you do for a living?
You never told me.
What kind of work doesn’t allow you to find love
or live a normal life?
You don’t have to think about that right now.
Let’s focus on our future.
Do you dance?
Not very well.
I’ll teach you.
Don’t step on my foot.
Sorry.
But one day, he’s just gone.
Like he’s completely disappeared.
He probably just didn’t want to confront me,
so he just disappeared.
Couldn’t he at least tell me straight up
if he didn’t want to be with me anymore?
Ghosting me was just nasty.
Maybe he was scared of me,
thinking I’d kill him if he broke up with me.
I’m not scared of you anymore
ever since you saved that woman’s life at the bowling alley.
You risked your life for a total stranger.
I know I’m in love with the right man.
Hey.
You alright?
What’s on your mind?
It’s nothing.
I’m just thinking about work.
You should leave work behind
when you’re with me.
You told me you’d quit your job and be with me.
Wait a little longer.
Wait until everything’s settled down.
We won’t have to sneak about to see each other again.
Don’t make me wait so long.
Dad!
Mom!
Help me!
Dad!
Mom!
Are you still scared?
I keep getting flashbacks to that day.
I understand.
It left a gaping hole in your heart,
of course it’s going to be hard to forget.
You don’t have anything you’re scared of?
Of course I do.
I used to be so scared of the sound of gunshots.
But I got over it with… pure grudge.
I want to avenge my family
so I learned how to use a gun.
“Pew, pew, pew!”
And I got over it.
That’s a gunshot?
“Pew, pew”?
That’s how it sounds when the shooter’s cute.
Okay.
You’re telling me I need a reason to get over it, then?
I guess so.
I want you to be the reason.
How would that work?
I know how much you love the ocean.
If I want to be with you,
I have to overcome this fear.
Alright, then.
It shouldn’t be too scary when…
Here.
Just a little further.
I won’t let you go.
Let’s keep going.
I think this is far enough.
Baby steps, huh?
One day,
I’ll be swimming with you in the middle of the ocean.
You don’t have to spoil me so much, you know?
Both in bed and about traveling,
if you spoil me so much,
it gets boring, you know?
You gotta oppose me sometimes.
Don’t take it back.
I’m definitely taking your word for it.
Go for it.
You’re in my turf.
Okay!
Hey!
Stop.
Hey.
You’re going to turn saltwater into syrup at this rate.
Wanna play frisbee?
I’m not playing.
I ain’t a kid.
Being a kid every once in a while is fun, you know?
Come on.
What do you say?
We’re in.
Okay.
Get ready, then.
Back when I was a kid,
I used to love just sitting here with my parents.
I never thought I’d get to do that with my boyfriend one day.
It’d be a shame to leave.
Why not just stay?
Just become an islander.
Don’t be ridiculous.
We still have a job to finish.
Do you think we’d get to come back here again?
Of course.
Once we wrap up the last mission,
we can go anywhere and do anything.
Not sure if they’d come with us, though.
Just tell me where, and I'll go with you.
My engine’s hot and ready.
Style, you fearless jerk.
This is probably the first time I’ve seen my brother-in-law laugh.
Brother-in-law?
Bold.
Hello, brother-in-law.
Let’s not get in touch for a while
for everyone’s safety.
In the end, we can only wait for them to come back to us.
Didn’t you say we should stay away for a while?
I got worried about you.
You need to let me help with your last mission.
I’ll help you start over with me.
You have me watching your back.
Don’t worry.
You and I will be alright.