=Eight Hundred=
=Episode 15=
(Report Letter)
(Yingxiong Internet Cafe)
Han Ning,
pass me my dialysis bag.
Hold on,
here's a letter for you.
(To: Gao Songge)
(Want to make some extra cash?)
(Fengyang Police Station, Jiangbin Municipal PSB)
(Just do as I say.)
(Don't let anyone see the bottles.)
(Bring the empty ones)
(back to me next time.)
(If you break the rules,)
(you're out for good.)
Who delivered this?
The post office
dropped it off this morning.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Songge, are you packed?
Let's go.
I can go by myself.
The cafe will get busy soon,
and we can't
leave Han Ning to run it all alone.
(Confirm)
You get back to work.
I'll just take a cab over.
Be careful then.
I'm off.
(Yingxiong Web Cafe)
Hui.
Did you get your family stuff sorted?
When do we start?
Soon.
I contacted my downline.
Don't lie to me.
Or I might get a might ruthless.
Tomorrow,
you'll get a final answer.
Even if we keep doing this,
you need to give me time
to come up with a plan.
Don't play games with me.
We've been looking all over for you.
And here you are, chilling.
Qiang. Long.
Have a seat.
You should know
why we're here.
What did I do?
Playing dumb, huh?
Let me jog your memory.
Last Friday.
Jinxiu Club.
Think about it.
Excuse me, sir.
Another customer
asked me to pass this along to you.
He also asked me to say,
"Have a safe trip."
Alright, thank you.
(126 Fanyu Road)
Hello?
Hey, Hai.
Did you receive
my parting gift?
How did you find out
about this address?
Of course I know.
What are you doing? What's going on?
You know exactly
what you've done.
126 Fanyu Road.
It looks like a club,
but you know exactly
what's hiding in there.
If you haven't left the city
by tomorrow morning,
the police will seize the stash
at your warehouse.
And when that happens,
you really will lose everything.
Are you threatening me?
Right back at you,
Hai.
By the way,
that bottle of liquor is expensive.
I couldn't even
bring myself to drink it.
So, enjoy it for me.
(Want to make some extra cash?
Just do as I say.)
Hello, Jiangbin City Paging Station.
Operator 18 at your service.
What number will it be?
Page 3546987.
Call this number back.
Understood.
Please hold.
Who is this?
My husband told me to contact you.
He has a message for you.
What is it?
That day at Fengyang Police Station,
he recognized you.
He wants you to have
100,000 yuan ready for me.
Otherwise,
he'll rat you out in the prison.
Are you going to pay up?
You lost me there.
Scar-face,
you can stop pretending.
If you don't agree to this,
you and your boyfriend
can both wait to get locked up.
Give me some time to get it ready.
Hongbing and me
can't be with Hui forever.
If Hui is left all alone
to carry such a heavy burden,
when the time comes,
how could Hongbing and me rest in peace?
I owe your whole family.
I won't let Chen Hui get hurt.
Even if it kills me.
What is it? What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Chen Hui.
Do you think there's such a thing
as karmic justice?
Why do you ask?
I've been thinking a lot lately.
Do you think karma
is finally catching up with us?
If there really was karma,
why'd you get so sick
at such a young age?
Maybe
this is just my fate.
Maybe that's part of karma too.
What's wrong with you?
You are acting strange.
It's nothing.
I just wonder sometimes.
What if we're just
not meant to beat fate?
I think you're overthinking it.
Look at our lives.
Aren't things slowly getting better?
There's no problem we can't solve.
But what if
the things we did in the past
come back to haunt us?
What would you do?
We worked so hard to get what we have.
I won't let anyone take it away.
Hello?
I have the money ready.
Can you hear me?
Today at 2:00 PM.
On the bridge
west of the Litou Village railway.
Hello?
Hai, our warehouse was
raided by the police!
The funds in our accounts are frozen!
Mao and the others were arrested!
What?
I barely managed to escape.
What do we do now, Hai?
Darn you, Hui!
Mail this out for me.
Hello, sir. What was that?
Send it out for me!
Right away, sir.
Who is it?
Chen Hui, you set me up!
Didn't you?
What do you mean?
My warehouse in Jin'gang
got raided by the cops today.
Don't play dumb!
You were careless.
It's not my fault.
You threatened to report me yesterday,
and today my warehouse is gone.
Let me tell you,
if I get caught, you're going down too.
That's why I told you to run!
My dad has seen you.
If you don't run now,
you won't get another chance.
Where can I go?
I can't go back to Jin'gang,
and I can't stay here.
You're forcing my hand, Chen Hui.
I'm forcing your hand?
You forced me to keep selling.
You even threatened me at my house!
If I hadn't helped that night,
you'd be locked up already.
You deserved
to get raided!
It really was you two.
Officer Liu.
What about us?
The ones
selling cough syrup in Fengyang
were you and Hui.
Who told you that, Officer Liu?
Director Chen has
suspected you all along.
And I kept hoping
that he was wrong.
What are you talking about, Officer Liu?
If there's nothing else,
I'll be going now.
Give it back!
Carrying cash isn't
against the law, right?
I'm not a cop anymore.
I just wanted to confirm something.
If there's nothing else,
I really have to go.
Songge!
You still have a chance, Songge.
Come with me and turn yourself in.
- Let go of me, Officer Liu!
- Songge!
Songge!
Let go!
Let me take you to the hospital.
It's no use.
My time...
is almost up.
I just wanted to help Director Chen
before I'm gone.
I want to help you too.
You couldn't stay put in Jin'gang.
You just had to push me!
You had it coming!
Alright then.
I'm taking you down with me!
My money is gone.
I can't go home either.
You won't let me live?
Then none of us gets to live!
Even if you kill me,
that report letter will still be sent.
I never wanted to kill anyone.
It was you guys.
It was you!
You just kept pushing me!
You pushed me again and again!
You won't let me live,
and you won't let Songge live!
Hai?
Songge.
Whether you admit it or not,
the police are already
investigating this case.
You still have a choice right now.
Turn yourself in.
Songge,
have you thought
about Chen Hui's father?
In your life,
are Chen Hui's parents
important to you?
Of course.
They are like my own parents.
You should know
that here in Fengyang,
Chen Hui's grandfather
was a hero admired by everyone.
Since he was young,
Chen Hui's father has been
the most honorable man
in this 800-meter radius area.
The only thing
he ever wanted to do in life
was to protect the peace here.
Everything you and Hui have done
is destroying his faith.
That is far crueler
than taking his life.
If it were up to Director Chen,
he would rather die with honor
than see you two
break the law.
Songge.
Turn yourself in.
There's still time.
Officer Liu.
I did everything
all by myself.
Chen Hui was never part of this.
I am the scarred woman
you've been looking for.
I went behind Chen Hui's back,
and his parents' too,
to sell cough syrup in Fengyang.
I just wanted
to make some extra money.
I wanted
to live a little longer.
All the blame
falls on me alone.
Arrest me
if you must.
Songge.
Wanting to live is never wrong.
But your methods were wrong.
And what you did was wrong.
If I could,
I would trade my own life
so that Chen Hui's family
could live a good life.
You're wrong.
Only by staying alive
can you pay back the debts
you owe in this life.
That is the only way
your family can live happily together.
Songge.
This is your only chance.
Listen to me.
Turn yourself in.
Even from another world,
I will be wishing you all well.
I'm going to
call Director Chen right now.
You can tell him yourself.
Okay?
(Cautious)
Hello?
Chief Liu.
Someone...
- Chief Liu?
- Someone...
Someone...
wants to personally
tell you something.
Who? Who is it?
Tell me what?
Chief Liu?
I'm listening, go ahead.
Hello?
Hello? Chief Liu?
Say something!
Promise...
Promise me...
(Incoming Call: Chen Hongbing)
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
(People's Public Security)
Alright, everyone settle down.
This is
Guo Lei, the new Criminal Chief
from the municipal PSB.
Starting today,
he will be taking over Liu Na's duties.
Let's welcome him.
Welcome.
Hello everyone, I'm Guo Lei.
Let's keep this brief.
We just received word.
(Suspect Profile: Tian Jinhai)
Tian Jinhai isn't a foreigner.
He's a Jin'gang local.
He partnered with a friend abroad
to run a pharmaceutical company.
Their main business operation
is this Peidun Cough Syrup.
We've exchanged information
with the Jin'gang police.
A week ago,
Tian Jinhai's partner
was arrested overseas.
Tian Jinhai's inventory in Jin'gang
has also been seized.
Chief Guo, here's the thing.
A few days ago, Tian Jinhai
made a trip to
the home of Director Chen
of the Fengyang Police Station.
At first, we figured he'd be
hiding around here.
Correct.
However, Tian Jinhai might've
already gotten wind of it.
So our mission now
is to work fast
and inspect every hotel.
We must find Tian Jinhai.
Is that clear?
Understood!
Let's move out.
Yes, sir.
Chief Guo.
Thanks for that.
I have a meeting to catch.
Alright.
You must be Kang Limin.
Yes, Chief Guo.
I am Kang Limin.
I heard Chen Hongbing
is your Master.
Yes, he is.
We'd like to ask
Director Chen for a favor.
Since Tian Jinhai
visited his home,
if we manage to catch Tian Jinhai,
we'd like him to identify him for us.
Chief Guo, since you just got here,
you might not know.
My Master's family...
I know.
That's why I need him
to come here,
but don't disclose any details.
Once we catch the guy,
have him ID the suspect.
Alright.
Chief Guo.
I'll find him.
Hello, Mr. Tian.
This is the hotel front desk.
The letter you wanted to send
was dropped off too late.
It didn't go out.
We'll send it out first thing
tomorrow morning.
Yeah.
Alright, I won't disturb you any further.
Goodbye.
- Limin.
- Master.
Something's come up.
I need you to come by tomorrow.
What is it?
I can't talk about it
until you get here.
What is it this time?
Why so mysterious?
By the way, Limin,
there's something else.
Have you seen Chief Liu?
No, I haven't.
What's wrong, Master?
Here's the thing.
She called me just now.
Someone on the phone
wanted to tell me something.
And then,
there was nothing.
When I called back,
no one answered.
You should go look for her.
See if she needs help.
Alright.
Don't worry, Master.
I'll have the guys look into it.
You should come to the city first.
Okay. I'm on my way.
Hello? Songge?
Chen Hui.
Something happened.
Take it easy. Where are you?
I'm at the railway bridge.
I'll be right there.
(Cautious)
Songge?
I'm here.
Officer Liu is gone.
She's gone.
Still haven't reached Chief Liu?
Not yet.
We've been calling her,
but she won't answer.
We went to her place last night,
and no one was home.
That's weird.
Master.
I hate to say this,
but we should prepare for the worst.
I mean it.
What do you mean?
Chief Liu hasn't been doing well lately.
So I was thinking,
maybe she just wanted
to be alone and, you know...
Stop being ridiculous.
Songge.
I'm here.
It's going to be okay.
Pull yourself together.
Act like everything is normal.
Understand?
I understand.
I have to go to the hotel
and get that letter back.
Chen Hui.
Be careful.
I'll be here waiting.
Master.
Chief Guo, this is Director Chen
from the Fengyang Police Station.
- Hello, Director Chen.
- Hello.
I'm Guo Lei, from the municipal PSB.
I've heard a lot about you.
We're all on the same team.
No need for formalities.
Chief Guo.
Hold on, let's talk outside.
Director Chen, please wait in the car.
Alright.
What's the situation?
Tian Jinhai left yesterday afternoon
and hasn't come back.
No one answered his room phone.
How many exits at the hotel?
Two.
And a loading bay at the back.
Let's split up
our tasks at hand.
Si, Chang.
You two cover the back door.
The rest will
follow me through the front.
Got it.
Is everybody clear?
Hello, I'm picking up the mail.
Alright, give me a sec.
Why didn't Chu come today?
He had to take the day off.
You're here pretty early today.
All checked.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Thanks.