Hey, will I lose my job then?
What's the doubt in that?
If you hang out with Nedumaran's
daughter, isn't your job at risk?
You should have thought
about it when I called you.
What's this, Kumudha?
Is it really a trap as I said?
Nothing like that.
I've already told him
that I had forgotten my phone
at the resort
and that you brought it over.
So, there won't be any
problem after this, right?
No, there won't be.
I've already spoken to my dad.
But, when you call Mr. Nedumaran
as dad, it feels weird.
Even I feel the same.
Do you know that I sometimes
call him chef at home?
Oh, no!
- What?
Nothing. By the way,
what's the matter with your sister?
What's going on between
your father and sister?
My sister cooks better than me.
- Oh!
But..
She wants to travel the world.
She wants to meet a lot of people.
She wants to connect with them
and hear their stories.
She wants to write it as a book.
That is her wish.
But, our dad forced her
to become a master chef.
So, she ran away from home.
Oh, no!
I am the one
you should be feeling bad for.
Actually, she escaped.
But, I got stuck with him.
One day, I will also run away.
- Oh, no!
If you run away,
who will fulfil your dad's wish?
Hey, are you supporting me or him?
I will give you an idea.
You cook well, right?
You fulfil his wish.
Oh, no!
Why the unnecessary trouble?
He will find fault even in that.
But, I think people from every walk
of life face their own problems.
Debt is my biggest problem.
My family is struggling.
I have to educate my sister.
I have to give her money.
I don't know what she is doing.
I long to provide for my mom.
But, she is working as a house help.
I wanted to do a part-time job
for some extra income.
Because of my mistake,
the shop was taken away.
What are you saying?
Is that the same shop where we ate?
- Yes.
The food there was good.
What can I do? It's my ill fate.
I want to become a chef from here.
But, you are saying that you
don't like the profession I love.
What kind of life is this?
But, I must admit.
I forgot everything
and played the guitar with delight.
I am very happy.
I can't forget it.
It's okay. - Let me know
if I have to do it again.
I'll come and play
without charging you.
Even the ones who love
playing wouldn't talk like that.
This is my spot.
Okay.
- This is the hostel.
Dogs might chase if you go in.
You go.
- Okay, we'll meet tomorrow.
Okay, bye.
- Bye. - Hey! Your guitar!
Yes.
- Don't you want it?
Here. Wear it.
Thank you. I will leave now.
- Ride carefully.
Bye.
- Bye.
Vetri, listen to me patiently.
- Mom.
What is this?
How could you let her work?
I have told her so many times.
I told her to just study, and that
we'll deal with the problems.
But, she doesn't listen to me.
She told me not to tell you.
What should I do?
Mom, what you are
doing is not right.
Why did you hide it from me?
- Oh, God! Forgive me.
I'm stuck between the two of you.
Okay, what has happened
to her now? How is she?
She is in pain.
What led to her disc problem?
They won't allow her
to sit where she works.
Which shop is that?
Chitra Clothing Store that is
located on the main road.
Oh, God! I've heard that
they treat the employees badly.
You should have told me.
What is this?
Okay, tell me.
She's been on her feet
the whole time.
Standing continuously
has hurt her spine.
- Her spine?
Yes, Vetri.
We should take care of her
from now on.
Where are you now?
- At home.
She didn't tell me anything.
She went to the hospital alone
and then told me all about it.
Vetri..
Hello, Vetri.
Vetri, can you hear me?
Give the phone to Selvi.
- Okay, I'll give it.
Here, your brother is on the line.
Careful, get up slowly.
Sit carefully. Here, talk to him.
Brother.
- Selvi, why?
I wanted to do what I could.
Sorry. I didn't expect this.
I don't know what to say, Selvi.
If you knew,
you wouldn't have let me.
That's why I didn't tell you.
Okay, take rest.
I will talk to you later.
- Shall I give the phone to mom?
No, I will go home
and then call her.
I'll hang up.
- Okay.
Hey, why are you talking alone?
I asked you to enquire
about the job. Did you?
Don't get me started.
Migration workers have come in.
No openings
for the next two months.
When we ask for more salary,
they work for 10 hours
at half of our salary.
They seem shocked when I asked
for a high salary for only four hours.
We can't do anything.
We have to wait. Okay?
'Vetri, you've to deliver
food to room no 108.'
'Vetri, are you there?'
Hey, Vetri, they are saying
something. Ask them what it is.
'Vetri, deliver food to room 108.'
Talk to them, or you
might lose this job as well.
Okay, sir, I'll come.
- 'Come soon.'
When are you coming home?
I will feel at peace
if you come there.
Do you miss me a lot?
I've missed you ever since
you moved out after your wedding.
Okay, Dad.
But, I like being here
more than being at home.
Actually, I am happy here, Dad.
What are you saying, dear?
Whatever it is,
can I just leave you like that?
You need someone to take
care of you at this time, right?
That's not a problem, Dad.
I grew up here.
I have Aishu to take care of me.
Rajan is here.
Also, I feel
comfortable being here.
Dad, don't worry about anything.
I will be fine, okay?
I am safe here.
Okay, dear.
If you've decided, what can I say?
Okay, dear..
Thank you, Dad.
Riya.
- Tell me, Dad.
If you want anything,
call me immediately, okay?
Bye.
- Bye, Dad.
Okay, thank you.
Uncle, what happened?
Is it something important?
You know what is going
on in Riya's life, right? - Yes.
She shouldn't think there's no one
for her, in any situation.
I know your work pressure.
But, I don't know
whom to trust right now, Rajan.
So, you please take
care of her in this situation.
Take care of her.
- Sure, uncle.
What are you
room service people thinking?
Is this a resort?
What are you all thinking?
Yes, come. Stand here..
They are taking advantage
because of you.
Sir, what happened?
- What happened, eh?
Will anything happen here
without your knowledge?
What happened?
- I will tell you.
Hey, didn't I tell you
to call the manager?
He said he will come.
- Why are you standing here?
Go and get him.
- I'll go, sir.
Excuse me, sir,
I want to say something.
As you know,
we run this exclusive resort.
We have so many
variety of dishes here.
Then, why do you buy food
from outside and eat it?
Sir, there are a variety of dishes,
I'm not complaining about that.
The starting price here
ranges from Rs. 700-800.
I can eat three full meals
at the same price.
Customers come here
to save on cost.
So, how can you
charge them like this?
Sir, just to make you understand,
what you eat here
is not normal food.
It is done with clean
and fresh inventory.
Moreover, it is cooked
by the master, the GOAT,
Chef, Mr. Nedumaran.
- Yes, I know, sir.
I am also a fan of Mr. Nedumaran.
- Of course, who else is not?
At this resort, large crowds gather
to enjoy Chef Nedumaran's food.
But, I'm not satisfied.
How can you charge so much, sir?
Good food equals fair price.
LHS equals RHS.
You understand, I believe.
Sir, delivery guys are not
allowed inside the resort.
That's why I asked the room boy
to get the parcel, sir.
Sir, it is not fair.
What you are saying
is not right, sir.
You keep asking me questions.
If you keep talking like this,
I'll have to escalate the issue.
Sir, what I eat and where
I eat is my personal choice.
Don't interfere in that.
Just you may go now.
- Sir, you are an educated person.
Why are you talking like this?
I don't.. - Excuse me, sir.
I will deal with this.
What happened?
Sir, that is..
I got the parcel and handed it
over to the guest as requested.
That's why he is shouting, sir.
- Am I shouting?
Hey, do I look like a fool to you?
- John, look here.
There is no rule that says you
cannot order food from outside.
Why are you stressing the guest?
If the guest orders food from
outside, why do you deliver it?
That's not in the rules.
If you're here, who will look after
the other guests? Go back to work.
I will go, sir. Go.
Sir, next time, there won't be
any issue. - It's okay.
Okay, thank you, sir.
- Thank you so much. - Thank you.
Mr. Rajan, what are you doing?
If you behave like this with
the guest, our revenue will drop.
John, don't mind
that I'm being harsh.
But, there is no point
in talking to you.
Whatever I say,
you won't understand.
Your point of view
is only about the kitchen.
But, it's not the same for me.
I have to see
all the aspects of this resort.
Leave it.
Continue with your work.
I don't understand?
Okay, sir.
Who is it?
Uthaman?
That was a creditor.
- Oh..
I don't know what to do, Pandi.
- Why?
Ms. Bhavani's shop also is closed.
I don't know what she is doing.
Not only that, I can't do anything
without my monthly salary.
My head is spinning.
We will figure something out.
I can't stop thinking
about what that guy said.
Yes, he spoke too much.
- Yes.
I am so angry
that I want to build a resort.
Can we build one?
- Yes.
Only if I set it up and provide
John with a room service uniform,
will I die peacefully.
Hey! Why are you talking
about dying now?
This problem led me to a fantastic
business idea. Shall I tell you?
If you tell me to open a tea
shop outside this resort,
I will kill you.
- Not that.
We could get food from outside
and give it to the guests.
What if we take
a commission from them?
That is wrong.
They eat outside
because the food here is expensive.
How can you do this?
Hey! You made me
a villain in a second.
I have an idea.
Why don't we put a small
kitchen set inside the resort
and provide food
for the guests at a lower cost?
People here are like hounds.
If they find out,
they'll tear you to pieces.
The shop will do well
if it's in the right spot.
I don't want to do this.
They have already kicked me
out of the kitchen.
Are you planning to kick me
out of the resort?
Okay, leave it.
This seems risky.
But..
- But?
We have to do something about John.
Why are you talking like me?
Okay, leave it. Don't feel bad.
Let's keep a doll.
- A doll? What doll?
The doll.
If we twist its hands and legs..
I am more scared of you
than the doll.
Do it soon.
- Lift it.
Lift it well..
Are you alright, Riya?
Shall I get you a pill?
No, I don't want that.
I will be fine if I get some sleep.
Then take rest.
I will leave. Bye.
Rajan.
I have some doubts
about our resort.
Why is the food
in our resort so expensive?
If we reduce the cost,
we can run it better, right?
You asked such
a big question so easily.
Tell me, I will learn.
What you asked
is not just a question.
It's history.
I hate history.
Even I don't like it.
But, I have to know.
I've had this doubt
for a long time.
There were so many negative
feedback and comments.
Why didn't anyone think about it?
We can't go against
Mr. Nedumaran's rules.
It's already decided
what to do and what not to do.
Since you are the one
after your dad,
he had asked me
to explain it to you.
Thank God,
you asked at the right time.
Let me explain.
Rule number one.
Discipline and behaviour.
Sir, this is newly built.
- Oh, lovely.
Was it there when you visited?
- No, it was not.
There was nothing.
What's your name?
- My name is Vetri.
Vetri, do one thing.
Bring Nedumaran.
Mr. Nedumaran?
Sir, you can't meet him
as easily as you think.
Do you think
I am a fan of Nedumaran?
It's not like that. He is my
old friend. Go and get him.
Sir, you have got
the wrong person for that.
What did you say?
- Nothing, sir.
Tell him that Leo is here.
He will definitely come.
Okay, sir.
- This is the room, right?
I will go. You go and get him.
Is Chika here?
Chef Chika.
Call him too.
- Chika?
There is no chef
with that name.
Is that so?
Okay, go and call Nedumaran.
- Okay, sir.
I keep landing in trouble.
Hold on for a minute,
get the pepper. - Yes, Chef.
Do you want me to pour it on top?
- Yes.
Okay.
- That's fine.
Here you go, Chef.
- Yeah.
That should be fine, John.
Just take this and..
- I will just come, Chef.
Where is the order list?
It's not a food list, sir.
There is a guy named Leo.
Says he is Mr. Nedumaran's friend.
He is waiting in his room
to meet him.
Anybody can claim that they know
him. Can he meet all of them?
You..
- John. - Chef.
I am coming, Chef.
Tell him
I will come after plating this.
Plating..
- Yes.. I will tell him.
Did you hear that? He will
come after plating it. You go.
Okay.
Sir..
Is there anyone named
Chef Chika in the kitchen?
I mean.. He was asking.
Chika?
- Yes.
There is no..
- Room number? - Sir.
Room number?
- He is asking you the room number.
Sir, room number 211.
Thank you, sir.
Hey, Nedumaran!
- Leo!
Yes.
- How are you?
I am doing great.
How are you?
I am fine as usual.
- Wonderful.
It's been a long time.
- Yes.
Where did Chika go?
Chika?
I don't know who he is.
Chika, Nedumaran. You both
were friends. Did you forget?
Hey.
I don't remember anyone like that.
Then how would I forget?
You really don't remember Chika?
Hey, I don't know.
Chidambaram, Nedumaran.
Did you forget?
There are many people around.
You know, I'm in the hotel industry.
I can't remember everyone.
Moreover, I am getting old.
Good that you didn't forget me.
How can I forget you,
useless fellow?
Come in.
The TV remote is not working.
That's why I asked you to come.
Check it.
- Okay, sir.
I had to leave the kitchen
midway because you called.
I will go back, okay?
- Okay, Nedumaran, carry on.
Sir, it's working now.
- Thank you.