Umm
That's enough, you!
We've done it a lot already
We've done it a lot already,
but can't we do it again?
You're all out of cum.
Ohhh!
You really are something.
Heh...
Champ!
I…
Hey!
I think we should just stop here.
I’m afraid we won’t be able to be friends again like we were.
Save this kind of thing...
for someone you actually love.
Hey
Yeah, man.
Hmm...
Where’s Hia Sorn been?
I...
Haven’t seen him in two or three days.
Did you guys fight or something?
Or...
He gave up trying to win you back?
He’s not answering. Whatever, forget it.
Hey!
calm down.
I’ll help you.
Should I message Hia Tai?
Hia Tai, have you seen Sorn lately?
I've tried to contact him, but no luck.
Maybe he's sick.
It seems like he hasn't come to work for several days.
Jun,
Hia Tai said...
Hia Sorn’s sick.
For real?!
How is he?
I don’t know.
Hia Tai’s working with P’June.
Wait—where are you going?
I’m heading out...
I’ll call a cab.
Alright, take care.
Jun!
Whoa!!
Hia Tai told Win you were sick,
so I came rushing over…
but you...
Then I’ll go.
Jun, wait!
Let me go, P’Sorn!
Guys, don’t move yet—it's slippery...
Let go!
If I let go, you won’t listen to me.
I don’t want to hear anything from you anymore.
Be as jealous as you want, Jun.
but just listen to me.
Don’t step yet.
it’s slippery.
Sorn.
How are you feeling?
Whoa!!
Are you okay?
Let go!
Sorn.
Have you told him about us yet?
Heh!
Since we’re all here.
Let’s just clear everything up.
I’ve got nothing to clear up.
I’m leaving.
If you think you can just walk out of my house.
Go for it, Jun.
Hey!
Stay still.
Calm down and just listen to me.
Back then,
Sorn and I...
we were friends with benefits.
But it wasn’t wrong.
neither of us had anyone else.
I don’t know.
why...
Sorn decided to end it.
Maybe we were done…
or maybe it’s because of you.
I swear I don’t have anyone else, Jun.
How would I know that?
You’re so...
Believe me.
There’s really no one else.
Then why didn’t you tell me you were sick?
I couldn’t even stand up.
I haven’t even properly called in sick yet.
Sorn’s been out for days.
I was nearby, so I dropped in.
And I happened to find Champ already taking care of him.
Sorn was seriously sick.
Hia told him to go see a doctor and he refused.
Good thing Hia had a hunch and came to check.
Lucky you didn’t die.
So damn stubborn.
Where are you now?
I’m nearby.
Let’s meet in half an hour, okay?
I’ll head off first.
I’m leaving now.
Thanks a lot.
Hey! Watch your step—it’s slippery!
Whoa!!
Heh...
I’m outta here.
Has P’Sorn taken his meds yet, Hia?
I have eaten.
Champ, got it for me.
You sure you’re okay?
Hmm...
Should we get Sorn to eat something?
Yeah, go eat.
Penny bought you some porridge.
I don’t feel like eating porridge.
It’s too mushy.
Stop whining.
Your throat hurts, so just eat something warm.
How can I eat Penny’s stuff?
That kid’ll get jealous again.
Didn’t you see how possessive he is?
Who’s jealous of you?!
A moment ago, it...
I just...
Just what?
Say it. Acting all tough.
You’re just as bad as me.
Okay stop—enough.
So what do you actually wanna eat?
No clue.
Hia Jom?
I was about to order…
Why you calling Jom?
Ordering food for you!
You won’t eat this or that.
How’re you supposed to take your meds?
Then order from somewhere else!
Hia Jom’s place is the closest, duh.
Hand it over.
I’ll get one porridge and...
one spaghetti.
Thanks.
That’s it?
You love pushing my buttons.
And you’re jealous for no reason.
No reason?
I just…
damn,
My head hurts.
You idiot.
See? Acting all tough while being sick.
[You idiot.]
You okay, dude?
Here, Hia.
Huh?
I ordered extra for you.
Thank you very much.
What about Sorn?
The porridge’s for him.
Looks good.
This place’s food is great.
I want rice.
You’re so fussy, man!
Why eat something hard to swallow?
Just eat the damn porridge.
I don’t like porridge.
Oh!
come on, liar.
You eat this so you can take your medicine.
If you don’t get better,
I’m sending Jun to find a new boyfriend.
Yeah,
Hia...
just force yourself to eat,
so you can take the meds.
Feed me.
Heh.
You can eat it.
Eat it yourself.
Eat.
Feed.
Hia, where are you taking Jun’s stuff?
To my place, obviously.
Can I leave a bit later, bro?
Not yet...
I haven’t finished the paperwork to transfer my internship yet.
Can I go another day?
When you moved to the factory,
You didn’t need any paperwork.
Just grab your stuff!
Are you in a rush or what?
Yeah.
I’m in a rush.
And I already job took leave for you.
That means...
So Hia Tai knows everything now, huh?
Yep.
He gave the green light.
You can start interning at the office today.
You’re stealing Jun from me again, Hia...
Win, don’t you feel bad for me?
I’ve been apart from Jun for ages now.
That’s your own fault.
Come on, don’t!
Three days.
No way, bro.
Then just one day.
Ughhh…
Jun!
choose—me.
Or... Hia?
Heh...
I’ll take the day off.
to pack my things.
But...
can I finish one more week at the factory?
Then I’ll head...
to the city office.
Is that okay?
He's okay.
Give me a handshake, my friend.
If you didn’t say no, I’ll take that as a yes.
Gotta get back to work.
Oh!
yeah.
Bye, bro!
So...
you feeling better now?
Did you see a doctor?
Yeah, I’m getting better.
Let’s go pack.
I told you I don’t wanna leave?
What kinda couple lives separately, huh Jun?
You keep saying "couple"
you ever get embarrassed?!
Nah, not at all.
‘Cause it’s true.
So...
Then can I ask for something?
When I go back to the office.
let’s keep our relationship a secret, okay?
And don’t try anything at work.
No touching in front of others.
But… if it’s just the two of us…
that’s allowed, right?
Huh...
Pack your stuff already!
You promised me. About the office.
P’Sorn.
I’m sleeping in this room tonight.
I don’t approve.
Why not?
Because I’m too lazy to knock when I wanna get it on with you.
Seriously?!
Do you always have to bring up sex?
I just want some time for myself.
Time for yourself?
You’re telling me you’re gonna handle yourself,
when I’m literally right here?
Hgh...
I meant me time...
like personal space.
You’re not secretly seeing someone else, right?
The reason I want my own room.
because I’m tired at work.
You’re way too clingy, man!
I don’t wanna be exhausted, alright?!
Hmm...
Okay!
Now go. I’m packing.
Coffee’s here! For P’Praew and P’Korn!
Beena, Pete.
thank you so much.
You two delivered this yourselves?
Yep.
The café’s quiet today,
so we figured we’d bring it up ourselves.
Hmm...
It’s been quiet up here too lately.
Jun’s been gone.
P’Sorn—my boyfriend,
oops!
he’s been gone too.
I’ve been so lonely!
But I saw you chatting it up with the security guard earlier.
Didn’t look lonely at all!
Oof!
And the other day I saw you talking to Auntie Maew.
scribbling down some long list of numbers.
Doesn’t look like someone lonely!
Korn!
What?
you seriously handed your lottery sheet to Auntie Maew?!
Yeah!
Submit what?
Oh!
Nothing, sweetie.
Just a little note for Auntie Maew.
I missed her, that’s all.
So you two not heading back to the café yet?
You haven’t paid us yet!
Ah!
Payment! Okay.
Here’s the QR code.
If they need anything else,
make sure to follow up, alright?
Of course.
I’ll count on your team to support from this side too.
Hey Jun,
Wanna grab some crispy noodles across from the factory.
Come eat with us.
it’s as good as us.
Sure thing.
Since you’re heading back to the city office soon anyway.
Hmm...
Yeah!
we should totally throw you a mini send.
Our beloved prince of the factory is leaving soon.
we gotta go all out!
Oh!
That’s too much.
I’m not that popular.
Hey!
Sorn…
Once we send our handsome intern back to the city,
if you get any other good-looking newbies,
send them here, okay?
Jun!
one of the city office’s resident charmers.
He always spreads his charm around.
That’s why he’s got a whole fan club.
You’re just making stuff up…
Oww! Come on, bro!
Don’t bite my lip,
that hurts!
I want to.
Well, I want to too.
Hold on a sec!
I meant…
I wanna eat...
eat food!
I’m hungry.
Can’t you eat later?
But...
Everyone’s waiting, though!
I’m waiting for you, duh.
Come on, bro…
I’ll be home again by Saturday anyway.
Can’t you give me a little down payment first?
Down payment?
Down payment!!
I’m outta here.
Jun!
you little shit!
Ah!
Oh.
Guys, help me! help!
Alright, alright!
we’re coming!
Heh..
You ordered food?
Nah.
Oh!
Right this way.
Whoa, that’s awesome, bro!
Here’s your soy milk.
Shit, it’s hot! Damn it!
That’s all you brought me?
You’re watching your figure.
right? Why eat more?
And why are you showing up so late?
I’m crashing here tonight.
Huh?
You’re sleeping in Jun’s room, right?
But...
The room’s not soundproof.
Keep it down, alright?
You jerk, Win!
Later, bro!
I’ll be back.
Where you going?
Grabbing my clothes from the car.
Hey! Bro!
Where’d you come from, the desert or something?
I don’t feel like it.
I know.
I won’t push it.
Let me just cuddle you real hard.
Hey!
I’m so proud
got myself a hot boyfriend.
But I hate it when people look at you.
Now.
You’re complimenting me to my face now?
You used to not even look me in the eye.
I was complimenting you in my head, okay?
Jun…
I wanna get serious with you—for real.
I also...
serious about you.
I wanna do this right.
But I’m scared you’re not ready.
Not ready for what?
Coming out to my family.
Well, well, if it isn’t my brother-in-law!
Whoa—P’Nu!
What the heck did you just say?!
And what are you doing here?
You visiting?
How long you staying?
Want me to show you around?
You sure you’ve got the energy?
My brother actually let you outta bed?
Nu
Stop teasing him.
Yeah, seriously
Back me up here, P’Sorn.
Dude, stop blurting out the truth all the time! People might actually…
You told Mom about him yet?
Feeling better now, honey?
Yeah, I’m all good now, Mom.
Has Tanu arrived?
He’s here...
And all he’s done is nag me.
So annoying!
How did you even raise that guy, Mom?
I raise him the same way as you.
Mom…
What is it?
Um…
What if I had a boyfriend.
It’s a good thing.
My eldest son is going to fall in love.
But...
It’s not the kind of love people see as “ideal”?
If it’s the love you choose, it’s gotta be good.
Jun’s a sweet boy.
Wait—Mom, you knew?!
Don’t underestimate your own mother.
The way you look at him says everything.
So… do you like him?
Whoever you love, I love too.
Jun’s adorable.
Bring him to visit again sometime, okay?
Will do.
Love you, Mom.
And you?
Why are you here?
Came for a friend’s wedding…
And to check in on stuff for Lady Wandi.
Our mom’s starting a new business.
Man, you never stop working, huh?
I swear, she’s gonna run for district mayor next.
You’re such a model son.
Of course I am. Not like you—
ditched the farm life to be a salaryman.
You asshole…
P’Sorn
Where’d all the stuff in the bedroom go?
Since Tanu’s staying over, you gotta sleep in my room.
Why didn’t you put him in your mom’s room?
Didn’t have time to clean it up.
Alright, alright—
just sleep in my room, okay?
That way I don’t have to roll in dust in my mom’s room again.
Settled.
Quit whining and go to sleep.
Jun…
Can I?
Hey hey! I brought your stuff—
Ohh, wow...
wait, are y’all making babies in there?!
You little devil!
Tanu!
Get your ass home NOW!
I didn’t know y’all were doing that! You didn’t even lock the damn door!
And seriously—put your shirt on, you’re flashing me, dude!
You saw something just now, didn’t you?
Are you seriously embarrassed right now?
I’ve seen your junk since we were kids!
Not mine
Jun’s!
Oh...
I only saw his chest.
Just the chest, okay?
You sure?
Totally! Just a glimpse. Then you kicked me out.
Next time, wait for permission before barging into someone’s room!
This is your house.
And my house too!
I’ve been here loads of times
I come and go like I own the place.
Huh? What the—!?
I’m trying to teach you something!
Okay, okay! I’m sorry
I really didn’t know!
How’s Jun? Is he mad at me?
Mad at me? That’s fine. But mad at me? I’m screwed.
P’Sorn! Go sleep with P’Tanu
I’m locking the door tonight!
See?! This is your fault, dumbass! Shit
Jun! Don’t lock the damn door!
Hey, P’Sorn.
Are you still mad at me about last night?
Of course I am! Why didn’t you lock the damn door?
Ughh, now Tanu’s gonna tease me to death!
Tanu left at like 7 a.m.
He had to go be the best man at that wedding.
So you really are mad at me, huh?
Come on, don’t be mad.
I seriously didn’t know the door wasn’t locked. Forgive me?
Fine. But next time—don’t forget.
I mean it!
Got it.
Drink your coffee—I made it for you.
Drink it first.
Morning, everyone.
Whoaaa Jun! Our precious intern.
I thought you ran off for good!
Where’ve you been, man?
Welcome back, Jun!
Hello everyone.
Hey hey, let’s not crush him with hugs, alright?
Hmph! I missed him too! Look at him, he’s grown two whole centimeters!
Whoa, that’s a big deal, huh? Two whole cm!
You’re so cute.
Glad you’re back, Jun.
Thanks, P’.
We thought you were quitting to go work at the factory full time. Didn’t even tell us.
Yeah, sorry about that.
I didn’t plan to transfer—it all happened pretty fast.
Besides, I was only gone a little while. I’m back now.
Hi P’June, P’Penny!
- Hii there!
- Hello!
Alright, we’ll catch you later.
Okay!
What?
P’June, P’Penny did I miss something?
They seem normal to me...
Feels like P’June and P’Penny are dating!
Gosh, Praew! Don’t go blurting that out without proof.
P’June and P’Penny? OMG, really?
Yup!
No way! Penny and June? Can’t be!
Listen, this tea’s been filtered! Auntie Maew—our cleaning lady—told me.
She saw them kiss after work!
Whaaat?! Dead!!
Our ship is sinking!! Who do we ship P’Sorn with now?!
Okay, enough gossip! Back to work, everyone—line up, students!
We’ll talk later—move it, before they walk in! Scatter!
See you this evening! Back to work now!
Sit down and start working, you troublemaker!
Yeah, yeah.
How’ve you been?
I’m good! The factory was hot as hell.
I missed this office so much—AC’s heaven here.
You ran off and didn’t even tell me. I was kinda hurt.
Awwww you poor thing, always so sensitive!
Here ya go.
welcome back to work, my dear intern~
Whoa, that’s way too much.
Can I just fake my death?
Hey, what do you mean? That’s all James’s work.
Just wait till he’s done with the meeting—he’ll come teach you.
So you can level up, bro!
Still too much, bro!
That’s what you get for disappearing!
Wait, where is P’James?
He’s in a meeting, bro.
Oh right, and who are these kids—
Oh, I’m an intern here.
And this is P’Champ
He’s on the sales team
P’Champ…
oh! I’ve heard about you from P’Korn.
But dang, you look super young! I thought you were another intern.
So good-looking too.
I’m Tos, by the way. Just started working here.
Oh! Nice to meet you, man.
So where do you usually eat lunch?
Around here, just nearby.
Mind if I tag along?
I’m new and don’t really know who to eat with yet.
Sure, let’s have lunch together this noon.
Thanks a lot…
See you at lunch, P’Champ!
Yes, sir. Absolutely, I’ll take care of it.
Okay, goodbye.
P’Puth~ are P’Ei and P’Pae around?
Oh hey, it’s Vena! Doing coffee runs today?
Yep! They placed an order.
Ahh, they’re not here right now. P’Praew sent them to prep meeting docs.
Then can I leave these with you?
Sure!
Cool, bring ’em over.
Thanks a lot.
By the way, is there a new intern joining?
Oh, you mean the new guy? Actually no—he’s not an intern, he’s a full-time hire. His name’s Tos.
The higher-ups asked me to take care of him.
Then don’t forget to send him to buy coffee at my dad’s café too, okay?
You’re tiny but a pro at selling stuff, huh? Damn, impressive!
You’re doing great, I’ll take care of it!
Alright, we’ll get going now.
Don’t forget to give the coffee to P’Toey and P’Pae!
Will do! Get back safe.
I gotta get back to work. Byeee!
Kids these days… really know their stuff
P’Tai, P’Sorn
Can I ask you something? Just 5 minutes, promise.
What is it?
P’Korn and P’Praew said you guys are really close to P’Champ…
I wanna ask him out.
So I was hoping you two could give me some advice.
You guys still here?
Do that stuff somewhere private!
Were you spying on me?
I want your dad and sister to know we’re together.
And if your dad doesn’t approve?
Has Jun ever brought a home?
Or… does Dad need to go propose for a wife?
Or... a guy?
So you’re flirting with my brother?
Or are you already together?
Sis…
Sis, ask Sorn.