There are many important birthdays
Your first, then ten, double digits,
Thirteen, obviously,
Fifteen or sixteen,
and then the big one-eight,
How was your body scrub?
My almost-adult skin is feeling
Now, is your glow from your facial
are heating back up
The facial,
Honestly, I would die of happiness
But after the way I hurt her last year,
What about you and Min Ho?
I don't know,
Even if he wanted to make it work,
Anyway, you still haven't RSVP'd
Yeah, about that…
There's no way you're not coming
I know, I'm sorry,
I already promised Yisoo
But I have an entire itinerary
I even found
- Camellia pink,
Why camellia?
It was my mom's favorite flower,
Birthdays always make me think of her,
I think she'd like that
who helped me become the person I am,
You are definitely one of those friends,
Oh, Kitty,
I still can't go,
- Yuri!
I'm sorry,
Okay, well, Yuri's dead to me,
Kidding, But come on, it's my birthday,
Oh, Dae, I'm so glad you're here,
I think that my birthday invite
You'll be there, right?
I wish I could,
- Yep,
- But I only turn 18 once,
Should I have sent out
Ah, ah, ah! Those are for Jin,
Mm, You're trying to butter him up,
Make him feel batter
- That was cute, I like that,
I've been leaving him treats and gifts
Hm, Well, I think a demonstration of love
Look at you
- Speaking of…
- I have some bad news,
- I don't think I'm gonna be able to…
- …make it to your--
You are coming to my birthday party,
I can't,
I… I have a thing for track,
It's a… It's a track thing, So…
- Hm,
First Yuri blows off my party,
Oh my God,
Are you throwing me a surprise party?
No one's ever thrown me one before!
Maybe that's because you're
What's the ruse?
- There's this dress that--
And don't go digging
You're gonna have to wait
Me, wait and see?
Yeah, tall order,
NYU, here I come!
Kitty, you have so much to celebrate,
Sorry to miss your party,
Yeah, we have a thing
Where across town?
Hongdae? Jamsil?
Oh God, look at the time,
- Is this a dressy thing you're going to?
Or is it more--
- Hey,
I hope you got my birthday invite,
And I hope it wasn't weird
No, I… I'm glad you did,
But I can't make it,
Oh, I get it, I mean, everyone's busy,
Yes, I actually decided to go visit
And meet up with a few music contacts,
That's great,
I'm… really excited for you,
See you later,
All right, mate,
When are you gonna fess up
I was going to, all right?
But then she got the email from NYU,
So?
So now it doesn't matter,
Her future is mapped out, literally,
She's happy,
And I'm not about to ruin that,
I think a "congratulations" are in order,
Honestly, I didn't see this coming,
Jiwon literally cried when she found out,
Kitty, you told him?
- Well, I suppose you're disappointed,
Alex, no, this is not--
- NYU is perfectly respectable,
Wait,
What?
Okay, I've been seeing Miss Ahn
We're in love,
And I'm gonna be a dad,
- You two are practically kids yourselves,
I'm sorry, I… I didn't mean that,
I'm gonna let you two talk,
Look,
I don't know if I'm ready,
But what I do know
I hope you know…
I would have dropped everything
Everything,
I'm glad you get this chance
to be the father I wasn't,
Be there for all the important firsts,
Well, I was hoping that
maybe we could
Grandfather,
- It's Bora,
She said Kitty called our restaurant
to ask if we had a birthday party
This morning I "accidentally" left
a sky-diving brochure
Ah,
Dae, thank you for helping me
I might actually get into uni,
I'd do anything for you, Eunice,
Like be my date
I thought you'd never ask,
Hey, are you okay? Is something wrong?
You texted 911!
I meant SOS911, the girl group,
Soo-jin called me,
Sounds like him, but…
I told the girls
Now they want you to be their new manager,
You do this, your dad's gonna have
It would be fun to mess with his head,
but you and I are just getting started
I still haven't told my dad
Just because my career is over
Happy birthday, dear Kitty
Happy birthday to you
Anyone figured out
when people sing "Happy Birthday"?
If you wish away my heartburn,
I'm so glad we got the chance
And I'm so glad that Professor Lee
He's super happy for us,
but teachers aren't allowed to date,
- Actually?
Right now, Jiwon and I
The baby,
Look at that poor woman over there,
She's been rocking her baby
and she hasn't had one bite of food,
How am I supposed to do this?
I don't know anything
No, you're going to be great,
You know you could talk to somebody
My halmoni would disown me if she knew,
Professor Lee is a tough cookie,
Maybe Imo-Halmoni will too,
Please, Jiwon, can I call her?
If you like my peanut butter cookies,
You don't have to keep bringing me treats,
Sorry, I have a lot going on right now,
Are you working on your uni apps?
Lee told me my chances aren't great
now that I'm not a track star
I wish there was something I could do,
Well, maybe Kitty's party
You're still coming, right?
Yeah, I can't wait to see
Who's this?
This is Alex, we work together,
You've got this,
He's going to be my baby's father,
Grandma…
I'm pregnant,
What?
Oh my God!
Are you trying
You're just determined, aren't you?
I thought you wanted
If you were just going
you could have stayed in Bukjeon!
I just wanted
Is that so wrong?
Oh, I see,
You don't need me anymore!
Grandma…
I need you more than ever now,
We're both matchmakers,
They're a perfect couple!
Alex will take care of Jiwon,
Ah, Oh,
Oh my, you speak so well,
You're all grown up,
I really
love Jiwon,
And I would really love for us all
to become a family,
What a handsome chin,
Okay,
Ugh, I hate being in the dark,
But I guess I'm pretty flattered
that my friends are trying so hard
And it's actually working,
Just hang in there a little longer, Kitty,
Hello,
Happy birthday, Kitty,
Thank you, You're up early,
My boss just emailed,
Of course she does, Wait, that's amazing,
So I have that dedication page,
'Cause that would be
If I ever get published,
I'm gonna dedicate the first book to Mom,
But you get the sequel,
Yes, I've edged out Margot,
Thank you,
Oh, um, that reminds me,
Wait, what?
- Peter and I have some news,
Obviously there's things we have
but we are gonna make it work,
Love is worth the risk, right?
This is the best news ever,
I love you so much,
I hope you have an amazing birthday,
Love you too, Bye,
Call it a matchmaker's intuition,
but I knew Peter and Lara Jean
even if they had to go the long way,
Best gift ever,
Okay, how about…
Okay, pretty good, I think we could sell
Like, almost dead,
I'm sorry that I couldn't be more chill
I just thought that
I could let go of the one
It's not like you haven't crossed off
Yeah, but none of them
Like, when I pictured talking
I never thought I'd be hard-selling Alex
Or when I defined
I never thought
I know you're bummed,
It's about you,
You're right,
And thank you for whatever
Sleeping on my own, what a crime
Losin' self-control every time…
Happy birthday!
This is incredible!
Wait, so all of the clues, they were lies?
More like misdirections,
Well… you gave us no choice,
You came,
We all decided
to keep you guessing,
It's called a Kittytini!
- My very own mocktail! Thank you,
Are these camellias?
Min Ho brought them in,
Now go change,
- My dress?
Thank you!
Thank you, everybody,
This is amazing,
Yo,
Good job keeping Kitty in the dark,
Right? That girl's like
Hey, so, are you still planning on
No,
I mean, don't get me wrong,
but I'd much rather just enjoy
Why?
I might need a favor,
Wanna take me for a ride
Do you got more than meets the eye?
But, baby, come and take a seat
Need you to inspire me
I'm only giving you one try
Ready, set, go
So hot, like summertime
I can make you melt
One look, you're hypnotized
Baby, I can tell
I'm running through your mind
So catch me if you can
Text me, though they miss me
XO, XO, XO, XO
- Okay, time for gifts!
- Happy birthday, Kitty,
A lock?
Because we first met at Namsan Tower,
Aww,
- I love it,
So I'm launching my new line with
and this label's gonna be on it,
Yuri!
Mm,
Aww, cupcakes!
It's to remember the first night we met,
when you absolutely demolished
And because you're the sweetest
Was the point of these gifts
Well, we each wanted to get you something
Yeah, it was Min Ho's idea,
That's so thoughtful,
Thank you, guys,
When people keep repeating
That you'll never fall in love
When everybody keeps retreating
But you can't seem to get enough
Let my love open the door
To your heart
Damn,
Future CEO Jin really works,
Thanks,
If only it were that easy,
Well… do you have any plans,
- Q, stop,
It's an interview with Marius's dad
His company has a branch in Seoul,
- I don't want to owe Marius anything,
Look, Marius really wants
And…
So do I,
I've actually been reaching out to a few
so while I appreciate the help…
I want to do this on my own,
Of course,
Jin, I only did this because…
I love you,
And I know
But maybe I can show you,
And I'll keep showing you, however long
Part of me wants to make you grovel,
Like, forever,
But…
I love you too,
I want to trust you again,
Especially since we only have
"Together?"
Still wondering how we got here
With every mess we made
But all of it still means nothing…
If I can't take your breath away
What are you doing up here?
Just thinking about
All the changes, and…
It's been quite the journey,
Well, I'm really impressed
And…
I'm glad you're getting a second chance,
I also really love this song,
But I think it would be better
I would love to,
Your eyes are like weapons
Your lips could teach lessons
Don't use them so reckless
'Cause for you, I'm helpless
You gotta take caution
You know that I'm all in
The chance of me falling
You know that it's often
But if you don't wanna stay…
So…
How does it feel to be 18?
I feel very wise,
Well, would wise old Covey
like to dance?
You're starting up a wildfire
Hope it's what you meant…
So let me get this straight,
The themed gifts were your idea,
And the camellias,
And here, I totally bought your lie
Kitty, I wasn't lying,
I did have a ticket booked to LA,
But I decided
I'd rather be here,
Can I ask you something?
Yeah,
When you applied early decision to NYU,
how did you know
Oh, um…
Well, I kind of fell in love with it
And I really love my life in Seoul,
but when we weren't together,
it gave me a chance
- Mm,
And I realized it was NYU,
So I decided to just go for it,
Why?
SOS911 is firing my dad,
They want me to be their manager,
Min Ho, that's huge!
Yes, but I'd have to miss
Well, are you gonna take the job?
Honestly, I'm not sure,
What do you think I should do?
Happy birthday, Covey,
I'm not a person
I like taking the wheel,
But I learned something
If you're surrounded by
you can always trust them
Thank you!
All the city's sleeping
Every street light's calling out…
As quickly as it came,
I'm halfway to graduation,
I had so many expectations
I even wrote them all down in a list,
I wanted it to be perfect,
It wasn't,
It was… messy,
Sometimes it hurt,
But it was beautiful,
Even the surprises,
There may even be more to come,
Oh, when the lighthouse fires
Feel a world away
Then you just have to remember
That the dark won't last forever
I'm always yours
It's good!
It turned out really well,
Thanks for helping me,
I told my dad I'm pursuing music,
Really?
What'd he say?
He said he spent his whole life
and doesn't want that for me,
He would be proud of me
That's all I ever wanted
He'll come around,
Maybe he will, maybe he won't,
I keep thinking about
About what I really want for myself,
I've been too focused on
Maybe I want to pursue something I love,
Gotta go,
Good luck!
Hey, is Kitty here?
She already left for break,
But she's taking the subway
- Right, subway,
Which subway?
Oh God,
- What? I've never taken one before,
Here, take my T-card,
It's the airport line
Welcome to how the other half lives,
- Great, thank you, Thank you!
See you next semester!
Good luck!
We've been running circles
Worried, I was stressing about you
I need you to let me know
If you feel the same 'cause I
I
Recognize that we might be
But in your eyes, I've always known
Kitty!
So before we say XO, goodbye
Let me tell you why
The sun doesn't rise without you
The more I hold the night
The rain wouldn't stop
The clouds, they will always cry
Can't take it anymore
Time will never make it right
'Cause the sun doesn't rise
By my side
By my side, without you
What can I do?
You've chosen your place
If this is what you want
But my future feels so dark
Without the one I can't replace
So before you say XO, goodbye
Let me tell you why
The sun doesn't rise without you
The more I hold the night
The rain wouldn't stop
The clouds, they will always cry
Can't take it anymore
- Time will never make it right
'Cause the sun doesn't rise
I heard your song,
It's incredible,
I'm so sorry
that it took me so long
Covey, I don't want
And I don't know
I want it to be with you,
And I couldn't let you go
Or without saying…
I love you,
You what?
I love you too,
Started in the strangest way
Didn't see it coming
Swept up in your hurricane
Wouldn't give it up for nothing
Now I'm all caught up
It's a shock to my system
I don't wanna run away, so I stayed
My head gets messy when I try to hide…
I don't know what this means
I don't know what our future holds,
I don't have a plan this time,
But if I've learned anything this year,
it's that sometimes, it's just better
I like first class,
Mm, Technically, this is business class,
Don't get posh on me, Covey,
It's going to be freezing in Portland,
We'll get you some warm clothes,
I think you would look
I can't wait to see the city
Yeah?
Well, if you thought LJ was something,
Oh, I think I've lost my senses
Am I walkin' straight into
A burnin' light?
'Cause I tossed and turned the covers
Tried to make a shape of you
I'm tryna find you in a crowd again
You were there, then you were gone
Now I'm tracin' all my steps to you
Oh, I think I'm losin' my mind
Over here, over you, every night
Both hands holding on to the wire
Fight over here
Without you, every night
Sittin' here with my head on fire
Ooh