[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOOTS MARCHING]
[BOMB WHISTLING, EXPLODING]
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING]
[SEAGULLS SQUAWKING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Right there.
[DOOR HANDLE RATTLES]
[BUZZER BLARES]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[DOOR OPENING]
[PASSERBY GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[SIGHS]
[BRIEFCASE SETTING DOWN]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[CONTINUES KNOCKING ON DOOR]
MICHAEL: Mr. Bau, is that you?
I'm not here. Go away!
MICHAEL: Please,
I... I must speak with you.
Uh, my name
is Michael Wancowski.
I'm the attorney representing
the Plaszow prisoners.
JOSEPH: What's it this time?
Are you going to sue
for an apology
from the Nazi Party?
Or maybe for back wages for time
spent working in camps?
No, I'm suing for justice.
A trial has been scheduled
against Franz Gruen.
And we want,
we need, you to testify.
This man
has been acquitted twice,
and he will always be acquitted.
There is no proof
of the charges against him.
And it doesn't matter if one
or a thousand of his victims
comes forward, all he has to do
is smile and say,
"Oh, it must have been
somebody else. It wasn't me."
"It was that other
mass-murdering Nazi."
And he's free.
I promise you,
this time will be different.
How can you promise me that?
You don't know who I am?
Of course I know who you are,
another attorney,
who likes to milk his clients
for all they're worth.
And at the end of a case,
nobody wins but you.
So, good day!
MICHAEL: Okay, but Mr. Bau,
Mr. Bau, please.
This is our chance.
Okay, here is how this will go.
When I say "stop," you stop.
And when I say "go," you go.
You have my word.
JOSEPH: Now go.
MICHAEL:
Fear never stopped you before.
[SIGHS, SNIFFS]
[SMACKS LIPS]
Would you like some tea?
MICHAEL: Please.
[WATER RUNNING]
[WATER POURING]
JOSEPH: Would you mind, um,
turning off the faucet for me?
Sure.
Ah. [CHUCKLES]
I've heard it said that art
is a reflection of the soul.
Ah.
Art critic and an attorney?
Now, I'm really thrilled.
Is this, um...
JOSEPH: Um.
Did you come here to stare
at my walls or to talk to me?
[EXHALES, CHUCKLES]
Yes. Well, uh...
Do you mind if I record you?
Have at it. [GROANS]
This will take the place of me
having to appear in Vienna, huh?
Well, having you in person
would be much more convincing.
This is testimony
of Mr. Joseph Bau.
The State versus former SS Guard
Franz Gruen, October 1971.
Now... Is that all right?
Yes, very creative.
MICHAEL: Thank you.
So, uh, your first encounter
with SS Guard Franz Gruen
was in the Plaszow Camp.
So tell me....
No. It was in my later days
at the ghetto,
uh, when he was just a soldier
in the Nazi army.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SEAGULLS SQUAWKING]
WOMAN: [IN POLISH]
They're coming! Quickly!
The trucks are coming!
[VEHICLES APPROACHING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[IN GERMAN]
Leave your stuff. Move it!
[SOLDIERS SPEAKING GERMAN]
[INDISTINCT CLAMOR]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[BELL TOLLING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR HONKING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[SOLDIER SPEAKING GERMAN]
[BABY CRYING]
[BRAKES SCREECHING]
[SOLDIERS SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
Your papers. Next!
[SOLDIER SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
Hat off.
[SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
[IN ENGLISH] Oh. I'm sorry, sir.
[IN GERMAN] Sorry?
You Jewish pig! How dare you?
Show me your I.D. card.
[IN ENGLISH] Uh, I'm sorry, sir,
I do not speak German, um...
I'm on my way
to the administration offices.
Get to your feet!
[FINGERS SNAPPING]
JOSEPH: I'm on my way--
Show me your
Kennkarte.
Uh, perhaps you could take it up
with your, um, Untersturmführer?
I can what?
You can kiss my ass,
you piece of shit!
[GUNFIRE]
As you like. [KISSES]
Mm. [SMACKS LIPS]
You didn't.
Is this my deposition or yours?
Yours.
I kissed him, on the cheek.
MICHAEL: Uh-huh.
And ran.
[SOLDIERS LAUGH]
[BYSTANDERS SCREAM]
JOSEPH: Whoa. Sorry, so sorry.
[EXCLAIMS]
Your hat![GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
[IN HEBREW] Crazy.
[PANTS]
NATHANIEL: Joseph...
[GRUNTS]
[IN ENGLISH] Nathaniel,
they stopped me.
[PANTS]
I thought I was a dead man.
You look alive to me, my friend.
Do you have the IDs?
[PANTS, CHUCKLES]
Well done.
Excellent work, thank you.
No, no, no, no, no.
Thank you.
For letting me do this.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
It's healing nicely.
My dear,
why do your waste your time
on someone like me?
If a gentleman
is attractive enough,
it is never a waste
of a lady's time. [CHUCKLES]
Now, you stay off that foot.
Yeah.
And away from trouble.
You keep that hat.
Looks gorgeous on you.
[SIGHS]
[BABY CRYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
BYSTANDER: Shalom, Joseph.
[CHANTING IN HEBREW]
[IN ENGLISH] Hey, hey. Hey!
Mama.
Shabbat Shalom, Joseph.
ABRAHAM: You're late.
You aren't still forging IDs,
are you?
Joseph, I've told you--
CYLA: Hey.
What kind of Shabbat blessing
is that, Abraham?
No, Papa. Just maps.
You can't get into trouble
for that. Not yet.
Anything you do
for the Resistance
can get you in trouble.
Already, half the ghetto
has been deported to work camps.
Stop being such a coward,
Abraham.
Anything this boy can do
to help our people fight back,
you should be proud of him.
This is a family matter.
We may be forced to live
in this small room together,
but you are not family.
You think you are a hero.
As if you should be complemented
for being courageous.
But actually, all you are doing
is risking your life,
and the lives of your family.
I'm just trying
to give people hope.
Exactly how will you do that?
By reminding people that
there are some things
that they can't take from us.
Laughter, joy, our spirits.
And we are not helpless.
These are just men with guns.
Just?
Stop persecuting him, Abraham.
We have Nazis for that.
[EXHALES]
Forgive me for thinking
it's important we keep believing
there's more beyond all this.
[CYLA CHUCKLES]
You have any new movies
to show us?
[BOTH GIGGLE]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
ABRAHAM: No!
[BOTH LAUGH]
Burn it!
These drawings will be
a death sentence for us all!
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
Your fear
is their greatest weapon.
It's the first weapon
that we need to take from them.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR OPENING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
I just want you to know,
I'm very proud of you.
I don't think anyone,
even your father,
could damage your optimism.
Thankfully.
Because hope is in high demand
these days. Hmm?
[KISSES]
[DOOR CLOSING]
[SNORING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[ENGINES RUMBLING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Wake up! Trucks are coming!
Trucks are coming, wake up.
Hurry! Hey!
[ALL CLAMORING]
And what, we should outrun them?
[SOLDIERS SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
[AUTOMATIC GUNFIRE]
[RESIDENTS SCREAMING]
[IN ENGLISH]
Joseph, do what they say.
Do not give them
a reason to harm us.
[SOLDIER SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
Move it or you will be shot!
[INDISTINCT CLAMOR]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[RESIDENTS SCREAMING]
[SPEAKING GERMAN]
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
Hey.
[SOLDIER GRUNTS]
[BELL TOLLING]
[OFFICER SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[PRISONERS GRUNTING]
[REBECCA GRUNTING, PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTS, PANTS]
ALEKSY: [IN ENGLISH]
You pick up the smaller one.
I'll pick up the larger.
[GRUNTS]
ANIA: This is all the bread
I can get today.
Ania, stop.
Everyone is starving.
But, we are all we have left.
I have to do what I can.
Mama would have done the same.
You know that, little brother.
Thank you. What's your name?
My name is Aleksy. And you are?
Joseph.
How did you land
in this lap of misery?
Forgive the obvious,
but you don't exactly blend in.
My father was the wrong color.
Well, how dare he?
[CHUCKLES]
[SOBS INTENSELY]
She's my mom! [SOBS]
[CONTINUES SOBBING]
And what do we have here?
He says it's his mother's grave.
[PRISONER SOBS]
Hmm. Sad.
[GUNSHOT]
[HORSE NEIGHS]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[IN GERMAN]
You two. Take him to the pit.
Back to work!
[IN ENGLISH]
Prisoner number 69084!
You are wanted
by the Kommandant.
Follow me
to the administration office.
That way.
Name?
Uh. Joseph Bau.
Glad to make your acquaintance.
[GUNSHOT]
[HEAVY THUD]
[IN HEBREW]
Blessed is the judge of truth.
GOETH: [IN ENGLISH]
Mietek, get in here! Schnell!
Best to keep your eyes down.
He doesn't usually kill twice
in the same hour.
[CLOCK TICKING]
I can't believe it.
Such a tragedy.
The carpet is ruined.
[CIGARETTE CRACKLING]
Why are you here?
Your new mapmaker, Kommandant.
Hmm. Is that what you are?
JOSEPH: Well, uh...
I have a degree
from the Academy
of Fine Arts in Krakow, uh,
I'm skilled in cartography,
Gothic lettering, drafting--
Hmm.
Gothic lettering?
JOSEPH: Yes, gothic lettering.
That was actually my specialty.
Then you could be of service.
How fortunate. [CHUCKLES]
For you.
Mietek, get me a new carpet.
And a manicurist that knows
how to cut some damn cuticles.
Yes, sir.
[GUNSHOT AND SHOUTING
IN DISTANCE]
[DOOR CLOSING]
MIETEK: Are you all right?
How do you do this?
I try to focus on each moment
as if it's my last.
How does that help you?
[GUNSHOT IN DISTANCE]
[GASPS] Oh!
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[JOSEPH EXHALES]
You really pull some strings.
I wanted to make sure
you had all you needed,
to keep you alive.
Time to put your special
ID forgery talents to good use.
We have an office
where you can work your magic.
Wow. These are brand new.
MIETEK: They are. The best.
[EXCLAIMS]
[MIETEK CHUCKLES]
Nathaniel!
[NATHANIEL CHUCKLES]
This is my brother,
Itzhak Stern.
I told him of your involvement
in the Resistance.
He wanted to meet you.
He's Oskar Schindler's
accountant.
Privilege to meet you.
Who is Oskar Schindler?
[SOLDIER SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
[IN ENGLISH]
I'll let you two talk.
Need to get back to my work
before the guards
come looking for me.
Mind if I join you?
Well I certainly hope
this office meets
my extravagant standards.
I can only do slave labor
for psychopathic monsters
in, uh, a place
of absolute luxury.
[MIETEK CHUCKLES]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[JOSEPH WHISTLES]
Whoa.
Ah, I already see
that I'm going
to have complaints.
I mean, where's my girl?
No fan? No grapes?
I don't know.
Yeah, I may just have to
take it up with the little guy
with the funny moustache
and the tiniest pee-pee
in the known universe.
Yeah, yeah, he holds the record.
If we do our work,
maybe we can survive
this madness
and tell our story.
And the world needs to know.
[JOSEPH INHALES DEEPLY,
EXHALES HEAVILY]
Is it possible
to change my seat?
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[IN HEBREW]
Blessed is the judge of truth.
[BELL TOLLING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
JOSEPH: [IN ENGLISH]
Look what I got here.
I made that for the Kommandant.
I show it to him before he goes
to bed every night.
[ALEKSY CHUCKLING]
JOSEPH: He likes that
and a glass of warm milk.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
Better make a copy
for the Fuhrer,
or he too will be jealous.
JOSEPH: He may be.
[GROUP CHUCKLES]
All right, all right,
give it to me
before you get us all killed.
And the Kommandant,
sometimes he can't go to sleep
at night. So, I help him.
If he's not listening to me
or disobeying, I have no choice.
I bend him over his office desk
and I give him
a nice, good spanking.
[ALL LAUGHING]
And then boom, lights out.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[TRUCK ENGINE STARTING]
And we are where?
We are here, sir.
[DOG WHIMPERS]
But in a certain sense,
where are any of us, really?
Nietzsche.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[GROWLS]
It's time
for your manicure, sir.
GOETH: Yeah, thank God.
Your reports as requested, sir.
[DOG GROWLS, BARKS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOG GROWLS]
[AIR RAID SIREN BLARING]
[NEARBY EXPLOSION]
[RUMBLING]
It's just a drill, right?
JOSEPH: Yes, it's a test.
It's a test to see
if a building explodes
when you drop a missile on it.
[NEARBY EXPLOSION]
[RUMBLING]
[AIR-RAID SIREN
CONTINUES BLARING]
Come on.
Where-- where are we going?
The closest shelter. Not far.
Just stay calm.
[NEARBY EXPLOSION]
[INDISTINCT CLAMOR]
[RESIDENTS SCREAM]
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING, ECHOING]
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING]
Are you okay?
[SIGHS]
Sometimes I feel like my mind
can't tell the difference
between... [SIGHS SHARPLY]
...memories and reality.
I know what you mean.
The good news
is I'll die soon, so...
[CHUCKLES]
...you know, never get old.
You're Austrian, huh?
Yeah.
Why does an Austrian,
such as yourself,
care about us Jews, huh?
[DISTANT WEAPON FIRE]
Well, there's something
I should tell you.
[NEARBY EXPLOSION]
[RESIDENTS SCREAM]
[RESIDENTS CLAMORING]
[ALARM BLARES]
[ANNOUNCER OVER SPEAKER]
Attention, you can now exit
the bomb shelter.
Alive?
MICHAEL: Yes, yes.
[ANNOUNCER SPEAKING IN HEBREW]
[IN ENGLISH] Well,
all good things
must come to an end.
We're done here.
But, I have more to ask--
Goodbye, Michael.
For what it's worth, I like you.
You've got some brains
with a side of balls.
Good luck with your case.
[JOSEPH GROANS SOFTLY]
[GROANS]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
I want a map
of the men's barracks, 52 to 57.
Three copies by tonight.
Uh. But there's no sun.
I need it for the emulsion
to harden.
Perhaps I should find
a new mapmaker?
JOSEPH: No. Absolutely not.
You've already found
the finest mapmaker in the land.
Heh, I might even make four.
Hmm. Get to it.
[SIGHS]
If you nick me...
you're a dead woman.
Yes, Kommandant.
Slower.
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
JOSEPH: You're scary, huh?
You are such a pain in my ass.
[GRUNTS]
All right. Okay. All right.
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
How does this work?
Well, I am waiting
for the sunshine to come out.
Without the sun's rays,
the emulsion won't harden.
And Goeth wants three copies
by evening, naturally.
Looks like you might
have a problem.
Maybe you can be my sunshine?
SOLDIER: What are you doing?
I'm Joseph, by the way.
Hey,
back to the woman's barracks.
Eyes back on your work!
Mapmaker!
A regular Paganini.
Okay, now I'm going
to close my eyes,
and see the future I want.
Oh, no. I'm only seeing black.
Okay.
Oh, no, no, no, not the rabbit.
I was thinking rabbi!
The spirits can't spell.
[GROUP CHUCKLES]
Joseph,
will you make one for me?
Well, obviously,
you're not a Jew.
So, what's your offense?
Let's just say that...
they don't approve
of who I choose to love.
What would you like
your card to be?
I was studying
to be an architect.
Then an architect it is.
[PENCIL SCRIBBLING]
GOETH: Hmm.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
See what you can do
when properly incentivized?
All it takes
is a little Aryan push.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Kommandant.
GOETH: Hmm.
Our new mapmaker
is proving to be
far more industrious
than the previous one.
This Jew here...
this Jew is far more
than just a mapmaker.
He is also a very,
very funny fellow.
We're done.
Thank you, sir.
Listen to me carefully.
That funny little Jew
is proving to be quite useful.
So, if you intend
on disposing of him,
you'd better have
someone equally as talented
to replace him.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I only have a moment. [PANTS]
I spoke with Joseph.
Good.
[SIGHS] He worries me, Itzhak.
He's soft.
He can do the work.
And my brother vouches for him.
That's all I need.
Itzhak...
Listen to me.
Don't mistake soft for weak.
[REBECCA SIGHS]
He's determined.
And he's a genius.
He's eccentric, yes,
but he's an artist.
[SIGHS]
Don't worry about him.
Give him a chance.
[BELL TOLLING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Papa.
[COUGHING]
Hey.
You have to eat. Come on.
[ABRAHAM GROANS]
Come on, you stubborn ox.
Come on.
Hey.
I have a plan, Papa.
There are ways
to get out of here.
I'm going to get you,
and put you--
[SPEAKS POLISH]
[IN ENGLISH] Huh? No plans.
[SNIFFS] Don't you see?
There is no leaving.
None of us will ever escape.
You run around here
handing out false hope,
but the truth is,
all that is left is pain.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANS]
Life in here
is like a chess game.
Except every move is checkmate.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOLDIER SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
[PRISONERS MUTTERING]
SOLDIER: Line up, first row.
[SOLDIER CONTINUES SHOUTING
IN GERMAN]
JOSEPH: [IN ENGLISH] Papa.
I got you.
Thank you.
Come on.
Thank you, son.
JOSEPH: Okay, okay.
[ABRAHAM GROANS]
Okay.
[PANTS, GROANS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[ABRAHAM GRUNTS FAINTLY]
This man is done.
No, please! He's just tired!
He's a strong man, he can work.
Mm, the mapmaker, hmm?
The Kommandant
was just advising me
to take the very best
care of you.
Your father?
Hmm. I see the resemblance.
Why don't you help your father
and pull up his shirt
for me. Hmm?
JOSEPH: No, please.
Whip me instead!
You want me to whip you instead?
I beg of you, please whip me!
Well, since you insist.
No, no. Son!
[JOSEPH GRUNTS,
BREATHES HEAVILY]
Don't worry, I won't touch
your precious hands.
Count in German!
Eins!
Zwei!
[WHIP CRACKING]
JOSEPH:
Drei!
GRUEN: Again!
[WHIP CRACKING]
[JOSEPH GROANING]
GRUEN: Start again!
[WHIP CRACKING]
[GRUEN GRUNTS]
[JOSEPH GROANS]
Herr Kommandant,
I hesitate to even mention this,
but, um...
Yes?
Your mapmaker is currently
being beaten out in the yard.
And I fear we may have
some trouble finding a, uh...
suitable replacement.
[SCREAMS]
GRUEN: Nothing funny to say?
Huh? Tell us a joke,
why don't you.
[GROANS]
GRUEN: I'm sorry. What?
[LAUGHS]
[WHIP CRACKING]
So go deal with it.
Right away, Herr Kommandant.
Schnell!
[ABRAHAM WAILS]
See, you're finally starting
to make me laugh!
[JOSEPH GROANS]
Herr Gruen, the Kommandant
would like to see you
immediately.
GRUEN: Yeah, when I'm done.
No, no! He-- he asks
that you come immediately.
I said when I'm done!
Of course. [BREATHES HEAVILY]
I'll notify the Kommandant.
This isn't finished.
[MEN CHATTERING]
Hello?
[JOSEPH CHUCKLES FAINTLY,
BREATHES SHAKILY]
[GRUNTS] Thank you.
How did you...
My sister works in
the Kommandant's kitchen.
Oh, a chef!
I imagine she turned down
many job offers
at high-end,
fine dining establishments
for this job, huh? Mm, I mean,
who would want to work
anywhere else?
We're also the best
to cook for, you know,
because no matter
what you make us,
it's always the best thing
we've ever had in our lives.
I'm Joseph, by the way.
Michal.
JOSEPH: Hmm.
Nice to meet you.
[GRUNTS]
[PENCIL SCRIBBLING]
[TRUCK ENGINE RUMBLING]
[SOLDIER SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
[BLOWS]
[DOOR CLOSING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
MIETEK: [IN ENGLISH]
How are you?
Not so bad.
It only hurts when I'm awake.
Thank you. For stopping it.
I'm sorry it wasn't sooner.
Um. A new shirt for you.
It's funny,
this is all I can draw now.
This heavenly experience.
Yes, but-- but side-projects
like this put you in danger.
And people are counting
on you now, to help them.
[GROANS] You see, there are only
so many maps to be made.
So, I mentioned
to the Kommandant,
the deteriorating conditions
of the camp signage
and how other camps
have much bigger, better signs.
He ordered me straight to work.
I, uh...
hope you guys
aren't sick of me yet.
Because we're back in business.
[GROANS]
Itzhak!
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHISTLING]
[DOG GROWLS]
JOSEPH: [WHISPERING]
Our little secret.
Yes.
[GROWLS SOFTLY]
[GROWLS, BARKS]
[BARKING]
JOSEPH: Bad dog.
[GROWLS]
[BARKS]
[GROWLS, WHIMPERS]
Ah, it's just a thank you,
for being my sunshine.
Meshuga. [EXHALES]
That was a stupid thing to do.
Strong words
coming from a bread thief.
Did you know that "Rebecca"
means "captivating?"
[SIGHS] Well, I am captive.
You will always be
captivating to me.
They couldn't cage you
if they tried.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[PATRIOTIC GERMAN MUSIC PLAYING]
ALL: Prost!
[SMACKS LIPS]
Oskar, that's so good.
So, you want some more
of my prisoners?
Correct me if I am wrong,
but are you not already
at capacity?
I mean, how many of these people
does it take
to make these pots and pans?
[CHUCKLING]
You'd be surprised, Kommandant.
This demand for new mess kits
is sky high.
GOETH: Hmm.
Hmm.
And we need more workers
to meet it.
And of course,
I would remain grateful.
[CHUCKLES, SNIFFS]
This man loves his wine,
his woman,
but most importantly,
the Fatherland.
ALL: The Fatherland!
GOETH:
Ja.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[LAUGHTER]
Hello.Hi.
Don't forget your food.
Ania.
What would my barracks
do without you?
Thank you.
GOETH: [SHOUTING]
Where is our food? [CHUCKLES]
Go.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER
AND LAUGHTER]
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
[YELPS]
You burned me,
you carless bitch!
[BOWL SHATTERING]
[CUTLERY CLATTERING]
[BOWL SHATTERS]
[GASPS]
I'm so sorry, sir,
I didn't mean to--
I'll get a cloth.
Go.
No.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
My apologies about that.
Amon, she's just a servant.
I'm sure
she did not intend to...
GOETH: No, no, no, Oskar,
one only gets so many chances.
[SCREAMS]
[SOBBING]
[HEAVY THUD]
Mm-hmm.
No!
[GRUNTS]
[HEAVY THUDS]
[SOBS]
[HEAVY THUDS CONTINUE]
[GRUNTS]
[REBECCA SOBS]
You must try the sauerkraut.
My loyal Gruen.
Why don't you go
clean yourself up?
Danke.
Oh!
I had a thought.
I want your opinion
on something.
Mapmaker!
[FINGERS SNAPPING]
Where are my posters?
What do you think
about putting up a dozen
of these around
your Emalia factory?
They are very...
striking.
Oh, the typhus. Was my idea.
It's a very under-reported
but significant element
of the Jewish problem.
Hmm.
Striking and informative. Bravo.
I can guarantee five dozen
of these works of art
to be exhibited at Emalia
if you can guarantee my workers.
Oskar,
you drive a very hard bargain.
[CHUCKLES]
Are you sure
you're not half Jew?
[LAUGHS]
Five dozen. Danke.
Please, sit.
OSKAR: So, the opera tonight.
[SOLDIER SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHISTLES TUNE]
[IN ENGLISH] Hey.
You couldn't have saved her.
You don't know that. [GASPS]
We should have fought back.
I should have killed that man.
Even if you had killed him,
you would have never made it out
of that house alive.
I want you to live.
I need you to.
Why? Huh?
[BELL TOLLING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAN SNORING]
[CHANTING IN HEBREW]
GROUP: Amen.
[BELL TOLLING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[SOBS]
[WOMEN MUTTERING]
[IN ENGLISH]
He's going to do it.
He's got that look in his eyes.
[SOBS]
[REBECCA GASPS]
[MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBS]
[WHISTLING TUNE]
That should do it. [GRUNTS]
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS] Hey.
Would you do me a favor
and just hold this for me?
There we go.
Thank you. Okay.
[WHISTLING TUNE]
That's a good idea,
use your foot instead. There.
What is he doing?
JOSEPH: Thank you again
for that bread the other night.
After the whipping...
the pain was unbearable.
But you know what they say,
time is the best doctor.
Of course, I always say,
how can he be such a good doctor
when he kills
all of his patients?
[SOBS]
JOSEPH:
Well, that's not entirely true,
sometimes he tortures
and gives them diarrhea.
Has Nazis whip our asses
into Swiss cheese.
No laugh
at the Swiss cheese, huh?
Oh, now I see.
You don't want them
to waste the bullet on you.
That's very considerate, Michal.
They killed my sister over soup!
I know.
I was there.
And I'm sorry.
[SOBS]
Now, imagine.
If that fence wasn't there,
where would you go?
What would you do?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFLES, SOBS]
Would you be a baker?
No!
You give away your bread.
[CLICKS TONGUE] You'd go broke.
Or maybe, hmm...
A pole vaulter?
I don't know.
If you could do that,
you would have cleared
the fence a long time ago.
No.
[SOBS]
Or maybe... [SNIFFS]
...it's something else.
What do you want,
more than anything?
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Revenge.
JOSEPH: Wow, revenge!
Now there's
a worthwhile pursuit.
But... why don't we call it
justice?
If you want justice...
you're going to have to survive.
And once we get out of here,
I'll make your first
business cards free of charge.
Although tips in bread
are always appreciated.
Don't let them win, Michal.
Don't let them win.
Can I see a smile?
There it is.
Who is he?
His name is Joseph.
You are a gift from God.
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
Nonsense.
I am just happy to be of use.
[WOMAN MOANS SOFTLY]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Third down, on the right.
WOMAN: Oh, good. [MOANS SOFTLY]
[ROMANTIC QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[IN HIGH-PITCHED VOICE]
Oh, may I be next?
[REBECCA GASPS]
What are you doing here?
If they catch you here,
they'll kill you.
But I'm in disguise.
What, you don't think
I can pass for a woman?
Too handsome?
[SIGHS] That is not the point.
I'm sorry, I had to see you.
Please. I'm already here.
Give me just five minutes,
please.
I'll massage your feet.
[CHUCKLES]
My feet?
Are you out of your mind?
Yes!
[GROUP GIGGLES]
If not for me,
then for your arches, huh?
[SIGHS]
Five minutes.
We'll see how enamored
you are with me,
after you take off my shoes.
[JOSEPH BREATHES DEEPLY]
This is going to take
a lot longer than five minutes.
Oh!
No. I'm just kid-- Ah! Hey.
They're beautiful.
[LAUGHS]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
REBECCA: You really are crazy.
[SNIFFS]
I saw what you did.
You saved Michal's life.
All I did was show
a confused boy a drawing.
It was much more than that.
Please, you're distracting me
from my work.
I only have
a few minutes left, huh?
[GIGGLES]
Tell me your story.
I want to know you,
I want to know everything
about you.
Everything?
You only have four minutes left.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Well...
actually...
I'm a nurse.
Or I was one in the ghetto.
Now all I do is nails.
No, you do much more than that.
I see you.
You take care of everybody.
I do what I can
with what I have.
But who takes care of you?
Time's up.
Next time.
[WOMEN GIGGLE]
[ALL LAUGH]
[BELL TOLLING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Mama! How are you?
Still here. How is your father?
JOSEPH: Still Father.
Mama, I've met a woman!
The most wonderful woman!
Only you, Joseph could find
something like that
in a place like this. [CHUCKLES]
Move it along.
[CUTLERY CLATTERING]
JOSEPH: Hey.
Thank you.
For Rebecca.
[ROMANTIC QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[DYTA WHISTLES]
A date? In here? [LAUGHS]
Are you going to go?
[SIGHS] I don't know.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
I've nothing to wear.
[CHUCKLES]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
SOLDIER: [IN GERMAN]
Inspections!
Get away from your desks.
[JOSEPH SIGHS]
[SOLDIER SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
[IN ENGLISH] Good, good, yes.
Excellent.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[ITZHAK CLEARS THROAT]
[CHUCKLES]
Afternoon, Mietek.
Good afternoon, sir.
Careful there. Precious cargo.
He will be back soon.
Itzhak.
Oskar, have you met Mr. Bau?
OSKAR: Not formally.
Oskar Schindler.
Very familiar with your work.
Yes.
But have you seen his latest?
Ah.
Excellent.
You have all the makings
of a master criminal, Mr. Bau.
Have you heard?
They want to shut down Emalia.
They're closing all factories
that don't contribute
to the war effort.
Yeah. Who needs enamelware
anyway, hmm?
Restaurants without customers?
Munitions,
that's where the gold is.
A booming business.
I'm scouting in Czechoslovakia.
[SOLDIER SPEAKING GERMAN]
[OSKAR CLEARS THROAT, SNIFFS]
Heil Hitler.
So, my friend,
what do we have today?
OSKAR: Oh, nothing much.
A few bottles
of Château Lafite Rothschild
and some beluga caviar
from the Adriatic.
My favorite, Oskar. [CHUCKLES]
You never cease to amaze me.
Two glasses, schnell. Come.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Who is this Oskar Schindler?
How can you trust him?
The man has saved
hundreds of our people.
He's convinced the Nazis
to use us as free labor
in his factory.
Everybody wins. Nobody dies.
I make a list
of prisoners for Schindler.
He asks Goeth
to re-assign them as workers.
[SHUSHES] Let's just say,
God has given us a goy messiah.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CORK POPS]
JOSEPH: If Schindler
gets his workers for his factory
with Goeth's approval,
what's with all the forgeries
I'm creating?
There's danger
in knowing too much.
Oh, well, I'd hate to be
in danger.
The Resistance
is quite creative.
The system with Oskar
is just part of the plan.
Weekly, Goeth signs off
on a separate list
of prisoners to be executed.
Our inside man
who works closely to Goeth
provides us a copy
of this list.
The execution list
from the inside man
is given to Goeth's prostitute.
WOMAN: Oh!
MIETEK:
She gets the list
to the gardener.
The gardener passes the list
to a Resistance member
in the Krakow morgue.
He then finds IDs
from recently deceased
non-Jewish families
that can be forged to match
the names on the list.
He gets those IDs
back to the gardener, who then--
Hands them to me.
I get them to you,
and you work your magic.
MIETEK:
And then they're smuggled out
before they are executed.
So, this inside man
whose copying this list
from inside Goeth's villa
must be very good.
She certainly is.
Goeth keeps a copy of the list
sitting on his desk
in the same spot every week.
He likes to review it,
as he has his nails done.
But-- No!
If he ever saw her doing this...
Everyone puts their life
on the line
for the greater cause.
[GUNSHOTS]
It's time we go. Come.
[SOLDIER LAUGHING]
[BELL TOLLING]
So, tell us, what's it like
in the administration building?
Oh, it's rough boys.
It's not all caviar
and foie gras.
We also have lobster pâté.
That's only on Wednesdays.
No!
Yeah.
Who do these sauerkraut
servants think they are, huh?
[ALL LAUGH]
[JOSEPH GRUNTS]
One has to watch
these Nazis like a hawk.
I'm not sure what it is
about them yet,
but I don't believe
they can entirely be trusted!
[LAUGHS]
[IN GERMAN] Back to work.
Faster!
[IN ENGLISH] You going let him
talk to you like that?
Oh, the talking down I'm going
to give that man later.
Nathaniel,
he's going to be so scared,
his balls are going to be
in his throat.
He's going to have
three Adam's apples, a bushel.
I'll do it later in private.
I find that when I publicly
humiliate this one,
he starts to think
we're in a relationship.
And I'm just not ready
for that kind of commitment.
[ALL LAUGH]
So, you know him, then?
I do. [SNIFFS] He's Franz Gruen.
You stay away from him.
[MEN SNORING]
[DOOR RATTLING]
[IN GERMAN] Everybody up!
Outside! Let's go!
[IN ENGLISH] All of you, up!
Come on!
[SOLDIERS SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
SOLDIER: [IN ENGLISH]
Get in there!
[SOLDIERS SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
[PIPES RUMBLING]
[GENTLE ORCHESTRA MUSIC PLAYING]
[OPERA SINGER SINGING IN GERMAN]
[INAUDIBLE]
[OPERA SINGER CONTINUES SINGING]
[PIPES RATTLING]
[MEN SCREAM]
[IN ENGLISH] You Jews,
always complaining!
Do your friends
find you funny now? Hot?
[MEN SCREAM]
[IN GERMAN]
Are you cold, Jew? You pigs!
[IN ENGLISH] Aleksy. Do you know
why they're doing this?
I don't think
they need a reason.
Next time, we'll vacation
in the tropics, okay?
[LAUGHS]
[OPERA SINGER CONTINUES SINGING]
I've always told you
to play by the rules,
but look where
this has brought us.
I should have seen this coming.
I should have protected you.
I'm your father, it's my job
to pr-- Protect you.
Papa, you were trying
to protect your family.
I am the one
who should be sorry.
[CONTINUES SINGING]
You've always played
by your own rules, Joseph.
And I think that has frightened
me for a long time.
But it doesn't anymore.
And I am so, so proud of you.
[CONTINUES SINGING]
[APPLAUSE]
Bravo!
[APPLAUSE CONTINUES]
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
[DOG HOWLING]
[AIRPLANE ENGINE RUMBLING]
[GUNFIRE IN DISTANCE]
[WHISTLES TUNE]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
I thought you'd stood me up.
I would never.
You were in the barracks,
the one they kept out all night.
I heard about it. [KISSES]
[JOSEPH SIGHS]
I'm sorry to postpone our date.
I really don't like being cold.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
You're warm now, yes?
Yeah, definitely getting warmer.
I should go.
JOSEPH: Wait.
[SIGHS]
ITZHAK: [CLEARS THROAT]
Joseph...
Do you have those maps
for the Kommandant?
[PANTS]
[SOLDIER SPEAKING GERMAN]
[IN ENGLISH]
Why were you torturing
my mapmaker?
You forced him to stay
in the cold overnight.
Are you that stupid?
What if you had killed him?
How am I supposed to build
a work camp without maps?
He was disrespecting me.
You dare speak back to me?
I don't care what he was doing.
Don't forget your place here.
I picked you up
from the gutter,
when you were
just a lowly boxer,
getting beaten for a living!
Now, you get to do the beating.
When I say so.
Do you understand?
Nod, you stupid boy.
What's that?
On your cheek?
Are you crying?
[LAUGHING] Pathetic!
Stop crying!
Leave.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[BELL TOLLING]
[MEN LAUGHING]
Looks like you.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Give that to me.
ABRAHAM: No.
This is mine. I drew this.
No?
Herr Gruen! That's a lie,
you know this is my work.
A lying Jew? Hmm. [TUT-TUTS]
If he says it's his drawing,
then I believe him.
So...
It's your drawing?
ABRAHAM: Yes.
JOSEPH: Papa, please!
Shh.
You swear on it?
Yes, I swear on it.
Well...
I'm very sorry about this.
[GUN COCKING]
[LOUD THUD]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Papa. [SOBS] Papa.
[SNIFFLES] Mama...
It's all my fault.
[SOBS]
The very thing he begged me
not to do over and over
is how I killed him.
[CYLA SOBS]
I never should have...
You know you did not do this.
You did not kill him.
You don't bear
any of these sins. No.
[SOBBING] There is no logic
in why anything happens anymore.
Dear, dear God,
why have you done this to us?
[SOBS]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TRUCK ENGINE RUMBLING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
There is something
you need to see.
Liquidation?
The entire camp.
But it is not confirmed.
And so far,
it's just a recommendation.
Oskar knows?
Yes.
Yeah?
[DOOR HANDLE RATTLING]
You.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
"Making the world
a purer... place."
It should be race.
"Making the world
a purer... race"!
[SHOUTING] No?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes, Herr.
You're right,
"a purer race" is much better.
I'll fix it immediately.
Did I say that you can go?
[CLOCK TICKING]
I could kill you right now,
sit down and finish my tea,
and nobody would even care.
The usual, Kommandant?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Today...
is your lucky day.
[TELEPHONE CONTINUES RINGING]
Out!
Ja,
what?
In two weeks, the whole camp?
And how do you suggest
I do that?
It's impossible.
[BELL TOLLING]
He's there.
That way.
I'm sorry about your father.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
JOSEPH: All I can think is,
I can't lose you, too.
This nightmare...
I don't know how to stop it.
REBECCA: But you do.
You do.
You...
You are the magician.
Dream-maker.
The one we all look to for hope.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Whenever a heart has gone cold,
you have brought it
back to life.
I know because...
you did it for me.
Don't let them
take that from you.
What if it's already gone?
What if it was never
real to begin with,
and I was just fooling myself?
Well, you fooled me, too.
So, keep pretending.
In here, we are free.
You taught me that.
[GENTLE VIOLIN MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you hear that?
Are those violins?
Shall we dance?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
Four? You said three!
No. I changed my mind.
It's now four.
[SIGHS] It's a good thing
I hate eating.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
Rebecca Tennenbaum.
However long forever is,
share it with me.
[LAUGHS]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS, GIGGLES]
I still think
you're a crazy person.
Warn me if that ever changes.
[LAUGHS]
I'm afraid it's going
to be a very short engagement.
In fact, I have already
sent out the invitations.
[WOMAN SQUEALING, GIGGLING]
REBECCA: Cyla! [LAUGHS]
[CYLA GRUNTS SOFTLY]
A woman?
Rabbi would have
a harder time sneaking in.
You know,
he's not as pretty as me.
[REBECCA LAUGHS]
[CHANTING IN HEBREW]
[SPEAKING HEBREW]
[LAUGHS]
[CLEARS THROAT, SNIFFS]
[SPEAKING HEBREW]
JOSEPH: [IN ENGLISH] Okay.
Shh.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[WOMEN LAUGH, CHEER]
[LAUGHS]
[EXCITED CHATTER]
[ALL GIGGLING]
ALICJA: It's a nice reminder.
That even in here,
you can still find love.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Well, maybe not you.
[WOMEN SNORING]
[ALARM BUZZING]
[WOMEN GASPING]
Roll call. At this hour?
If I'm not at line up...
Then go.
[INDISTINCT CLAMOR]
Your scarf.
[PANTING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOLDIERS SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
[DOGS BARKING]
[ALARM CONTINUES BUZZING]
[SOLDIER SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
[SOLDIERS SPEAKING GERMAN]
[SOLDIER LAUGHING]
[IN ENGLISH] Well?
Where are they?
What?
You have my sign posts, yes?
What sign posts?
Well, I've been waiting,
I was told that someone
was bringing me posts
to hang these signs
around the women's barracks.
What signs?
For the cholera outbreak.
The smell by the women's
latrines is truly horrifying.
A mass case
of explosive diarrhea, like...
Like a bomb went off.
Well, that's your job,
you handle it.
Go!
Yes, sir.
SOLDIER: Go, go, go!
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
Did you do it?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
A wedding? I can't believe it!
JOSEPH: Itzhak! Hey.
Eh, so, what's next?
More IDs?
I'm afraid the time
for that is over.
What's happening?
ITZHAK: The liquidation
is to proceed.
Mietek has seen memos
to confirm.
They plan to leave
no trace for the Russians.
[SIGHS]
What does that mean for us?
Extermination.
Most of us are being sent
to Auschwitz almost immediately.
The lucky ones
will go with Schindler
to his factory in Brünnlitz.
There must be more
that we can do.
There must!
Let's think about that once
you get to Schindler's factory.
Rebecca, she has to get
sent to the factory.
We have to get her on that list.
And my mother.
I cannot.
I can't add any more names.
The total number is final.
I'm sorry.
[PANTS, HESITATES] Itzhak!
Then let me
take their place for them.
Take them instead of me.
I'll be your inside man
at Auschwitz.
Please! Help them.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
I will see what I can do.
And Joseph, uh...
mazel tov on your wedding.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
We don't encounter
much good news around here,
so when we do, it's...
it gets around quick.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOOTSTEPS DEPARTING]
[DOOR OPENING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What do you think you're doing?
I'm only setting up, Kommandant.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS, BREATHES HEAVILY]
You think I don't see you
always looking around?
Everywhere, like a little rat
looking for some cheese.
Perhaps you found some?
[WHIMPERS]
Do you know what this is?
[SHOUTING] Do you?
No.
These people will be sent
to a factory,
where they will work
for the Reich.
[LAUGHS]
You should be happy for them.
Why are you looking
at this list?
No reason, Kommandant.
My eyes just fell on it.
I meant no harm.
Traitor!
[SCREAMS]
You Jews are all the same.
So scared all the time.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
But you are not
my problem anymore!
[SHOUTING] Get out!
[YELPS]
[DOOR CLOSING]
Joseph isn't here.
I came to speak with you.
Why is my name
on Schindler's list
and not Joseph's?
He made you change it.
To save me.
Change it back.
ITZHAK: Rebecca, please--
You have to, Itzhak.
And you know it.
He's far more valuable
to the Resistance than I am.
Look, I don't want--
He will be angry with you,
worried for me.
But that means nothing
next to the hundreds
of people he can help.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
That is our mission.
Not to save one life.
To save hundreds. Thousands.
I'm a survivor.
I'll find a way.
[SNIFFLING]
[SIGHS]
Take care of him for me.
Tell him nothing.
[EXPLOSIONS]
[BOMB WHISTLING]
[GUNFIRE]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXPLOSION]
SOLDIER:
[OVER SPEAKER, IN GERMAN]
All prisoners report
to the train platform
immediately.
Ah, don't you look pretty?
[SOLDIERS SPEAKING GERMAN,
LAUGHING]
[SOLDIER GRUNTS]
[DOG BARKING]
[INDISTINCT CLAMOR]
[GROANS]
SOLDIER: [OVER SPEAKER]
Passengers to Auschwitz,
go to platform four.
All other passengers
go to platform three.
[IN ENGLISH] Out!
[TRAIN HORN BLOWING]
[SOLDIERS SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[WHISTLES TUNE]
Rebecca.
Joseph? Joseph...
Joseph.
JOSEPH: Rebecca.
[SOBS] Joseph.
JOSEPH: [IN ENGLISH] My love.
I'll be okay, I promise.
I wrote this for you.
I'll find you. No matter what.
I love you.
This one is mine.
Where did you think
you were going?
I love you!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's go.
I specifically asked
the Kommandant
to let me give you
a special goodbye.
He forbid it.
Now he is not here
to stop me, is he?
[ITZHAK SHOUTING]
This one is on the list
for Schindler's factory.
What is that?
Give that to me.
You've made a mistake!
Take her instead of me.
Rebecca!
ITZHAK: This is what she wanted!
[INDISTINCT CLAMOR]
[TRAIN HORN BLOWING]
[INDISTINCT CLAMOR CONTINUES]
[SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
JOSEPH: [IN ENGLISH]
I measured your figure
with my own,
counted your eyelashes
with the tip of my tongue.
And hungering for you,
recited your virtues
from memory.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLOCK BELL DINGING]
[TRAFFIC RUMBLING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[SEAGULL SQUAWKING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
SAUL: Good to see you,
my friend.
JOSEPH: Ah.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
SAUL: Please.
[JOSEPH GROANS]
SAUL: Well,
did you bring me anything?
[SIGHS]
Great.
This should see our friends
safely into Argentina.
And the Russian ones?
They're coming. I'm...
I'm sorry, I just...
I've had a lot
on my mind lately.
Anything you'd like
to talk about?
Uh... I'm fine.
You know, Joseph, I may come
across as an ungrateful sod,
but the agency values you
and your work immensely.
So, have you decided
if you're going to testify?
Nothing gets past the Mossad.
Testify, you mean...
What's the good in this, huh?
I mean, it's not going
to bring anybody back.
It's not about going back,
it's about moving forward.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[JET ENGINES ROARING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MACHINERY WHIRRING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[MACHINERY CREAKING]
OSKAR: Joseph.
When will the next set
of documents be ready?
Oskar.
What is happening at Auschwitz?
[HESITATES]
Nothing is confirmed.
All I know is that
the Allies are gaining ground,
and the Reich continues
to demand all evidence
of the camps be destroyed.
They hung Goeth.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
[ECHOING THUD]
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
[OSKAR EXHALES]
The Nazis found a warehouse full
of prisoner property.
Never a good idea to steal
from the Reich.
But what have you heard
about Auschwitz?
There must be survivors, right?
Very little from Auschwitz
has ever been reported.
But what is that little?
You're asking a question
to which you already
know the answer.
They're just rumors.
[SIGHS]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
An old friend...
from Goeth's warehouse.
GRUEN: Give that to me!
Never give up.
Miracles do happen.
[ALARM BUZZES]
SOLDIER:
[OVER SPEAKER, IN GERMAN]
Attention!
All prisoners report
to Schindler's factory.
[ALARM CONTINUES BUZZING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[SOLDIER CONTINUES MAKING
ANNOUNCEMENT OVER SPEAKER]
MIETEK: [IN ENGLISH]
Psst, psst, Itzhak, Joseph.
Germany has surrendered!
The war is over?
What... what does that mean?
It means we survived.
The Fatherland has surrendered.
This telegram confirms it.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
There's no reason for you
to die in a Russian prison camp
or to be tortured to suffer
an agonizing death?
No, your best bet
is to flee, quickly.
Go! Don't worry,
I won't report you for running,
you can count on that. Go.
The rest of the telegram
instructed him to exterminate
all the Jews in this building.
What a pity they left
before I could finish.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PRISONERS CHEERING, LAUGHING]
Oskar. What will you do?
I'll have to flee, too,
of course.
But this moment isn't about me.
Now, is a time for celebration.
[CHUCKLES]
To freedom.
[CORK POPS]
[PRISONERS LAUGHING, CHEERING]
OSKAR: To freedom!
So... we can go?
Just like that?
Yes.
We're free to go, Joseph.
We can do as we please.
Well, then I must see you later,
dear friends.
[CHUCKLES]
[TRAIN CHUGGING]
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
[DRAMATIC SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
WORKER: Who are you looking for?
Um, an Auschwitz survivor.
Tennenbaum.
Rebecca Tennenbaum.
Maybe Rebecca Bau.
Are you certain
she was sent to Auschwitz?
Uh, in '44.
I don't know the month.
There is no record of her.
JOSEPH: Are you sure?
For either name.
I'm sorry.
DYTA: Joseph?
Dyta! [CHUCKLES]
[DYTA CHUCKLES]
Where is she?
Uh, um, before the camps
were liberated,
a... a number of us were moved
from Auschwitz to Lichtewerden.
The Nazis were trying to stay
ahead of the Allies. But...
eventually, they got too close
and... most of the Nazis fled.
Rebecca and I escaped,
on a wagon outside Silesia.
But... uh...
Th... There was an accident.
The wagon flipped.
[SIGHS]
And... I was thrown clear but...
Rebecca, she, uh...
was trapped underneath, and...
I ran for help,
but it was so dark,
and I couldn't find
my way back to her.
I just left her there.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
I am so sorry, Joseph.
I am so sorry!
And my mother?
I'm sorry.
JOSEPH: I'll keep looking
for Rebecca, no matter what.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
JOSEPH: Rebecca,
Rebecca Tennenbaum.
No.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Try upstairs.
[SHOUTING] Rebecca?
Rebecca Tennenbaum?
Rebecca Bau?
Rebecca.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
GRUEN:
This Jew is far more
than just a mapmaker.
This one is mine!
JOSEPH: Rebecca!
[BELL TOLLING]
KARL: Mr. Bau.
I'm Karl Richter.
I am lead counsel
for the defendant.
I would like to say, that I am
an admirer of your work.
And that I'm sorry
for your loss during the war.
Losses.
I see the anger.
There is no reason
to direct this at me.
Don't you believe every accused
party deserves a defense?
Go to Plaszow prison camp
in 1943
and ask the same question.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[ECHOING THUDS]
GRUEN: [ECHOING]
Nothing funny to say?
GRUEN:
I said start again!
[WHIP CRACKING]
[JOSEPH GROANING, ECHOING]
Herr Richter.
[MUSIC FADES]
Enjoying a chat with my witness?
Hardly a chat, Counselor.
Only a courtesy.
See you on the stand.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Would you like
to run through anything?
No.
No run-throughs. [GROANS]
No practices, no advice.
No encouragement.
I will say what I will say.
And that will be that.
MICHAEL:
You know, there's
something I've been meaning
to say to you.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Justice.
You're not here because of me.
I'm here because of you.
Michal?
[CHUCKLES]
You gave me a future.
JOSEPH: No.
I merely reminded you
it was there.
[CHUCKLES]
Wow.
To justice.
Now, let's show some balls.
[MUSIC FADES]
KARL: So, you didn't actually
see the defendant
strike Ania Wancowski.
I heard him beat her to death.
KARL: But you didn't
see it happen.
[ANIA SCREAMING, ECHOING]
The sounds were horrible.
Unmistakable.
[ANIA CONTINUES SCREAMING]
Do you know of anyone else
who might have seen it happen?
I was right there.
I know what happened.
KARL: And yet
you didn't see anything.
Is it not possible,
that your traumatic experiences
in the camp...
of which I'm sure
there were many,
has left your memories
a bit unreliable?
[HIGH-PITCHED RINGING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Is it not the case
that certain medical records
state that you suffer
from shell shock.
[WHIP CRACKING]
[GROANS]
KARL: [ECHOING]
A form of mental illness?
[EERIE SCREECH]
GOETH: [ECHOING]
I could kill you, right now,
and nobody would even care.
[ECHOING EXPLOSION]
KARL: You don't think that
affects your memory at all?
You are the magician.
In here, we are free.
Don't let them
take that from you.
I know this is difficult,
Mr. Bau, to revisit the losses
you suffered in the war.
I can imagine
the trauma that comes
with losing
a close family member.
How that... disturbs the mind.
Objection. Is...
is there a question here?
Get to the point,
Herr Richter.
Mr. Bau.
To your knowledge,
did your counsel suffer the loss
of a family
member during the war?
Yes. His sister.
Ania Wancowski.
The victim who you accused
my client of murdering.
So much loss.
So much suffering.
And only one Nazi official here
to blame.
Is it not natural instinct,
Mr. Bau,
to place your rage on him?
Well...
he has earned it.
[CHUCKLES]
KARL: You believe
the defendant is guilty
of horrible, repeatable crimes.
I do.
Do you hate him?
And yet you are so calm
and unemotional
in your demeanor. Why?
Because your client
doesn't scare me anymore.
To what are you referring?
Ask your client. He'll remember.
KARL: Remember what, Mr. Bau?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
The moment of my revenge.
Shall I elaborate?
Not at this time.
Reserve the right to re-cross,
Your Honor.
Your Honor,
I request a brief recess.
No, keep going. Talk to me.
Actually, uh, permission
to redirect, Your Honor.
Granted.
[MICHAEL CLEARS THROAT]
Mr. Bau...
have you ever actually seen
the defendant kill a person?
Yes.
He killed my father
right in front of me.
[AUDIENCE GASPING]
Would you be
all right describing
that experience for us?
I would.
The inciting incident
is actually quite amazing.
Amazing?
JOSEPH: Yes.
I'm an artist, so in the camp
I would occasionally
draw cartoons
for the other prisoners,
you know,
to keep up their spirits.
MICHAEL: Oh, cartoons?
Yes, mostly drawings
depicting the humiliation
of Nazi guards in various ways.
And since the defendant
was the most laughable
of the guards, by far,
he was frequently the object,
victim of our ridicule
and mockery.
MICHAEL: Mockery as to what?
Oh, his lack
of intelligence, mostly.
And his pitiful desperation
to impress superior officers.
Yeah,
principally Kommandant Goeth.
[AUDIENCE CHUCKLING]
Gruen was obsessed with seeking
the Kommandant's approval,
a task which he was never able
to accomplish.
That day, I had drawn
an especially accurate,
detailed rendering
of the defendant's face
on a roll of toilet paper.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
JUDGE: Order!
Actually, it was of Hitler.
The defendant
will remain silent.
JOSEPH: I had shown the drawing
to dozens of prisoners already,
to an extraordinary reception.
You'd think I had painted
the Mona Lisa.
But do you know
who loved it most of all?
Kommandant Goeth.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
I had shown it to the Kommandant
earlier that day.
Uh, I was his mapmaker, you see,
and so I had a lot of close,
personal contact with him.
We considered
each other friends.
[SCOFFS]
JOSEPH: He complained to me
often about Gruen.
When I showed him
this toilet paper masterpiece,
he found it
particularly amusing.
He actually asked me
to make copies for him,
one to keep,
and a number of extras,
which he said he wanted
to "give out to his friends."
I... I remember very clearly,
as I was leaving the room,
the Kommandant looked at
the drawing
and he said, laughing...
[IN GERMAN ACCENT]
"Right where he belongs."
"That piece of shit."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
JUDGE: Order.
Objection!
[GAVEL BANGING]
The witness
is provoking my client.
Overruled.
Would that be the, uh,
"Moment of revenge"
to which you referred?
Oh, no. Not even close.
It was a prelude.
Later on that day,
I was walking with my father,
and as I was showing him
the drawing it dropped.
The defendant
saw it on the ground.
The defendant was quite familiar
with my art
and knew it was my work.
But my sweet father
shouted that he had drawn it,
wanting to protect me.
But... didn't work.
No.
The defendant pulled
out his Luger...
and he said something
he must have felt was witty,
because he laughed.
But my father...
My poor father...
who had kept me
safe all my life.
Please. Papa, please.
Shh.
And?
Then he shot him in the face.
[AUDIENCE GASPING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[OSKAR EXHALES SHARPLY]
But then...
came the moment.
Do you want to tell this part,
Franz, or should I?
[GAVEL BANGS]
Witness shall direct comments
only to counsel.
What happened next, Mr. Bau?
Well, in a rage,
I threw myself at Gruen.
My body slammed into the gun,
he let go,
I grabbed it and smashed it
across his face!
You cannot possibly
believe this!
Order!
JOSEPH: I yanked his arm
with all my might
and he toppled off the horse.
Lies. This is a lie!
[GAVEL BANGS]
He was sprawled out in the snow,
and all the men were shouting,
"Kill him, kill him!"
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
And I crushed the gun
against his ear,
right here! Right here!
You filthy lying Jew!
You stop this now!
Defendant will be held
in contempt of court
if there is one more outburst.
And a little blood
let out into the snow.
And I will never, never forget
the look in that man's eyes.
And what was that look?
Terror. Absolute terror.
I pistol whipped him again
against the side of the face,
and all the men
were around me screaming,
"Kill him! Kill him!"
And I put the muzzle
right in his eye,
and he was begging
for his life, crying,
tears running down his cheeks!
Whimpering and shaking
like a scared dog!
And I yelled at him, "I'm going
to shoot your face off!"
"This is how you die,
pleading for mercy,
helpless and alone,
beaten by the righteous hand
of a Jew!"
You lying kike!
Franz Gruen, sit down!
You begged for mercy!
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
I shot your weak, useless father
right in front of you!
There it is.
You weak Nazi coward.
I may be just one,
but I'm representing
six million more of these.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
I should have killed you
when I had the chance.
I was a patriot!
Following orders.
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
I was... a patriot.
Guards, get this man out
of my courtroom immediately.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
The witness is excused.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[WHISTLES TUNE]
[BIRD CHIRPING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[WHISTLES TUNE]
[DISTANT WHISTLED TUNE]
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SHOUTING] Rebecca?
Keep whistling!
Rebecca?
[WHISTLES TUNE] Rebecca?
Rebecca!
[WHISTLES] Rebecca?
Where are you?
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[WHISTLES TUNE]
Rebecca?
[MUSIC SWELLS]
[REBECCA SOBS]
[SOBBING] It's you!
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
That was quite impressive,
Mr. Bau.
Big talk for such a small man.
I've learned from the best.
[CHUCKLES]
You've always been my sunshine.
I know a nice little cafe
just around the corner,
they serve, uh,
a marvelous cherry brandy.
I hope it's kosher.
OSKAR: Of course it's kosher!
Sounds great.
And the one thing
I could never forget?
What is that?
Nazis...
they can't take a joke.
Mm-hmm.
[TROLLEY BELL RINGING]
[GENTLE VIOLIN MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey. Can you hear it?
What?
Violins.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
JOSEPH: May I have this dance?
["HOW EVER LONG FOREVER IS"
PLAYING]
♪ You are a long time coming ♪
♪ I had given up hope ♪
♪ Lost the only thing
Left to hold ♪
♪ We were so tired of running
♪ But the path never led ♪
♪ To each other's doorstep ♪
♪ You gave me your hand
Mine started shaking ♪
♪ The love that you offered
♪ Our story was over
Time and again ♪
♪ Life was so fragile
But you never bent ♪
♪ Every time they tried
To fold us ♪
♪ You were reaching out
To hold us ♪
♪ Nothing's ever
Keeping us apart ♪
♪ If I'd turn around
And asked you ♪
♪ How long could you love me?
You'd say ♪
♪ However
♪ However long forever is
♪ However long forever
♪ Forever is ♪
♪ It was a long cold winter
♪ But we weathered the storm
And we danced in the rain ♪
♪ Now we made it to summer
♪ Every kiss heals the cracks
From a lingering past ♪
♪ Every memory that holds us
♪ All the pain
Can never fold us ♪
♪ Nothing's ever
Keeping us apart ♪
♪ If I'd turn around
And ask you ♪
♪ How long could you love me? ♪
♪ You'd say ♪
♪ However
♪ However long forever is ♪
♪ However long forever
♪ Forever is ♪
♪ If you could have told me
♪ You would be
Holding me tonight ♪
♪ I can't believe it
Now that I see ♪
♪ How long have we got? ♪
♪ However
♪ However long forever is ♪
♪ However long forever
♪ Forever is
♪ However
♪ However long forever is
♪ Whoa
♪ However ♪
♪ However long forever ♪
♪ Forever is ♪
[SONG CONCLUDES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]