[whimsical theme song playing]
[whimsical theme song continues]
[twinkling chime]
-[air hissing]
-[ball pops]
[whimsical theme song continues]
[song concludes]
[fox squealing]
NO TAIL TO TELL
-[twinkling chime]
-Sis, I found a way!
It's going to take some time,
but I found a way for you to turn back
into a nine-tailed fox.
-[tense music playing]
-Okay, let's talk about it later.
That means he can
go back to his life too, right?
[inhales sharply]
Wait a second.
What are you guys talking about?
Woo-seok, the thing is--
Turning back into a nine-tailed fox?
[sighs]
Then that means…
[music rises]
You weren't
actually doing this for me.
You just couldn't go back?
Well…
-Let me explain--
-That's right.
-It's exactly as you heard.
-[sighs]
So what? What's it to you?
-Hey!
-Nothing's going to change anyway.
Me, Si-yeol, and you.
We're all going back
to the way things were.
It'll just take a little more time.
Really?
[sighs deeply]
How much longer?
So you're saying you're human now,
just like the rest of us?
And you're looking for a way back, right?
-So you found a way? How?
-[music concludes]
Now that useless human's involved,
this all just got a lot more complicated.
["Geum-ho"] Hm…
So there's a chance we can't switch back
if that method doesn't work?
-Well, that is a possibility.
-[unsettling music playing]
Why the hell do you care?
This matters to me as well.
Why?
Are you afraid I might get in the way?
[scoffs]
You tell me.
I think you're fully capable of that.
So tell me.
Are you going to get in the way?
[sighs] Stop it, both of you.
Why are you acting like this?
You heard what he said, didn't you?
Don't tell me you're still clinging
to the idea of human friendships.
-You're just being too harsh.
-[Woo-seok] Si-yeol.
I need to know what's going on.
Otherwise I can't relax.
And there might be something
I can do to help.
You shouldn't just hide everything
from me like this.
I understand what you're saying.
Still, it would be best
if you left for now.
-Later, if I need--
-Erase it.
[tense music playing]
Pardon?
Erase that human's memory.
But my spiritual power isn't that strong--
I know. Just do it.
Okay.
-[twinkling chime]
-No, wait--
[music fades]
[engine revving]
[tires screeching]
[panting]
What the…
I was just waiting for Si-yeol.
Why am I here?
[phone ringing]
DAD
Hi, Dad.
[Sang-cheol]
Why are you just picking up now?
-[somber music playing]
-I can't really remember right now--
Have you been drinking
at a time like this?
No, it's not that--
[Sang-cheol] Do you know
what kind of mess you caused?
You went to Korea
without the club's permission.
Are you out of your mind?
[sighs]
It's the preseason right now.
I've got the international call-up
next week anyway.
I just came to Korea a few days early.
What's the big deal?
You've still got training,
even in preseason!
You just transferred,
and you've already upset the coach
and the club owner.
You're being unprofessional!
Do you think I'm doing this for myself?
What?
Forget it. I'm hanging up.
[phone beeps]
-[sighs]
-[car horn honks]
-Let's keep it like this…
-[discordant buzz]
-…for now.
-[groans]
-Thank you, Si-yeol.
-[discordant buzz]
[unsettling music playing]
Wait, what was that memory just now?
Did I actually meet Si-yeol?
-[music fades]
-["Geum-ho"] By the way,
where is the house?
It's right here.
[wobbly boing]
Isn't this a public restroom?
There are lots of these in the mountains.
-[wobbly whoosh]
-[quirky music playing]
This isn't a restroom.
It's what we call a rooftop apartment.
It might not look like it,
but people actually live here.
It's a home.
Was it really necessary to go that far?
-[music concludes]
-What?
I don't think we had to go so far
as to erase Woo-seok's memory.
We could've just explained it
and sent him on his way.
[tense music playing]
You still don't seem
to grasp the situation.
If you'd talked to him nicely
and sent him on his way,
do you think
you'd ever sleep soundly again?
What do you mean?
Well, let me give you an example.
If you just dropped dead tonight,
who do you think would benefit?
What?
No more worrying about
when he'd have to switch back
or about ending up back
in this shabby rooftop place.
Everything he has now
would be his forever.
How long do you think
it'll take him to realize that?
A day or two?
Jeez, why is your example so morbid?
What, are you saying Woo-seok
will try to kill me or something?
Come on, that's nonsense.
Don't you remember?
What did your friend do
when I gave him the chance
to switch your lives back?
I mean, that was then.
This is a different situation.
Besides, Woo-seok's not that kind of guy.
[scoffs] Get real.
Humans are all the same.
You think there's
a special "kind" that's any different?
[music rises]
Anyway, erasing his memory
is just a temporary fix.
An eight-tailed fox doesn't have the power
to fully wipe a human's memory.
Whether it takes a few days
or a few months,
your friend's memory will eventually
come back, bit by bit.
Oh, really?
So we need to get back to how things were
before your friend remembers
and gets any funny ideas.
-[music fades]
-Now that the nuisance is taken care of,
why don't you finish what you were saying?
You found a way?
Right, yes.
All we need is
for you and me to switch fates.
Like you did with him.
[downbeat intriguing music playing]
[twinkling chime]
What?
[whimsical theme song playing]
[scoffs]
-[fox squeals]
-[Si-yeol] Huh?
[whimsical theme song continues]
What's with her?
-[song concludes]
-[fox squealing]
EPISODE 6
THE FALSE KINDNESS
[doorbell chimes]
[door lock clicks]
[Yoon] Come in.
PERSONAL PROFILE
KANG SI-YEOL
So who is this guy?
Nobody special.
He went through rehab for about a year
after the accident,
and his soccer career
went downhill after that.
He was recently cut
from a fourth division team too.
So what does he do now?
He doesn't seem to have a job.
So, does he come from a rich family?
Not at all.
He has no parents
and no inheritance either.
[dark intriguing music playing]
That can't be right.
He's a client of that money-grubbing fox,
and you're telling me he's broke?
That makes no sense.
Anything else peculiar?
There's something I found out
during the investigation.
You know the boy
who was a witness to that incident?
Apparently, he's Hyeon Woo-seok.
Hyeon Woo-seok?
While you were away,
this athlete named Hyeon Woo-seok
became a huge star--
I watched the World Cup in prison too.
I know who he is.
Oh, okay.
[inhales sharply]
[sighs] Hyeon Woo-seok.
Kang Si-yeol is completely broke,
but Hyeon Woo-seok is his friend?
[music rises]
I think I should meet this Hyeon Woo-seok.
-[slurps]
-[music fades]
[slurps]
Ah!
I feel a bit better now.
Usually, I last half a day in human form,
but erasing his memory
must have drained me.
If you've got your strength back,
could you finish
what you were saying earlier?
Earlier? I meant exactly what I said.
I mean, is switching fates
actually possible for you?
You tried switching Woo-seok
and me back last night,
but it didn't work.
That's because I lack power right now,
but what if I become a nine-tailed fox?
[intriguing music playing]
What?
Then I'll have powers too,
so we can just switch our fates.
You can become
a nine-tailed fox instead of me,
and I can become human faster.
It's good for both of us.
Then what about me?
I don't think
there's anything I can do about that.
But she can probably help you later.
Wait, why?
You could just switch me back first
after you become a nine-tailed fox.
It's urgent for me too.
It doesn't work that way
because I'm the one who cast that spell.
-But--
-["Geum-ho"] I'm younger than her,
and my spiritual power is much weaker.
So even if I become a nine-tailed fox,
it'd be hard for me to undo her spell.
Well, okay then.
It doesn't matter how we get there
as long as I get my life back.
Well, the logic holds up.
So problem solved, right?
[echoing rattle]
Nothing's solved.
[cymbals clash]
I was wondering
what you were talking about.
That doesn't sound like your idea, though.
Who told you that crap?
Pardon?
Well…
I was told not to say anything
because it's a secret.
[clicks tongue]
You don't have to say it. It's obvious.
What's obvious?
Just go. Quit talking nonsense.
-But sis--
-I said, go.
You're talking nonsense.
Why are you chasing her off?
-Should I really go?
-No.
[Eun-ho] Listen to me.
I'm telling you this
for your own good, so pay attention.
You are being scammed.
What?
Why do you want to become human?
What do you know about them?
Do you honestly think
that was your own idea and decision?
["Geum-ho"] Well…
Isn't that just the way it works?
It's what all the other foxes did.
And the ones above said
it's the right path.
Works for me.
If I trick a clueless kid like you,
I can become a nine-tailed fox again.
But what about you?
You turn human, totally unprepared.
Then what?
When you regret it later,
you think the ones above
are going to help you?
[music concludes]
["Geum-ho"] Hm…
[swallows]
What's so bad about living as a human?
-I like it. I'm satisfied.
-[quirky music playing]
You're satisfied? Right now?
Hey, that's different.
I'm only in this mess because of you.
I was perfectly happy with my old life.
It's all the same.
You could've fallen apart
at any time, with or without me.
Isn't that what human life is?
[breathes deeply] You never know
how your life will turn out either.
Your old age might be miserable.
What?
Did you seriously just say that to me?
Anyway, I'll figure out
how to change back on my own.
So go live your own life
and mind your own business.
But…
No, no. You don't get to
decide that for her.
She just wants to become human
as soon as possible.
Unlike you.
She didn't make that decision
knowing all the facts.
You'll be glad you stayed
a nine-tailed fox in the end.
But like I said, that's not your call.
How is what you're doing any different
from the ones above?
What?
[Si-yeol] You chose
your own way of life, right?
Well, she's got her own path too.
Right?
I mean, I guess.
What do you mean by that?
So you're dead set on becoming human?
-Well…
-[echoing plop]
The decision's up to you.
Don't worry about anyone else.
You want to become human, don't you?
That's right!
You decide since it's your life.
[echoing rattle]
[quirky music continues]
[giggles]
Now that you're both pressuring me,
I'm not so sure.
[chuckles]
-[scoffs]
-[echoing chirp]
Talking to you is pointless.
-[echoing squeal]
-[music fades]
VIOLENT CRIMES UNIT 2
[man] Let go of me! I'm the victim here!
You're going to pay for this!
Get your hands off me!
[overlapping chatter]
[police sirens wailing in the distance]
[timidly] I'm scared, sis.
Don't look away. Watch.
If you become human,
you'll have to live among trash like them.
-What?
-[tense musical sting plays]
-[quirky music playing]
-I have to live around them?
With people like that?
She won't run
into people like them very often.
Yes, she will.
These people can spot
clueless kids like you
a mile away, you know?
Just look at her face.
Doesn't it just scream "easy target"?
[downbeat quirky music playing]
[echoing squeak]
[Si-yeol and Eun-ho sigh]
Hey, what are you in for?
-Mugging.
-[Eun-ho] You?
-Online scam.
-Assault.
-[Eun-ho] You?
Illegal filming on the subway.
[gasps]
[Eun-ho] Wow,
you must be so proud of yourselves!
Excuse me.
-Who are you?
-[Eun-ho] Never mind.
Make sure you investigate them thoroughly.
See that?
The human world will rob you blind
right under your nose.
Do you really think
you can survive
dropping into this den of evil?
[echoing squeal]
[sighs] Well…
Hey, hold on.
You shouldn't pressure her
for an answer in a place like this.
[fox yipping]
The human world has its good side too.
-[echoing squeak]
-This time, I'll take you somewhere nice.
-[fox yipping]
-[echoing chirp]
[music concludes]
[upbeat music playing]
Feel free to eat whatever you want here
without worrying about what others think.
["Geum-ho"] Really?
In all my 500 years,
I've never seen so much food.
Wait, hold on.
Like this.
[in English] Enjoy.
-[snickers]
-[scoffs]
[in Korean] Slow down.
No one's going to take it from you.
This is the best food
I've had in half a century.
That's because you were stuck
in the mountains,
eating nothing but greens.
This is nothing, really.
Back when I was a nine-tailed fox,
I ate way better stuff than this.
There are so many delicious things
in the human world.
If you become human,
you can eat like this every day.
[echoing plop]
[echoing squeak and plop]
[scoffs]
[fork clangs]
You really think so?
[music fades]
You can't just go in there.
[mutters]
How much do you think
that meal you ate cost?
[chuckles softly] I don't know.
The human world has classes.
-Here…
-[downbeat intriguing music playing]
[Eun-ho] Right.
That one over there is at the very bottom.
No matter how many dishes she washes,
she'll never be able
to afford a meal like you just ate.
Why? Because the pay is garbage.
Who starts out as a chef from day one?
Everyone works their way up.
You think hard work is
all it takes to get to the top?
There are tons of humans who end up
washing dishes their whole lives.
[plate shatters]
[cook sighs]
You have to leave!
-Ow!
-Just get out, please.
[scoffs] Unbelievable.
I'm sorry.
You got us kicked out
before we could really eat.
-Did I say anything wrong?
-Wrong or not, that's not the point.
Why on earth are you taking it this far?
[huffs]
Do you actually have another way
to get back to how it was?
Well…
Not right now, but--
See? You don't have one.
This is the only way.
So why are you being so difficult?
I'm not.
But you're saying I should just stand by
and watch when I know how this turns out?
It's obvious what'll happen
if that idiot suddenly becomes human.
Since when did you care so much
about other people?
[Eun-ho] What?
Excuse me.
We went to the police station
because you wanted to,
and we came to this restaurant
because Si-yeol wanted to.
[music concludes]
-[echoing jingle]
-So?
So, isn't it my turn to go where I want?
There's somewhere I've always
wanted to go in the human world.
-[echoing plop]
-[echoing squeal]
[whimsical music playing]
[squeals, laughs]
Sis!
She doesn't know the first thing
about the world,
so where did she even hear
about a place like this?
She said the stranded kid she saved
kept bragging about it.
Just play along.
[scoffs]
What's so fun about that anyway?
Si-yeol, how long do we have to do this?
[wrapper rustling]
[sighs] Now, that's better.
[group cheering, laughing]
[sighs]
-Did you have fun?
-Yes!
But the kids in front of me and behind me
were all riding with their mom or dad.
So?
-[upbeat rock song playing]
-You want me to act like your mom now?
No, it's just that I keep riding alone.
You should be grateful
we even came here with you.
No!
[group cheering]
[group screaming]
-[group screaming]
-[upbeat rock song continues]
Tell them to stop this thing!
-[group cheering, screaming]
-[upbeat rock song continues]
-Whoo! [laughs]
[upbeat rock song continues]
["Geum-ho"] That was so much fun, sis!
Let's ride it again!
I can't ride it again.
-Why not?
-Uh…
This is a really popular ride,
so the line takes forever.
Is that why?
-[twinkling chime]
-[seat belts click]
What's going on?
This fixes everything, right?
We don't have to wait.
No, don't!
-[twinkling chime]
-Don't do it!
[safety bar clunks]
[whimpers]
What the…
I'm going to kill that idiot fox!
[upbeat rock song continues]
[whimpers]
[song concludes]
[indistinct chatter]
[retches, coughs]
Hey, are you okay?
[groans] I'm dizzy, and I feel sick.
I feel like I'm dying.
This damn human body.
I'm so sorry, sis.
I thought you'd like it too.
Hey.
Look at me right now.
Doesn't it make you feel anything?
Do you still want to be--
[cartoonish squeal]
Sis, let's go on that one next!
[cartoonish whoosh]
[scoffs]
Is a tail really
the only thing she's missing?
[Si-yeol] If you ask me,
I think she's got you
wrapped around her finger.
What?
Just accept it. It's easier that way.
-We're coming.
-[wobbly squeak]
-[scoffs]
-[dreamy pop song playing]
-[thud]
-Ah!
[dreamy pop song continues]
-[grunts]
-[laughs]
-[visitors laughing, screaming]
-[dreamy pop song continues]
[laughs]
["Geum-ho" and Si-yeol yelp]
[all three laugh]
[dreamy pop song continues]
-[dreamy pop song continues]
-[spooky music playing over speakers]
-[recorded wailing plays]
-[yelps, whimpers]
[dreamy pop song continues]
-[Eun-ho screams]
-[yelps]
-That hurts.
-[Eun-ho screams]
It really hurts!
You of all people
shouldn't be scared of that!
[gasps]
[chuckles softly] I wasn't scared.
I was just startled.
Those fake ghosts aren't even scary.
[dreamy pop song continues]
[Si-yeol] Unbelievable.
[screams]
-[song fades]
-[Eun-ho crying]
-[bell tinkling]
-[wind whistling]
[ominous music playing]
The Divine Spirit told me
that an ominous guest would arrive today.
That must be you.
They say you're
the best shaman in Sancheong.
[bag thuds]
You've invited quite the ghost in.
The sorrow of losing one's family
is a pain anyone can sympathize with.
But you dare defy the will of Heaven
and devour every divine spirit?
Save your breath.
I have my reasons,
so hand over that ghost behind you.
I was trying to catch a fox,
but it was just too vicious.
I'm running low on spiritual energy.
The karma you carry
is already as deep as the ocean.
How will you handle all that sin?
What's a little rain to the ocean?
So,
let's not be too difficult about this.
[snickers]
[beads clacking gently]
[ominous music continues]
[beads clack]
[engine starts]
[music turns eerie]
[music crescendos]
[music concludes]
[crowd cheering, applauding]
[whimsical music playing over speakers]
[sighs]
I never thought I'd say this,
but even after things go back to normal,
I'll probably still think about today
from time to time.
I mean,
it's my first time at a place like this.
[Eun-ho]
You've never been to an amusement park?
Don't humans go to these places
all the time as kids?
My grandmother was out working,
so I never got to visit places
like this as a kid.
And being on the sports team,
I hardly ever got to go on field trips.
You haven't really done much, have you?
I've been everywhere.
Jayeon Nongwon, Bugok Hawaii, you name it.
You have?
You were just puking your guts out.
That's because of this damn human body.
[clicks tongue]
You get sick from just a few rides
and have to wait an hour
for a one-minute ride.
How is this supposed to be fun?
You know,
you look like
you're having the most fun here.
[echoing plops]
[echoing squeak]
I only did this
because you guys made me.
[clicks tongue]
[groans softly]
[Si-yeol] What's wrong?
-What?
-Let me see.
Your heel is all scraped up.
Why didn't you tell me
before it got this bad?
I thought this was normal
when you walk a lot.
That's ridiculous.
Jeez, you're bleeding.
That must've really hurt.
[tender music playing]
[Eun-ho] Wait.
Are you worried about me right now?
Why?
Am I not allowed to worry about you?
[chuckles softly]
[clears throat]
I mean,
it's just unexpected, that's all.
Technically, what you're suffering through
-is also kind of my fault, in a way.
-[chuckles softly]
[Eun-ho] So…
So, is it your fault or not?
I don't know. Think whatever you want.
It just so happens that right now,
you're the only person
in the world on my side.
I don't have any friends or family
I can rely on.
You're all I have.
So you should worry about me too.
I'll be worrying about you.
[chuckles softly]
And if anything were to happen to you,
I'd never be able to go back to my life.
So how can I not worry?
Especially with all the enemies
you've made with your misdeeds.
What?
Now that sounds more like you. [scoffs]
Anyway, just wait here.
I'll go grab a bandage.
[tender music continues]
[chuckles softly]
["Geum-ho"] Sis!
[giggles, echoes]
[music fades]
[Eun-ho echoing] So, what's your wish?
-[Geum-ho] What?
-[serene music playing]
[Eun-ho] We made a bet
about a hundred years ago, remember?
We said that whoever becomes human first
gets their wish granted.
Don't tell me you forgot.
Oh, that?
Do you want me to dig up
that wild ginseng I hid?
I hear it sells for a fortune
in the human world.
Or maybe I should visit
the king in his dreams
to tell him to promote that scholar
you've got a crush on.
The mountain god
will scold you for that.
[scoffs] Only if I get caught.
You think I'm like you?
I know how to get around the rules.
I don't want to wish for things like that.
My wish is…
-[birds chirping]
-[serene music continues]
for you to do good deeds
and focus on your cultivation.
What? I do that every single day.
Not things like that--
So that you become human quickly.
We could live in the same village,
make mugwort rice cakes in the spring,
and make kimchi in the winter.
Wouldn't it be nice
to grow old together like that?
[music turns wistful]
But Geum-ho…
[Geum-ho] Yes?
What if it takes me a long time?
What if I finally become human,
and you're already a hunchbacked granny?
Hey, don't say that.
[mockingly] Grandma!
Let's go pick mugwort!
Grandma!
-Let go of me!
-No!
[Geum-ho] Let go!
[Eun-ho] Never!
[music fades]
["Geum-ho] Sis!
Why are you standing here alone?
Tell me.
Do you still want to become
human that badly?
What?
I used to know someone a long time ago.
-She was a fox, just like us.
-[pensive music playing]
She cultivated herself for a long time
and finally became human.
What happened to her?
She died
after dragging herself through a long,
cruel, miserable life.
That's what human life is to me.
It's fleeting, weak, and fragile.
And you still want to be one of them?
[pensive music continues]
Um…
You know,
today was really special for me.
How about for you?
What?
All this time, I wasn't exactly happy,
but I wasn't exactly unhappy either.
I just haven't had any days
that were memorable.
That's because you've been holed up
in the mountains--
["Geum-ho"] Then what about you?
You've lived in the human world
this whole time.
Have you had a lot of happy days?
Or even terribly unhappy ones?
I want to become human.
-Maybe I'll be unhappy.
-[soft uplifting music playing]
Maybe there will be moments
I can barely stand.
But still,
I want to live a life that's memorable.
Even if it's short,
I want it to be intense.
I want to be swept away.
Not a life where I can predict
and control everything.
I want to be tossed about, swept along,
crying one minute, laughing the next.
I want to live a real life.
Some days,
I want to be torn apart by regret.
I want to feel hollow.
But when I laugh,
I want to laugh out loud.
[music rises]
["Geum-ho"] Sis.
Even if I'm unhappy, sad,
and eventually die,
I still want to become human.
[Eun-ho] I will never become human.
I won't love a human as you did.
I won't live in misery,
and I won't die in despair.
I'll never
live like you.
Eun-ho.
Geum-ho? [breathes shakily]
Are you with me?
Do you recognize me?
I've…
lived my own life
with no regrets.
You need to live yours.
Whatever that may be.
[soft uplifting music continues]
[breathes shakily]
[music fades]
Yeon-su?
Isn't that Yeon-su over there?
No way.
She's single. How could she have two kids?
[sighs]
[Yeon-su] Goodness, these kids.
They've made a mess here too.
[sighs]
[child] Mom, hurry up!
Yeah, I'm coming!
-[indistinct chatter]
-[whimsical music playing over speakers]
[Si-yeol] Why are you being so moody?
Hold this.
[gentle music playing]
[Si-yeol] You are so stubborn.
You're not a nine-tailed fox
who can use earth-folding anymore.
Where did the other one go, anyway?
She left.
-[music concludes]
-What? Where to?
Where do you think?
She's from the mountains,
so she went back.
-Let's go.
-Wait, hold on.
Wait for me.
Hey!
What's going on?
Did you guys fight while I was gone?
If that's not it--
You got exactly what you wanted.
-What?
-We didn't fight.
We decided to switch our fates.
-Really?
-Yes.
Wait, hold on.
For real?
So it's all sorted?
Do I get my life back now?
[snickers]
Get a grip, Si-yeol.
You can't just
go back to normal overnight.
Why not?
Did you already forget the condition?
That half-wit eight-tailed fox
has to become a nine-tailed fox
before we can change our fates.
Right.
[inhales sharply]
But how long will that take?
-Will it be quick?
-[inhales sharply]
Usually, it takes about 100 years.
-[quirky music playing]
-What? A hundred years?
Did you think
growing an additional tail was easy?
How can you be so calm about this?
You think you'll still be alive by then?
Oh, come on! What's the point
if I die of old age first?
I said, usually.
So there's another way?
It takes 100 years for total rookies.
But I'm a pro.
I've got some tricks up my sleeve.
[twinkling whoosh]
[gasps]
-Is that…
-[twinkling hum]
Brace yourself.
Just so you know, this won't be easy.
We'll be slammed starting tomorrow.
[music builds]
[music concludes]
-[keypad beeps]
-[door lock chimes]
[Si-yeol grunts softly]
[door lock chimes]
[sighs heavily]
What?
I was too distracted to notice before,
but this place is a total dump.
What?
-You call this a home?
-[quirky music playing]
You can be broke and still have taste.
A roof and walls don't make a home.
Are you kidding me?
This isn't even really my place.
I changed your fate,
not your sense of style.
You just don't remember it,
but you're the one
who decorated this place.
And I saw your original place too.
It was completely empty.
Just some weird machine
you get into naked.
That's just a crash pad
for when I'm in Korea.
[chuckles]
My actual house in the UK
has a pool and a private theater.
The closet is huge, and the decor is--
[groans] This is so depressing.
I need to change back as soon as possible.
I can't live like this.
Yeah, I'm rooting for you.
Where are you going?
What?
Why? You need something?
I'm tired. I'm going to go rest.
I get that you're tired,
but why are you going in there?
There's only one bedroom,
so obviously it's mine.
This is my home.
And I slept in there last night, didn't I?
That's because I slept
with the eight-tailed fox.
Starting today, I get the bed.
-[echoing ding]
-I'm the oldest here.
[Si-yeol huffs]
Sure, whatever you say.
You're older than the Republic of Korea.
How can I beat that?
I'll just have to serve you.
Then I'm going to go wash up.
[Eun-ho] Hold it.
I get to shower first too.
Elders first.
-[sighs]
-[music concludes]
[gentle music playing]
[breathes deeply]
[huffs]
[gasps]
[gentle music continues]
[whispers] Si-yeol.
Si-yeol.
[music fades]
Wake up.
[Si-yeol grunts softly]
[Eun-ho] Hello?
[gasps, yelps]
My gosh!
What do you want now?
I'm hungry.
What? At this hour?
[Si-yeol] Come on.
You said you were stuffed
from the lunch buffet.
So you refused to eat dinner.
I was full then.
Now I'm hungry, so I can't sleep.
-[stomach growling]
-This damn human body.
Just try to go back to sleep.
You'll get fat if you eat this late.
It's fine. Once I turn back,
I won't gain weight anyway.
Any more of that stuff
she was eating yesterday?
What? Ramyeon?
-[shell cracks]
-[perky music playing]
[bowl clatters]
[Si-yeol] Dig in.
[slurping]
[chuckles softly]
[Eun-ho] Mm!
[mumbling] So good.
Is it that good?
Yeah.
Why did you only make one, though?
Aren't you eating?
No, I don't eat at this hour.
Especially not stuff like this.
I think the last time I had ramyeon
was 12 or 13 years ago.
[scoffs]
Come on, just have one bite.
It's really good.
No, I'm good. [clears throat]
We both reset when we go back anyway.
Just eat it while you can. Hm?
[wobbly squeak]
[sighs sharply] I guess that's true.
Then just one bite.
[clears throat]
[music concludes]
[exhales softly]
[echoing plop]
[quirky music playing]
[wobbly whoosh]
[music falls]
[Eun-ho] Come on,
surely you want more than that?
-What?
-[echoing chime]
Right. [clears throat]
-[quirky music resumes]
-Right? [clears throat]
I'll just have one more bite.
-[echoing rattle]
-[music falls]
[quirky music resumes]
-[slurping]
-[chuckles softly]
[chuckles] What the heck?
[slurping]
[wobbly plop]
Hey!
You can't just eat it all.
There's nothing left for me!
Should we make another?
-[chuckles]
-[music falls]
Make it two.
-[both slurping]
-[quirky music resumes]
[Si-yeol] Mm!
Tastes better with three eggs.
-Mix in some rice? [clears throat]
-Yeah.
-[rooster crowing]
-[Eun-ho gasps]
-What is this?
-[quirky music continues]
What is it?
What's wrong?
Oh no… my face.
[laughs]
You're all puffy.
I told you not to eat that late.
You think your face looks any better?
You're all puffy too.
[Si-yeol] Me too?
-[wobbly squeak]
-[gasps] What the heck?
[bright musical sting plays]
I think the swelling's going down a bit.
We should've just gone for a run.
I told you we'd be busy starting today.
We can't waste energy on useless stuff.
[scoffs]
What an excuse.
Whatever. Just go change the spoons.
-Get the cold ones.
-[music concludes]
[players chattering]
[players] Nice!
That's it!
Move it up! There we go!
Seo Beom, shoot! Shoot it!
-[whistle blows]
-[groans]
-[player 1] Nice!
-He skied it, damn it.
-This is so frustrating.
-[goofy music playing]
Coach, would you like some water?
Forget it. Put that away.
-[player 2] Cross it in!
-Okay!
-[players chattering]
-[echoing sigh]
[player 3] Come on, block him!
-[whistle blows]
-[groans]
-[player 4] Block him!
-Block!
-[sighs]
-[players yelling]
-[player 5] Nice!
-[whistle blows]
[Yong-gil] You've got to move up
as a group, okay?
Hey, Bae Jeong-bae!
-[goofy music continues]
-All you do is send crosses all day.
Try cutting inside sometimes.
And dribble
the ball up the field like this
so that they get confused!
Yes, sir.
How does the water taste,
Seo Beom, you punk?
-[coughs]
-[Yong-gil] You call that a shot?
You skied it way up there.
I thought you'd hit a damn airplane.
I'm sorry.
Damn it.
Are you guys just gonna play defense
the whole time and go home?
You have to score goals to win!
But why?
Why isn't anyone making a proper attack?
But, Coach.
Who are we supposed to cut back to?
What?
Well, even if we cut back,
there's nobody there to take it.
Hey, why isn't there?
Kang Si-yeol would be right… [hesitates]
-[music fades]
-[echoing wobbly boing]
Just pass it to the forward striker.
Who's the forward striker?
-What?
-[Beom] If we're being realistic,
we don't have a proper striker
on our team right now.
[echoing wobbly boing]
[downbeat goofy music playing]
Don't you guys know modern soccer?
Total soccer.
-[wobbly squeak]
-Everyone attacks, everyone defends--
[Chi-su] Excuse me, Coach.
-Instead, can't we just--
-[Yong-gil] No!
You're trying to bring up
Kang Si-yeol again, right?
You listen to me carefully.
Over…
my dead body.
That punk Kang Si-yeol is out!
-Out for good!
-[music concludes]
-[birds chirping]
-[indistinct chatter]
Didn't you say we'd be super busy?
But we're not exactly fishing here.
What are we doing?
[daring quirky music playing]
Fishing?
We're doing something similar.
Except we're fishing for people, not fish.
What? Fishing for people?
[Eun-ho] Yes.
Because from now on,
we're on a "Good Deeds Project."
[echoing ding]
[Eun-ho] Fine.
No matter what I say,
I get that you want to become human.
But before that,
becoming a nine-tailed fox
is no easy task to begin with.
Are you ready for that?
Can you follow my lead without complaint,
no matter what I ask?
Follow what exactly?
[wobbly boing]
What?
From here on out, you're on your own.
I'm not the one in a rush.
[scoffs]
Wait.
Well…
I mean, I'm still going to help you.
But you need to do good deeds
to build spiritual power so your tails--
Then I'll just give you my fox bead.
I'll use a spell to connect us
so you can do the good deeds
and build the spiritual power for me.
-[scoffs]
-[echoing ding]
[sighs] My transformation
is about to wear off, so I have to run.
-What do you say?
-[echoing ding]
-[music concludes]
-I think you were right.
I swear, she's got me
wrapped around her finger.
So what you're saying is,
when you do good deeds,
she gains the spiritual power instead?
But you can't actually use
her fox bead's power yourself.
That's right.
That's why from now on,
we have to do good deeds.
Aggressively and in massive amounts
in a short amount of time.
[quirky music playing]
But what does that
have to do with fishing?
[groans] Seriously?
Do I have to spell out
every single thing for you?
Who do you think is the reason
I'm stuck as a human
and suffering like this?
-[echoing plop]
-[echoing boing]
It's because I saved your life!
[clicks tongue]
Okay, fine. So what?
One human embodies an entire world,
so saving a person's life
is basically saving an entire world.
In other words,
the ultimate good deed,
the highest virtue of all,
is saving a life.
-[echoing squeaks]
-[music concludes]
[bird cawing]
[quirky music resumes]
Wait, don't tell me.
That's not what you're doing, right?
You're waiting for someone to jump
so you can save them?
Why? Is there a problem?
Hey!
Forget the problem!
How's that a good deed?
The karma will get you, you know?
Why would karma get me
when I'm saving a life?
[scoffs]
-Unbelievable.
-[downbeat quirky music playing]
Okay, fine.
I don't expect much
from your moral compass anymore,
but putting that aside,
it's just inefficient.
Do you honestly think this makes sense?
-It doesn't?
-No!
It's like lying under a tree
waiting for fruit to fall!
How long do you plan on waiting?
You think so?
[sighs] I guess you're right.
You do have a point.
Given the urgency,
this does feel too passive.
[Si-yeol] Exactly.
Even if the good deeds are forced,
we should try to do them the normal way--
-Fine.
-[echoing ding]
I'll just have to find another way.
[echoing chime]
SHAMAN'S SHRINE
ADULT STORE
GAME LAND
IMAGE SHOP
-[music concludes]
-[crosswalk signal beeping]
[Eun-ho] Here, Si-yeol.
Take this and burn that place down.
What?
Are you out of your mind?
[Eun-ho] Don't worry about it.
I know the guys inside. I met them
back in my nine-tailed fox days.
Loan sharks, illegal gambling,
organ trafficking, you name it.
This place is crawling with wicked
and evil people doing that kind of stuff.
-[quirky music playing]
-Trust me, they deserve to die.
Hey.
Didn't you just say
that "one human is a whole world"?
And now you want me
to burn people to death?
What are you talking about?
I'm a very cultivated beast, you know.
Then what's this for?
You start the fire,
then I'll swoop in and put it out in time.
Or we can just call the fire department.
That'd mean I saved
a bunch of lives
in that building all at once.
[Si-yeol exhales slowly]
First the river, now fire?
You really will stop at nothing.
[wobbly boing]
I can't do this. I won't.
Do you honestly think this makes sense?
What's wrong now? Why not?
Jeez, you never
just agree to anything. [clicks tongue]
So you're talking about
a false kindness, aren't you?
The important part is the kindness.
Hey!
You want us to be the bad guys,
not the good guys!
Either way, we're still saving them.
That's all that matters, isn't it?
Don't you know
what happens to the bad guys?
They always end up ruined
and in the gutter.
Enough!
I'm older than any bad guy out there.
So just do as I say.
If you want to start a fire,
do it yourself.
I can't do it.
-[clicks tongue]
-[music concludes]
I would've done it already if I could.
I need to do good deeds,
so I can't do bad things.
Oh, so you know it's bad?
[bystander] Fire!
Fire!
Did you…
It wasn't me.
It really wasn't. I'm right here.
But where is the fire?
[tense dramatic music playing]
[crowd clamoring]
HOPE ORPHANAGE
-Did you call 911?
-[worker] Yes.
But the children are still inside!
There are children inside?
[worker] Yes.
[breathes heavily]
Here, hold this.
-[music intensifies]
-Si-yeol, what are you doing?
You wait here. It's too dangerous.
What?
[workers clamoring]
Si-yeol!
[crowd clamoring]
[music falls]
[intense music resumes]
[coughs]
[coughs harshly]
Si-yeol, I can't see a thing.
[Si-yeol muffled]
I told you not to come! It's dangerous!
Come to think of it… [coughs]
…if anyone saves the kids,
it has to be me, not you.
[Si-yeol] What? Are you crazy?
Cover your face with this.
I think the fire started in the basement.
Let's get the kids out
before it spreads up here.
[coughs]
-Hey, kids.
-[child] Teacher!
[Eun-ho] Are you all right?
-Okay, let's go.
-[child crying]
[coughs]
Take the kids and get out first.
I'll check over there,
then follow you out.
-I'm scared!
-[Si-yeol coughs]
[coughs] Let's go.
[child whimpers]
-[crowd clamoring]
-[intense music continues]
[coughs]
[coughs harshly]
[sighs heavily]
Is that everyone?
[music falls]
I can't find So-jeong!
-[pants]
-[tense dramatic music playing]
[coughs]
[music intensifies]
[Eun-ho coughs]
[coughs, gasps]
[rumbling, clattering]
[crowd member] They're out!
[crowd clamoring]
-[coughs]
-[worker] Oh, So-jeong!
[coughs]
-[pants]
-[intense dramatic music continues]
[sniffs]
[crowd clamoring]
Where's the woman I was with?
She went back inside just now.
What?
[door thudding]
[Eun-ho] Why won't this open?
Damn it, open up!
[breathes rapidly]
[coughs]
[gasps, pants]
[gasps]
[thud]
Don't be ridiculous.
You think I'm going to die like this?
[grunts]
[wood creaks]
[pants]
[coughs]
[Si-yeol] Eun-ho!
Eun-ho!
Si-yeol.
Seriously, what are you doing?
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
[building rumbles]
[shelf crashes]
Eun-ho, are you okay?
[gasps]
-Si-yeol!
-[both gasp]
[Eun-ho yelps]
-[music falls]
-[echoing crash]
[dramatic resumes, swells]
[music fades]
[curtains rattling]
-[quiet chatter]
-[devices beeping]
[phone ringing in distance]
[footsteps approaching]
Oh, you're awake.
What?
Wait, what happened?
[Eun-ho yelps]
[gasps shakily]
Si-yeol. Where is he?
Excuse me?
Wait, ma'am!
-Where are you going?
-[Eun-ho] Si-yeol!
[breathes rapidly]
Si-yeol!
Where is Si-yeol?
[Si-yeol] You looking for me?
[tender pop song playing]
People will think I'm actually dead.
Why are you calling out for me like that?
I'm right here.
I seriously thought you were dead.
[chuckles softly]
Were you scared?
It just so happens that right now,
you're the only person
in the world on my side.
I don't have any friends or family
I can rely on.
You're all I have.
So you should worry about me too.
I'll be worrying about you.
[tender pop song continues]
Eun-ho.
You told me to worry.
You said I should worry about you!
I'm really okay, I swear.
Since when do you actually
listen to what I say?
[tender pop song continues]
If you had died,
I would've killed you myself!
[tender pop song continues]
[fox squealing]
NO TAIL TO TELL
["Geum-ho"]
You sure you're doing this right?
We haven't gained
one bit of spiritual power.
[Eun-ho] Why isn't the power building up?
[Si-yeol] How about we try
doing good deeds by the book?
[Eun-ho] What if I stay human
and just die of old age?
[Si-yeol] Was there really nothing good
about becoming human?
Last name Lee, first name Yoon.
You bastard!
[Yoon] Kang Si-yeol.
-He must be a very close friend of yours.
-[Woo-seok] This memory…
[old man] It is you.
I know this is all your fault!
-[yells]
-[tender pop song continues]
Subtitle translation by Susanna Kim